editted by Ash
The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn - Part 1
Childhood is not from birth to a certain age ...
And at a certain age, the child is grown and puts away childish things.
Childhood is the kingdom where nobody dies.
Jake! Jacob!
Phil!
It's happening.
Um, you just have to break them in.
I've been breaking them in. For three days.
- Can I just go barefoot?
- No!
Absolutely not.
I'm just thinking it's a little much, you know.
The dress, the shoes ...
All of this.
No, it's exactly enough.
Tomorrow will be perfect.
Where we do you want them boss?
One either side of the aisle.
- What aisle?
- Does no one have vision?!
You! Go home and get lots of beauty sleep.
That's an order.
All right...
I'm just checking for cold feet.
.....anymore****
It's not too late to change your mind.
What now you're having second thoughts?
You are.
I've been waiting a century to marry you, Miss. Swan.
but..."
I haven't told you everything about myself.
What? You're not a virgin?
Look, you can't scare me away now.
Look, a few years after Carlisle created me
I rebelled against him.
I've resented him for  curbing my appetite.
So for a while, I went off on my own
I wanted to know how it felt to hunt.
To taste human blood.
All the men I've killed
were monsters.
And so was I.
Edward, they were all murderers.
You probably saved more lives than you took.
Bella, that's what I told myself.
but they were all human beings.
I looked into their eyes as they died and I saw who I was.
And what I was capable of.
And what I'll be capable of.
Why are you telling me this tonight?
Did you really think this is going to change my mind about you?
Just wanted you to change your mind about yourself.
What you wanna see when you look in the mirror a year from now
I know I can do this.
And let me tell you why.
Because you did.
You should give yourself some credit for that.
And hopefully a year from now.
I'm gonna look in the mirror and see someone like you.
Someone capable of courage and sacrifice,
and love.
"What is that?
- Come on! Let's go!
I'm late for my bachelor party.
Send him out Bella, or we're comin' in after him.
So this party.. will there be strippers?
"Boring!"
No, just a couple of mountain lions.
Maybe a few bears.
Don't worry Bella, we'll give him back in plain time.
Okay go, before they break my house.
"Let's go!!"
I'll meet you at the altar.
I'll be the one in white.
Very convincing.
What did I say about beauty sleep?
Sorry. Bad dream.
I mean, it's wedding jitters.
- Do you Need some help?
I could do her hair.
"Really?
Please. I'm not offended by your choice of groom.
Just my plain lack of respect for mortality.
Essentially.
Weddings, they bring everyone together
Hey, did you find our daughter?
Are those..graduation caps?
Ha! How creative!
- Or weird
- Alice! Bella!
In here, Mom.
Oh My gosh! You are so beautiful.
Oh crap, my mascara.
Thanks!
Charlie, get in here!
Are you sure? I don't wanna...
I know. I look hot.
We thought you needed something blue.
And something old.
- Besides your mother.
- Ugh. Thanks.
- It was grandma's, once.
- But we added the sapphires
It's beautiful, you guys.
Wow, thank you so much
That's your first family heirloom.
You can pass it on to your daughter and her daughter.
Mom, I loved it.
No smudging my masterpiece.
She's right.
Thank you.
"Okay
Time for... the dress!
Do you want to see it?
They have got to be related.
What a gene pool.
Seriously.
You got some uh...drool.
So, do you think Bella's gonna be showing?
Jess, she is not pregnant.
Okay!  Who else gets married at 18?
Ready?
Just dont' let me fall, Dad.
Never.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are gathered here on this glorious day
to witness the union of
Edward Cullen and Bella Swan.
Please repeat after me.
"I, Edward Cullen ..."
I, Edward Cullen ...
"Take you, Bella Swan ..."
"To have and to hold"
For better or for worse.
For richer or for poorer.
In sickness and in health.
To love
To cherish
....love
I do
I love you.
I love you too.
I thought it would be bigger
- Yeah
"Hi,
- Hi guys.
We were just saying how pretty everything is.
Thank you. You don't think it's too much?
- No!
- Not at all.
Hey, man! Nice to see you!
- I'm happy for you.
Thank you!
I hope you'll be happy, Bella.
Thank you, Billy.
Have you heard from him?
I'm sure Jake wishes you the best.
Or plan on getting drunk.
They're serving up some pretty fancy champagne. Sue, can I get you a glass?
Sparkling...
Sounds great.
Bella!
Congratulations! Bella
- Eleazar and Carmen, right?
- Hola!
Yes. These are our cousins from Alaska. Tanya, Kate.
We've heard so much about you!
- Welcome to the family.
- Bienvenida!
Thank you.
Irina.
Come meet Bella.
I can't do this.
- You promised.
They invited one.
Irina, he is our friend.
They killed Laurent.
He tried to kill Bella.
I don't believe that. He wanted to be like us.
To live in peace with humans,
with me.
I'm sorry.
Irina!
Well, let's not monopolize the bride.
Thank you.
Sorry."
Well, what's a wedding without some family drama.
Excuse me. Is this is on?
Um, Hello!
Um, I'd like to propose a toast.
To my new sister.
Bella, I hope you've got enough sleep these past 18 years.
Coz you won't be getting anymore for a while. Hahaha.
Well, Bella was just like everybody else.
totally mesmerized by Edward.
Or the "Hair" as I call him
And then suddenly, Edward is all about Bella.
Eventhough she's not the captain of the volleyball team.
I'm Just kidding.  I'm Just kidding
Or president of the Student Council.
Edward will be a good husband.
I know this because
coz I'm a cop.
I know this..
Like how to hunt somebody
to the ends of the earth.
Now that you're my sister.
You'll have to get over your ___ fashion
And I know how to use a gun
Skirts, heels, handbags.
Go to sleep, my love
Go to sleep
When you wake
you'll see me
I would like to thank Renee and Charlie
for bringing such a wonderful person into the world ...
And into our lives.
We will cherish her and protect her forever.
It's an extraordinary thing
to meet someone who you can bury your soul to
Adn accept you for what you are
I've been waiting, for what seems like a very long time
To get beyond who I am
And with Bella
I feel like I could finally begin.
So I'd like to propose a toast to my beautiful bride.
No measure of time with you will be long enough
but let's start with "forever."
Another one of your gifts just arrived.
What?
Here, come on
What's a wedding present doing out here?
Just a little more private.
The best man didn't have time to get a tux.
Jacob!
Jacob.
Hi!
- Hi, Bella.
"Hey.
It's so kind of you.
Kind is my middle name.
I'll see if Rosalie wants to dance.
Sorry I'm late.
It doesn't matter.
Everything is perfect now.
Dance with me?
Where have you been?
___ put your face on a milk carton.
I was in northern Canada.
I think.
It's weird going back to be back on two legs again.
With clothes.
Didn't have time to practice with the whole human thing
"Are you okay?"
Being here.
Why? Afraid I'll crash the party?
You're not the only one.
i think I'll be used to telling you goodbye now
Come on, you're not supposed to be the one crying, Bella.
Everyone cries at weddings.
This is how I will remember you
Pink cheeks,
two left feet ...
Heart beat.
So, Soon I'm gonna be dead to you?
No.
I'm Sorry.
I'm just trying appreciate your last night as a human.
Well, It's not my last night.
I thought you..
Didn't really want to spend my honeymoon writhing in pain.
Well, what's the point?
It's not like you're going to have a real honeymoon with him anyway
It's gonna be as real as any one else's
That's a sick joke.
You are joking.
What, While you're still human?
You can't be serious Bella. Tell me you're not that stupid
I mean it's really none of your business.
- No, you can't do this.
- Jake ...
- Listen, to me Bella.
- let me go!
Jacob, calm down. alright?
Are you out of your mind? You'll kill her!
- Walk away Jake!
Get off of me!
Enough, Jacob!
Stay out of this, Sam.
You're not going to start something that we have to finish.
- She'll die.
- It's not our concern anymore.
Let's go, Seth!
- I'm really, really stupid.
- No, it's alright
Come on. They're probably miss us. Let's go back.
So you really won't tell me where he's taking you?
No, it's a surprise.
Well, wear hat and sunscreen.
- Take care of yourself.
- I will
Okay...
I love you, Bella.
I love you.
So much
Thank you.
Everything's packed and ready to go
Cool.
I'm gonna go see him
"Dad?"
Well, it will be strange
You're not under my roof
Yeah.
It's gonna be strange for me too
You know that this will always be your home, right?
I love you, Dad.
Forever.
I love you too, Bella.
Always have and always will.
All right...
Go. You don't wanna miss your plane
Wherever its going
Okay..
Goodbye."
Ready?
Yeah I'm ready.
So we're not staying in Rio
No, just passing through.
Are we close?
That's Isle Esme.
It was a gift from Carlisle.
Is this totally necessary?
I'm nothing if not traditional.
Want to take a look around?
Are you tired?
Do you want to go for a swim?
Yeah, that sounds nice.
I could use a few human minutes.
Don't take too long Mrs. Cullen.
Okay.
Alice!
Don't be a coward.
You're so beautiful!
I promised I would try,
but if this doesn't work ...
I trust you.
It's okay.
How badly are you hurt?
What?
No, Bella. Look.
Bella, I can't tell you how sorry I am.
I'm not.
Really, I'm not!
Don't say you're fine.
Just don't.
No, you don't!
Don't ruin this.
I've already ruined it.
Why can't you see how perfectly happy I am?
Or was, five seconds ago.
And Now I'm sort of pissed off actually.
You should be angry with me.
We knew this was gonna be tricky, right?.
I think we did amazing.
I mean, It was amazing for me.
That's what you're worried about?
That I didn't enjoy myself?
I know it's not the same for you.
But for a human
I can't imagine that it gets any better than that
Last night, was the best night of my existence.
You're the best.
You're not gonna touch me again aren't you?
You know that' s not what I mean.
Let me make you breakfast.
I win.
Bella.
Are you having a nightmare?
No.
It's just a dream
And it's a really good dream
Then why are you crying?
Because I wanted it to be real.
Tell me.
Bella, I can't
"Please..."
Maybe they'll say she was in a car crash.
Or tripped and fell off a cliff.
At least, I'll get one thing out of it
No you won't
The Cullens are not a danger to the town or the tribe.
Well, he's either gonna kill her or change her.
- And the treaty says ...
- I say, Jacob.
I say.
You know if you wanted things to be different, you should've become Alpha.
Turning it down seemed like a good idea at the time
Jake, you really think you could kill Bella if she comes back a vampire?
No. He'll make one of us do it and held a grudge against us..
Shut up, Leah.
Would you just get over it?
It's not like you've imprinted on her
At least they seem happy.
Yeah, some people are just lucky I guess
Lucky?
None of them belong to themselves anymore
And the sickest part is..
their genes tell them they're happy about it.
At least if you've imprinted on someone, you'd finally forget about Bella
I mean, being any kind of happy is better
than being miserable about someone you can't have.
Bella, these are our housekeepers, Gustavo and Kaure.
-This is my wife, Bella.
-Nice to meet you
Guess let's just leave them to it.
What was that all about?
She's afraid of you.
Why?
Because I have you here, all alone..
you mean, She knows about you?
She suspects.
She's a native Ticuna.
They have legends about blood drinking demons
that prey on beautiful women.
- Monster!!
I've gone to the mainland to hunt. Be back before you wake.
You're late.
Bella.
Don't come in here.
You don't need to see this.
In sickness and in health, remember?
It must have been the chicken.
Would you grab my bag?
What is it?
How many days has it been since the wedding?
14, why?
Will you tell me what's going on?
I am late.
My period is late.
That's impossible.
Can this happen?
-Whoa.
- Alice.
- Bella, are you alright?
- I'm not 100% sure.
- Why? What's wrong?
- I just ...
You just what?
- Alice, what did you see?
- Here's Carlisle.
Bella, what's going on?
I don't know. I'm a little worried. Can vampires go into shock?
- Has Edward been harmed?
- No.
I know that it's impossible, but I think that I'm pregnant.
Carlisle, I swear something just moved inside me.
Is this even possible?
- I don't know.
What's he saying?
The sooner you get Bella home, the sooner we can find out what it is.
Yeah, I will
Well?
Damn it.
Kaure's making sure you're still alive.
What have you done with this little girl?
- I know that you're a demon. You've killed this girl.
- What?
- People have legends. She might have seen this before.
I will not let it hurt you.
Carlisle will get this thing to you.
The thing.
Wait here.
Hello?
- Rosalie.
Bella?
I need your help.
Hey, son.
What's going on?
Bella called him.
Hey, haven't seen you in a while.
Are you OK?"
- So you finally heard from Bella?
They're extending their trip.
It seems she caught a bug.
They  wanna wait til she feels better before they travel.
She's sick.
She told me not to worry, but she sound..
I don't know.. off.
She'll be okay Charlie.
Come on, let's eat.
Jacob.
Let it go.
Is it true?
- Hello, Jacob. How are you?
Listen, just give it to me straight.
Jake, is that you?
She's here?
- They came home two weeks ago.
Jake ...
I'm Glad you came.
- Close enough.
- What's your problem?
Rose, it's okay.
You look terrible.
Yeah. It's nice to see you too.
So are you gonna tell me what's wrong with you?
Rose, you wanna help me up?
You did this!
We didn't know it was even possible.
What is it?
- I'm not sure.
Ultrasound and the needles won't penetrate the embryotic sac.
I can't see it either
And I can't see Bella's future anymore
We've been researching legends, but there is so much to go on.
We do know that it's strong and fast growing.
Why haven't you done anything? Take it out of her!
This is none of your business dog.
Rose!
- All this fighting isn't good for Bella.
- The fetus isn't good for her.
Say the word, Alice. "Baby". It's just a little baby.
Possibly.
Carlisle, you've got to do something.
No.
It's not his decision. It's not any of yours.
Jacob, I need to talk to you.
I always knew you'd destroy her.
She thinks Carlisle can turn her on the last minute.
Like he did with me and Esme.
- Can he?
- The probability is.. slight
And if her heart fails..
Jacob, I need you to do something for me.
- Huh.
For her
You have a connection with her that I'll never understand.
Maybe you could talk to her,
change her mind.
Anything to keep her alive.
And if I can't
If she dies,
you will get what you always wanted ...
To kill me.
Rose, I'm fine. Really.
So Edward sent you in here to talk to me?
Sort of.
Though I can't figure out why he thinks you would listen to me
I mean, you never had before.
Since when are you and blondie BFFs?
Rose understands what I want.
What are you thinking, Bella?
Seriously.
I know this seems like a scary thing
It's not.
It's like this miracle or something
I can feel him
So it's a bouncing baby boy.
I'm sorry I didn't know. I should've brought some blue balloons.
It's just a guess.
When I picture him I see a boy
We'll see!
- You won't
- Jake, I can do this.
- I'm strong enough.
- Oh, Come on!
You can spout that crap to your bloodsucker, but you don't fool me.
I see what that thing is doing to you.
- It's a killer, Bella.
- You're wrong.
And when you die, well, what's the point?
Of me loving you. Of you loving him
How is that right for anyone?
Coz I sure don't see it
Live, okay?
"Please..."
Jake everything's gonna be okay.
Jake, don't go.
I know how this ends.
And I'm not sticking around to watch.
Jake, I can do this.
I'm strong enough.
Jake, don't go.
You did this
Jake everything's gonna be okay.
What they created won't be able to control his thirst.
Every human will be in danger.
- We are ready.
- We'll handle it
Now?
We must destroy it before it's born.
You mean, kill Bella?
Her choice, affects us all.
Bella's human. Our protection applies to her.
She's dying anyway!
We have real enemies to fight tonight.
"Tonight
You will fight with us, Jake.
I am the grandson of the chief!
I wasn't born to follow you or anyone else.
Whoa. Don't worry. they're not following us.
What are you doing here?"
- I left Sam's pack.
- Go home, Seth.
- I won't stand behind him
- Oh yes you will.
I'm not kidding. Get out of here.
Is that an order?
Are you gonna make me bow down too?
I'm not ordering anyone.
I'm just going off on my own here.
"Great!
- I've got your back
- No you don't!
If Sam comes after Bella,
are you really ready to fight your own brothers?
Your sister?
If it's  the right thing to do.
Whatever
I'm gonna go give the Cullens a heads up.
Do whatever you want.
How cool is this?
A two man pack.
- It's two against the world.
- You're getting on my nerves, Seth.
I'll shut up
Can do
Get ready.
They're coming for Bella
I can smell them all the way out here
____What the hell are you doing here?
I'm not gonna let my little brother get himself killed.
Go away, Leah! I can take care of myself.
Yeah you think so proves that you need a babysitter.
Will the both of you shut up?
- Did Sam send you?
-  Sam doesn't even know I left
I think he just figured it out.
Jake,
I know what his plan is
Sam lost the element of surprise
and he doesn't want to take you on outnumbered
so he's not gonna come at you head on.
He's got the place surrounded and he'll wait for his opportunity
He won't get through without a fight
No fights.
- We won't be the ones to break the treaty.
- The treaty is void
- At least in Sam's mind
- Not in ours
Carlisle, no one's hunted for weeks.
We'll make do.
You've done us some great service Jacob
Thank you."
I know they're out there somewhere
but i can't hear them anymore
It's so quiet ...
i stopped hearing them too
the second I decided to leave
it's nice
- You know you can't stay here.
"but i don't have..
I can't trust you with the Cullens
You hate them too much
- You don't even like me
- I don't have to
I just need to follow you
Look, Seth doesn't want you here.
And neither do I.
Being unwanted isn't exactly a new thing to me.
Look, I'll be stay out of your way
I'll do whatever you want except go back to Sam's pack
and be the pathetic ex-girlfriend he can't get away from
You don't know how many times I wish I could imprint on someone
Anyone..
Just to break the connection
All right...
I'm gonna do a perimter run
You got my flank?
Thank you."
Her rib is cracked
There are no splinters
Didn't even puncture anything
- Yet
- Edward.
It's breaking her bones now
It's crushing you from the inside out
Carlisle, tell her what you told me
- Tell her
Carlisle, tell me
It's alright.
The fetus isn't compatible with your body.
It's too strong
It won't allow you to get the nutrition you need.
It's growing by the hour. I can't stop it and I can't slow it down
At this rate, your heart will give out before you can deliver
- Then I'll hold on as long as I can
- Bella ...
There are some conditions that even venom can't overcome
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
Edward, I'm sorry.
I can't live without you.
You're gonna have a part of me.
He will need you.
Do you honestly think I could love it,
or even tolerate it, if it killed you?
It's not his fault.
- You have to accept what is
- Because you've given me no choice!
We're supposed to be partners. remember?
But you decided this on your own.
You Decided to leave me.
- Don't see it that way
- I have no other way to see it.
Because it means I'll lose you.
And I don't choose that
I don't choose that
Are you cold?
I got it.
Don't do that.
What?
Smile. like I'm your favorite person in the world.
You're one of them
It feels complete when you're here Jake
We need to find a way to get some food into her system
- If I could only see the fetus ...
- Baby.
Maybe I could figure out what it wants.
I think you might be right.
Jacob just had an idea.
It wasn't an idea. It was a snide comment
What were you thinking?
That it's just  probably looking for someone to sink its teeth into
He's thirsty.
I know the feeling.
If its craving, it's not gonna want animal blood.
I have some O negative set aside for Bella
Walk with me?
Wait, wait, wait! You're gonna make her drink that?
It 's the fastest way to test the theory.
Only if you're comfortable with it
I'll try anything.
Just hold on.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
This will make it a little easy to take
It tastes...
good.
Your pulse is already getting stronger
It's working.
- Well, you sound better.
- I am.
He still walks on water, and all that?
Yeah I mean it is different now
The important thing is that you're better and that you're coming home soon, right?
Okay Dad, I don't want you to freak out
but..."
I'm going to a medical center in Switzerland
What? No, you're not going to Switzerland!
- You said you were better!
"I am."
No, Bella, I'm getting on a plane now
No, It's really more of a spa
And I'm sure that i'd be better by the time you got there
Bells I don't know
Dad, don't come.
Picture me healthy
LIke I'm sitting on the couch with you, eating pizza.
You want me to visualize?
They say that it helps.
Just picture me like that
Like I was
It will make me feel better
Dad, I gotta go okay
Bella ...
- I love you.
- Bella ...
I'm sorry I've been so angry
I would be too.
I've left you alone in this.
Marriage.
They say the first year is the hardest.
- What was that?
"What?"
I thought I just heard...
Just say something else.
Like what?
Edward, what's going on?
He likes the sound of your voice.
You can hear him?
His mind.
He likes my voice too
It's weird ...
I thought he was like me, but he's not. He's like you
Good and pure.
He's happy.
Of course you are.
Of course you're happy. How could you not be?
I love you so much!
What you do hear now?
He loves you, Bella.
My God!
Jacob.
So, That's the last of it?
Bella could deliver tomorrow
If she's gonna have any chance at all, she needs more blood
And you need to feed.
You have to be at your strongest for her. We need to go tonight
Carlisle, you're the enemy now
Sam won't hesitate. You will be slaughtered
Emmet will come with us
- That won't be enough
- We have no choice, Jacob.
If there's anything we can do to save her, we've got to try
You'd risk your lives for her?
Of course we would
Bella is a part of our family now
Yeah
I can see that
This really is a family
As strong as the one I was born into
I know what I have to do.
Jake, they're coming!
I know
- We should phase Jacob
We can't protect ourselves like this
They'll see that as a threat
I want to talk!
It will be easier if I can hear you too.
This isn't your territory anymore
How's your new family working out?
You done?
You coming home, Jake?
Not until I finish this
What do you mean?
I want Sam to take Seth and Leah back
What? No way!
Be quiet.
I want them safe, and I want this over
I need Sam to wait until Bella is separated from the problem
- You mean 'til she's dead
- Ease up Paul
Then waht>
Tell Sam that when the time comes,
I'll be the one to destroy it
Jake!
I am the only one who can.
They trust me.
You played us!
Thank you."
- They make it out alright?
-Yeah
Good.
Hey
Are you OK?"
Yeah, it's not like I'm the one carrying a demon
This is pretty important, Bella.
Why don't you tell Jacob what you've decided
What now?
Rose  is trying to talk Bella out of her baby names
She hates them.
Well then I'm on your side no matter what you picked
They're not that bad
If a boy, EJ.
Edward Jacob.
Okay, fine. That one's not awful
Why don't you tell them the girl's name?
I was playing around with our mom's names
Renee and Esme.
And I was thinking, Renesmee.
R-Renesmee?
Is it weird?
Well, that's not too weird.
It's Beautiful!
And it's unique
It certainly fits the situation
I like Renesmee.
He likes it
Rosalie, pass the morphine.
Carlisle said the placenta must've detached
- He's coming as fast as he can
- We'll have to do it
Rose, let the morphine spread
There's no time. He's dying.
Get him out now!
Look at me, Bella.
Rosalie, don't!
Alice, get her out of here.
Rosalie!
- Save her! You gotta change her.
- I can't. Not while he's still in there.
I gotta get him out first.
Stay focused. Keep your heart beating.
He's suffocating!
It's Renesmee.
You're beautiful!
Bella.
Bella!
Jacob, take the baby.
Get that away from me.
Edward.
I'll take her
I promise I'm okay
What is that?
That's my venom
It's supposed to be working
Bella, come on.
Come on.
I won't kill you.
That would be too easy.
You deserve to live with this.
She didn't make it.
You're not dead. You're not dead.
Come on!
Come on!. It will work.
Please, please.
Come back to me, please.
Bella, please.
I don't care what he's done
He's still my son
I'm sorry, Billy.
I just thought you should know.
Bella is dead.
It killed her.
Let's go!
It's like gravity.
Your whole center shifts
Suddenly, it's not the earth holding you down
You would do anything,
be anything she needs
A Friend.
A brother,
a protector
Alice! Jasper!
You'll be fine.
- We're outnumbered.
- By lots.
I won't let them hurt my family.
Stop it! It's over.
If you kill her, you kill me!
Jacob imprinted.
They can't hurt her
Whoever a werewolf imprints on, can't be harmed
It's their most absolute law
She shouldn't be this still.
It's  the morphine.
- Maybe I was too late
- No, Edward.
Listen to her heart.
editted by Ash 112911