General, maybe you should slow down,
we have a big day tomorrow.
We're celebrating, captain. It's not every day you win
a war, let alone against the American devils.
I'm getting another bottle.
Excuse me.
I'm pretty sure it was my fault.
You speak Vietnamese.
I'm an interpreter.
I speak many tongues.
Let me buy you another drink...
unless you're here with someone.
I'm alone.
A bottle of Johnnie Walker please.
You're going to the Summit tomorrow?
A pretty girl interested in politics...
Looks can be deceiving.
Terrible thing.
Wha t is?
Being born like that.
Is it?
Can you imagine...
Looking in the mirror and seeing that
staring back at you?
Yes, I can.
Where do you think she comes from?
You think she has a family?