("You Really Got Me" intro playing)
(echoing giggle)
ALVIN:
We're back!
(rhythmic clapping,
electric guitar playing)
Let's go!
(cheering, whistling)
(audience screaming)
♪ Girl, you really got me now ♪
♪ You got me so I don't
know where I'm going ♪
♪ Girl, you really
got me now ♪
♪ You got me
so I can't sleep at night ♪
(camera shutter clicking)
♪ Girl, you really got me now ♪
♪ You got me so I
don't know where I'm going ♪
♪ Girl, you really got me now ♪
♪ You got me
so I can't sleep at night ♪
(barks)
♪ You really got me,
you really got me ♪
-♪ You really got me ♪
-(barking)
♪ Yeah, you really got me ♪
(guitar string clinks)
Nuts.
Give me the Black Beauty.
Alvin, take it easy out there.
You gotta share the spotlight.
You got it, Dave.
AUDIENCE (chanting):
Alvin!
-Uh, Dave!
-I'm serious, Alvin.
This is a charity benefit.
It's not all about you.
Sorry, Dave, I can't hear you over the
thousands of fans screaming my name.
(grunts)
I'm back, fellas.
(chuckles)
Yeah!
A little help, boys.
(cheering)
(laughs)
Yeah, man!
(electric guitar riff)
Alvin, will you please
get down from there?
I can't hear you.
Alvin,
I'm not kidding!
What? Whoa, whoa.
(electricity snapping, popping)
Dave! Look out!
Huh?
DAVE (screaming):
Alvin!
Dave!
(audience gasping, sighing)
Oh, Dave!
Dave?
MALE DOCTOR:
This should help with the pain.
I wanna talk to my boys.
Well, I just gave you a sedative
that will take effect
in about one minute.
So, uh... well,
let them in quickly.
-Dave!
Dave, you're alive!
-DAVE: Hey, guys.
-It was an accident!
-I swear!
-Are you okay?
I'm really sorry, Dave.
I'll be fine.
I'm just gonna be stuck here for a while.
Uh, and... and until I get out,
I've made arrangements for my Aunt Jackie
to come stay with you.
Who's Aunt Jackie?
The one who sends us those metal buckets
of yummy popcorn for Christmas.
Oh, Popcorn Jackie.
You don't have much time, Mr. Seville.
Uh, now listen.
I want you guys to go home
and live a normal childhood.
(sighs)
I've even made arrangements...
for you to go to school.
ALL:
School?
Yes, school.
Simon, I'm putting you in charge.
You are?
I'm... counting on... you.
Dave!
Wait a minute! Why is he in charge?
Whoa, he's counting on me.
Dave, please don't die.
He's just sleeping.
He's had a sedative.
Oh, a sedative.
Excuse me.
I'm here to escort the chipmunks home.
We're not leaving Dave!
I'm putting my paw down on this one!
You come here!
(mechanical whirring)
(chipmunks screaming)
I got it.
I'll fix it.
Nope, made it worse.
-Please, please, go.
-Oh, this must be it.
Uh-oh.
More stress you put on Monsieur Seville,
the longer it will take him to recover!
Whoa! Uh-uh!
You are too slow for me, nurse.
-DOCTOR: No, don't.
-You'll never take me!
I'm not going anywhere
without Da...
♪ Daydream believer
and a homecoming queen... ♪
(snoring)
I hope for your sake
he stays asleep for the entire flight.
Maybe we should give him
another shot.
Just to be sure.
(gasps)
Ugh.
(sniffing)
Any ideas on how we find Aunt Jackie?
Got it! Follow me!
Excuse me. Ooh, sorry.
Ooh, excuse me.
Coming through.
Look! Aunt Jackie!
(chuckling)
Oh, yeah.
-Aunt Jackie!
-Popcorn Jackie!
Oh, hello, dears!
-Cool wheelchair.
-Yay, we found you!
Popcorn!
Where's Simon and Theodore's?
Oh, there's plenty for everyone.
Let's have a hug first.
-Oh.
-Get over here,you old teddy bear.
I'm not really much of a hugger.
Oh, boys,
I want you to meet someone.
This is my grandson, Toby. Toby...
Hi, I'm Theodore.
Toby.
Ah! What? What happened?
-What?
-The boys.
-Oh, hey. Hey.
-Hi.
How are ya?
I'm Toby. Nice to meet you.
Toby's living with me till he figures out
what he wants to do with his life.
So far that means going, "pew, pew,
pew, pew, pew" with his thumbs all day.
Well, for the record, going "pew, pew,
pew, pew, pew" with my thumbs right now
is keeping me in first place,
so that's important.
Toby, get the bags.
-What bags?
-The luggage. Get the luggage.
Uh, oh, the lug... right.
Yeah, let me get those.
TOBY: Oh, sorry.
-Toby.
-Hit the brakes!
-Abandon wheelchair!
AUNT JACKIE:
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Tob-y-y-y.
Toby!
(sighs)
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
(crash)
(chipmunks groaning)
I'm so sorry, Aunt Jackie!
I'm so sorry! Is she gonna be okay?
Don't worry about me.
I'll be home in no time.
-In you go.
-(groans)
I wouldn't be so sure.
Wha...
It was an accident.
I swear.
Been there, done that.
Several times.
I guess you'll be taking care of us now.
I'll take "frightening thoughts"
for 500 please, Alex.
(grunting)
Not a problem. I could totally do this.
I took care of my cat.
Until he ran away.
Well, "ran away"
is kind of strong wording.
I think he just wanted his space.
I still see him around the neighborhood.
You know, he like, uh,
hisses and claws at me,
but I think that's just his way
of saying we're still tight, you know?
You guys have nothing
to worry about, seriously,
'cause I'm not gonna
be like Dave. You know, Dave's gone.
Gone?
Not "gone."
Not "gone" gone. He's... he's not dead.
He's very much alive.
He's completely coming back.
I'm just gonna be in his room
keeping his bed warm.
I'm gonna be doing my thing.
You'll be doing your thing.
You're not even gonna know I'm there.
Uh, we're supposed to know you're there.
That's, uh, that's the whole idea.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah, absolutely, yeah.
You'll know that I'm there.
I'm just saying
I'm not gonna be like,
"I know everything.
And you do this and you do that."
Like my dad.
-All right. Let's do this.
-(engine starts)
Oh, boy.
-(tires squealing and screeching)
-(clattering)
(tires squealing)
SIMON: Theodore, we're gonna be just fine.
The important thing is
we're all... still alive.
Well, maybe my "Get Well"
card will help Dave get home faster.
Um, it needs just a touch more glitter.
Yep, that should do it.
Who's hungry?
Ooh, ooh, me, me, me, me!
Let's eat!
Nada. Simon?
It's a food ghost town in here.
Alvin?
Holla!
The cheese balls are in the hizzouse.
♪ Well, you can tell
by the way I use my walk ♪
♪ I'm a cheese balls man ♪
♪ No time to talk ♪
♪ Whether you're a brother
or whether you're a mother ♪
♪ You've gotta love cheese balls,
gotta love cheese balls ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Get in my belly,
cheese balls, get in there ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Stayin' alive... ♪
(clanging)
Bingo!
Dinner, cheese a-served.
-Yay!
-All right!
Hey! What are you doing in here?
Uh... cheese ball?
MAN (over phone headset):
Dude, let's go. Come on.
Uh, Tombo, hey, hey.
Give me a second, real quick.
Alvin, I really,
really need to focus right now because
I am one knockout away
from a heavyweight title.
Ooh, can we play as well?
Uh, you know, I don't...
I don't want to hurt your feelings,
but I also don't want
to see anybody get hurt,
and there are going
to be fists of fury a-flying.
We can play Monopoly.
We play Monopoly with Dave all the time.
Do ya? That sounds...
that sounds fun.
And we should do that sometime,
but right now I gotta get back
to floating like a butterfly
and stinging like a bee, so...
TOBY: Hey, Tombo,
you still there, buddy?
Oh.
Ah, who needs Toby, Theodore?
-You got us!
-Yeah!
Who needs Toby?
Boys, right this way.
(all laughing)
♪ You spin me right round, baby ♪
♪ Right round like
a record, baby ♪
♪ Right round round round ♪
(holding note)
(all laughing)
I'm gonna puke!
(laughing)
Wait, wait.
Do you know what Dave would say
if he were here right now?
BOTH (screaming):
Alvin!
Not bad, but I think it needs
to come more from the belly.
ALL:
Alvin!
(all laughing)
-(rings)
-BOTH: Oh!
Hold it. Get it together.
(clears throat)
-Yee-haw!
-Shh, shh. Be cool.
-Yes?
-Hello?
DAVE: Boys, it's me.
-Huh? Dave?
-Dave?
As in... Dave?
Well, I guess since you
answered the phone,
you haven't burned down
the house yet.
ALVIN:
Have a little faith, Dave.
Yeah! Mayday!
(clattering)
What was that?
(whispering)
Don't stress him out.
Uh, that was Aunt Jackie.
Yeah. She's making us
a zesty five-course meal. (chuckles)
Really? Well, can I talk to her?
She's practicing her pole dancing.
DAVE: Pole dancing?
What happened to making dinner?
-Guys? What's going on?
-Gotta go, Dave.
-Alvin, I'm not kidding.
-Feel better.
-DAVE (yelling): Alvin!
-(phone disconnects)
Yep, nobody does that better than him.
(snoring)
(whimpering)
(shrieks)
(gasping)
(whimpering)
-Toby? Toby, wake up.
-(gasps)
What?
Oh, sorry.
Huh? No. That's... That's, uh... That's...
It's okay. What is it?
I... I had a nightmare.
Oh, the nightmares.
I hate the nightmares. What was it?
I... I dreamt
we didn't have a family anymore.
Oh, Theodore... Theodore,
that couldn't happen.
No. You guys are tight.
Nothing could ever separate you.
Unless, like an eagle swooped down
from the sky and was, like, "Caw! Caw!"
-What?
-And grabbed you and... (blubbering)
(laughs)
(whimpers)
Which... Which... Which...
couldn't happen ever.
So why would you... why would you ever
think that that would ever happen?
You know,
'cause the Eagles are in Philadelphia.
THEODORE:
No! No!
Sweet dreams.
(alarm clock buzzing)
ALVIN: Toby! Toby, make it stop!
What are you doing?
There's something wrong
with the clock. It won't shut up!
I can't sleep.
(screams)
That's the, uh...
That's the point.
It's a... It's a...
It's an alarm clock.
It's... It helps you
wake up early in the morning.
Why would anyone want
to wake up early?
Well, for school.
You got to be there by 8:00.
In the morning?
Look, I don't like getting up
this early any more than you do.
But we are in this together, Alvin.
Sooner you get to school,
sooner I get to come home
and get back to sleep.
You mean,
you don't stay with us at school?
No, no, no, no, no.
I've done my time.
Thank you very much.
-But school is fun, right?
-(laughing) Fun?
Well, I guess maybe it's, uh, fun-ish.
Hey, it's my cat.
Hey, remember?
I was telling you. Hey, hey.
Hey, kitty, it's me, remember?
(hisses)
(yelling)
Whoa!
(cat yowling)
I treated you good.
(yowling)
(tires squealing)
("Bring It On" playing)
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on,
come on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
get up and move yourself ♪
♪ Go on, go on, go on,
go on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
it's time to bring it on ♪
(tires squealing)
Okay, here we go.
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
Enjoy your first day at school.
See you around 3:00-ish.
(tires squealing)
Okay.
(school bell ringing)
We got this.
This should be a walk in the park.
A chaotic and frightening walk
in the park.
Hi. I'm Theodore.
Hi! I'm Theodore.
-Hi. I'm... Oh!
-Look out!
Hi. I'm The...
(screaming)
Guys! Guys!
(chipmunks yelling and screaming)
Oh, boy.
(gasps)
Eagle!
-BOY: Go, Eagle!
-Eagle!
(screaming)
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Oh! Ow! Ouch! Aah!
(crashing)
That wasn't very fun-ish.
-(clears throat)
-Oh.
You must be our new students.
I'm Dr. Rubin, the principal.
And we are The Chipmunks.
Yes. Well, that would explain
the fur and the bushy tails.
Follow me, gentlemen.
Gentlemen?
Oh, us. Right.
There was a minute left
and we were down by two,
and I'm, like, "Coach, I don't care if my
leg's broken. Put me in. I can win this."
I never get tired of this story.
So I hobble out, barely able to stand.
Did I mention my leg was broken?
-(knocking)
-Miss Ortega?
Yes?
Good luck.
Thanks.
Well, guys, welcome to homeroom.
Good to be here...
I hope.
So this is a classroom.
(sniffing)
I love the smell
of zit cream in the morning.
Hello, ladies.
(girls chattering and squealing)
The Chipmunks!
GIRL:
Love you, Alvin!
GIRL TWO: Hi.
Hi. I'm Theodore.
Hi, I'm Theodore.
(muffled)
Hi. I'm Theodore.
Yes, he's Theodore,
in case you missed it, and I am Simon.
GIRLS: Aw!
The name's Seville.
Alvin Seville.
Oh.
(speaking French)
Enchante, mademoiselle.
(sighs)
Somebody's gonna have to knock
those guys down to size.
Well, that should be pretty easy.
I mean, they're only eight inches tall.
("The Song" playing)
♪ 'Cause when I rock,
no one rocks harder than me ♪
♪ And I don't stop
'cause I got that energy ♪
♪ I got the bass and the drums,
they're moving me along ♪
♪ Oh, inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ You think I'm crazy, baby ♪
♪ Inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
HAWKE:
I had 15 cars.
I mean, that's like five more cars
than anybody really needs.
I had seven maids.
I had courtside seats to the Lakers.
Even my maids
had courtside seats to the Lakers.
-And now, look at me.
-MAN (over radio):Time for number one.
-Look at me!
-MAN: With Alvin and the Chipmunks.
I lost everything...
except for my dignity.
They can't take that away from me.
-♪ Girl, you really got me now ♪
-(chirps)
And it's all because of them.
♪ You got me so I
don't know what I'm doing ♪
(yells)
Oh, hey. Breakfast.
(laughs)
Now I run around, hoping and praying
that I can find other animals
that can sing or dance.
-I mean...
-(squeaking)
Wait a second.
You don't sing, do you?
Hey! Hey,
that's my muffin! My...
Give me my muffin,
you dirty rat! (grunts)
(squeaking)
I will get you, chipmunks.
(yelping)
Girls, we got to get out of here.
I can't see.
Ow! Not on my nose.
-That's my tail.
-Sorry.
-Move your butt.
-Okay.
Who's pushing me?
(grunting and groaning)
(gasping)
(sighs)
We made it.
JETT Records.
Whoo...
Oh, my gosh.
It's him. Ian Hawke.
Um, Mr. Hawke?
That voice.
I can't get it out of my head.
Hello! Mr. Hawke!
That's not in my head.
That's really happening.
-What do you want?
-We want to introduce ourselves.
That's right.
I'm Brittany.
And this is my sister, Eleanor.
Hello, sir.
Such a pleasure to meet you.
And I'm their sister, Jeanette.
Although, I feel more like an Olivia.
Or sometimes...
Anyway, we are The Chipettes.
And, well, we would just be so honored
to have you represent us.
You made Alvin and the Chipmunks stars.
-We want to be stars too.
-Yeah.
And hang out with the Chipmunks.
(laughs)
Okay. Now, listen, before we get all girly
and giggly about this,
uh, just tell me one thing.
You can sing, right?
(whispering)
Anyway, hang on.
Not here. Um...
Why don't we, uh, take this meeting
upstairs in my penthouse office?
Sure.
Oh, this is so exciting.
We're really on our way now.
Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
Can you believe it?
Oh, my first penthouse office!
Oh, wow.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my...
The Hollywood sign.
-Oh.
-Wow.
Thought you might like the view.
So, ladies, tell me a little something
about yourselves.
Well, we grew up in a small town,
population 300 and--
Yeah? Really?
That's fascinating.
Great. All right.
Impress me.
(chipmunks whispering)
One, two, three.
(snap fingers)
(singing "Put Your Records On")
♪ Three little birds sat on my window ♪
♪ And they told me
I don't need to worry ♪
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah ♪
♪ Girl, put your records on ♪
♪ Tell me your favorite song ♪
♪ You go ahead,
let your hair down ♪
♪ Go ahead,
♪ Sapphire and faded jeans ♪
♪ I hope you
get your dreams ♪
♪ Just go ahead,
let your hair down ♪
Girls, girls, girls, girls.
Guess who just became the number one
Chipette fan in the whole dang world?
Ian Hawke, that's who!
(Chipettes cheering)
Oh, my goodness.
So when can we meet the Chipmunks?
Uh, that's an excellent question,
and the excellent answer is
I don't really represent
Alvin and the Chipmunks anymore.
-Oh, no!
-What happened?
Oh. Classic tale.
Sweet and innocent when I met them.
They had nothing, and then,
I worked my butt off to make them
rock stars and... they changed.
Turned on me like bad cheese.
No!
Oh. That's terrible.
I know.
I mean, I treated Alvin
like he was my own son,
you know, and then
he just goes and spits on me.
Literally. He filled his chipmunk cheeks
with saliva and just had at it.
Don't even get me started about Simon.
(gasps)
But not Theodore, right?
It's the cuddly ones
-you have to watch out for.
-(sighs)
HAWKE: But what are we talking
about them for? Come on.
HAWKE:
They're over. Tired, novelty act.
Chipmunks who can sing.
(yawns)
But...
Girl chipmunks
who can sing?
Fasten your seat belts.
(cheering)
ALVIN: So, I'm on Jay Z's yacht, right?
And I say, "Jay, where's Beyonce?
And he says, "She's holding
a plate full of cheese balls."
Turn around, and guess what? She was.
(girls laughing)
P.S.
Dave left me in charge.
Staying up till 10:00 every night.
-Oh, yeah.
-(laughing)
Hey, girls.
Look what I can do.
(girls laugh)
-You are Theodorable.
-THEODORE: Thank you.
You're so cute.
Whoops.
Oh! I am so sorry.
It's cool.
No harm done.
Not yet.
Girls, please.
Private conference.
-(scoffs)
-RYAN: Thank you.
Listen up, rock stars.
If you talk to those girls again,
you're dead.
If you look at those girls again,
If you even think about those girls...
Are you thinking about them?
Well, I am now!
That's it.
-You're dead!
-CHIPMUNKS: Run!
Daniel, come on!
Get back here, you dirty rats!
-Hang ten, bros!
-Whoa!
Scatter!
Go, go, go!
That way, over there!
Oh, Ryan!
Hey, slowpokes.
Catch me if you can!
You're dead, furball!
Not!
-It's wedgie time!
-Oh!
My butt!
-(groaning)
-(Alvin laughing)
(panting)
Oh, boy...
Uh, eagle.
(screaming)
-Eagle! Eagle!
-RYAN: Get him!
(screaming)
Bully, bully!
This way! This way!
RYAN: Gotcha!
-SIMON: Guys, wait, wait. Time-out.
-RYAN: It's swirly time!
Oh, come on. Come on, guys.
This is so 1980s.
(screaming)
Police! Police!
(gargling)
Oh, man!
Oh, come on!
That, that's
a good look for you. Oh. Thank you.
I can't swim. Help!
-Grab on, Simon.
-(Simon grunting)
Oh, thanks.
(blubbering)
You okay?
Well, uh, considering
that you just saved me
from drowning in a toilet,
I'm, uh, pretty good.
I'll be right back.
A-Alvin, Alvin! We're not gonna
solve anything with violence.
-RYAN: It's the fatty ratty.
-THEODORE: Cut it out.
-This rat has serious junk in the trunk.
-BOY: Yeah, little fatty.
THEODORE: Hey, stop it.
-RYAN: He jiggles when I poke him.
-(growling)
-(boys screaming)
-RYAN: Mommy!
Simon, does this make
my butt look smaller?
Theodore, your butt looks fine.
Those guys are just jerks.
(door opening)
(growling)
-(barking)
-(boys whimpering)
Gentlemen.
You threatened to climb inside
of him and build a nest.
That was out of line. Um, I'm not
even sure that's physically possible.
I should suspend all three of you.
Please do.
Instead, I have a better idea.
Due to budget cutbacks,
we are in jeopardy of losing our beloved
music program.
-That's awful.
-DR. RUBIN: I know.
But there is one small ray of hope.
Every year, the district sponsors
a music competition
and the winner's school receives $25,000.
If we win, we can save our program.
And you want us to perform?
'Cause I didn't think you were a fan.
Why don't you sleep on it?
-Wait a minute! What is that?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait, wait, wait.
-THEODORE: I look skinny.
-That's us.
Promise me that you won't say anything.
A principal has a certain image to uphold
and if the faculty
ever found out about this, I could...
Oh... I just cannot believe
that you're actually sitting in my office!
I have all of your CDs.
I even went to see you
last year in Denver.
That's where I got this.
It was my birthday.
And I was like, "Oh, The Chipmunks!"
So, what do you say?
Will you represent our school?
Honestly, suspension
still sounds pretty good to me.
Come on, Alvin, what do you say?
One for all and three for one!
Well put, Theodore, very well put.
Count us in.
ALVIN (unenthusiastically):
Yay.
Go, Eagles!
(hisses)
Eagles? Where?
HAWKE:
Ah, the penthouse level.
(speaking French)
Tres exclusivo.
(dog whimpering)
BRITTANY:
Isn't that that Chihuahua?
You know, from the movie?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it is.
I mean, yeah, of course it is.
A lot of, a lot of big names live here.
(speaking Spanish)
Hola. Como estas?
I must have his autograph.
Hey, hey, Brittany, uh-uh.
You wanna be a star?
Act like a star.
All right, you don't get autographs.
You give them.
Oh. Right.
Uh, uh... Hey, look, over there.
There's a couple of the Jonas Brothers.
(gasps)
Where?
-I don't see them.
-HAWKE: Here we are.
Okay. Let's, uh, scoot into my apart...
What? Did I?
I, oh, darn it!
Darn it to heck!
-What's wrong?
-Girls, I apologize,
but I seem to
have left my keys back in my office.
Ah...
What if one of you
were to shoot through that mail slot
and open it up from the inside? Huh?
Oh, I'll do it.
(grunting)
I'm stuck!
All right, I got you. I got you.
(grunting)
Oh, oh, ow!
Not so hard!
-HAWKE: Might wanna lay off the nuts.
-Oh.
All right, how about you, glasses?
You're in better shape. Wanna go?
Uh, I'm not that great
at things like this.
I got it!
(lock clicking)
Yes.
Ooh, impressive!
(gasps)
Nice.
Gee willikers.
-Stripes.
-Oh, snazzy.
(gasps)
Circles!
This is the best tree house ever!
A red piano.
-Oh, red.
-Is this a dream?
Somebody pinch me.
-Ah...
-Oh...
This is way better than a tree.
Oh, I just adore a penthouse view.
Nice one, Hawke.
-Yeah, you like it?
-Do I?
-I live here.
-It's so beautiful.
HAWKE: Yeah.
ANNOUNCER:
Last time we visited Meerkat Manor,
a rival group called the Commandos
was making large inroads
into the Whiskers' territory.
(Meerkat Manor
theme song playing)
(sniffing)
Ah, Toby.
I thought Alvin was messy.
This is literally disgusting.
I feel like I'm living
in a dumpster. Ooh...
Simon, it's Meerkat Manor.
Watch with me.
(sighs) Well, yeah, you know you're right.
You're right. I just need to relax.
Maybe that'll, uh,
ease my nerves a little.
-(crunch)
-Wait. What is this?
What? Oh, you gotta
be joking. A taco? In a blanket?
Toby.
TOBY: Ladies and gentlemen,
going for his turkey, it's the Tobester.
(grunts)
Come on, baby.
(Toby laughing)
Yes.
Yes!
-Eh?
-No problem.
Watch and learn, my friends.
(crackling)
Whoops.
Well, it looks like it's time to play
my second favorite game,
"Hide the broken TV from Dave."
You wanna play?
No!
Go easy on him, taco boy.
This day's been bad enough already.
Oh, I think I see what's going on.
TOBY: You guys been having
some problems at school?
Uh, no, not really.
Unless you consider having your head
dumped into a public toilet a problem.
(laughing) Ouch.
Swirlies are the worst.
At least, that's what I've heard.
Because there's no way that I could
possibly know that on a...
on a personal level.
Toby, what was school like for you?
THEODORE: Toby...
-(school bell ringing)
-Toby?
(toilet flushing)
(gurgling and chuckling)
Ow, ow.
Ow, ow!
(shrieking)
(school bell ringing)
THEODORE: Toby?
THEODORE (yelling):
Toby!
What?
What was school like for me?
Uh, in a word...
awesome.
But, you know, that's 'cause
I was like extremely popular.
Is that why you still
live with your grandma?
And refer to yourself
as "The Tobester"?
And go "Pew, pew, pew" all day?
(chuckles smugly)
Bedtime.
(alarm buzzing)
Alvin?
Alvin, wake up and turn off the alarm.
(alarm continues buzzing)
Alvin!
Alvin, I'm not kidding.
I'm not kidding, buddy. Turn it off!
Guys, guys...
(alarm buzzing)
Boys, this isn't funny.
ALVIN (muffled): Hello, Humane Society?
Yes, I need help. A man is after us.
He wants to take us to a terrible place!
-School!
-TOBY: Out.
-Oh, have a heart, huh?
-Have a heart?
Dave wants you to go to school,
so you're going.
Yeah, well, don't worry about
picking us up at 3:00, Toby.
We'll get a ride in a hearse!
Guys, guys, come on.
Look, trust me.
The second day is never
as bad as the first.
(grunting)
SIMON: Glasses, glasses!
You wouldn't hit a guy with glasses,
would you?
Right in the pancreas.
(grunting)
(panting, groaning)
Call... the... nurse.
Out, out, you're out!
Come on, Alvin!
Remember your five Ds!
Dodge, duck, dip, dive, and dodge!
-BOY: Move!
-You're next, furball.
You talking to me?
I'm the only one here,
so you must be talking to me.
(crowd laughs)
-Yeah!
-Whoa!
-Got him!
-RYAN: Did you see that?
Ooh, booyah!
Unbelievable.
He caught it. You're out, man.
-(school bell ringing)
-And the fat lady, she's a-singin'.
Dude's got hands.
-I think they're paws actually.
-Whatever.
We can definitely use him on the team.
Hey, furball.
RYAN: How'd you like a spot
on the football team?
Football? Moi?
I gotta say, you're good.
I'm gonna let you
hang out with us at lunch.
RYAN: That is,
if you wanna be on the team.
Hmm...
Interesting proposition.
THEODORE: Alvin?
Let me get back to you on that.
This is a one-time offer.
Don't take too long to think it over.
(boys laugh)
Right.
Like I would ditch my brothers
just to become the first chipmunk ever
to play on an actual
varsity football team.
(forced chuckle)
Fat chance.
ALVIN: The stadium is pandemonium.
It's fourth and goal.
It's up, it's up...
And he catches it!
The crowd goes crazy.
(mimicking screaming crowd)
RYAN: Psst. Hey.
Me?
ALVIN (chanting):
Alvin! Alvin! Alvin! Alvin!
(mimicking screaming crowd)
Alvin, I think the super-cool jock table
is paging you.
Why would I go over there?
Like I really need to worry
about being popular.
Hello! Talking chipmunk.
Huh?
World-famous rock star.
Guy with his own plush doll.
Guys, I'm on pajamas!
Not toot my own horn, but...
(mimicking honking horn)
Come on.
(chuckling)
It's... It's... It's laughable.
Just go, Alvin.
-Really? You mean it?
-Yeah.
Oh, thanks.
I'll be right back.
-What up, dudes?
-What's up, lil' man?
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Welcome to the cool table.
-Bring it. Pound the paw.
-Yeah.
("It's OK" playing)
♪ Hang tight, just hold on ♪
♪ Get up, you know
you gotta push on ♪
(Alvin groans)
I want it!
I got it! I got it!
I... (grunts) don't got it.
-I think he's cute.
-Me too.
ALVIN: Toss.
And he's up.
(cheering and applauding)
Thank you.
Hey, Alvin.
Call me.
Bernie, I'm telling ya.
Chipmunks are old news.
I got the next big thing.
Singing female chipmunks.
Hello? Bernie? Hello?
Oh, God! What part of "singing female
chipmunks" don't these people understa...
Girls... we're going to school.
And he's up.
-BOYS: Oh!
-And he scores!
(boys cheering)
Hey, what up, S?
Whoa, don't hate on the high-five.
Yeah. High-five.
Look, Alvin, I know you guys
have been busy with your
sporting endeavors and what not,
but, uh, I could really
use your help at home.
Oh, no, can do.
Ry Dog is going to teach me
how to get pretty girls to do my homework.
Uh, well, Alvin,
you promised Theodore we'd hang out.
We are watching
Meerkat Manor tonight. No pretty girls.
Dude, I can't swing it today, bro.
That's what you say every day, Alvin.
Need I remind you
it's your day to do the laundry?
RYAN: Better listen to your daddy, Alvin.
You don't want to get grounded.
Oh!
Are you going to pick that up?
Are you going to make me?
(chuckles) (speaking French)
Au contraire, mon frere.
I'm just going to elegantly show you
how it's done.
Eh, Simon...
Off the glass.
And you call yourself a jock.
-(laughs)
(laughs sarcastically)
Ha, my brother.
He's a real jokester.
Always kidding.
Uh, anyhoo, um, see you guys in class.
-Hey, that's my plate.
-It's my plate.
(laughs)
Why are you trying to embarrass me
in front of my friends?
Are you kidding me?
They are the ones you should be
embarrassed by.
-Good luck with the show, guys.
-Front row seats.
Can't wait.
So, what song are we gonna sing?
No pressure, but the whole school
is counting on us.
Oh, relax.
It's like Ryan says.
"Who's gonna beat singing chipmunks?"
("I Want to Know What Love Is"
playing)
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
(all sigh)
(school bell rings)
Oh, that Simon is dreamy.
I think Theodore was looking at me.
Yeah, I know.
But, guys, remember what Ian said?
We can't trust them.
Whoa.
-(sighs)
-(purrs)
(piano playing)
(chipmunks singing
"Follow Me Now")
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Get up, get up ♪
♪ Let's go,
won't you follow ♪
♪ Let's go, won't you... ♪
(sighs)
What happened?
I'd never thought I'd say this, but,
pink is my new favorite color.
Her glasses were quite fetching.
She's like a beautiful, green gumdrop.
Okay, well, if you guys want to do this,
you have to pay attention.
Maybe this is a good time
for us to take a break.
Good call.
Take five.
Oh, she...
Oh, she's right.
-Oh, we need to focus, fellas.
-Right.
This is for my screen saver.
Cheese balls!
Hey, guys. Hey.
You guys ready to go?
Guys, I got a lot of important stuff
to do at home.
Oh, you must be their guardian.
Guard... That I...
That I am.
Yes, I am. Hi. How are you?
How are you, Dr. Rubin?
I know that because I went to school here
a few years ago.
I don't know if you remember me.
Toby Seville. Probably not.
Mmm. I...
Toby?
(gasps)
MISS ORTEGA: No way!
Hi!
Hey, no braces.
-(breathing heavily)
-You look great.
You... I... Thank you. Appreciate it.
I did... I did...
I... I did get my braces off
because they were just...
(clattering)
(screams)
TOBY: Oh! Okay.
(glass shattering)
Oh, that.
(clattering)
(mimicking trumpet)
(nervous chuckle)
That...
(clanging)
You know what? I know a guy who actually,
who... who works on drum heads.
So that's very good.
I'll be in the car, guys. (sighs)
ALVIN (sing-song):
Somebody's in love.
That aside, uh, we're... we're going
to replace everything. Chipmunks' honor.
HAWKE: Ah, yes, the old false modesty
suck-up routine.
-Ian Hawke?
-Ian?
Thought I smelled a rat.
May I help you, Mr. Hawke?
Well, I was wondering
if I could, uh, help you.
I... I just heard about
your musical competition
and I just skedaddled down here
as quick as I could to volunteer my girls.
Oh. Well, that's very thoughtful of you,
but I've already made up my mind.
Well, um, perhaps,
this will change your mind.
Girls!
(all gasp)
They're with Ian?
Curtains.
(chipettes whispering)
One, two, one, two.
("Hot N Cold" starts)
(guitar and drum intro playing)
♪ You change your mind ♪
♪ Like a girl
changes clothes ♪
♪ I should know ♪
♪ That you're
no good for me ♪
♪ 'Cause you're hot,
then you're cold ♪
♪ You're yes,
then you're no ♪
♪ You're in,
then you're out ♪
♪ You're up,
then you're down ♪
♪ You're wrong
when it's right ♪
Wow, they're good.
Good?
They're astounding!
♪ We kiss, we make up ♪
♪ You, you don't really
wanna stay, no ♪
♪ But you, but you don't
really wanna go, oh ♪
♪ 'Cause you're hot,
then you're cold ♪
♪ You're yes,
then you're no ♪
♪ You're in,
then you're out ♪
♪ You're up,
then you're down ♪
♪ 'Cause you're hot,
then you're cold ♪
♪ You're yes,
then you're no ♪
♪ You're in,
then you're out ♪
♪ You're up,
then you're down ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
(holding note)
(cheering and applauding)
My good people
of West Eastman,
you have just witnessed the debut
of The Chipettes!
-(cheering and applauding)
-Thank you.
So?
They were splendid, but as I said before,
I have made my decision.
-Brit!
-No.
I see.
You... you've made your decision.
I don't mean to speak out
of school, Doctor, but,
um, in the true spirit of democracy,
which our great,
wonderful country was founded upon,
I say, "Let the people vote."
Let them choose. One person, one vote!
I say, "Let us vote."
Let us vote!
ALL (chanting):
Let us vote! Let us vote!
Let us vote!
Please, don't be a Fascist Franny.
Let freedom ring, Doctor.
ALL (chanting):
Let us vote! Let us vote!
You make a persuasive case, Mr. Hawke.
All right, here's what I'm going to do.
This Friday, each group will perform
one song in front of the student body.
-Yeah!
-Right!
Whoever gets the most applause
will represent the school.
-(cheering and applauding)
-What?
-Thank you.
-Yes.
We did it.
In your face!
Oh, it is on like Donkey Kong.
ANNOUNCER (on TV):
The meerkats huddle together
at the end of a traumatic day
to reaffirm their family bond.
The Whiskers are going to have to rely
on each other more than ever.
Guys, I am so happy that Miss Ortega
can rehearse with us
every day after school.
Whoa! Every day?
-But, Ryan and I...
-Alvin, stop right there, okay?
We're a team.
We need you.
Would you relax?
We're not gonna lose.
We'll talk about this in the morning.
Not much to talk about.
I will see you at rehearsal.
Stop hogging!
I'm not hogging.
You might as well be rooting out truffles
in the French countryside
because are you in fact hogging!
-I'm not! Not!
-Are so!
-So! So! So!
-I'm not! Not! Not!
-(overlapping chatter)
-Ah, forget it!
I think I'll sleep in my own bed tonight.
Ditto for me.
-ALVIN: I'm so glad I'm not a meerkat!
-SIMON: Oh, really? Why's that?
ALVIN: Because as cold as I am,
I would never huddle with you!
-SIMON: Good.
-ALVIN (muffled): You hear me?
I won't huddle!
SIMON (muffled): Fine.
(whimpers)
Uh, Toby.
Can...
Can I sleep with you?
What?
Dave lets me.
My brothers are fighting.
Well, I'm...
You... okay.
(groans)
(sighs)
(breaking wind)
THEODORE:
Oh, man! Dutch oven! Not the Dutch oven!
Oh, anything but the Dutch oven!
Must find fresh air before it's too late!
(screaming)
It's too late!
Oh, it burns!
Mama, it burns!
(inhales sharply)
(whimpering)
(sighs)
Hmm, let's see...
What else am I in the mood for?
How about a side order of friendly advice?
Courtesy of me.
No, thanks.
Grapes, please.
-Oh. Ow!
-(chuckles, clears throat)
-Excuse me.
-Yeah, well...
I... I just wanted
to warn you about Ian.
What? You should be grateful to Ian.
He did everything
for you, Alvin, and you broke his heart.
Hmm, really?
How do I put this gently?
He's the devil.
He doesn't have a heart.
Oh, and one of the things he did for us
was put us in a cage.
Alvin, he would never do that.
Yeah, 'cause you were there.
I forgot.
Brittany, you better watch out.
-I don't need advice from you.
-But--
But nothing, Alvin. Ian's taking us
straight to the... (screaming)
(clattering)
(laughing)
Got it.
Straight to the top. Ironic.
Yeah, funny.
(mockingly laughs)
THE CHIPETTES:
♪ Uh oh oh, uh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Uh oh oh oh ♪
We are so going
to destroy those Chipmunks.
I don't want
to destroy them. Me neither.
I just wanna hang out with them.
All right, all right,
hold on, all right, look.
Uh, you know, if you feel that way,
maybe we should just
withdraw from the contest.
-What?
-And then I'll put you in a FedEx package
and mail you back to whatever tree
you came from. Sound good?
-No.
-HAWKE: Okay, then.
Take it from the top.
Let's go.
-("Single Ladies" starts)
-♪ Uh oh oh ♪
HAWKE: All right, wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, stop.
Short one in the green dress.
What's your name again?
Eleanor.
Yeah, look, I'm losing you there,
you know?
-Have you always been that short?
-I... I guess.
Well, you gotta work on that, okay?
All right, let me,
let me try something here.
Uh, Brittany, here, come up here.
No, you two stay back.
-HAWKE: A little further.
-Um...
Oh, yeah.
Now that I like.
And it's not just because Brittany's
more of a mega ultra superstar
than you guys.
Good, good. Okay, you know what?
Let's get a little more separation.
Brittany, stay there. Let's get a little
more separation from you guys.
Yeah, let's give her some room.
Give her some room, guys.
Back, okay.
All right, watch me now.
-One, two, three, now watch me.
-(music starts)
HAWKE:
Watch me now.
♪ Uh oh oh,
uh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
(ringing)
Hello?
Toby?
What are you doing at the house?
Where's Aunt Jackie?
Dave, hey.
Hey, Dave, what's happening?
Uh, Jack...
Aunt Jackie is, uh...
in the hospital.
I'm a little worried.
Who's watching the boys?
I am.
So, Dave, uh, how is Paris?
Wait. Are the boys behaving?
Absolutely.
They've been just peachy.
Toby, what's going on?
Huh? Nothing. Nothing.
No, don't even...
Don't even worry about it.
You know, I know that you're
not supposed to be stressed out,
so I'm gonna go right now,
but it's all good here.
Come home soon.
Bye.
-Toby? Toby?
-(monitor beeping rapidly)
Nurse!
Nurse, get me out of here!
Help!
(mumbling)
I don't mean to interrupt your game,
but, I saw you stand up
to Ryan when he littered.
-That took guts.
-Really?
And that's the type of guy
that we're looking for.
Jeremy Smith,
Student Body President.
How do you do?
I'm--
International recording star
and litter monitor, Simon Seville?
Litter monitor?
Litter monitor.
It's a new position that we've created
to help raise awareness
of a pressing problem in our society.
I agree 99% plus one.
You do the math.
Well, Simon, I know this is a lot to ask,
but, we're looking for
a take-charge guy to
take charge of this
very rewarding position.
What do you say?
(drum roll)
SIMON: Excuse me, everybody.
Quick announcement.
Uh, I'm Simon.
I'm the litter monitor.
Put your trash in the garbage can.
Peace out.
(students laughing)
Hello, ladies.
You probably weren't aware
that you dropped a wrapper on the ground,
so we're just going
to call this one a warning.
Carry on.
(students laughing)
-What up, dudes?
-What up, Al?
Hey, everybody, check it out.
The newest member of the football team.
RYAN: Suiting up for our first away game.
Ry, don't mess with me.
I talked to Coach.
You're in.
Dude, that's great.
Awesome!
So check it out, A-Man.
We're watching the new litter monitor.
I wasn't aware
the school even had a litter monitor.
We don't.
But don't tell him that.
(chuckles)
Are you going to pick that up?
No.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
I, uh, guess I'm going
to have to give you a citation.
-Oh! Oh, no, I...
-Oh ho...
-I got a citation for littering.
-BOY: Oh, no.
(laughter)
Oh, you want to play that game,
do you? (scoffs) Well, guess what?
-I can play that game all day long.
-Simon...
-It's a joke, dude.
-Litter is no joking matter.
-(laughter)
-BOY: No, you're the joke.
We're messing with you.
There's no such thing as a litter monitor.
-What?
-Good one, huh?
(chuckles)
You knew about this, Alvin?
Does the word "brother"
mean anything to you?
Y-Yes, o-of course.
Yeah, well, he has some new brothers
now that he's on the football team.
You still haven't picked up that litter.
-You want me to get rid of litter?
-Yeah.
Let's start with you.
Hey... let go.
Let go.
No... Whoa!
ALL: Oh!
-Downtown.
-Whoo!
(school bell ringing)
Uh, I'll catch up with you guys
in a second.
-GIRL: I'll catch you later.
-BOY: Good luck...
ALVIN: Simon!
Simon! Simon!
Okay, I am a total jerk.
I admit it.
So are we cool now?
-(screams)
-(yelps)
(both yelling and grunting)
(panting)
Alvin, I am going to put this behind us
for Theodore's sake.
I know. That's why I'm giving you
the Alvin guarantee
that I will be at that sing-off
Friday night.
W-W-Wait.
Why wouldn't you be there?
Uh, because, uh, I have a, uh...
(mumbling)
A football game.
-What?
-(mumbling) A... football game.
-You have a what?
-A football game!
There, I said it.
A football game.
(both yelling and grunting)
Simon, Alvin, is everything all right?
Theodore.
Oh, yeah, we're fine.
Just a little dumpster wrestling.
(chuckles)
Crazy in here.
Right.
Don't worry, Theo.
Everything is gonna be fine. (chuckles)
Alvin, do not miss that sing-off.
Don't worry, Simon.
I'll be there.
I can do both.
Hey, guys, thanks so much
for helping out today.
Toys for Tots
is a really cool organization,
so everybody's getting cool points today.
(grunting)
What's going on with Theodore?
I have no idea.
(sighs)
Hey, Eleanor, why don't you see
if Theodore needs-some help?
Well, okay.
(murmuring)
(muttering)
Whoops.
Oh, um...
They don't look very comfortable.
(sighs)
Oh, my shoes?
They're not.
But, um, Ian says that I need to work on
being taller.
Well, I think you look great
just the way you are.
You do?
Uh-huh.
("I Try" playing)
♪ Games, changes and fears ♪
(phone ringing)
♪ When will they go
from here? ♪
ANSWERING MACHINE:
Hi, you've reached Dave Seville.
-Please leave a message.
-(machine beeps)
JULIE (on phone): Hi, Toby.
This is Julie Ortega. We talked yesterday.
Well, we kind of sort of did.
Um, anyway, the reason I'm calling
is that I'm worried about Theodore.
He's been acting a little down lately.
Um, I hope you're going
to the sing-off Friday.
You know, with his dad gone,
Theodore needs all the support
he can get.
So, um, I'll see you there.
I hope we get a chance to talk.
Bye.
♪ I try to walk away and I stumble ♪
(machine beeps)
♪ Though I try to hide it... ♪
CROWD: Let's go, Eagles!
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Okay, folks,
time to get behind
your undefeated Warriors.
The visiting Eagles are down by five
with about 30 seconds left in the game.
Time is running out for the Eagles.
-Go, Eagles!
-COMMENTATOR: Quarterback Ryan Edwards
really needs to make a move
here or this game is over.
I know they're going to put me in.
They've got to put me in.
(shouting, groaning)
-(whistle blowing)
-Time out. Time out.
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Time out, Eagles.
Fourth and 15 with nine seconds
remaining in the game.
(marching band plays)
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Substitution, Eagles.
All right, boys.
It's time for the Big "A."
I'm going to crush them!
I'm bringing the pain.
The Alvinator is in the house.
You sure about this?
Fourth and ten, Sam.
We need to go with the secret weapon.
Tribbs, right.
Alvin, left. Motion on me.
Time to make history, boys.
-Ready?
-ALL: Break!
(crowd cheering)
This ain't no dance, baby!
I'm taking you down, Jennifer.
You're the one going down, rat-face.
I'm going to crack you like an acorn
and eat you for dinner
with some fava beans and a nice Chianti.
(slurping)
Is he talking about my father?
Okay! Let's go!
Hut!
(grunting)
Incoming!
(people gasping)
-(cheering)
-(whistle blows)
(cheering)
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Touchdown, Eagles.
Oh, yeah!
Come on. That's what
I'm talking about.
Don't hate the player.
Hate the game.
And I love how awesome I am.
Ah, ah, ah.
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Final score. Eagles 15, Warriors 14.
Oh, what do you think
about that, suckers?
Oh, yeah.
In your faces.
That's what
I'm talking about.
You're like the Randy Moss of chipmunks.
-Whoo!
-Yeah!
Give me an A. Give me an L.
Give me a V.
Give me an I.
Give me an N.
What does that spell?
Awesome!
I'm the king of the world!
Running with the MVP!
ALVIN:
Oh, yeah!
Party with Alvin!
ALVIN:
You got that right.
Everybody to the beach house!
ALVIN:
Let's do it!
CROWD (chanting):
Alvin! Alvin! Alvin! Alvin!
Chipmunks!
Chipettes! Chipettes!
Chipettes!
So, look, guys, I just want you to know
that I'm... I'm here for you.
TOBY: There's plenty of time.
I'm gonna go find Alvin.
Everything's gonna work out.
CROWD (chanting):
Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
Thanks, Toby.
EMCEE: Ladies and gentlemen,
Dr. Rubin.
(applause, cheering, and whistling)
DR. RUBIN: Thank you, students.
Thank you.
Welcome to our exciting
sing-off competition
between the Chipmunks
and the Chipettes.
(cheering and applauding)
(applause stops)
Remember, students,
there are no winners or losers...
Yeah, remind me to tell the Chipmunks
that when we blow them off the stage.
The group that we choose today will give
our school a chance to win $25,000
to save our music department.
So without further ado,
I give you the Chipettes.
(cheering and applauding)
This is it, girls.
Can you believe it?
Brittany, your time to shine, baby.
Go out there and knock 'em dead.
Yes, sir. I can do it.
You two, I just want to let you know
not to get in Brittany's way.
Oh.
Ah. Oh, okay.
(upbeat intro plays to "Single Ladies")
(cheering and applauding)
♪ All the single ladies ♪
♪ All the single ladies,
now put your hands up ♪
♪ Up in the club,
just broke up ♪
♪ I'm doing
my own little thing ♪
♪ You decided to dip
and now you wanna trip ♪
♪ 'Cause another brother
noticed me ♪
♪ If you liked it, then you
should've put a ring on it ♪
♪ If you liked it,
then you should've put a ring on it ♪
♪ Don't be mad once
you see that he want it ♪
♪ If you liked it, then you
should've put a ring on it ♪
♪ Uh oh oh ♪
♪ Uh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Uh oh oh oh,
uh oh oh ♪
Like what you see?
Call Ian Hawke.
310-555-5309.
♪ If you liked it, then you
should've put a ring on it ♪
Don't worry, Simon.
Alvin will walk through
that door any minute now.
-(door opens)
-Alvin!
(laughing)
I am back.
♪ Whoa-oh-oh-oh,
ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, ah ah ♪
(cheering and applauding)
Girls, that's for us.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
DR. RUBIN:
Well done, ladies.
And now...
let's hear it for a group
that will rock you like a hurricane.
At least, that's what many
of you students have told me.
Here they are.
The Chipmunks.
(cheering and applauding)
Hey, you know, they say there's no "I"
in the word "team,"and...
and they're right.
But you know what there is an "I" in?
"Alvin."
(laughs)
Sucks to be you.
Girls!
Sadly, he's correct.
(door opens)
Did you find him?
Guys. Sorry, I...
I... I searched the whole perimeter.
And I don't know why,
but the team's not back yet.
Well, what should we do?
I would, um...
CROWD (chanting):
Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
I would ask someone who's not me.
(sighs)
I know what we should do.
CROWD: Chipmunks!
Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
(cheering and applauding)
Hi, everyone.
(clears throat)
Uh...
Our brother, Alvin couldn't...
couldn't be here today.
Um, the thing is, we've...
we've never performed without Alvin,
and... we're not starting now.
(audience clamoring)
You can't have only two little pigs.
You can't have only two musketeers, so...
So, you know you can't
have only two chipmunks.
Thank you.
(murmuring)
-(crowd booing)
-BOY: Why don't you go back to the tree?
I'll take you home.
(crowd booing and clamoring)
HAWKE: Hear that, girls?
That... is the sound of success.
(crowd groaning, booing,
and clamoring)
DR. RUBIN: I realize how devastated
you... Chipmunk fans must be.
So I guess that means
that the Chipettes...
Come on, girls.
Let's take a victory lap.
(cheering and applauding)
Hey, come on, guys.
HAWKE: Let's go.
Brit, we have to.
Let's go.
DR. RUBIN:
...Chipettes.
(cheering and applauding)
Thank you. Thanks.
(door opening)
Ah. Life is good.
Especially when
you're not a loser.
(door opening)
Hey, guys, I'm here.
Guys?
Oh, great.
They're gone, Alvin.
They're never gonna forgive me.
You know, Alvin, Ian was right.
You don't care
about anyone but yourself.
Oh, and by the way,
I never wanted to win this way.
(sighs)
(crickets chirping)
Simon?
Theodore?
Simon, are you awake?
Theo?
ALVIN (whispers):
(sighs)
Theodore?
Theodore,
I don't blame you for being mad.
Uh-oh.
"I ran away from home.
"Don't look for me at the zoo
'cause I'm not there."
Oh, no. Theodore.
(elephant trumpeting)
Hello?
Meerkat family?
(grunts)
Oh, brother.
Is anyone home?
My name is Theodore.
I'd like to be in your family.
Maybe they're hiding.
Don't be afraid.
(bird screeching loudly)
(gasps)
(squawks)
(whimpering)
You... are not a meerkat.
Toby, you take the lions,
the tigers, and the bears.
Simon and I will take the butterfly room.
Nice eagle.
(eagle screeches)
SIMON: Theo!
Don't move, Theodore.
No problem there.
Hang in there. Hang in there, little guy!
We're gonna get you out of there!
Okay, okay, we need a plan.
We need a carefully executed plan.
Or you could just, uh,
run in there like a maniac.
(screeching)
Theo, watch out!
Hi. I'm Theodore.
(eagle squawks)
(groans)
Hey, birdie, over here.
Are you hungry?
'Cause this "A" stands for "appetizer."
(squawking)
Oh, oh, um...
Let's all just relax,
and we'll talk this out, okay?
Look, um...
I get why you want Theodore.
I do.
But, I'm sorry.
I can't let that happen.
He's my brother,
not that he'd know that...
Because I've been such a big jerk lately.
If anyone deserves to be eaten, it's me.
-(squawking)
-Whoa. Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not literally.
I've got you, Alvin.
(squawking)
(screaming)
(panting)
Oh, Theo.
Help!
-(squawking)
-SIMON: Guys, it's a wedge-tailed eagle.
Their only mortal enemy
is the pygmy elephant.
Luckily, I speak a little pachyderm.
(squawking and trumpeting)
(trilling)
I think it's working!
-(squawking)
Hold on!
(yelling and groaning)
(whimpering and panting)
(sighs)
Guys, that was huge.
He's right.
So, are we back
to one for all and three for one?
Come on, Simon.
Hug it out.
You know I'm sorry, Si.
Si?
Don't make me have to kiss you.
Because I'll do it.
I don't care.
Here come my lips.
Make-out train is leaving the station.
(toots)
(laughs)
Think I'll, uh...
I'll take that hug.
Ah. Guys.
♪ If you liked it, then you
should've put a ring on it ♪
Interested? Call Ian Hawke.
310-555-5309.
Dolores, get me that Ian Hawke
on the phone.
(humming)
-There you are.
-Hi, Ian.
-My sweet little moneymakers.
-(giggling)
Do you remember when I told you
that I would make you all big stars?
-Yeah.
-Well...
Guess who's opening up for Britney Spears
at the Staples Center tonight?
(squealing, giggling)
Pinch me. Am I dreaming?
Oh, my gosh.
Wait. Tonight?
We'll miss the school contest.
That is correct.
You will miss the school contest.
HAWKE: You're so smart.
I can never get anything passed you.
It was never about
that stupid school contest.
It was always about making
Brittany... a star.
Oh.
That's what you wanted, right?
(gasps)
Well, yeah.
Well, tonight's your big chance.
It's all about you, Brittany.
What about Jeanette and Eleanor?
Yeah, well, they can sing backup.
I got them some stuff too.
Hey!
But, we're her sisters.
And the three of us sing together
or not at all.
-Okay, fine.
-Yes.
All I really need is the "B" Girl.
Ian, I won't do it without them.
Okay, fine, fine.
Let's, uh, move on to Plan B.
Um, okay.
Who likes barbecue?
-Uh...
-Barbecue?
Because I know this awesome little
barbecue restaurant in the Valley
that makes the best roasted chipmunk.
(sniffs, sighs)
Real tasty.
Unless, of course, you want to sing.
Oh.
(sighs)
(chattering)
EMCEE: Welcome to West Eastman
and thank you for supporting
music in our schools.
Now, remember, the group you pick tonight
will win $25,000 for their school!
(cheering)
Now, we've got a lot of acts,
and we have to turn the heat off at 9:30,
so without any further ado,
representing Orange Grove,
put your hands together for Li'l Rosero!
(cheering)
(hip-hop music playing)
("All Night Dance Crew" begins)
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Feels good, right ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ It's so classic ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ Let's go in the middle
of the floor ♪
♪ You can watch me
do what I do... ♪
(crowd cheering)
So, we meet again.
What? You want a piece of this, Eagle?
(chuckles)
(phone ringing)
Ian Hawke?
I'll take that.
Oh, I didn't realize
I pocket-dialed 1-800-LOWLIFE.
-BRITTANY: Alvin?
-Brittany?
Yeah, um, could you guys fill in for us?
We're not going to be able
to perform tonight.
What about the music department?
The whole school is counting on you.
I know. I know.
I should have listened to you about Ian.
Don't tell me...
Yep.
He locked us in a cage.
HAWKE:
What? This is the biggest you have?
I had my assistant call
and ask for the biggest limo.
This is not the biggest limo you have.
I'll, uh... I'll go break
the news to Dr. Rubin.
-Brittany?
-Alvin, don't move.
You got it.
Brittany,
I'm coming to get you.
Simon, tell Jeanette how to pick the lock.
Roger that.
Oh, man. I need to get to the girls. Fast.
Oh! I know how.
(engine roaring, tires screeching)
(screaming)
BOY BAND (singing):
♪ All night, all night ♪
(cheering and applauding)
Jeanette, focus.
The third number is notoriously
the hardest to crack.
I'm assuming it's a prime number,
but we can't assume--
Simon! The first two numbers were ones.
I got to go with one.
(gasps)
It opened!
HAWKE:
All right, girls.
Ian's coming. Put the phone back.
Hurry!
Get ready to be fabulous.
Oh, we're ready.
Yeah, you better be,
'cause tonight's performance
is going to put me back on top.
(tires screeching)
(gasps)
(engine revving)
EMCEE: Next up,
please welcome Charice.
(cheering)
("No One" begins)
♪ I just want you close ♪
♪ Where you can stay forever ♪
Driver man, take me to the arena,
VIP entrance.
(speaking French) Tout de suite.
How about a little moon-roof action?
Moon-roofs are go!
Roofs? Moon-roofs?
Roofs? Roofs?
Ooh, champagne.
(chuckles)
Don't mind if I do.
HAWKE:
You know why I don't mind if I do?
Because tonight, we've gotta toast to
a very special someone
named me.
(chuckles)
They said I couldn't do it.
They said I'd never bounce back.
Guess what? Time to kiss my sweet... Ooh.
(champagne pops)
HAWKE: Ah, yeah.
(champagne pouring)
A toast... to the ladies who are going to
make the world forget about the Chipmun...
-Wha...
-See ya!
No! No, no, no! No!
-What are you doing?
-(motorcycle revs)
Alvin!
Hi, Ian.
Good to see you.
You never write.
(exclaims)
-No. Brittany...
-ALVIN: Come on, girls!
No.
I signed a contract.
Jump, Jeanette.
Uh...
-HAWKE: Wait.
-I'm not really good at...(screaming)
-I got you!
-HAWKE: I'm dead if you don't perform.
-Punch it, Alvin! You got it.
-No! Don't!
Hey, Ian! In the words
of The Donald, "You're fired."
Alvin!
♪ No one, no one, no one ♪
♪ Can get in the way
of what I'm feeling ♪
Hey. Hey.
Hey, guys. Any sign of Alvin yet? Huh?
No. No Alvin and no Chipettes.
Just, just Dr. Rubin and, you know,
the entire school counting on us.
Well, um...
Yeah, you know, you know,
uh, don't, don't worry.
Everything will work out ...ish.
CHARICE (singing):
♪ Get in the way of what I feel ♪
♪ I know some people
search the world ♪
-Faster, Alvin!
-ALVIN: Don't worry.
I'm going to get a little
help from my friend, Digger. Whoo!
-Roger that, Alvin!
-HAWKE: Look out!
Whoa! Feels like I'm
back at the racetrack.
-(tires screeching)
-MAN: Hey! Careful!
Keep going!
What are you doing?
Wait till I tell
everybody back home I saved Alvin Seville.
I guess I owe you an apology about Ian.
Stick with me, Britts.
I'll never steer you wrong.
(tires screeching, Brittany screams)
BRITTANY:
Oh, yeah, I'll never doubt you again.
(propellers whirring)
(laughing)
I've got to say he
is definitely persistent.
We have got to lose him.
Hang on!
(screaming)
I've got a plan.
Jump on the count of three.
-Three!
-Whoa!
Oh, that's it.
JEANETTE: I'm not
really good with heights.
Just hold on tight, Jeanette.
Bring my girls right to me.
We need the remote.
Guys, I know what to do.
It's hats off to Ian.
Whoa!
The remote!
I can't reach it.
I'm going for it.
Grab my ankles.
(screaming)
I got it!
(sighs)
I got it.
Way to go, Jen!
Nice work, Jeanette.
Good going, Jen!
Hey, Ian!
You were wrong!
I don't need these.
Oops.
(groans)
Ooh.
Ouch.
My bad.
Adios, Ian.
And now for our final act of the night.
Now, listen, we've had
a last second change to the lineup,
but we don't think you're
gonna be too disappointed.
Representing West Eastman,
it's The Chipmunks!
(cheering and applauding)
We may have
to go out there, Theodore.
CROWD (chanting): Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
Chipmunks! Chipmunks!
Well, if there are no Chipmunks,
we're going to have to move on.
-(crowd booing)
-EMCEE: So now...
I don't want to be booed again.
EMCEE: I'm sorry.
We're going to have to move on.
Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi! I, uh, um...
(Toby chuckles nervously)
I'm not a...
I'm not a chipmunk as you can see.
(Toby chuckles nervously)
BOY:
Play some music, you loser.
BOY TWO:
Where's the music?
(crowd grumbling and clamoring)
-MAN: Play some music.
-TOBY: Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay. I got, I got, I got a...
I got a song. I got a song. I got a song.
Um...
TOBY (singing off-key):
♪ Ever since I met you ♪
♪ I wanted to be your guy ♪
♪ But as you
probably noticed, um ♪
♪ I'm pathologically shy and ♪
♪ Standing on this stage
right now ♪
♪ I think I'd rather die ♪
♪ So I'm just gonna
start by saying ♪
♪ Hi ♪
Hi.
Now, that was huge.
(crowd cheering)
TOBY: Thank you. Thank you. No, really.
(helicopter blades whirring)
Thank you. What's that?
The Chipettes are in the building.
It's the Chipettes!
Alvin!
Yo, Theo!
Hello, West Eastman!
(cheering)
I'm putting her down!
Hang on!
Alvin!
Double high-five,brother!
-(cheering)
-High-five!
Oh.
Whoops.
Ladies and gentlemen, representing
West Eastman, it is my great pleasure...
This is such an honor.
(laughing)
For you or for us?
TOGETHER: For us.
TOGETHER: Jinx.
TOGETHER:
Double jinx. Triple jinx.
Quadruple jinx. Infinity jinx.
Guys! We get it.
Huddle up, gang.
Here's the plan...
(whispering)
...I give you
the Chipettes and the Chipmunks!
♪ We are family ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ Everyone can see
we're together ♪
♪ As we walk on by,
yeah ♪
♪ And we fly just like
birds of a feather ♪
♪ I won't tell no lie, ♪
oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Just let me state
for the record ♪
♪ We're giving love ♪
in a family dose ♪
♪ We are family ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ I got all my sisters
with me ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ We are family ♪
♪ Get up everybody and sing ♪
♪ Sing it to me, baby ♪
♪ We are family ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ Get up everybody and sing ♪
♪ Sing it to me ♪
TOGETHER: Dave!
♪ Here's what we call
our golden rule ♪
♪ Our golden rule,
♪ All I want,
all that I need ♪
♪ Is to rock with my family ♪
♪ All I want,
all that I need ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ We are family ♪
♪ Baby, we are family ♪
♪ I got all my brothers
with me ♪
♪ Got my brothers with me,
baby, yeah ♪
♪ We are family ♪
(vocalizing)
(cheering and applauding)
-Thank you.
-Whoo!
ALVIN:
Thank you so much.
EMCEE: Hey, everybody.
Thank you!
It's clear that
we have a winner of the $25,000.
And it's West Eastman High!
-West Eastman High!
-(cheering)
-Guys, we did it!
-Wow.
-Yes!
-(squeals)
ALVIN: A little something
for the music department.
(cheering and applauding)
All right!
Right back at you, Dr. Rubes!
(laughing and squealing)
Oh, yeah!
CROWD (chanting):
Chipettes! Chipettes!
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
the Staples Center is proud to welcome...
The Chipettes!
(cheering and applauding)
(falsetto)
Hello, everyone. I'm Jeanette.
And I'm Eleanor.
-And I'm Brittany.
-(cheering stops)
And we're The Chipettes.
-What?
-(crowd murmurs)
One, two, three.
(singing in falsetto): ♪ All the single
ladies, all the single ladies ♪
♪ All the single ladies,
all the single ladies ♪
GIRL: That's not the Chipettes!
♪ Single, single ladies,
single-dingle-dingle ♪
♪ If you want to get married,
have a ring ♪
-(crowd booing)
-♪ Put your rings on it ♪
♪ If you want to get married,
put your... ♪
I know. I know.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I know. Sorry.
-(booing continues)
HAWKE: I'm going.
♪ Shake your groove thing,
shake your groove thing ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Show them how you do it now ♪
♪ Shake your groove thing,
shake your groove thing ♪
Dave! You're dancing!
Ah, you're
moving good, Dave. Yeah!
Welcome home.
So, did you miss us?
-Of course, I missed you. You're my boys.
-(guffaws)
And Dave, just think how much
you'd miss us if there were six of us.
Alvin, what did you say?
Well, the Chipettes needed
a place to crash, right?
So I said that you said they could stay
with us for as long as they needed to.
-Alvin.
-Okay! This one's for Dave.
Everybody shake what your mama gave ya.
♪ Shake your groove thing ♪
♪ Shake your groove thing,
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Show them how you do it now ♪
♪ Get up and shake it ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
(cheering and applauding)
DAVE:
Look at you.
All ready for bed.
DAVE: Looks like the Chipettes
are a good influence.
Thanks, Dave.
(chuckles).
Okay, guys, now, lights out.
-Good night, everybody.
-Good night, Jeanette.
-Good night, Simon.
-Good night.
-Good night, Alvin.
-Alvin?
-I'm not tired.
Sorry, but you've got school tomorrow.
Not tired.
Alvin, come on. It's time for bed.
Alvin.
Still not tired.
More awake. Tired. Just kidding.
Much more awake.
Alvin, that's it.
Don't make me come over there!
-Okay!
-Whoa!
(crashing)
Ooh, boy. I suddenly got really,
really tired. (chuckles nervously)
Night, Dave.
DAVE: Alvin!
♪ You spin me right round,
baby ♪
♪ Right round like a record,
♪ Right round round round ♪
♪ You spin me right round,
baby ♪
♪ Right round like a record,
♪ Right round round round ♪
♪ Oh and I,
I got to know your name ♪
♪ Know your name ♪
♪ Well and I, could trace
your private number, baby ♪
♪ All I know is that to me ♪
♪ You look like
you're lots of fun ♪
♪ Open up your loving arms ♪
♪ I want some, want some ♪
♪ You spin me right round,
baby ♪
♪ Right round like a record,
♪ Right round round round ♪
♪ You spin me right round,
baby ♪
♪ Right round like a record,
♪ Right round round round ♪
♪ I want your love ♪
♪ You spin me right round,
baby ♪
♪ Right round like a record,
♪ Right round round round ♪
♪ I want your love ♪
♪ You spin me right round,
baby ♪
♪ Right round like a record,
♪ Right round round round ♪
Good start, gentlemen.
Only ten more rows of bleachers to go.
Let's do it.
(groans)
("The Song" playing)
♪ 'Cause when I rock,
no one rocks harder than me ♪
♪ And I don't stop
'cause I got that energy ♪
♪ I got the bass and the drums,
they're moving me along ♪
♪ Yeah, ah, inside my brain
there's a song ♪
♪ You think I'm crazy, baby ♪
♪ Inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ I might just maybe, baby ♪
♪ Inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ There's a song,
♪ There's a song, there's
a song, there's a song ♪
♪ You may call me crazy
and maybe you might be right ♪
♪ The music inside me keeps
going all through the night ♪
♪ I'm Schitzo, Sublitzo, what
makes up with something bad ♪
♪ But baby, just maybe it's
better than what you have ♪
♪ 'Cause when I rock,
no one rocks harder than me ♪
♪ And I don't stop
'cause I got that energy ♪
♪ I got the bass and the drums,
they're moving me along ♪
♪ Yeah, ah, inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ You think I'm crazy, baby? ♪
♪ Inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ I might just maybe, baby ♪
♪ Inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ You think I'm out my mind ♪
♪ Inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ 'Cause my foot's
keeping time ♪
♪ Inside my brain,
there's a song ♪
♪ There's a song,
♪ There's a song, there's
a song, there's a song ♪
♪ There's a song,
song, song, song, song ♪
♪ Inside my brain
there's a song ♪
MAN: And it goes
a little something like this.
("Bring It On" playing)
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ It's time
to make it happen ♪
to make it lasting ♪
♪ A whole new chain reaction ♪
♪ Starting here with you ♪
♪ A new day
for a new beginning ♪
♪ Feels like the world
is spinning ♪
♪ And there's no choice
for winning ♪
♪ It's what we got to do ♪
♪ Well, all we know
just what it takes to be ♪
♪ Together we are everything ♪
♪ Everything we need ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on,
come on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
get up and move yourself ♪
♪ Go on, go on, go on,
go on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
it's time to bring it on ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ It's time to
make it happen now ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on,
and do it now ♪
♪ It's time to
make it lasting now ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ All the ladies say ♪
♪ Well, maybe,
it's been getting crazy ♪
♪ But I know we're ready
to take on anything ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on,
come on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
get up and move yourself ♪
♪ Go on, go on, go on,
go on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
it's time to bring it on ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on,
come on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
get up and move yourself ♪
♪ Go on, go on, go on,
go on and do it now ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up,
it's time to bring it on ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Yeah... ♪
♪ Oh, it's time
to bring it on ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ Oh, it's time
to bring it on ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Yeah, it's time
to bring it on ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Oh, it's time to
bring it on ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
Okay. All right, guys.
All right. All right.
All right, I'm out.
I'm out.
Oh, is this necessary?
Now, come on! Oh, is that necessary?
Is that...
HAWKE (muffled): At least, let me go back
and get my purse.
-(door closes)
-(chipmunks chuckling)