This is the Earth at a time
when the dinosaurs roamed...
a lush and fertile planet.
A piece of rock just six miles wide
changed all that.
It hit with the force
of 10,000 nuclear weapons.
A trillion tons of dirt and rock
hurtled into the atmosphere...
creating a suffocating
blanket of dust...
the sun was powerless
to penetrate...
for a thousand years.
It happened before.
It will happen again.
It's just a question of when.
Engineering director... Engineering...
- Say again, Rudy.
- Houston, affirmative.
I'm gonna try again.
This time why don't we put in a hold
at nine. Cancel the pending resume.
Almost got it.
- Dennis, I'm almost there.
- Houston, Pete's looking real strong.
Okay, Pete. We got that coupling
on the board here now.
We'll give you the go-ahead
from down here when it's in alignment.
Sounds good.
Give me ten seconds.
His heart rate's racing.
- Hey, Pete. It's Truman.
- Hey.
- How you doing up there, Hoss?
- Pretty good.
Now, listen, Pete.
We got an eye on your meds here.
I'll give you a buffalo nickel
if you'll calm down just a little bit.
- Can you do that for me?
- Whatever you say.
Okay, uh, now we got plenty of time,
buddy, so don't you worry.
- Atlantis...
- Okay. Looking good here.
- He's got it.
- He'll be all right.
- Go ahead, Atlantis.
Roger that, Houston.
Suggest we start reeling Pete in.
- The system's down.
- No.
- What the hell is that?
- My Lord.
We're down.
Houston!
- We've lost all contact.
- What happened?
Stewart, play that tape back!
Houston!
Multiple bogeys! Multiple bogeys!
Sector five, niner. I have three.
Now five. Unidentified tracts.
- My screen's full.
- Multiple tracts headed towards
the Atlantic seaboard.
This could be
a surprise missile attack.
Mr President, the shuttle Atlantis
just exploded in space.
Okay, I want three groups!
One: Internal malfunction.
Get the log tape. Start working back.
Maybe it's a glitch.
Two: I want NORAD Space Command
and the 50th Tactical comparing all
the space junk you track in every orbit.
I want you to check, recheck
and then do it all over again.
Number three: Wild cards,
anything and everything.
All right? Now, big Ross,
I want you to get on the telephone.
- Wake up 11,000 people.
- Right.
- Walt, get 'em going.
- Let's go!
- Karl!
Karl! Karl!
Karl! Your Stouffer's pot pie's
been on the table almost ten hours.
- I want a divorce.
- Dottie, I'm on to something big here.
L-I don't know what this is, but it
looks like something's burning up there.
Go get my phone book, will you?
Get my phone book. Get those names
of those guys from NASA.
Excuse me! Am I wearing a sign
that says, "Karl's slave"?
Go get my goddam phone book!
Get the book!
Space Command is reporting negative.
That is zero global launches.
- It might just be pieces of
the shuttle breaking up as it comes in.
- Yeah, it might be Santa Claus.
Until we get definitive, reliable
alternative confirmation, General...
we go to defcon three.
I'm getting ready for the big time
Someday you're gonna say
I'm big time too
Hey, little man! Little Richard!
Me and you, man!
We going to the top, baby! Big time!
Yo, man, I ain't gonna be ridin'
this bike the rest of my life!
You know what I'm sayin'?
I'm gettin' a motorcycle, baby.
We gonna travel in style.
I'm getting ready for the big time
Someday you're gonna say
I'm big time
Watch where you're goin'. I bet you,
none of y'all stop for brothers.
Slow down, Little Richard.
You've been ridin' all morning, man.
You gotta take a dump?
- We interrupt our regularly
scheduled programme to bring you
this special report.
- Hey, man, what happened?
The shuttle Atlantis exploded in space
at 3:47 a.m., Eastern Standard Time.
This morning
NASA officials are denying...
Hey! Hey, get! Get!
- That's my Godzilla. Come on, now.
- Yo, fool!
- Don't be kickin' Little Richard.
What the hell your problem?
- Now that dog's eating my Godzilla, man.
- And what's a little runt like you
gonna do about it?
- Get him, Richard. Sic him.
If I wasn't a Christian,
I'd be throwin' your fat,
pineapple-eatin' ass through the window.
- Why we not going, huh?
- Well, y-y-you know why?
'Cause this is New York City.
Anything could have happened.
Look at that. Uh, let's see.
It could have been a terrorist bomb.
It could have been
a dead body somebody shot, stabbed.
And it's Friday. Payday too.
- Somebody probably jumped,
didn't get their pay cheque. Yes.
- I want to go shopping.
Me too, but we ain't goin' nowhere
'cause this is a traffic jam.
- Little Richard.
- Hurry! Right over there!
- Go!
Yo, Little Richard!
Hang on, Little Richard!
I'm comin'!
Don't you worry about it.
I'm gonna get you outta there!
You okay, buddy?
Don't worry about it. Hang in there.
Somebody dial 911!
My screen's full!
They're all over the place!
Bogeys are breachin'
the atmosphere from Finland down
the North American seaboard.
Whoa!
Look at that!
Oh, we at war!
Saddam Hussein is bombin' us!
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
Get out of here!
Oh, my God!
Let's stay focused.
We need to map the trajectory now.
- That could take a week.
- Just find it, okay?
- I want to know if the worst is over
or if it's on its way.
- We've got General Kimsey on the line.
We've got hits from Finland to South
Carolina. We know they're not missiles.
Now what the hell is it?
It's a meteor shower.
That's what took out the shuttle.
- He's waiting for you.
- What's the death toll?
I've got the President
on Air Force One demanding answers.
Is it over?
General, we've got 11,000 people
at NASA trying to figure that out
right now. When we know, you'll know.
Okay, Karl, listen.
I want you to take your time.
Yes, sir. You are definitely the first.
Okay, first coordinate.
One-two-three-nine. 1239, right?
- FBI locked his location.
- Saw an explosion in space.
- Okay.
- The last one...
- Now, listen, Karl, this is top secret.
- Sir, I'm retired Navy.
I know all about classified.
But one more thing. The person
that finds her gets to name her, right?
- Yes, that's right. That's right.
- I want to name her Dottie,
after my wife.
- She's a vicious, life-suckin' bitch
from which there's no escape.
- That's... That's sweet, Karl.
S.D.I., this is Flight Director.
I want to get that Hubble movin',
and I want it now.
Roger that.
We're movin' the Hubble!
- It's enormous.
- This is the anomaly at 1643.
Here is the anomaly at 1658.
And here is the anomaly at 1700.
Enough with this
"anomaly" horseshit!
- What is this thing?
- It's an asteroid, sir.
How big are we talking?
Sir, our best estimate
is 97.6 billion...
- It's the size of Texas, Mr President.
- Y-Y-Yes, sir.
Dan, we didn't
see this thing coming?
Well, our object collision
budget's a million dollars.
That allows us to track
about three percent of the sky.
- And begging your pardon, sir,
but it's a big-ass sky.
- And the ones this morning?
Uh, those are nothing.
Uh, they're the size of basketballs...
and, uh, Volkswagens,
things like that.
Is this going to hit us?
- We're efforting that as we speak, sir.
- What kind of damage are we...
Damage?
Total, sir.
It's what we call a global killer.
The end of mankind.
Doesn't matter where it hits.
Nothing would survive,
not even bacteria.
My God. What do we do?
We have 18 days
before it hits Earth.
- Have mercy.
- Rise and shine!
Stop the drilling!
Stop the drilling! Stop the drilling!
- Fore!
- Stop the drilling!
Stop the drilling!
- Hey!
- Hey, that was close!
I gave you 50,000 a year in donations!
What do you think they're
so mad about, Chick?
Well, I think they feel that
drilling for oil is an evil thing.
Do you know how much diesel
that clunker boat pumps out in an hour?
You know, I just found out
something interesting.
- Number two chewed 180 feet last night.
- Who do we have to thank for this?
Well, I'll give you two guesses,
but you're only gonna need one.
Goddam it, A. J!
A. J!
A.J., you in here?
Oh, that's just perfect.
In bed. Get up!
- Uh, hey, you wanted to see me?
- Yeah, I was lookin' for ya.
You're pissed.
Okay, I can see that.
No. You know what, A. J?
I'm not pissed. You've seen me pissed.
This is way, way beyond pissed, though.
- You know I shut down number two
last night, right?
- Yeah, man, I had a hunch on that.
Dude, let me tell you somethin'.
Someday, many years from now,
when you're all growed up...
and you got your own
oil company and $8 million
of your own money on the contract...
you can do whatever comes
into that little A.J. -idiotin' mind
of yours you want...
but as long as it says
"Harry Stamper Oil" on the rig
you will not disobey my rules.
- You got that?
- Yeah, I do got it.
- Right now, I need to hear
five words from you.
- Uh...
- I'll never do that again.
- Never do that again.
I'm a fool. That was idiotic.
L-I mean, that was stupid.
I'm an idiot. I know what name's
on the sign. I'm not... I can't...
- What's going on here?
- What's going on? Well, l-I mean, l...
- I screwed up. I'm a little edgy.
- How long you worked for me?
- Five wonderful years.
In five years, you have never
apologized to me this quickly.
- Something's going on here.
I'm gonna find out what it is.
- No, no, no. Well...
l-I'm turning over a new leaf.
I'm trying to learn from the man.
What would Harry do?
I'm at a loss for words.
- Okay, I can explain this.
- You can explain that?
- I can.
- I would really like an explanation.
You just stay right here.
- Grace?
- Hi, Harry.
I have asked you repeatedly
to call me Dad.
- Sorry, Harry.
- Get up and get your clothes on.
You just stay right there.
I'll be right back.
Here's what we're gonna do.
I want every strategy we've got
on near-Earth object collision, okay?
Any ideas, any programs,
anything you sketched
on a pizza box or a cocktail napkin.
For 30 years, they questioned
the need for NASA. Today
we're gonna give them the answer.
You know about this, Rockhound?
You knew.
No, l-I had no idea.
Where's Harry?
Harry! All right! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I understand, okay?
You're mad.
Who-Who wouldn't be mad?
- But he's gonna shoot you.
- Nah. No, he's not. Oh, shit.
- Harry!
- What's wrong with you?
Make your peace with God, A.J.
- This guy's got a gun, man!
He's shooting at me!
- Harry, this is not funny!
- Harry, listen to me!
We can talk this over!
- So is this a, uh, serious thing?
- Yeah, pretty serious.
- Bear, man!
- What's up?
He's shooting at me. Uh, you see Harry
comin', crack him with that wrench!
You told A.J.'s dad just before he died
that you would take care of the boy.
Now, I'm not sure that shootin' him
is takin' care of him.
- Why don't you put the gun down, boss?
- You don't want none of this, Bear.
Get out of my way.
Just trying to give my man
a head start, that's all.
Not to mention the fact that I
don't think you wanna kill the best man
on your crew before we strike oil.
Ah, Chick, I ain't gonna kill him.
Just gonna take a foot off.
A man can work with one foot.
You remember old Frank Marx who
worked with one hand all them years?
- Yeah, but he wasn't very good.
- Harry, put the gun down!
You're acting insane!
Now honey, go get some clothes on
and get out of the way.
- You can't control my life.
- Fine. Clothes. Now!
All right, stop, all right? It was funny
for a minute, it's not funny any more.
- Harry, this is illegal, man.
- I'm temporarily insane, Rock.
It's all right.
- Do I look like I'm crazy to you?
- Well...
Harry, hey, just cool down.
- What are you... Okay, stop.
- All right. All right, Harry.
All right. Now, listen, man to man.
I'm serious. I love her.
Way wrong answer.
- Whoa, whoa, Harry. It's gettin' real.
- Harry! Come on, Harry!
- Stop him!
- You shot him!
Bullet never got close.
Just a ricochet.
You know, it's all funny
till somebody gets shot in the leg.
Hey, pucker up!
We got clients incoming!
Uh, b-back in, uh, 1974...
w-we first got the-the idea,
the possibility that a, that a meteor
or an asteroid...
I need somebody who's had a little less
caffeine this morning. Doc, translate.
Our first feasibility plan was to use
a spread-focus laser generator...
to heat the object
to the point of fracture.
That's like shooting a B.B. Gun
at a freight train, Doc.
Uh, some of us have got this idea.
We want to land a craft,
deploy solar sails.
You'll have a great big canopy.
Solar winds will be caught...
by these mylar sails.
- Okay.
- Come on, guys.
We gotta come up with something
realistic here. We got 18 days.
That's 431 hours,
15 minutes and 18 seconds.
Time's a luxury we don't have.
What?
Listen, Harry. A.J. Is my choice...
my choice and not yours.
He's the only one in your age bracket,
Grace. It's not a choice,
it's a lack of options.
I don't know what in the world makes
you think that you have the right
to tell me what to do any more, Harry.
I suppose being your father
doesn't count, huh?
- Not really.
- Since when?
Since I reached the age of 10
and became older than you, Harry.
Since Mom split.
Why don't you take your pick?
Look, I understand that you are
handicapped by a natural immaturity
and I forgive you.
I may be an immature father, okay?
But I'm still your employer.
And as your boss I want you
on that crew boat tonight
and back in the office by Monday.
- You got that?
- Okay. I quit.
Grace, you can't quit now.
I need you to keep on workin'.
- Hi, Harry!
- What are you smilin' about?
I've been seein' A.J.
For more than five months, Harry.
You little hypocrite. I ever held you
back once from doin' anything?
What about having a life, Harry?
The first time I got my period...
Rockhound had to take me
into Taipei for Tampax...
and then he had to show me
how to use 'em, Harry.
I ju... No, l-I told her how to use it.
I didn't show her, Harry.
I was playing
with titanium depth gauges when
I should've been playing with dolls.
I mean, I learned about the birds and
the bees from Freddie Noonan's tattoos.
Look, I was raised
on roughnecks by you...
and now you get all shocked and shaken
when I fall in love with one.
- So who is the hypocrite here,
Harry, huh? Who?
- Look at those nice pipes up there.
- Listen to me, Grace. I want you...
- No, you listen to me, Harry.
I grew up.
With the proximity of the asteroid...
and no prep time,
none of our primary plans can work.
Why don't we just send up 150 nuclear
warheads and blast that rock apart?
- Terrible idea.
- Was I talkin' to you?
This is Dr Ronald Quincy from research,
pretty much the smartest man on the
planet. You might want to listen to him.
General, if you consider your target...
her composition, her dimensions...
her sheer velocity, you could fire
every nuke you've got at her...
and she'll just smile at you
and keep on coming.
You should know that the president's
scientific advisors...
are suggesting that a nuclear blast
could change this asteroid's trajectory.
I know the president's chief scientific
advisor. We were at M.I.T. Together.
And in a situation like this, you...
you really don't want...
to take the advice of a man
who got a C-minus in astrophysics.
The president's advisors are,
um, wrong. I'm right.
Hitting the rock from the outside
won't do the job.
Imagine a firecracker
in the palm of your hand.
You set it off.
What happens? Burn your hand, right?
You close your fist around
the same firecracker and set it off...
Your wife's gonna be opening your
ketchup bottles the rest of your life.
Are you suggesting
we blow this thing up from the inside?
- That's exactly what I'm saying.
- How?
We drill. We bring in the world's
best deep-core driller.
Harry, get up here!
We're takin' a hit!
- Get A.J. Up here! Whoa!
- Come on!
Send another pipe on down!
Right now! Full pipe!
- It's a gas pocket.
- I told you. Am I lucky
or am I just a genius?
I shut it down for a reason, you
jackass! The relief valve's fried open.
Shut off the number two valve!
Grace, get the clients outta here now!
Chick, get 'em outta here!
Get 'em off the rig now!
Get the hell down!
This thing is gonna blow!
Get out! Chick, get out now!
Get down!
Three dozen research calls and every
time the same man is recommended.
He's worked on every terrain
this planet can offer.
Whenever they said it couldn't be
drilled, this guy drilled it.
- Everybody all right?
- We struck oil, baby!
Somebody could've got killed out here
today. You want that on your conscience?
High thumb. You are man, Harry.
Thumbs high.
You're fired.
Who's Harry Stamper?
Yeah, I'm Harry Stamper.
What's all this about?
Mr Stamper, I'm General Montgomery,
commander of the Pacific air forces.
I've been sent here
by the secretary of defence...
on direct orders from the president
of the United States.
It's a matter of urgent
national security.
I need you to get on that chopper
right now, no questions asked.
- Crazy Willie put you up to this?
- Afraid I don't know Crazy Willie.
Sir, I'm dead serious about this.
- Harry.
- What?
Man, I swear to God,
she never told me her age.
It's all right.
Relax. It's about me.
Oh. Forget it.
All right, General.
I'll go with ya.
On one condition...
we have to take my daughter along.
- What did I do?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Where you guys
takin' her? Wait a minute.
- Sir, stay right here.
- Well...
Chick! Get him paid,
get him off the rig!
- Mr Stamper?
- Yeah, I'm Harry Stamper.
How ya doin'? Miss Stamper.
I'm Dan Truman, executive director here.
- Now listen, on behalf of all of us,
I'd really like to apologize...
- Apologize.
I don't know if we can take
any more apologies, Mr Truman.
We've been apologized to
for the last 18 and a half hours.
So if you don't mind,
how 'bout if we just get on with it...
and you tell us why we're here
at the NASA space centre?
- We should probably talk alone.
- Mr Truman, I don't keep any secrets
from my daughter, Grace.
So whether you tell her now or
I tell her later she's gonna find out...
one way or the other,
so why don't we just get on with it?
So when the rogue comet hit the asteroid
belt, it sent shrapnel right for us.
For the next 15 days
the Earth's in a shooting gallery.
Even if the asteroid itself hits
the water, it's still hitting land.
It'll flash-boil millions
of gallons of sea water and slam
into the ocean bedrock.
Now, if it's a Pacific Ocean impact...
which we think it will be...
it'll create a tidal wave three miles
high, travel at 1,000 miles an hour...
covering California
and washing up in Denver.
Japan's gone. Australia's wiped out.
Half the world's population'll be
incinerated by the heat blast...
and the rest'll freeze to death
from nuclear winter.
That's unbelievable.
Well, actually,
this is as real as it gets.
Well, it's coming, right now...
right for us...
at 22,000 miles an hour.
Not a soul on Earth can hide from it.
I take it you're not
alerting everyone like this.
Nobody knows.
That's the way it stays.
For the next ten days, there are
only nine telescopes in the world...
that can spot the asteroid,
and we control eight of'em.
The president's classified
this information top secret.
If news like this got out,
there'd be an overnight breakdown...
of basic social services worldwide...
rioting, mass religious hysteria.
Total chaos. You can imagine.
Basically the worst parts
of the Bible.
Six billion people on the planet...
why'd you guys call me?
- We need you to prep the team
we're sending up.
- Up?
We'll send 'em to the asteroid,
they'll land, they'll drill a hole,
they'll drop some nukes...
take off and detonate
if we can fix this equipment problem.
Now, the, uh, drilling unit's
a prototype we've been building
for the Mars project.
You, uh...
you might recognize the rig.
Yeah, well, I guess I should
recognize it. It's my design.
What'd you do?
Steal a key to the patent office?
- Yeah, basically.
- Let me get this straight.
I got pulled off an oil rig,
flown halfway around the world
because you stole my drill design...
couldn't read the plans right
and did a piss-poor job
of putting it together, is that it?
- Well, technically,
patents don't apply to outer space.
- Just shut up, Quincy.
It's not going to Mars any more.
It's going to try to save this planet.
And we need to know
what's wrong with it pretty quick.
You said we did a bad job
of putting it together?
No, I said you did a piss-poor job
of putting it together.
First of all, you got
the flow system all reversed.
Let me guess: You've been tearin' up
rotors and you can't figure out why.
- Yeah, that's right, actually.
- Well, that's because your cams
are all wrong, Mr Wizard.
- Who's been operating this thing?
- Right there.
W-We've actually... we've had them
training for eight months solid now.
- Eight whole months?
- Well, pretty much, yeah.
- Well, gee whiz.
- Well, this is the team
that has to do the job up there.
We need you to train 'em down here.
Well, Mr Stamper, what do you think?
You know, drilling's a science.
It's an art.
I'm a third-generation driller,
doin' it all my life...
and I still haven't got it
all figured out.
I assume you sent for me because
somebody told you I was the best.
Well, I'm only the best
because I work with the best.
You don't trust the men you're
working with, you're as good as dead.
Now, you want to send
these boys into space, fine.
I'm sure they'll make
good astronauts.
But they don't know jack
about drillin'.
- What's your contingency plan?
- Contingency plan?
Your backup plan. You gotta have
some kind of backup plan, right?
- No, we don't have a backup plan.
This is it.
- And this is the best that you could...
that the-the government,
the U.S. Government can come up with?
I mean, y-you're NASA, for cryin'
out loud. You put a man on the moon.
You're geniuses! Y-You're the guys
that think this shit up.
I'm sure you got a team of men
sittin' around somewhere right now...
just thinkin' shit up
and somebody backin' them up.
You tellin' me you don't have
a backup plan, that these
eight Boy Scouts right here...
that is the world's hope,
that's what you're tellin' me?
- Yeah.
- Oh, Jesus. Damn it.
We're a little short on time here.
Will you help us?
- All they gotta do is drill?
- That's it.
No spacewalkin',
no crazy astronaut stuff?
Just drill.
How many men were you plannin'
on takin' up there?
We're sendin' up
two shuttles, two teams.
If I do this,
I'm gonna wanna take my own men.
You got it.
So you're saying you'll help us?
Yes, sir.
Thanks.
I just don't trust anybody else
to do it, that's all.
No, Mrs Curlene,
it's Harry Stamper.
If you see Bear, you tell him
Harry's lookin' for him.
Those guys get off this rig,
they scatter.J. Otis Curlene Bear...
probably the only black man
on a big hog in Kadoka, South Dakota.
Come and get Papa Bear!
- Uh, Max.
- You got a weight limit on the shuttle?
- Max.
- Hey, Mama.
- Oh, that's so sweet, Maxie.
- Hey, did ya get me one of them
yellow jelly bear claws I like?
Maxie, are you in trouble
with the law again?
- No, Mama.
- Maxie.
I swear, Mama, I'm...
- You know I want Rockhound.
- We call him Hound because...
well, um, he's horny.
Well, you might want to start
with every bar in New Orleans.
That is a big, shiny mount,
isn't it?
- How long you been married?
- For two weeks.
- See this diamond?
- Yeah?
- It's not a diamond.
Would you like another drink?
- Yeah.
- Sir, FBI.
- She's so cute.
- No, thanks.
- We have a national security matter.
- Good for you.
- Let's go.
- Now.
- How old are you?
Oscar Choice... spacey
but absolutely brilliant geologist.
He owns a horse ranch
outside of El Paso.
What the...
Mr Chick Chapel, at the craps table,
Caesar's Palace, Las Vegas, Nevada.
Yes! About time.
Charles Chapel, game's over.
Who's gonna run the other rig?
How 'bout Benny? He's good.
The only one knows
how to run it as well as I do is A.J.
I thought you said
you couldn't trust him.
I thought you said I could.
Yep, you are on your way, A.J.
Well, you know, bein' in business
for yourself has its advantages...
make my own hours,
nobody shoots me in the leg.
You don't got
a gun on ya now, do ya? Oh, good.
'Cause I kinda wanted to get back
to this whole thing
about you askin' me for help.
Does that mean that there's actually
a job that Mr All-Go-No-Quit-Big-Nuts...
Harry Stamper can't handle by himself...
and needs my expert advice?
- Somethin' like that, yeah.
- Well, no, no, no.
I mean, is it-it something like that,
or is it that?
You know,
you and me got a real problem.
You know, Harry,
there are only, uh...
five words I wanna hear
from you right now.
And those words are: "You know, A.J.,
I really look up to you.
"You've been a hero of mine
for a long time, and...
I'm very impressed with your work;
I'm emotionally closed off."
That's like...
that's like 11 words or somethin'.
You know what? How about just,
"A.J., I'm sorry, and... and I love ya."
You know, A.J.,
there's not a job on the planet...
that I want you
to work with me on.
I mean that.
So what are you doin' here?
Harry, what's the job?
- Big Daddy!
- What's up, baby?
Yeah, big Bear.
What's up? What's up?
What's up, Harry?
Did NASA find oil on Uranus, man?
None of you have to go.
We can all just sit here on Earth...
wait for this big rock to crash into it,
kill everything and everybody we know.
The United States government
just asked us to save the world.
- Anybody wanna say no?
- Twenty years...
haven't turned ya down once,
not about to start now.
- I'm there.
- Guess I can't let you
go up there alone.
I'm with you.
I mean, this is...
this is historic.
Guys, this is
like deep blue hero stuff.
- Of course I'm in.
- While I don't share his enthusiasm...
you know me... beam me up, Scotty.
- You all right, Max?
- L-I don't... l-I don't...
Whatever you think.
- What about you?
- I'm in.
All right, then.
We go.
I don't mean to be the materialistic
weasel of this group, but...
you think we'll get
hazard pay out of this?
If you're trying to make me feel better
about this scenario, give it up.
To tell you the truth, I'm kind of
encouraged. This guy Chick here was
an Air Force commando for six years.
We got robbery, assault,
arrest, resisting arrest.
We got a collection agent
for the mob. Two of these guys
have done serious time.
- Look, they're the best at what they do.
- So am I.
And I'm not
so optimistic.
We spend $250 billion
a year on defence.
And here we are. The fate
of the planet is in the hands...
of a bunch of retards I wouldn't
trust with a potato gun.
- So what's the verdict?
- They'll do it.
- They've made a few requests though.
- Such as?
Just a few things here, uh...
Nothing really big, just...
Well, as an example...
Uh, Oscar here's got some
outstanding parking tickets.
Wants 'em wiped off his record.
- Fifty-six tickets in seven states.
- I'll tell him, Oscar. I got it.
- Okay.
- Uh, Noonan's got two women friends...
that he'd like to see made
American citizens, no questions asked.
Max would like you to bring back
eight track tapes.
Not sure if that's gonna work,
but let's see what else.
Chick wants a full week's Emperor's
Package at Caesar's Palace, um...
Hey, you guys wouldn't
be able to tell us who
actually killed Kennedy, would ya?
Uh, Bear would like to stay
at the...
White Horse, the...
White House.
White House. Yeah, he'd like
to stay in the Lincoln Bedroom
of the White House for the summer.
- Stuff like that.
- Sure, I think we can, uh...
take care of some of that.
Harry!
Yeah, one more thing. Um...
None of them wanna
pay taxes again.
Ever.
Who's that for?
Mr Ed?
You stick that in me, I'm gonna
stab you in the heart with it.
You ever see Pulp Fiction?
Oh, say can you see
We're losin' him,
we're losin' him. Clear! Kaboom!
- Freddie, you all right?
- Does this look okay to you?
- Does this look okay?
- It's not all bad. It's kinda tingly.
Mr Chapel, you're next!
Oh, gee, lady,
I just came here to drill.
Oh, so did I.
Your triglycerides
are way high...
and your bad cholesterol
is shockingly bad.
- Tell ya to lay off
those pork rinds, Pooh Bear.
- Yeah, pork rind this.
Pork rinds this!
Yeah!
Take it off, baby!
Well, at least
they're in good spirits.
Piece of cake.
Look, you wanna compare brain pans?
I won the Westinghouse Prize
when I was 12. Big deal.
Published at 19. So what? I got
a double doctorate from M.I.T. At 22.
Chemistry and geology.
I taught at Princeton for 21/2 years.
You know, I think this might be
the most uncomfortable room
I've ever been in in my life.
Why do I do this? Because the money's
good, the scenery changes...
and they let me use
explosives, okay?
Okay, you wanna be
all psychological with me, that's fine.
I'll tell you one thing
that really drives me nuts...
is people who think that Jethro Tull
is just a person in the band.
Who is Jethro Tull?
My favourite dish is haggis...
heart, lungs, liver.
You shove that all in a sheep's stomach,
then you boil it.
That'll put some hair on your ass.
I am not crazy. I'm just
a little emotional right now, okay?
You all throwin' all this stuff
at me, man. Look... get... I mean...
After this is over, could I, like,
get a hug from you or somethin'?
Okay, Cyclops lady's
startin' to bug me.
- Can you handle it?
- I mean, I can handle what I'm,
you know, I'm gonna do.
I can handle that, but I don't know
if I can handle this room.
Woman with large breasts.
- Woman with medium breasts.
- Here's Harry givin' me a hard time.
And, uh, this is Harry tellin' me
it's not good enough.
I can't marry his daughter.
Thanks a lot. I appreciate it.
Just let it out.
I suffered a major head injury
when I was in high school.
This one looks like you...
with breasts.
Yeah, I can handle it.
A home run! The Cubs win
the World Series!
Fail. Fail.
Depressively fail.
One toxicology analysis
revealed ketamine.
- That is a very powerful sedative.
- Sedatives are used
all the time, Doctor.
Well, this one's used on horses.
Some of these guys
are pretty big.
It would normally take 18 months
to psychologically prepare...
prescreen viable subjects
for space travel.
- We have seen evidence of a wide
variety of territorial aggression.
- Can they physically survive the trip?
- That's all I need to know here, okay?
- Personally, I don't know how
they survived the tests.
Talk about the wrong stuff.
Good morning.
I'm Colonel Willie Sharp.
In addition to flying one of
the X-71 teams to that rock...
my job is to train you how to deal
with the mental and physical
rigors of working in space...
so you don't freak out
on the asteroid.
United States astronauts
train for years.
You have 12 days.
Do we have any intelligent questions
before we get started?
- What's an X-71?
- You're the first civilians
to ever see her.
We call 'em the X-71 s.
It's a top secret joint venture
with the Air Force.
She and her sister ship at Vandenberg
are leaving tomorrow
for launch prep in Florida...
but I thought
you oughta take a look.
The two shuttles going up are
the Freedom and the Independence.
Her titanium alloy impenetrable skin
covers the toughest, meanest...
most sophisticated space vehicle
man has ever made.
Okay, Air Force Colonel Davis,
NASA pilot Tucker...
will command the shuttle
Independence.
Air Force Colonel Sharp,
NASA pilot Watts, shuttle Freedom.
Munitions specialist Gruber and Halsey
will supervise the nuclear ordnance.
Anyway, uh, I just thought, uh...
thought you guys should meet.
Gentlemen, welcome to our weightless
environmental training facility.
So we're going swimming on this
asteroid? Is that what this is for?
Here at downtown NASA,
we call this the "Monster Armadillo."
Gonna be retrofitted
with your drilling arm. She'll turn
800 turbo horses in near zero gravity.
Mind if we take a look at her now?
All these rubber hoses gotta go, Max.
Count 'em up.
Make sure it's
short-throw shiftin'.
Quincy!
Somebody tell me what this is.
Plastic ice cream scoop?
What'd that cost? About $400?
This is about the sorriest group
of people I've seen in all
my entire military career.
Your space flight's gonna be
a brutal assault on your senses.
I'm here to give you a taste
of that. NASA's got some of
the finest pilots in the world.
They're gonna be suckin' your eyes
into the back of your heads.
Go easy on me, okay?
It's my first time.
I just wanna seriously say
I have a small fear of flying.
I'm gonna twist ya.
- And I'm gonna flip ya.
- What's the matter with you?
Frap your body
till your bones hurt.
When you squeal, I'm just
gonna go faster and harder.
No, take me down!
- How's the rest of the crew?
- Well, uh...
Sorry about the rib chunks
all over your dashboard.
Don't forget:
We gotta X-ray all these...
- If you had to say, who would you say?
- I don't know, Oscar.
Who do you think you are?
- Han Solo.
- No. If anybody's anybody, I'm Han.
And you're...
you're Chewbacca.
Chewie? Have you even
seen Star Wars?
All right, men, let's go.
Step it up.
Neil Armstrong, 1969,
bouncing on the moon.
He's bouncing because there's
less gravity up there than on Earth.
This will be similar
to the asteroid, so watch it.
Something gets launched off
that asteroid with enough force...
it's gonna keep on going
right into outer space.
What is the deal?
Is it just me, or is Watts really hot?
Yeah.
So we have these new generation suits
with directional accelerant thrusters.
- You won't bounce like Neil Armstrong.
- Yeah, think so?
- Bear!
- Yes?
- Do we have a problem?
- No.
'Cause I'm trying to describe
to you how these D.A.T. S
keep your ass on the ground...
so that if I were to kick you
in the balls...
and you don't know how to work them,
what happens to you?
- I float away.
- Yeah.
And, uh, when do we
start training for that?
Gentlemen, I'll give you 30 seconds
to put your helmets on...
then the oxygen will be sucked
out of this vacuum...
and you will know what it's like
to be in space.
Go!
Depressed in 30 seconds.
Main valves have been activated.
Vacuum P.S.I. S are open.
Okay, gentlemen,
so here's the flight plan.
Now, let's keep the laughter to
a minimum. I know this is not to scale.
Both shuttles will take off
Tuesday at 6:30 p.m.
Now, 67 minutes later...
you're gonna dock with the Russian space
station to meet cosmonaut Andropov...
who will refuel the shuttles
with liquid O2.
That's your fuel.
Then you'll release...
and take a 60-hour trip
toward the moon.
Now, we only have one shot
of landing on this rock...
and that's precisely when
the asteroid passes by the moon.
You'll then use lunar gravity
and burn your thrusters...
slingshotting you
around the moon...
coming up behind the asteroid.
- You'll be upward of 11 Gs.
- Yeah, I remember this one.
It's where the, uh, the coyote
sat his ass down in a slingshot...
then he strapped himself
to an Acme rocket.
- Is-Is that what we're doin' here?
- Rockhound.
- No, no, really, because it didn't
work out too well for the coyote, Harry.
- Hey, Rock.
- Remember that one?
- Well, actually, we have a lot better
rockets than the coyote.
Now, when you've finished
your Road Runner thrust move...
you'll be moving
at 22,500 miles per hour.
Coming around behind the asteroid,
where we're hoping...
that the tail debris'll be
cleared by the moon's gravity.
And you'll land right here.
That's it.
We got separate landing sites
for each team. Softest parts
of the rock as we can figure.
At NASA, we don't take chances.
We double up on everything.
First team
that hits 800 feet wins.
Now this rock is big, it's dense, it's
got some gravity. You can walk around.
But use your thrusters
so you can work easier.
Okay, Mr Truman, let's say that
we actually do land on this.
What's it gonna be like
up there?
Two hundred degrees in the sunlight.
Minus 200 in the shade.
Canyons of razor-sharp rock.
Unpredictable gravitational conditions.
Unexpected eruptions.
Things like that.
Okay, so the scariest
environment imaginable. Thanks.
That's all you gotta say:
Scariest environment imaginable.
Okay, so you drill,
you drop the nuke, and you leave.
Now, here's the key: You're gonna
remote detonate the bomb...
before the asteroid
passes this plane... Zero Barrier.
You do that, and the remaining
pieces of rock...
should be deflected enough
to pass right by us.
Now, if the bomb explodes
after Zero Barrier...
game's over.
Paul, this is Houston.
Fire your rockets.
- Okay, your rockets are maximum.
Beautiful boost.
- Oscar!
Hey, Harry. Hey, how's it goin'?
- Have you seen Grace?
- Yeah, she's over in the hangar
with A.J.
Harry, wait a second. Did you say Grace?
Okay, I thought you said Bear.
Will you marry me?
Grace is old enough
to vote, Harry.
She's old enough to have a drink or
get married if she wants, get a divorce.
Let me tell you something, fellas. When
I get back, when we get this job done...
I will deal with this
in my own way.
Come on, Harry. It's not like
I'm rootin' for A.J. Here.
- I'm just sayin',
Grace is not a little girl any more.
- Hey, Rock, you know, wait a minute.
Let me get a pencil and
a piece of paper. I wanna jot down
all your pearls of wisdom here.
Get serious, Harry. Come on. While we're
off trottin' the globe, hunting mud...
Gracie grew up to become
a full-blown hottie, you know?
- Harry, she is fully hot. She is...
- She's a babe.
Max, Max, okay. You're talkin'
about my little girl, all right?
I think I know
who and what she is, okay?
Okay, but Harry, all we're sayin' is,
we're talkin' about a kid who's
comin' into her own right now.
And she's gettin' curious about her body
and she's exploring her sexuality.
And you know what?
- Oscar.
- That's a natural thing.
You are about five minutes older than
Grace is. Why should I listen to you?
And I know what it feels like to have
your hormones pullin' you in just, you
know, a thousand different directions.
- You don't know which end is up.
- Yo, Harry, no disrespect, man,
but we all helped to raise her.
- So, in part, we all feel
like a bunch of daddies here.
- That's true.
I'll be damned if I worked all
these years so my little girl
can marry a roughneck.
She's better than that.
Better than all of us.
Harry, just sit back, relax.
I'm gonna put on a little
free Armadillo driving clinic for ya.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Two shuttle teams. A.J.'ll be
running the drill team with Oscar,
Bear and Noonan on the Independence.
I'll run the drill team on Freedom
with Chick, Rockhound and Max.
Once we land, we'll have
eight hours to get the job done.
In order to split this rock
on the fault line,
we're gonna have to drill to 800 feet.
Let's get our game faces on.
Now it's time for underwater simulation.
Come on, Independence. Keep it up.
Let's go. We're the younger team here.
We're the varsity team.
Take it to 11,000.
Okay, gentlemen, we're gonna
trick 'em up. My computer
will simulate a gas pocket...
at 625 feet and then
hard iron ferrite at 635.
I'm gonna draw up some more O2 in.
We're takin' her up.
- I'm givin' it more torque right now.
- All right, lookin' good, Bear.
Clamp it down. Watch your time,
Independence team.
Thanks, Harry. Would you mind
lettin' me run my own team?
You're gonna blow the tranny, A.J.
Slow it down, baby.
Take it easy, Bear.
Just relax. She can handle it.
A.J., you're at 600 feet.
Your pipe is long.
Let's back the R.P.M. S down to 8,000.
- We don't have time for 8,000!
- A.J., take it back down.
You're gonna snap the pipe.
I don't wanna blow this transmission.
- Damn it, 11,000.
- Slow it down, A.J.
Bear, come on.
Get on our team for a little bit.
- Whoa, space cowboy.
- Harry, are you listenin' to this?
- Yeah, I'm listenin', Bear.
Harry? You don't work for Harry
any more, okay?
Out there you gotta listen to me.
When we're on that rock,
you gotta do what I say.
Now send more to the turbine.
I'm throttling up to 11,000.
A.J., back it off.
You're gonna blow the transmission.
Hey, Harry, would you let me
run my team, please?
- R.P.M. S are at red line.
- Bear, goddam it, I know what I'm doing.
Come on. She can handle this.
She'll be fine. Trust me.
- A.J., back the R...
- Transmission overload.
- Number one transmission is down.
Oh, son of a... The computer's wrong,
and you know that.
- We did the right thing.
- We're gonna restart the simulation.
If you wanna replace a member
of the crew, now is the time.
I'll take care of this.
Get him out of the tank, Chick.
- You wanna go home?
Is that it? You wanna be fired?
- No, I don't.
- My crew was doing the right thing.
- Your crew?
- Yeah.
- Your crew just blew
the transmission, A. J!
Listen, that NASA computer is just
playin' it safe. The machine you built,
the rig, could do it.
Shut up. Just shut up!
Shut your mouth!
Those men in that room
have zero tolerance
for showin' off, hot doggin'...
goin' by your gut instinct or
you tryin' to be a hero, you got that?
- Say the words, A. J!
- I got it!
- I want my men to have
tomorrow night off.
- What do you mean "off"?
I mean, off. Out of here. For at least
ten hours. Then we'll go to Kennedy.
Well, there's no possible way we can
do that, Harry. There's a potentially
huge security risk. What if they talk?
- What if they get hurt?
- What if they're too burned out
to do the right thing?
What if they get up there,
and they forget what
they're fighting for?
You see what's goin' on up there.
These boys are ready to snap.
They didn't ask to be here.
They got pulled off the street.
For all we know, tomorrow night could be
the last night they ever see Earth.
I don't think it's too much to ask to
let 'em spend it with their families.
- Well, listen, there's
no possible way we can do that.
- You got family, Colonel?
- Two girls.
- Wouldn't you like to spend tomorrow
night with your little girls?
I'm not askin' ya.
I'm tellin' ya.
Make this happen.
This is a pretty big loan.
Why don't you count the cash?
Nah, this looks like
100 grand to me.
I'm givin' you this at 60 percent.
I hope you know what you're doin'...
because I'll bust your head
with a sledgehammer.
- You'll get your money back.
- You don't look too healthy.
You're not gonna die on me,
are ya?
Let's just say,
no more than you are. Thanks, Vic.
Don't wanna close my eyes
I don't wanna fall asleep
'Cause I'd miss you, baby
- And I don't wanna miss a thing
- You know what I was thinkin'?
- What?
L-I really don't think that the
animal cracker qualifies as a cracker.
- Why?
- Well, 'cause it's sweet,
which to me suggests cookie.
And, you know, putting cheese
on something is sort of
the defining characteristic...
of what makes a cracker
a cracker.
I don't know why
I thought of that. I just...
Baby, you have
such sweet pillow talk.
I got a little animal cracker, Discovery
Channel thing happenin' right here.
Watch the gazelle
as he grazes through the open plains.
Now look
as the cheetah approaches.
Watch
as he stalks his prey.
Now, the gazelle's
a little spooked...
and he could head north
to the ample sustenance...
provided by
the mountainous peaks above.
He could go south.
The gazelle now faces man's
most perilous question:
North, or...
south?
Way down under.
Tune in next week.
Baby...
do you think it's possible
that anyone else in the world...
is doing this very same thing
at this very same moment?
I hope so.
Otherwise, what the hell
are we tryin' to save?
Don't wanna close my eyes
I don't wanna fall asleep
'cause I'd miss you, baby
And I don't wanna miss a thing
Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- I was just passin' by on the, uh...
I came...
- Who's he?
- That man's a salesman.
Would you go inside?
Thank you.
He got big.
You can't come around like this.
The court says you can't.
It confuses him.
No, I know. I just...
I wanted to say
that I'm sorry...
about everything, and...
I got somethin' comin' up.
It's something kinda big.
You just might be proud of me.
Would you do somethin' for me?
Would you just give him this?
You don't have to... You don't have to
tell him who it's from. Just...
Everybody talkin'about
what it is, what it ain't
Kiss on the devil
and you piss off a saint
But it can't be love
if you don't have to crawl
You say you don't need nothin'
but you got to have it all
- Come back here!
- Hey, Noonan, you need ten grand?
- Yeah.
- We gotta put
these girls through college.
- I love this astronaut stuff.
- All right!
- Good work if you can get it.
Yeah, I'm just in town doin'
a little astronaut training.
Ooh! Astronauta.
Ah, si.
I'm a mission specialist.
- Yes, and what's that mean?
- I don't know.
Hey! Who the hell
do you think you guys are?
- You're hoggin' all the action.
- Hey, pinhead. Why don't you
go find your own party?
- Why don't you spread the wealth, pal?
- Here. Why don't you go
buy yourself a neck?
Hey, Mr Clean!
- Man! Call NASA!
- Get over there.
- They'll confirm it! We're astronauts!
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, we're astronauts.
- Yeah, we're all astronauts.
You are so messing with national
security right now, man.
- Turn around.
- You are fired tomorrow morning.
I'm telling ya.
I'll get the CIA and the FBI.
- You'll be working security at Toys
'R' Us. Oh, oh, baby. No, no. No, no!
- Bye-bye, little astronaut.
- Oh, it's time to go now.
- Oh, don't leave, baby. No, no.
- You see, I'm goin' into space,
and I'm not comin' back.
- No, no, no.
- It's coming in at 30,000 miles an hour!
- Give me a projected impact.
- East Asia, 11 minutes.
- We're gonna have to warn...
Warn who?
The entire South Pacific?
So the whole world knows.
Tell me you've never let
anybody down before.
I never quit yet.
How's that?
I guess that'll have to do.
You know somethin'?
I still remember the first,
middle and last name...
of every guy that qualified
for the astronaut programme
the first year I was here.
Thanks. I went
into the engineering programme.
Kinda had to.
But, boy, I wanted to go up there.
I wanted to be one of those guys
with a mission patch on my arm.
I tell you, I'd be on that shuttle
with you, Harry, if I could.
You don't want to be up in that shuttle
any more than I do.
Well, good luck in Florida tomorrow.
The death of 50,000 people in Shanghai
yesterday has rattled the na...
A French satellite has tracked
an object in space...
Sources are estimating
that the tidal wave was five...
This is CNN, live in Florida.
We have just learned that NASA
is on a full-scale military alert.
They're calling this
a global killer.
The government has been
very tight-lipped throughout this...
The Pentagon is getting involved
at this point with some kind...
of a project involving NASA
and perhaps a shuttle mission...
Senior Pentagon officials
refused comment...
adding fuel to the speculation that
there could be a very serious problem.
We have a special team of astronauts
that arrived in Florida this evening.
NASA's in emergency launch
preparation...
in cooperation with Russian, Japanese
and French space agencies...
on the most massive
joint space venture in history.
Gracie?
Got your note.
- What are you doing out here, honey?
- Um, just thinkin'.
- Yeah.
- I, um, want to apologize to you for...
Oh, no, Grace. Stop.
You don't have to apologize at all. L...
I sh...
I shouldn't have dragged you around
on all those oil rigs. I just...
I don't think that I did
the right thing with you.
- You're wrong.
- You see...
I love my life.
I love everything
about my life...
and I don't blame you
for my mother leaving.
She left us both.
And-And I love you.
And don't talk
like you're not comin' back.
Promise me that you'll come back.
- Okay.
- Say, "I promise."
I promise, Grace.
It's gonna be all right, Grace.
If it's not too much trouble, can you
please bring my fiancé home with you?
Oh, Jesus.
The president will be
addressing the nation...
and all of you personally
within the hour.
Astronauts.
I'll see you
in a couple days, honey.
All my bags are packed
I'm ready to go
I'm standing here
outside your door
I hate to wake you up
To say goodbye
So kiss me and smile for me
Let me know you'll wait for me
Hold me like
you'll never let me go
'Cause I'm leavin'
On a jet plane
Don't know
when I'll be back again
Leavin'on a jet plane
I don't know
when I'll be back again
- Leavin'on a jet plane
I don't know
when I'll be back again
- Leavin'on a jet plane
- So, Truman, this is who you found
to save the planet.
- Don't know when I'll be back again
- Frost, you good to go?
- Mm-hmm. One-One sec.
- Leavin'on a jet plane
- That boy don't take anything seriously.
- Yeah. Reminds me of
a guy I used to know.
- Don't know when I'll be back again
Leavin'on a jet plane
- I don't know when I'll be back again
- I'm marrying you.
- Bet your ass you are.
- Leavin'on a jet plane
I don't know
when I'll be back again
I address you tonight...
not as the president
of the United States...
not as the leader of a country...
but as a citizen of humanity.
We are faced with the very gravest
of challenges.
The Bible calls this day Armageddon,
the end of all things.
And yet,
for the first time...
in the history of the planet,
a species has the technology...
to prevent its own extinction.
All of you praying with us
need to know...
that everything that can be done
to prevent this disaster...
is being called into service.
The human thirst for excellence...
and knowledge...
every step
up the ladder of science...
every adventurous
reach into space...
all of our combined
modern technologies and imaginations...
even the wars that we've fought,
have provided us the tools...
to wage this terrible battle.
Through all the chaos
that is our history...
through all of the wrongs
and the discord...
through all of the pain
and suffering...
through all of our times
there is one thing...
- that has nourished our souls...
- Mom, that salesman's on TV.
And elevated our species
above its origins...
and that is our courage.
The dreams of an entire planet
are focused tonight...
on those 14 brave souls...
travelling into the heavens.
That man's not a salesman.
That's your daddy.
And may we all, citizens the world over,
see these events through.
Godspeed and good luck to you.
Freedom crew.
Independence crew.
- How you feelin'?
- Uh, good, you know.
I mean, considering I've never been this
scared in my entire life. L... You know...
Listen, once you get up there,
you're gonna be on your own.
If anything should happen,
I just wanted...
I know, Harry. I'll, uh,
try not to disappoint you.
Take care of yourself, kid.
Freedom's on the bridge.
Attention in the firing room.
The oxidizer loading is complete.
- Independence on the bridge.
- Attention all personnel.
We are Tminus two hours
to the programme goal.
- Hey, Harry.
- Yeah, Rock?
You know, we're sittin' on four million
pounds of fuel, one nuclear weapon...
and a thing that has
270,000 moving parts...
built by the lowest bidder.
- Makes you feel good, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
- How ya doin', Oscar?
- Great.
- Yeah?
- I got that excited, scared feelin'...
like 98% excited, 2% scared.
Maybe it's more. It could be 2... It
could be 98% percent scared, 2% excited.
But that's what makes it
so intense, is it's so confused.
I can't really figure it out.
Will you make mine really tight,
'cause I don't want to fall out.
- Yes, sir.
- I mean, almost to the point
of cutting off circulation.
- Ow.
- It must be a comfort to know...
that if the space programme
goes under you can always get a job
at Helga's House of Pain, huh?
- All right. Flight directors on
with the go/ no-go for launch.
- Retro.
- Go flight.
- Booster.
- Ecos.
- Go flight.
- Trajectory.
- FIDO.
- Go flight.
- EVA.
- CAPCOM Freedom.
- Go flight.
- CAPCOM Independence.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
it's pucker time.
Independence and Freedom,
this is Kennedy firing room.
We're Tminus one minute.
All crew members,
close and lock your visors.
Independence, this is launch control.
Be advised, we're in a smooth count.
T minus 31. You're go
for auto-sequence start.
B.L. T. S, perform
your A.D.U. Pre-start.
Okay, gentlemen, you're our warriors
up there. God be with you.
- You're already heroes.
Just sit back and enjoy the ride.
- F. T.D., we're clear to launch.
We're T minus 20 seconds.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
four, three, two, one.
We have main engine start.
- We have booster ignition.
- We're going.
And liftoff.
Freedom, this is flight deck.
Roger, Freedom.
You're looking good.
- We have go for Independence.
- Three, two, one.
- Independence, we have booster ignition.
- We have liftoff.
We are cooking, Houston.
Houston, the tower is clear.
They're all yours.
- Heads up, everybody. They're ours now.
- All engines are go.
Keep a sharp eye out on both of'em.
Start roll manoeuvre.
- Two good roll programs.
- One down.
- Independence, we have a max cue.
Roger, Control.
We are a max cue.
S.R.B. Sep...
- We are single-engine, press, demi-go.
- Copy, press, demi-go.
Houston, this is a kick-ass ride!
Freedom, this is Houston.
Main engine cut out on schedule. Out.
Freedom, stats are good.
- Independence,
telemetry is up and running...
- Oh, my God!
This is space! 'Course, we're just
in the beginning part of space.
We-We haven't even gotten
to outer space yet.
Roger, Houston.
We have a visual on the Russian
space station. Initiating retro burn.
Gentlemen, remember the Russian space
station has been up there for 11 years.
Most of us
don't have cars that old.
Now, the cosmonaut on board has been
on that tin can for 18 months, alone.
So don't be surprised
if he's a little off.
- Independence, we're gonna put you...
- All right, crew.
Let's exit these flight suits.
Hello. This is Russian
space station. Can you hear me?
We copy, Russian space station.
This is Houston.
I'm ready to fire
my thrusters any time.
- Stand by.
- Okay. I'm not going anywhere.
We have a go.
Initiate gravitational spin.
You are maxed at 40% spin.
Okay, Houston.
I can feel I'm having gravity.
All right, gentlemen.
We're gonna dock in a minute.
Now, the Russian space station has
fired her rockets to simulate gravity
and let us work faster.
But it's gonna make you queasy,
so prepare yourself.
Well, it's about time.
I haven't thrown up in about an hour.
Initiating first phase
of docking procedure.
- Switching to manual.
- Manual override.
One foot per second.
Let's take this slow and
do it right, folks. Twenty feet.
Ten feet. Looking good on radar.
Five feet.
Locks are engaged.
Fuel teams, let's go.
Freedom, telemetry is looking good.
- We have soft dock.
- Fuel teams, prepare to unload.
All right, gentlemen, watch your heads.
Let's go, Independence.
Colonel.
Where is he? Anybody home?
Welcome, everybody!
I am not gas station.
This is sophisticated laboratory.
I'm in charge.
So do not be touching anything.
I need one... I need you.
- Go with him.
- I need you. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Come on. Come on.
It's very important you watch the
fuel gauge, okay? Put on cold suit.
- Countdown clock will hold at...
- Copy that, Houston.
Prepping for fuel transfer.
Countdown clock will hold
at Tminus 20 minutes and...
- Fuel pod is down there.
- It's down here, huh? Great.
Let's go. Move it on.
Here we go. We go. We go.
Bring it down. Bring it down.
Okay, let's connect
these fuel lines.
Freedom on the left,
Independence on the right.
All right. We're goin' left here.
To the right is fuel gauge.
You watch the fuel gauge. 150, okay.
160, okay. 200, bad disaster
for space station.
So if you watch 200,
you can call for Lev, on,
and you see here number one, on.
You ask for Lev. And you pull
this down, all the way down.
- What's Lev?
- I am Lev Andropov,
colonel of Russian space agency.
In Russia I'm a very big man.
- We're ready to transfer.
- I'm coming. No problem.
You. You. You there!
- Hard locked.
- Ready for transfusion!
Fuel is pumping.
Hey, Lev, the, uh, the-the pressure's
climbing. Is there a problem here?
Houston, we're on
fuel transference.
Don't touch my uncle. You know?
He's a genius of my family.
Lev! Can anybody hear me?
Guys? Hello, guys.
He used to work
for a big bomb factory.
He used to make the tip of the bomb,
the thing that finds, uh...
New York or Washington, you know?
- Ooh.
- Check your hoses.
We got some thermal variation.
Stamper, let's look at the couplings
back on the shuttle.
Okay. Shut down. Uh...
- Guys!
- Hold on a second.
- What's that noise?
Oh, no! God!
- What is it?
- Leak! Leak! Leak!
Get your men
back to the shuttle! Go!
Go on! Hurry up!
Get out of there!
Now there's really sparks!
- Pull lever!
- This is the lever!
- Colonel, we must get him out of there!
- A.J., come on out!
Hurry! Hurry!
Emergency! Break away!
We got a fire
in the fuel pod!
- Come on!
- Come on! Get in here!
A.J.'s stuck in the fuel pod!
- We're losing it!
- Come on out of there!
Control, this is Independence.
I am seeing vibration...
- Malloy, talk to me!
- Not good. We got sparks
and fire in the fuel pod.
- Independence, blow those locks
and get outta there now!
- Dump the hoses now! We're going!
- What happened?
Let me shut off the O2 feed!
- Harry, it's burnin' up!
Damn! Max, Rock, get in here! Get down
there and crack these pipes over here!
- Harry, no! It's burnin' up!
- We're goin' back for the other team!
Switch on the personnel locators.
Trackin' A.J. He's climbin'.
- No!
- Go! Go!
It's too late! Get back to the shuttle!
This thing's gonna blow!
No!
Colonel, we gotta move now!
Come on! You're gonna die!
- Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
We got a man in there!
- Open that door and we'll all die!
- Fuel leak!
- Get out of there!
Evac now! Let's go! Let's go!
Come on back!
No, wait! The door is broken!
- No!
- They got the fire
sealed in the fuel pod.
- They locked it down.
- Tracking 'em back to the shuttle.
They've still got two men
trapped in there!
Keep running! The shuttle's another
75 feet! Where's the rest of the team?
- Let's get out of here! The pod...
- Wait, wait, wait! Where's A. J?
- A.J.'s gone!
- We're not leavin' without A. J!
- He's gone! It's too late!
Come on!
This way is our only chance!
So it's minus 100!
Very cold. Hold breath,
or lung freezes!
Get back to the shuttle!
And lock that door!
- Come on!
- Hurry, A. J!
- Leave him alone! Leave him alone!
- I tried! I tried. But A. J...
- It's on fire! It's on fire, Harry!
- It's them or all of us!
- It's on fire!
- Full thrust.
- We're gonna get hit.
Lev! Lev, the door's gonna blow!
No!
We're going! It's gonna blow!
www.moviesubtitles.org