Improved By: FidelPerez
Subtitle By: explosiveskull
Sub Upload Date: September 25, 2018
(ENGINE CHUGGING)
(TRAIN HOOTING)
Budapest.
- The next stop's Budapest.
- (ALL GASPING)
Budapest is the next stop.
Budapest.
Tickets, ladies.
(IN FALSETTO)
Oop, here you go.
- (IN FALSETTO) Here's mine.
- (IN FALSETTO) And mine.
- (IN FALSETTO) Mine, too!
- (IN FALSETTO) Here you go!
Thank you, young man.
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
Man, I hate wearing disguises.
These heels are killing me.
Okay, take it down a notch.
We don't want to alarm
the humans.
(BOY WHIMPERING)
Psst. Drac.
(GERMAN ACCENT)
I'm about to und freak out!
You're a nice kitty.
I'm und kitty-cat.
Meow. Meow!
(ALL GASPS)
Oh, no, not this clown again.
Good evening, travelers.
I am Professor
Abraham Van Helsing.
Yes. One of the Van Helsings.
For centuries, my family
has protected humanity
from the evils of monsters.
So you can believe me
when I tell you,
there are monsters
hiding amongst you!
(LOUD CLUCKING)
But fear not,
for I am a professional,
and I know how to flush out
these beasts
and bring them into the light!
Fire bad!
(YOWLING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (CHICKEN CLUCKING)
(ALL WHIMPERING)
(YELPING)
FRANKENSTEIN: Whoa!
Sorry, guys.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GRUNTING AND GROANING)
(MURRAY SCREAMING)
Finally! First I kill Dracula,
and then
the rest of the monsters!
Why do you keep doing this?
Your dad, your grandfather,
your great-great-granny...
I defeated them all.
When will you Van Helsings
ever learn to let go of the hate?
Never! Because you, monster,
are a...
(HIGH-PITCHED)
Eh, squeak, squeak.
What? A mouse?
VAN HELSING: Ahhh!
You can't run from me,
Prince of Darkness!
I will hunt you
for all eternity!
(SCREAMS)
I swear I will never rest until
I destroy you... (GROANS)
And... (YELPS)
Every... (GROANS)
Other...
Monster... Ow!
If it's the last thing...
(GROANS)
I... (GRUNTS)
Ever... (GROANS)
Do!
(THUNDER CRASHING)
Boy, that guy is annoying.
Maybe one day
there will be a place
where monsters can go
to get away from it all,
take a vacation.
Who knows,
maybe even get married.
Wouldn't that be something?
(SCREAMING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
- (♫ "HERE COMES THE BRIDE" PLAYING ♫)
- (♫ BAND MOANING MELODY ♫)
GUESTS: Hmm?
(BABIES BAWLING IN DISTANCE)
(SHUSHING) It's okay.
Oh, when is this thing
starting?
Aw, you made them cry,
Wayne.
All except this little one.
Coochie-coochie...
WAYNE:
That's Sunny. She doesn't cry.
(YELPING IN PAIN)
- She bites.
- (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
- This is a very special moment, Carl.
- (WHIMPERING)
Any second, your beautiful bride
is going to walk right down the aisle.
Oh, no, Drac,
she's not coming.
- (AIR DEFLATING)
- Oh, don't worry.
Mavis is with her.
I'm sure everything is under control.
Mavey, is everything
under control?
Um, yep, just a slight case
of pre-wedding jitters.
(SCREAMING)
Ahhh!
(HISSING)
(WHIMPERING)
Yep, everything is fine here.
(SOBBING)
Please try to relax, Lucy.
I've taken care of everything.
The wedding
is going to be perfect.
It's not that.
Just, how do I know
I'm doing the right thing?
(BLOWING NOSE)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
- (CRYING)
- I know just how you feel.
The day I married Johnny
was the best day of my life,
but I was so nervous.
Not as nervous as I was.
And you should have seen my dad.
He was a mess.
I wouldn't get out
of my coffin that night.
But he knew it was meant to be.
It doesn't matter
where you come from
or how different you are.
A Zing only happens
once in your life,
and you have to cherish it.
(CRIES, CHUCKLES)
ALL: Aww.
You're right! Thank you!
(GRUNTING)
Okay. All right. Okay.
Oh. Uh... Okay.
(FORCED CHUCKLE)
(BLABBING)
I do.
- (♫ "WEDDING MARCH" PLAYING ♫)
- (ALL CHEERING, WHOOPING)
(DISTANT THUDDING, RUMBLING)
Do you hear that?
Yes. I thought we locked him
in his room.
We did!
- (BARKING)
- DENNIS: Whoa! Whoa!
- (PANTING)
- Hi, Mom. Hi, Papa.
- Dennis!
Tinkles was crying,
so we let him out.
(BARKING)
Ahhh!
Tinkles, sit!
(TINKLES WHINING)
DRACULA: Ah. Whose idea was it
to let Dennis have a puppy?
- Um... Yours?
- (CHUCKLES SHEEPISHLY)
(STAMMERS)
Right.
Poor Tinkles.
MAVIS: Dennis...
Look, honey,
I know you love Tinkles,
but we're not allowed
to bring our dogs...
- (GASPS)
- Uh... I mean, our pets everywhere.
Okay?
Okay.
(♫ UPBEAT POP MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
- ♫ I'm in love ♫
- ♫ I'm in love with a monster ♫
DJ Jazzy Johnny in the house.
It's time to welcome the happy couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Prickles!
- (♫ "ALWAYS AND FOREVER" PLAYING ♫)
- CROWD: Aw!
JONATHAN: The bride and groom
invite everyone
to join them
on the dance floor.
♫ Always and forever ♫
FEMALE MONSTER:
Care to dance?
♫ Each moment with you ♫
GRIFFIN: Is that her?
Ooh! Watch out now.
She got stitches
in all the right places.
Okay, there's no way that
is related to you, Frank.
No, she's my right arm's cousin.
(CHUCKLES)
- (BONES CRUNCHING)
- Ay! Oh!
- Oh!
- GRIFFIN: Ah! I see it now.
- Frank wanted me to meet you.
- (BONES CRUNCHING)
We're arm cousins,
twice removed.
DRACULA: Of course.
I'd recognize that bicep
anywhere.
He thought, since we're both single,
we might hit it off,
maybe go on a date?
DRACULA: "Date"? Oh!
Well, eh,
it's just that, eh...
- (♫ ROCK MUSIC BEGINS ♫)
- Whoa!
The DJ booth
is a sacred space!
(GIGGLES) I love this song!
(GIGGLING)
Don't you?
Dracula?
Oh, where'd he go?
(DEEP GROWL)
What's the matter, Drac,
you didn't like her?
No offense,
but you can't be too picky.
You haven't had a date
in 100 years.
Look, guys, I appreciate your concern,
but it's not up to me.
You only Zing once,
and I did.
Times have changed, buddy.
You can even find someone
to Zing with on your phone now.
What? Really?
Oh. Oh, no, no, no.
I'm far too busy.
I have Mavis and Dennis
and the hotel, and blah, blah-blah.
Um, did you guys hear that?
He actually said,
"Blah, blah-blah."
I don't say,
"Blah, blah-blah"!
(BEEPS)
(AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE
SPEAKING)
Eh, uh,
I'm looking for a Zing.
- Okay. Changing phone ring.
- (RINGTONE PLAYS)
No, no.
I'm looking for a date.
(AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE
SPEAKING)
No, no, no.
I want to meet someone.
(AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE
SPEAKING)
Are you kidding me right now?
Don't you get it?
I want to go on a date!
I'm... lonely.
(AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE
SPEAKING)
- You want baloney.
- (GROANS)
- (CELL PHONE CONTINUES PINGING)
- (DRACULA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(MUMBLES)
What? Look at that hair.
Come on.
Ah. Too many eyes.
Too few eyes.
- Not into tentacles.
- (CELL PHONE CHIMES)
"Match found"?
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- No, no, no!
First things first.
- (CATS SNARL)
- Whoa!
I'm not into games.
You'd better have a job,
and my cats have to like you.
- (CATS YOWLING)
- (DRACULA EXCLAIMING)
DRACULA: Oh, no.
Oh, whoa, no.
Dad?
Oh! Mavis! Oh.
Uh, what are you doing here?
I was just checking on the honeymoon suite,
and I heard something.
Oh, I'm sorry,
my little bed-bug.
I wa... I was just cleaning
the attic.
(♫ SCATTING MELODY ♫)
It's so dirty, ah, yes...
- WITCH: (OVER PHONE) Who is that?
- Are you on the phone?
What, this? I was just, eh...
trying to find a maid
- to help me with the mess.
- WITCH: A maid?
Who do you think...
Thank you,
I'll check your references
and get back to you. Goodbye!
(♫ RESUMES SCATTING MELODY ♫)
- Dad.
- (STAMMERS)
Stop trying
to hide it from me.
Hide? Who?
I mean, what? Me?
Yes.
And I know what it is.
Uh... Really?
You're stressed out
from working too hard.
Oh!
Okay, yes.
You got me, yes.
Hey, it's a big hotel,
you know?
Can't get to everything.
But what about you?
You're pretty busy yourself.
I know. It seems like now that
we're working together more,
we're seeing each other less.
Ah. Yeah.
You're absolutely right.
I am working too much,
you're working too much.
We should really take a break,
starting right now.
Night-night.
(SIGHS)
WITCH: I'm still here!
(CAT YOWLS)
(♫ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING ON TV ♫)
(ALL SNORING)
Aww.
Oh! Hey, honey.
You ready for... (YAWNS)
date night?
- (YAWNS)
- Aww.
That's okay, sweetheart.
You rest.
- (RESUMES SNORING)
- (SIGHS)
You know, Dad's right.
We need a break.
We need to all be together again,
like a family.
Like we used to.
MAN: (ON TV)
Are you overworked and stressed out?
- (GRUNTS)
- Do you need some family time?
Are you a monster?
Then you need a vacation,
a monster vacation.
♫ Sail away, sail away,
sail away ♫
STEWARDESS: Welcome aboard
Gremlin Air.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(CACKLING)
- Ah!
- (SCREAMS)
(SHOUTING GIBBERISH)
(CACKLING)
(GREMLINS GRUNTING
AND CHATTERING)
(GREMLIN CACKLING)
Ladies and gentlemen,
please direct your attention
to the front of the cabin.
For your safety,
please unbuckle your seat belts.
Ooh.
(SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
In the likely event we experience
a sudden drop in cabin pressure,
oxygen will be provided.
(GREMLIN BLOWING)
Can I stow that for you, sir?
All right. Thanks.
Beverages. Snacks. Beverages.
Beverages. Snacks.
Beverages.
(BUZZING)
- (BONES CRUNCH)
- Ahhh!
- Coffee?
- That would be lovely.
(SCREAMING)
- (RUBBER DUCKY SQUEAKING)
- (CACKLES)
(GRUNTS)
Mavis, please,
you're torturing me.
You know I hate surprises.
(CHUCKLES)
This is a fun surprise.
There are no fun surprises.
Just tell me where we're going.
Why are we on a plane?
We can fly, you know.
Back in my day,
people took trains.
Now, that's classy.
Sure, Dad. Forty hours
in a closet-sized room
with you and Uncle Bernie
and his smelly cigars,
arguing who was more attractive,
Cleopatra or Nefertiti.
(GROANS) Nefertiti.
- Okay, Dad, thank you.
- (LAUGHS)
Mavis, this is such
an amazing surprise!
I can't wait to spend time
with the people I love most.
But I beg of you,
tell me where we're going!
Nope. I've taken care of everything,
so you don't need to worry.
You've been
so stressed out lately.
It's time for you to relax.
(MAVIS CHUCKLES)
- (GRUNTS)
- Now, isn't that better?
Oh, yes.
So relaxed.
I'm gonna go check
on you-know-who.
I'll be right back.
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- (GREMLIN CACKLES)
Hey, did you see that?
Dennis went to the bathroom!
Uh... Okay.
Psst. Hey, where are you?
(WHINES)
There you are, Tinkles.
Don't worry, we'd never
leave you home alone.
PILOT: (OVER P.A.)
Okay, folks, you're free to move
about the cabin, as we have
started our descent.
(ENGINE WHINES)
(SCREAMING)
- (OVEN DINGS)
- (MUZAK PLAYING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
So, any big plans
for the weekend there, Bill?
Oh, you know, the usual.
Got to take the kids
to soccer.
(BOTH SLURPING)
STEWARDESS: Snacks. Beverages.
Snacks. Beverages. Snacks.
(HULL CREAKING)
Ladies and gentlemen,
we've arrived at our destination,
the Bermuda Triangle.
ALL: Ooh!
(PASSENGERS WHOOPING,
LAUGHING)
Welcome to the Bermuda Triangle,
where you'll embark
on a monster cruise of a lifetime.
A cruise?
Surprise!
(GRUMBLES)
Oh, no, you... No.
But it's... just like a hotel...
on the water.
I just figured
you need a vacation
from running everyone else's
vacation.
You've barely been
out of the hotel since...
Well, since Mom died.
But this is a chance
to make new memories,
with all of us.
With Dennis.
- Boat!
Who made you
such an amazing daughter?
You.
(CHUCKLES) That's right!
What a father I am.
Come on, Denisovich,
let's get cruising!
- DENNIS: Yay!
- (DRACULA CHUCKLES)
(WITCHES CACKLING)
(WHOOPING, CACKLING)
- DENNIS: Wow!
- (ALL GASPS)
(HORN BLOWING)
(FAINT CHEERING)
(PUPPIES CRYING AND GROWLING)
Okay. Smile.
- (CRYING RESUMES)
- Thank you.
(CACKLING)
Ow!
DENNIS: "No pets allowed"?
Uh-oh.
Perfect.
(GROANS)
FISH MAN: Welcome aboard.
How are you doing?
- Dennis, come on.
- FISH MAN: Nice to see you.
Oh, lovely shirt. Yes.
Oh, hello. Welcome aboard.
Uh, this is Bob.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Say hi, Bob.
"Hi, Bob."
Oh, my gosh, Griffin.
I'm, like, so excited.
This is, like, the nicest hotel
I've ever been to.
GRIFFIN: Yeah! (CHUCKLES)
Man, this is amazing!
There's so much to do!
Olympic-size swimming pool...
All-you-can-eat buffet?!
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
Full-service Spa?!
Whoo! I'm gonna get me
a seaweed rewrap!
Wow, it sounds like
everything we can do
at our hotel!
Except on the water!
(MURRAY CACKLING)
- (FIREWORKS EXPLODING)
- (SHRIEKING)
- (CROWD GASPING)
- (WHINING)
(CROWD GASPING)
ALL: Ooh! Ah!
- (GIGGLING)
- Wow!
You nailed it, honey.
Your dad
is going to love this!
Best summer vacation ever!
Wait till you see
the itinerary.
- (FIREWORK EXPLODES)
- Oh!
That's nice.
Frank, "Fire bad." Remember?
Oh, yeah, right, but, uh...
maybe you'll find
your own fireworks
on the cruise, huh?
It's not the Love Boat, Frank.
I'm just here to have fun
with my family.
- (GRUNTING)
- DRACULA: Huh?
Ha!
Ahoy there!
Welcome aboard!
(GREETS IN SPANISH)
(GREETS IN GERMAN)
(GREETS IN RUSSIAN)
(GREETS IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(PURRS)
(DEEP GROWL)
Whoa! Who is that?
I am Captain Ericka.
And, yes, I'm human.
But don't hold that against me.
I could not be more excited
to have all of you on-board
our first-ever monster cruise!
(ALL CHEERING)
(RAPID HEARTBEAT)
Whoo-hoo! (CHUCKLES)
Dad? Are you okay?
Eeny feeny fanny foonyah
wah wah?
Oh, no! He's having
a heart attack!
Drac? Not likely.
Yeah, the only heart attack that can
hurt him is with a wooden stake.
It must be a stroke!
Actually,
I think it might be her.
Ow! Watch where you're pointing,
mister, I'm right here.
You always stand
so close to me.
It's creepy.
For so long, monsters were hiding,
living in the shadows,
but not anymore!
You've stood up and waved your hand
or claw or tentacle
and said, "We're here, we're hairy,
and it is our right to be scary!"
(ALL CHEERING)
Now it's time to celebrate!
You'll enjoy gourmet dining,
thrilling adventures,
and nonstop entertainment,
all on the way
to our final destination,
the lost city
that isn't lost anymore,
Atlantis!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Oh, yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
The fish are acrobats!
They're fishcrobats!
- (JONATHAN GRUNTING)
- (MAVIS CHUCKLES)
Hello. How y'all doing?
- (♫ SULTRY MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
- So...
You must be
the one and only Dracula.
I have waited
so long to meet you.
Wow, you really don't age,
do you?
I would kill for your skin.
(CHUCKLES) Eh doobeeday
shoolah eh koobeeday?
Oh. You're speaking
Transylvanian.
Oh. Always wanted to learn.
Uh, eh doobeeday
shoolah koobeeday?
- Eh koobeeday.
- Koobeeday.
Eh doobeeday
shoolah koobeeday.
Doolah-day shoolah koobeeday.
Oh, such a romantic language.
You know, there's just
something about an accent
that makes a man
sound so intelligent.
- Alibooboo.
- (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
That's Transylvanian
right there.
He's saying it's...
"It's nice to meet you".
(CHUCKLES) Well, then
"alibooboo" to you as well.
- Alibooboo. Alibooboo.
- Drac! Drac, snap out of it.
Wait, wait. I've always wanted
to do this.
Wake up! Wake up, Drac!
(SLAPPING)
Snap out of it!
Hey, cut it out!
Hey, buddy, you okay?
No, not okay.
Not okay!
(STAMMERS) I... I...
I...
Zinged.
- (♫ PARTY MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
- (LIVELY CHATTER)
(♫ PLAYING "DOWNTOWN" ♫)
(♫ SPOKEN SINGING ♫) ♫ I went to the
moped store, I said, "Sell it" ♫
♫ Salesman's like, "What up?
What's your budget?" ♫
♫ And I'm like, "Honestly,
I don't know nothin' about mopeds" ♫
♫ He said, "I got the one
for you, follow me" ♫
♫ Ooh, it's too real ♫
♫ A chromed-out mirror,
I don't need a windshield ♫
(♫ VLAD SCATTING JAUNTY TUNE ♫)
Mmm!
VLAD:
♫ It's a lovely day ♫
- Ooh!
- Oh!
Check that out!
VLAD: Ah! (CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) Here we go.
- Mmm, yummy.
- (GROWLS)
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
WITCH: Ah!
WOMAN:
♫ Auf Wiedersehen ♫
♫ Danke schoen ♫
(MUFFLED GROANING)
(GASPS)
(RETCHES)
Papa.
- (BARKING, CRYING)
- (GASPING)
(PUPPIES WAILING)
"Kids Club."
What's a kids club?
(MONSTER BABY BELCHES)
(GRUNTS, GIGGLES)
Whee!
- Fish.
- That's right, dear.
I'm still not sure I understand.
You take my kids,
all day, on purpose?
Fish.
That's right.
What exactly
don't you understand?
- Why? Ow!
- Shh.
So they can have a great time,
and you can have a great time.
- (SNIFFLES)
- Fish.
Oh, don't worry, you'll get them back
at the end of the day.
Fish.
Oh, well. That's better than nothing.
(WHISTLES)
Oh. Oh!
- So...
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
What do we do now?
I think... I think we do
whatever we want.
"Whatever we want"?
Whatever we want.
Whatever we want!
BOTH: (CHANTING)
Whatever we want.
- Stop! Help me!
- Whatever we want.
Oh, hi. Hello.
How y'all doin'?
- Oh. (CHUCKLING)
- Good evening, Captain.
Oh, well, hello. Oh, my goodness.
Ah! (CHUCKLES)
Would you mind uh... lifting, uh...
lifting your tail? You know...
Oh! Certainly.
Okay. Thank you so much.
Oh, hello.
Welcome aboard.
Ugh! You were so right,
Great-Grandfather.
Monsters are disgusting!
VAN HELSING: They're animals!
(CHUGGING, SQUEAKING)
I'll be right there.
(PANTS, GROANS)
(SQUEAKING, SPUTTERING)
Dracula, is he on-board?
Yes. I saw him.
Face-to-face. Ugh!
I was so nice to him.
That pale face of his
and his goofy smile,
showing off his fangs.
Argh, it's just like
you taught me!
It's even worse than I feared!
It was that fateful night
that I realized
a human could never defeat
a monster.
(SCREAMING)
But I wouldn't let
our family legacy die.
And so, I began to search
for an answer.
And I saw it in an ancient text,
an instrument of destruction
so powerful
it destroyed Atlantis,
a whole city of monsters.
(CHUCKLES)
And there, deep within the rubble,
it lay, waiting.
Endlessly,
I searched for the lost city
Time passed,
and my body began to fail me.
Oh, it was so sad, Ericka.
First my liver, then my spleen,
followed by a kidney or two.
Then my golden locks.
(MOANS)
But I wouldn't let that stop me.
I replaced my failing organs
with technology!
Ha-ha!
And look at me now.
Mmm-hmm!
Oh, girl,
it's an improvement, really.
Um... sure.
And now, after 120 years,
I have finally found Atlantis.
Oh, forget about all this!
Let me get rid
of Dracula right now.
I was so close to him,
I could've just...
(GRUNTING)
No, no, no!
We have to stick to the plan.
Lure the monsters to Atlantis,
retrieve the instrument
of destruction,
trap them there,
and then wipe them out.
It's simple, Ericka!
Now, promise me
you won't try and kill Dracula.
Ugh, fine!
- I promise.
- Promise what?
(GROANS) I promise I won't try
and kill Dracula. Okay?
(SNORING)
Ugh.
Don't worry, Great-Grandfather,
I won't try and kill him...
I will kill him.
♫ Tonight... ♫
♫ I just want
to take you higher ♫
♫ Put yo' pinky rings up
to the moon ♫
- ♫ Girls ♫
- ♫ What y'all tryin' to do? ♫
♫ 24-karat magic in the air ♫
♫ Head-to-toe ♫
Whew!
♫ Uh, look out ♫
(EVIL CHUCKLE)
- ♫ Pop, pop, it's showtime ♫
- ♫ Showtime ♫
♫ Guess who's back again ♫
- ♫ Oh, they don't know? ♫
- ♫ Go on, tell 'em ♫
♫ I'll bet they know
as soon as we walk in ♫
- ♫ Sho' 'nuff ♫
- ♫ I'm wearin' Cuban links ♫
- ♫ Designer'minks ♫
- ♫ Yeah ♫
(BABBLING)
♫ Don't look too hard,
might hurt yourself ♫
♫ Known to give the color red
The blues ♫
(GRUNTS)
♫ Tell me whatcha tryin'
to do ♫
♫ 24-karat magic in the air ♫
(CHUCKLING)
Ugh! Darn it.
♫ Moon ♫
- ♫ Girls ♫
- ♫ What y'all tryin' to do? ♫
(LAUGHS)
Oh!
(WHIMPERS)
(RAPID, HIGH-PITCHED GRUNTING)
- ♫ Girls ♫
- ♫ What y'all tryin' to do? ♫
♫ 24-karat... ♫
(SONG PAUSES)
♫ Put yo' pinky rings
up to the moon ♫
(GRUNTS)
Work it, Dracula.
You know it.
Oh! Lookin' good, Drac!
Feeling good, Frank.
Look at you, so fancy!
What? This? Please.
Ooh! Dressed to impress, huh?
"Impress"? Oh.
Who do I need to impress?
Hey, isn't that Captain Ericka?
Oh, no! (STAMMERS)
Uh, what? Eh, oh...
GRIFFIN: Oops, no, not her.
(ALL CACKLES)
- Ooh, that's good!
- (DRACULA CHUCKLES)
Very amusing.
(CHUCKLES WEAKLY)
(SIGHS)
Sorry, Drac. You know, it's just...
we've never seen you like this.
I know, I know.
It doesn't make any sense.
You can't Zing twice,
it's impossible!
But I did! So now what?
(GASPS) And what about Mavis?
She wants you to be happy, right?
I'm sure she'll go
with the flow.
Oh, no, no, no!
Mavis needs me.
She depends on me.
I need to be home
with my family.
Hey, Murray here may be from Egypt,
but you're the one in
"da Nile."
(LAUGHS)
You guys get that?
- (THUDS)
- Ow! You hit me right in the...
Mavis!
Don't say a word,
or I'll haunt your dreams.
Having fun?
Oh, I'm having even more fun
now that you're here.
You know, Dad, I feel really lucky
to have this time with you.
All of us together,
it's really special.
Me, too, spider-monkey.
Now, are you ready for me to
destroy you in monster ball?
- Whoo-hoo! Monster ball!
- (GIGGLES)
Come on, Papa Drac!
(CHUCKLES) Bring it on!
For I am king of family fun!
Ha-ha! All right!
Who is ready to get pummeled?
(WHIMPERING)
I got to warn you,
I played second-team co-ed
intramural volleyball at Santa Cruz.
- (MAVIS CHUCKLES)
- Sure, pal. Whatever you say.
Everybody, just please
watch the hair.
Watch the hair!
Oh-ho-ho! Let's go!
Let's do this!
Oh, my gosh,
this is gonna be so much fun.
MURRAY: Ha-ha! Get ready.
Here comes the pain!
(SCREAMING)
- Spike!
- Not the hair! Not the hair!
- Whoa!
- (WHIMPERS)
No, no, no!
(LAUGHS)
- (ALL CHEERING)
- All right!
FISH MAN: (OVER P.A.)
Captain Ericka, you are needed on deck.
Next stop...
Buh-bye, Dracula.
Ha-ha! All right, baby!
(DEEP SNARL)
(SCREAMING)
(BABBLING)
(DISTORTED BABBLING)
(ELECTRONIC FEEDBACK)
(DISTORTED GRUNT)
Oh, baby, I got this.
Hey there, monsters.
Huh?
Yeah! What'd I say!
ERICKA: We're arriving
at our first destination.
(RUMBLING)
The underwater volcano!
Everyone, grab your scuba gear
and get ready to explore
the wonders of the sea.
Especially you,
Count Dracula.
(CHUCKLES)
You see that, pal?
She likes you.
Oh, no, no, no.
That sounds like a Zing
in full effect.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I'm just here to have family fun.
Family, family, fun, fun.
(HISSING, BUBBLING)
Hmm, let's see.
What about here?
- (HISSING)
- (YELLING)
(ALL CHEERING, WHOOPING)
Right this way, everyone.
Welcome to one of the true wonders
of the underwater kingdom.
I give you, Volcano del Fuego.
Or, as the local sea life call it...
(POPPING MOUTH)
(PEDALS SQUEAKING)
(MUFFLED YELLING)
(DENNIS GIGGLES)
DENNIS: Whee!
(WHALE SINGING)
(CHUCKLES)
Aw, what a cute family.
What? No, it's not.
Argh! Dracula bad! Dracula bad!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(PEDAL SQUEAKING)
(STOMACH GRUMBLING)
(COUGHING)
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
GRIFFIN: Frank, we just ate.
I can't believe
you're hungry already.
I'm sorry.
You know what it is?
It's all... Just all that seafood
just swimming around,
and when I "see food..."
Oh, man! I'm gone.
Oh! Dracula, Dracula, Dracula!
Dracula, Dracula!
I get so close,
but it's almost like he's teasing me.
I just...
I can't stand it anymore.
I have to get him!
(GRUNTING)
Boy, that underwater volcano
looked hot.
WITCHES: Mmm-hmm.
(ALL GASPS)
Oh... Hi, Bob.
Right. We promised you we'd play,
uh, ping-pong now.
Um, Dennis? Who is this?
Uh, it's our friend, Bob.
- Say hi, Bob.
- "Hi, Bob."
Okay! Time to go play ping-pong.
- FRANKENSTEIN: Drac!
- GRIFFIN: Drac!
- Drac!
Hey, boys, where's the fire?
Oh, well, Griffin here, he...
- He has something to tell you.
- Me? Uh...
Oh. Yeah, I got this bite
on my hand, and since, you know,
you're a biting expert,
I thought you could take a look.
- Yeah. Come on over here.
- The light is better.
Okay...
Okay, what is going on?
You guys are acting weirder than normal,
and your normal is pretty weird.
You are not gonna believe
what we heard, but...
(♫ VOCALIZING ♫)
♫ Ericka loves the Drac ♫
♫ She can't get enough
of that Drac ♫
♫ Oh, yeah ♫
♫ Drac is back ♫
♫ He's got the Zing ♫
♫ The Zinga-Zing ♫
Shh. I told you
I don't want to upset Mavis.
- But what are you talking about?
- (CROWD GASPS)
Okay, well, see, Frank got hungry,
so no surprise there...
But we swam back to the ship,
and we found Ericka raving about you.
She can't live without you, buddy.
It's serious!
♫ You can't deny
the Zing, baby ♫
So, Drac, this is great. Now, are you gonna
make a move on the captain, or what?
Uh, yes.
- Maybe? No, no.
- Ugh.
It's been a while.
I don't even know where to start.
It's easy, Drac.
Just make some small talk.
- And remember to smile.
- Look into her eyes.
- Keep it casual.
- Say something funny.
Ask her where her parts are from.
Oh, and say
that her wrappings look nice.
- "Do you like coffins?"
- Compliment her.
- "Your neck looks delicious."
- GRIFFIN: Here she comes.
Okay, Drac, hit it.
Your delicious neck wrappings
are in a nice coffin.
Would you like to see my parts?
(IMITATES MISSILE WHISTLING
AND EXPLODING)
Yes, I'd love to go out
with you.
Ay! What?
ALL: What?
Cantina. Midnight.
Don't be late.
Phew!
- That was a close one.
- (PANTING)
(SNORTS, SNIFFING)
- Wait! Stop it, Tinkles, stop!
- Wait, Tinkles. Come back.
- DENNIS: Tinkles, stop!
- Wait!
No, no, no!
(THUDS)
(GASPS)
(GROWLING, BARKING)
Tinkles, stop!
(GASPING) I've been found!
You'll never get me, monster!
DENNIS: Shh! Tinkles, stop.
Shh! Shh!
(YAPPING)
(YAPPING FADES IN DISTANCE)
Ew.
FISH MAN: Everybody, we are pulling up
to our next stop, the Deserted Island.
It's time to get lost
on the beach,
and we hope you'll find yourself
some fun and relaxation.
JONATHAN:
Whoo-hoo! Beach time!
Johnny, you go set everything up.
And, Dad, you go get in line
for the snow cones.
You know, actually,
I was thinking you and Johnny
should spend some time together.
What do you call it again?
Eh... date night?
Date night?
- What are you gonna do?
- Well, I thought
me and the guys
would take this opportunity
to spend some quality time
with Dennis.
Oh. Okay.
That's a great idea.
Come on, Johnny. Date night.
Duh-duh-duh-duh-date night!
(EXCITED SQUEAKING)
(SATISFIED SQUEAK)
Okay, here you go!
(PANTING)
- Good girl!
- I got this one.
(BARKING)
- (RETCHES)
- (YAPPING IN DISTANCE)
What was that?
- (RUMBLING)
- It sounds like our children.
- It is our children! Run!
- Run!
Please! Help! Someone!
Get the parents!
Frank? Would you rub
some moon-screen on my back
before I get burned?
Wait one second, honey.
You know, the kids buried me
in the sand.
(KIDS GIGGLING)
Mmm. Thanks, honey.
- Shall we have another?
- Sure.
- Sounds good.
- Straight up.
Isn't this place amazing?
Whoa! The menu is in a bottle!
Genius! Isn't that awesome, honey?
What? Oh, sorry.
I was just thinking
about my dad.
Don't you think
he's acting weird lately?
Not really. Besides having
a huge crush on the captain.
- What?
- (CHUCKLES) Oh, yeah.
The Love Boat is definitely
making another run.
No way. He's...
He's my dad.
I know, right? It's weird.
When my parents kiss,
I still close my eyes.
I guess I never thought about him
with anyone besides my mom.
You're cool with it,
though, right?
Of course. I want him
to be happy.
Totally.
(♫ PLAYING MARIACHI MUSIC ♫)
Good evening, my friend.
Have you a beverage
to quench me of my parchment?
Yes, of course,
Mr. Chupacabra.
(GOAT BLEATS)
Thank you very much.
(CHUCKLES)
(GOAT SCREECHES)
You look ravishing.
Oh.
Uh, thank you. I just...
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
(EXCLAIMS)
So, um...
Does Captain Ericka
have a last name?
Uh, oh, uh...
Oh, guacamole!
"Ericka Guacamole"?
That's so... international.
(CHUCKLES)
No. Guacamole for us to share.
Oh, how beautiful
is that full moon tonight?
Look. Right behind you.
Mmm! The food here
is to die for.
(BOTH MOANING)
Holy moly,
that was a lot of guacamole.
Are you feeling all right?
- Totally fine. Why?
- No reason.
(STOMACH GROWLING)
Oh...
There must have been garlic
in the guacamole.
- Oh, no.
- (GROANS)
Isn't that deadly for you?
No, no, no.
It's just that I'm...
Garlic intolerant.
(FARTS)
(CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
Was that you?
(GIGGLING) Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
Dolphin surfing!
(DOLPHIN CLICKING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Whoa!
Hi, Mama. Hi, Papa.
Hey-hey.
- Oh! Hey there.
- (GRUNTS)
- Papa.
- Hidey-ho!
Hi.
(CHUCKLES)
Is my dad in there, too?
(MONSTERS GASPS)
GRIFFIN: (AS DRACULA)
Don't worry, I'm over here. Blah, blah-blah.
(GIGGLES) No, Papa Drac's not here.
He's on his date.
Date?
Please, forgive me, I...
I'm just very nervous.
You see,
I haven't had a date since...
my wife died.
How old was your daughter?
She was just an infant.
It was hard being a single dad,
but I... I did my best.
I never knew my mother, either.
Or my father.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Who raised you?
My great-grandfather.
I basically grew up on this ship.
That's why you're a captain.
Yeah. It's all I've ever known.
It was just expected.
You know, a family thing.
I understand,
family is everything.
You have to honor the past.
But we make our own future.
- MAVIS: Dad?
- Mavis!
- JONATHAN: (CRUNCHES) Mmm.
- Johnny!
Captain Ericka and I were just...
discussing the hospitality industry.
You know, just work stuff.
You're working now?
This is supposed to be a vacation.
A family vacation.
I should really go...
do captain-y things.
Dad, you said you were gonna
spend time with Dennis.
Dennis. Dennis? Dennis.
Oh! Yeah, you're right.
Where is that kid?
Denisovich?
You're supposed to be with me.
Come on now, kid, it's family time.
Quit hiding. Dennis?
What was that about?
You mean your dad's date?
It wasn't a date.
It was... work stuff.
Uh-huh.
I'm telling you, Johnny,
there is something
about that woman I don't trust.
But you want your dad
to be happy, right?
Yes. Just...
Just not with her.
(CRUNCHING)
Mmm. Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Heads up, honey.
This guac is loaded
with garlic.
Garlic?
(GASPS)
(STOMACH GRUMBLES)
(SQUEAKY FART)
Aww! That was a cute toot, honey.
(LAUGHING AND BARKING)
- We've been up all night!
- Let's stay up all day, too!
- Let's get wild!
- (LAUGHS)
(BOTH HOWLING)
(LAUGHING AND BARKING)
- Ericka!
- (SHRIEKS) What?
- (SIGHS)
- Just where have you been, young lady?
Uh... doing work.
Wearing that?
You were with him! I know it!
Who? (CHUCKLES)
"Who?" You know who!
You've been sneaking around
my back
trying to kill Dracula again,
haven't you?
So what if I have?
I am a grown woman!
I have the right to kill
whoever I want.
It's not just about you.
You could have ruined
the legacy.
What if he discovered
who you were?
I know. I wasn't thinking.
There's just something about him
that just drives me crazy!
I just, I see him,
and I want to...
Punch him?
Uh... I guess.
Just, I can't wait
to get this over with.
Don't worry,
it won't be long now.
Once you recover the instrument
of destruction,
no one can stop us.
Not even Dracula!
- Oh. Excuse me.
- Spies!
(GRUNTS)
Now, quickly,
before someone comes!
- (GASPS)
- (GRUNTING)
(VAN HELSING YELPS)
(HORN BLOWING)
(P.A. CHIMES)
FISH MAN:
Everyone assemble on the forward deck.
We are arriving
at our final destination.
From the depths of creation,
the mighty city has risen
once again.
Home to the greatest
monster civilization
the world has ever known,
far surpassing Athens and Rome
in art, culture and sophistication.
I give you the legendary
lost city of... Atlantis.
(PASSENGERS GASPS)
(YELLS) It's a giant Kraken!
♫ There's a place
you've gotta be ♫
♫ A thousand leagues
beneath the sea ♫
♫ And it's waiting over here
for you and me ♫
(CAMERA CLICKS)
♫ Gonna take you for a ride ♫
♫ But first
you've gotta come inside ♫
♫ Get ready,
for the party's on tonight ♫
♫ So relax and just unwind ♫
♫ Leave your worries
all behind ♫
♫ And get ready,
for the party's on tonight ♫
Welcome to Atlantis!
THE KRAKEN:
♫ So get ready ♫
♫ Ready ♫
Oh!
♫ It's party time ♫
(BURBLING)
(BURBLES)
♫ It's party time! ♫
Ooh. I am so excited!
(CHUCKLES)
MONSTER: Come to Daddy!
(ALL CHEERING)
- Oh.
- FISH MAN: Twenty-eight black!
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh!
- Ahhh!
- Oh, no, you don't.
Last time you gambled,
you lost an arm and a leg. Literally!
- Replacement limbs...
- MONSTER: I'll raise you 40.
...aren't just lying around
like they were in the old days.
So, no gambling.
Frank!
Yes, dear! Got it!
No gambling!
- DENNIS: Tinkles, stop.
- Wait.
- Stop it, Tinkles, stop.
- Ah! Wait!
(MONSTERS SCREAMING)
Have you guys seen Mavis?
I have to find her.
Why? What's going on?
I'm going to tell her
about Ericka.
I can't lie
to my own daughter anymore.
She's the most important person
in the world to me.
I have to tell her the truth.
Right after I talk to Ericka.
(FRANKENSTEIN SNICKERING)
Hey.
All right, I'm all...
Frank, are you sure
you know what you're doing?
I got this. I'm all in.
Johnny, have you seen
my dad?
- Maybe he's with Bob.
- Why would he be with Bob?
Bob's a great guy.
- Oh, there he is.
- Who? Bob?
There he is! Hi, Bob!
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(YELPS)
(GRUNTING)
Oh.
(SNARLING)
(RAT SQUEAKS)
(GASPS)
There it is.
You saved my life.
Of course. Why wouldn't I?
I just... can't believe
you would do that for a human.
Humans, monsters,
what's the difference?
Yeah, right. Right.
Wait. What are you doing here?
Oh, uh... Well, you know,
vampires can predict the future,
so I knew you would
need my help.
Ha! Never heard that before.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a well-known fact.
(STAMMERS)
What are you doing here?
Oh! Uh...
Well, I'm here to get that.
Yeah, it's a family heirloom.
Yeah, it was lost at sea,
and my great-grandfather is... Was!
Uh, was totally obsessed
with getting it back.
So, anywho, thanks for saving my life,
but I can take it from...
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Got to be a little more careful.
How many times
can you save my life, right?
I don't know. Every time?
(CHUCKLES)
Really? Well, then...
(♫ TANGO MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
(CRASHING)
(GASPS)
Wow!
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
Ah, that was incredible.
Oh, uh...
Don't you want to get
your family heirloom thingy?
Oh. Right.
(CHUCKLES) Got it.
(RUMBLING)
(BOTH PANTING)
- Mmm.
- (CHUCKLING)
Oh, here, let me get that for you.
(DRACULA AND ERICKA CHUCKLING)
Dad!
Mavis!
What are you doing to my father?
ERICKA: Wait! Whoa. Whoa!
Mavis, stop! Put her down!
No! She's trying to hurt you.
Why can't you see that?
(GROANING)
Because I...
Because I Zinged.
- (ERICKA GRUNTS)
- What?
I Zinged... with Ericka.
No, that can't be true.
You only Zing once.
That's what I thought, too.
"Zing"? What's a Zing?
Uh, well, it's a thing
for monsters.
It's kind of like our
"love at first sight."
What? No. No, no, no.
- You don't even know me.
- Well, not yet.
- But we're just...
- No, you don't understand.
I can't be with you.
I could never be
with someone like you.
I could never be with
a monster.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
- I...
- It doesn't matter.
You heard what she said.
But a Zing never lies.
Ha! You got it! (CHUCKLES)
Yes.
(LAUGHING)
Now that we have
the instrument of destruction,
our family legacy will be
fulfilled.
But first, we'll draw them in
with a dance party!
I love to dance.
- (♫ OLD-TIMEY MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
- (LAUGHING)
EUNICE:
Frank, could you zip me up?
We're gonna be late. (GASPS)
Where did you get those?
Uh, see, (STAMMERS)
here's the funny thing.
I lost my hands gambling, but...
It's no big deal!
Look, I got these
from the seafood buffet.
Look at this. Clickety-click,
click, clack, clack, click, click.
I kind of like 'em.
I like 'em.
Mmm! Mmm! Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm.
A-ha!
(GASPS)
(SOBS, SQUEALING)
(SQUEAKING)
(BOTH SQUEAKING EXCITEDLY)
Ah, I guess the party's this way.
Whoo!
Whoa!
(EXCITED CHATTER)
(GASPS)
Wow.
Let's get this party started right!
- Whoo-hoo!
- All right!
- (ALL GASPS)
- MONSTER: What?
EUNICE: Huh?
I thought they said
the party was this way.
(♫ ELECTRONIC DANCE MUSIC
PLAYING IN DISTANCE ♫)
(♫ MUSIC GROWING LOUDER ♫)
DJ in a clamshell?
(GASPS) I'm so jealous.
- (♫ DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES ♫)
- (RUMBLING)
(SPOTLIGHTS WHOOSHING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL WHOOPING)
(♫ DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES ♫)
(WHOOPING)
(CRYSTAL AND GRIFFIN LAUGHING,
WHOOPING)
I can't believe my dad Zinged
with someone who's trying to kill him.
Yeah, the Zing makes you do
crazy things.
Really, Johnny?
What's most important to understand
is that love is an infinite enigma
that is beyond our understanding.
You and I were two halves,
a world apart.
But then we followed the strands
of destiny
and were brought together.
And our halves made one whole.
But what if she and he...
You must release all the negativity
and look within.
Your bond is unbreakable.
You're right, honey. Wow.
Thanks.
Whoa, you sounded pretty smart, Dad.
Oh, that? Yeah, it was just
the philosophy
of Sifu Sing from my favorite
TV show when I was a kid,
Kung Fu Shaolin Monk Master.
Anyways,
let's get back to dancing!
Cool.
Dad? You have to talk
to Ericka.
- What?
- I know.
I know what I said before,
but maybe I overreacted
a teensy bit.
It's just the thought
of losing you.
What? What are you
talking about, losing me?
Well, obviously,
after you get married,
you're gonna live on the ship
and travel around the world...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down, Mavis.
There are two things
I can promise you.
One, nothing can ever take me
from you and all my family.
Two, I will never live
on a boat.
You're my cute little tarantula.
How could I ever leave you?
Now, seriously, go talk to her.
I can't.
You heard what she said,
she could never be
with someone like me.
No, Dad.
You're just a half,
and you have to follow your destiny
to find an infinite whole.
You sound like Johnny.
Point is,
you can't deny a Zing.
Monster, human, unicorn...
It doesn't matter.
So go to her! Now!
Okay. I'm on it.
(MUSIC STOPS)
DJ: Hey, man,
you're not allowed up here.
The DJ booth is a sacred space.
(SCREAMS)
- (THUDS)
- (DJ GROANS)
(ALL GASPS)
(GROWLS, BARKING)
No. Tinkles, quiet.
Who is this?
Ha! I know you recognize me,
your greatest rival.
Hmm. Oh, right.
You own that Holiday Inn
down by the airport.
No! It is I,
Abraham Van Helsing.
Van Helsing?
After all these years?
You look... awful.
Always with the quick insults.
Well, this will shut you up.
And all monsters.
Eh, huh? That's just Ericka's
family heirloom thingy.
(EVIL CHUCKLE)
Good one, Ericka.
Ericka?
You fool.
Not only is she
the ship's captain,
but she also happens
to be...
(SNICKERING)
Wait. You tell him.
I'm his great-granddaughter.
I'm Ericka Van Helsing.
(GASPS) I knew there was
something wrong with her.
But...
(STAMMERS)
See, what happened...
Now that we're all caught up,
let's get back to the dying.
Behold, the key to the demise
of all monsters.
(ALL GASPS)
(SCREAMS HYSTERICALLY)
(CRACKS KNUCKLES)
(GROANS)
Let's see.
Right... Okay.
(♫ PLAYING ELECTRONIC,
SYNCOPATED RIFF ♫)
Listen to the melody
of your destruction.
Ooh, what's this little
doodad do?
(♫ TURNS UP BASS ♫)
Yeah!
(♫ SYNCOPATED RIFF CONTINUES
IN DISTANCE ♫)
(EYES MATCHING
SYNCOPATED RHYTHM)
(DEEP RUMBLING)
Hey, look! It's the Kraken.
(ROARS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
- (♫ RESUMES SYNCOPATED RIFF ♫)
- (BABBLING ROAR)
Everybody out! Now!
We're trapped! Everybody back!
(PANICKED SCREAMS)
(BABBLING GROWL)
- (GRIFFIN GASPS)
- (YELLS)
(GROWLING)
(CACKLES)
(WINNIE SCREAMS)
- (TINKLES GROWLING)
- BOTH: Yay!
(ALL WHIMPERING)
Baby!
Papa!
(SQUEAKY GRUNTING)
This has to stop now!
Drac, no!
Ah!
(YELLS)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
Dad!
(GRUNTS)
Mavis!
Time for the immortal Dracula
to die.
(♫ PLAYING DRAMATIC
ORCHESTRAL MUSIC ♫)
Dad!
(STRAINED YELLING)
No!
Ericka!
(GRUNTING)
Bob! Help!
Huh?
Tinkles?
Dennis.
Oh, no.
Bob is Tinkles?
How did he get here?
But thank goodness he did,
'cause look!
(THE KRAKEN GROWLING)
(BELLOWING)
You can't do this!
You're wrong about monsters!
Dracula... He saved my life.
What?
I'm so sorry, Drac.
I was trying to kill you
this whole time,
but then I realized
how wrong I was.
How wrong all of this is.
And then I...
I Zinged.
"Zing"? What's a Zing?
It's a monster thing.
You wouldn't understand.
It's like true love.
Love?
(GROWLING)
Well, I guess the legacy
ends with me.
Hmm, that's an awkward ending.
(CHUCKLES)
ERICKA: Nope!
It's time to start
a new legacy.
A monster-human legacy.
No!
(♫ PLAYING POUNDING DANCE BEAT ♫)
Drac! Van Helsing's beats are controlling
the giant octopus thingy.
If there's one thing I hate,
it's an evil DJ.
We need positive energy!
Get ready for a DJ battle!
You just carry all that stuff
around with you?
Once a bar mitzvah DJ,
always a bar mitzvah DJ.
We're gonna use good music
to defeat his evil music.
- What?
- Trust me, I know the tunes,
but you've got the power.
All right. Okay.
Opening song needs to be
off the shizak.
Ooh, got it. Play this!
(GIGGLES)
(♫ "GOOD VIBRATIONS" PLAYING ♫)
♫ I'm picking up
good vibrations ♫
(WHOOPING)
♫ She's giving me excitations ♫
- ♫ Good ♫
- ♫ I'm picking up ♫
♫ Good vibrations ♫
♫ She's giving me ♫
♫ Excitations ♫
♫ Good, good, good ♫
- ♫ Good vibrations ♫
- (ALL CHEERING)
♫ She's giving me... ♫
What is that noise?
♫ I'm picking up
good vibrations ♫
♫ She's giving me
excitations ♫
Wow! I like this one.
This feels good.
- ♫ Good vibrations ♫
- (LAUGHING)
The fool.
- (♫ "GOOD VIBRATIONS" FADES ♫)
- (♫ PLAYING POUNDING DANCE BEAT ♫)
- (BABBLING)
- (ALL SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Whoa! His music is too powerful!
We're gonna need something
even more positive.
Now, Drac!
(♫ "DON'T WORRY, BE HAPPY"
PLAYING ♫)
♫ So don't worry ♫
♫ Be happy ♫
♫ Don't worry ♫
- Really?
- It has a nice message.
♫ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh ♫
♫ Don't worry ♫
♫ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh ♫
♫ Be happy ♫
♫ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh... ♫
I've had enough of this nonsense!
(♫ PLAYING POUNDING,
SYNCOPATED RIFF ♫)
(LOW GROWL)
(RUMBLING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(♫ SYNCOPATED RIFF CONTINUES ♫)
(GROWLING)
Johnny, we need the most
brain-dominating,
toe-tappinating song
in the history of all the universe.
(GROWLING)
JONATHAN:
Come on. Where is it?
I don't know!
There's too many choices.
(♫ ELECTRONIC,
SYNCOPATED RIFF CONTINUES ♫)
No, wait!
This... is... it.
(SYNCOPATED RIFF STOPS)
(♫ "MACARENA"
PLAYING FAINTLY ♫)
What the...
(♫ MUSIC GROWING LOUDER ♫)
Boy, that stinks.
It's working!
(♫ "MACARENA" CONTINUES ♫)
Hey, Johnny's corny music
is defeating the evil music.
I kind of like it.
WITCHES: Ooh!
(♫ VLAD SINGS ALONG ♫)
(SCREAMS)
- (♫ "MACARENA" CONTINUES ♫)
- (♫ PLAYING SYNCOPATED RIFF ♫)
(♫ "MACARENA" DROWNING OUT
SYNCOPATED RIFF ♫)
(♫ DANCING TO THE TUNE
OF "MACARENA" ♫)
No!
- (♫ "MACARENA" BEAT CONTINUES ♫)
- (HAPPY SHOUTS)
Argh! Ahhh! Whoo!
I'm a slave to the rhythm!
(♫ SCREAMING ALONG TO "MACARENA" ♫)
(SONG STOPS)
No!
Drac, what are you doing?
You got to be greater
than the haters!
(SCREAMING)
- (WINGS FLAPPING)
- Huh?
Why?
Why, after everything,
would you save my life?
Because basically
we are all the same.
Claws or hands, two eyes
or three eyes.
- Green skin.
- No skin.
- Prickly.
- Brainy.
(BARKS)
(STAMMERS SOFTLY)
I'm sorry.
(MUFFLED YELLING)
Ew. (EXHALES)
You are amazing.
Look at me, Dennis.
Look at me.
Come on,
you can't deny it.
No! I'm too young to Zing!
Well, I feel kind of silly now.
Heh. For decades
I have hunted your kind,
persecuted you.
(DISGRUNTLED CHATTER)
The only thing I can do
to make it up to you is
give you, eh...
(STAMMERS)
a 30% refund.
- (ANGRY CHATTER)
- Preposterous!
Oh, all right.
Full refund.
(ALL CHEERING)
(TIRED GROANS AND CHATTER)
(PANTING)
(SCREECHING)
(SNIFFING)
- (GROWLING)
- (HIGH-PITCHED YIPPING)
(TINKLES YIPPING)
(PUPPIES BARKING)
GRIFFIN: Wayne, Wanda,
what happened to you guys?
CRYSTAL: Yeah, we, like,
hardly saw you on the cruise.
Yeah, I know.
We got tranquilized and spent
most of the trip locked in a closet.
(SIGHS) We're gonna book it again
for the holidays.
Hi. Checking in?
Yes. Thank you.
- Great. I have a room all ready for you.
- (ERICKA AND DRACULA GIGGLING)
Hey, buddy, would you mind?
- Sure thing, pal.
- (ERICKA LAUGHS)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(DRACULA GIGGLING)
(LAUGHING)
Okay, what's going on,
sneaky-pants?
Oh, nothing.
It's just, I wanted to make sure
nobody would bother us.
Oh! Why?
Are you going to suck-a my blood?
Blah, blah-blah.
(CHUCKLES)
No.
I was going to ask you
if you would marry me.
(INQUISITIVE GRUNT)
(GASPS)
Well? What do you say?
Will you marry me?
(STAMMERS) I... I...
Woobee deeba doobee?
Wha...
I mean, I...
woobee doobeedee?
(GROANS)
MONSTERS: What did she say?
Uh... I'm not sure.
Yes!
(GASPS)
Whee!
(CHEERING, WHOOPING)
- ♫ I see love ♫
- (GREMLIN CACKLING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
♫ I see love around me ♫
- (GREMLIN CACKLES)
- ♫ From a river to a flood ♫
♫ I see love around me ♫
♫ Love around me ♫
♫ All of you helped me
find my heart ♫
♫ I didn't even know my name ♫
♫ Then I was blinded
by the dark ♫
♫ My eyes will never
look the same ♫
♫ Come on, let's run
and get lost in the crowd ♫
♫ Into the light
as the night's coming down ♫
♫ I'm double-tapping,
I'm focusing now ♫
♫ We're focusing now ♫
♫ I see love ♫
♫ I see love around me ♫
(CACKLING)
♫ From a river to a flood ♫
- (MUSIC STOPS)
- (CACKLING)
(SCREAMS)
(♫ MUSIC RESUMES ♫)
♫ From a river to a flood ♫
♫ I see love around me ♫
♫ Love around me ♫
♫ Come on, let's run
and get lost in the crowd ♫
♫ Into the light
as the night's coming down ♫
- ♫ I'm double-tapping, I'm focusing now ♫
- Ha-ha!
♫ We're focusing now ♫
(GRIFFIN WHOOPS, LAUGHS)
♫ I see love ♫
(MOTOR WHIRRING)
♫ I see love around me ♫
♫ From a river to a flood ♫
♫ Love around me ♫
♫ I see love ♫
♫ From a river to a flood ♫
- ♫ I see love around me ♫
- (BURPS)
♫ I see love ♫
(♫ "FLOAT" PLAYING ♫)
(GREMLIN CACKLING)
♫ No, I can't be patient ♫
♫ Pullin' up
in this spaceship ♫
♫ Don't need no destination ♫
♫ Baby, come on ♫
♫ Don't need
to complicate this ♫
♫ We're lifting off
of this pavement ♫
♫ I'll take you to that place
where we can vibe on ♫
♫ There ain't nothin'
but a slow ride ♫
♫ So, come on, let's catch
some more vibes ♫
♫ Baby, let me get
by your side ♫
♫ And hold on ♫
♫ Wanna float away with you ♫
♫ Nothing else I'd rather do ♫
♫ You, baby ♫
- ♫ Away, yeah ♫
- (CACKLES)
♫ Away, yeah ♫
♫ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♫
♫ Sun over that ocean ♫
- ♫ Sippin' on that potion ♫
- (CRASHING)
♫ Don't matter where we
rollin', baby, come on ♫
♫ Your love prescription ♫
♫ Is gettin' me so lifted ♫
♫ 'Bout to take this trip
where we can vibe on ♫
♫ There ain't nothin'
but a slow ride ♫
♫ Slow ride ♫
♫ So, come on, let's catch
some more vibes ♫
♫ More vibes ♫
♫ Baby, let me get
by your side ♫
♫ And hold on ♫
♫ Wanna float away with you ♫
- ♫ Wanna float away with you ♫
- (GREMLINS CACKLES)
♫ Nothing else I'd rather do ♫
(WHOOPING)
♫ Wanna float away with you ♫
♫ Float ♫
(♫ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING ♫)