M doesn't mind you earning\Na little money on the side, Dryden.
She'd just prefer it\Nif it wasn't selling secrets.
If the theatrics\Nare supposed to scare me...
...you have the wrong man, Bond.
If M was so sure that I was bent...
...she'd have sent a double-0.
Benefits of being section chief...
...l'd know if anyone had been\Npromoted to double-0 status...
...wouldn't I?
-Your file shows no kills, and it takes--\N-Two.
Shame.
We barely got to know each other.
I know where you keep your gun.
I suppose that's something.
True.
How did he die?
Your contact?
Not well.
Made you feel it, did he?
Well...
...you needn't worry.
The second is--
Yes.
Considerably.
So how do I trust this man\Nthat I've never met with my money?
You asked for the introduction.
That's all my organization\Nwill guarantee.
I suppose our friend\NMr. White will have told you...
...that I have provided\Nreliable banking services...
...for many other\Nfreedom fighters over the years.
Do you believe in God,\NMr. Le Chiffre?
No.
I believe in\Na reasonable rate of return.
I want no risk in the portfolio.
Agreed.
And I can access it\Nanywhere in the world?
Yes.
I have the money,\Nso short another million shares...
...of Skyfleet stock.
Sir, you must know you're betting\Nagainst the market.
No one expects this stock\Nto go anywhere but up.
Just do it.
Looks like our man.\NBurn scars on his face.
I wonder if bomb-makers\Nare insured for things like that.
He's on the move.
He's on the move,\Nand he's heading straight for me.
Stop touching your ear.
-Sorry?\N-Put your hand down.
Holster the bloody weapon, Carter.\NI need him alive.
Weeping blood comes merely\Nfrom a derangement of the tear duct...
...my dear general.
Nothing sinister.
All in.
I have two pair, and you have\Na 17.4 percent chance...
...of making your straight.
When does Ellipsis expire?
-We have less than 36 hours. I can--\N-No. No, no.
That's all the time I have anyway.
Give our guests\Nfive minutes to leave...
...or throw them overboard.
Who the hell do they think they are?
I report to the prime minister,\Neven he's smart enough...
...not to ask me what we do.
Have you ever seen such a bunch\Nof self-righteous, arse-covering prigs?
They don't care what we do, they care\Nwhat we get photographed doing.
And how the hell\Ncould Bond be so stupid?
I give him double-0 status,\Nhe celebrates by shooting an embassy.
Is the man deranged?\NAnd where the hell is he?
In the old days, if an agent\Ndid something embarrassing...
...he'd have the good sense\Nto defect.
Christ, I miss the Cold War.
You've got a bloody cheek.
Sorry.
I'll shoot the camera first next time.
Or yourself.
You stormed into an embassy.
You violated the only\Nabsolutely inviolate rule...
...of international relationships.
And why?\NSo you could kill a nobody.
We wanted to question him,\Nnot kill him.
For God's sake. You're supposed\Nto display some kind of judgment.
I did.
I thought one less bomb-maker\Nin the world would be good.
Exactly. One bomb-maker.
We're trying to find out how an entire\Nnetwork of terrorist groups is financed...
...and you give us one bomb-maker.
Hardly the big picture,\Nwouldn't you say?
The man isn't even a true believer.\NHe's a gun for hire.
And thanks to your trigger finger...
...we have no idea\Nwho hired him or why.
And how the hell\Ndid you find out where I lived?
The same way\NI found out your name.
I thought "M" was randomly assigned.\NI had no idea it stood for--
Utter one more syllable\Nand I'll have you killed.
I knew it was too early\Nto promote you.
Well, I understand double-0s\Nhave a very short life-expectancy...
...so your mistake will be short-lived.
Bond, this may be too much\Nfor a blunt instrument to understand...
...but arrogance and self-awareness\Nseldom go hand in hand.
So you want me to be half monk,\Nhalf hit-man?
Any thug can kill.
I want you to take your ego\Nout of the equation...
...and to judge the situation\Ndispassionately.
I have to know I can trust you,\Nand that you know who to trust.
And since I don't know that,\NI need you out of my sight.
Go and stick your head\Nin the sand somewhere...
...and think about your future.
Because these bastards\Nwant your head.
And I'm seriously considering\Nfeeding you to them.
And Bond...
...don't ever break into\Nmy house again.
Ma'am.
Good day, sir,\Nand welcome to the Ocean Club.
Hey. Hey.
Hello.
Are you going to take this\Nor make me wait?
Certainly, sir. Sorry, sir.
Security to car park.\NSecurity to car park.
Absolutely incredible.
Welcome to the Ocean Club, sir.\NChecking in?
Yes. But it's a spur-of-the-moment\Nthing, and I haven't got a reservation.
Okay.
-We have an ocean-view villa.\N-Perfect.
Could you do me a favor?\NI was here last night...
...and I parked my car next to\Na very beautiful 1964 Aston Martin.
I nicked the door.\NYou wouldn't happen to know--?
-Mr. Dimitrios.\N-Right.
If he hasn't noticed,\NI'm not sure I'd mention it.
Isn't the type\Nto take bad news well.
But if I felt compelled to find him?
He has a house just up the beach.
Thank you.
-What?\N-He's in the Bahamas.
You woke me\Nto share his holiday plans?
Well, he's logged into\Nour secure website...
...using your name and password.
Well, how the hell\Ndoes he know these things?
Well, I'm doing my best to find out.
-Who's he looking at?\N-Alex Dimitrios.
That slimy bugger.
Now known associates....
Le Chiffre.
We've had a good night,\Nwe've had a few drinks.
How can I assist you, sir?
Good evening.\NLarge Mount Gay with soda, please.
-Look what just happened.\N-Good job, big boy.
Yeah.
Do you mind if I join?
-Oh, good evening. How are you?\N-Good evening.
Small blind, big blind.
I'm in.
Bet's to you.
If that was for luck,\Nyou're two hours late.
Two hundred to you.
Bet's to you.
I heard you.
Five to call.
-Action's to you.\N-Pair of sevens.
Ace high.
Check or bet.
-Check.\N-And to you.
Five thousand.
Five to call.
-Check.\N-Check to you, sir.
All in.
No, wait.
Twenty thousand.
Table stakes. I'm sorry, sir.
Okay. This is on the table.\NThat's my car. Wanna bet?
I'm sorry, Mr. Dimitrios.
Please, no. Give him a chance\Nto win his money back.
All right, show me, gentlemen.
Three kings.
There you go with my night.
Trip aces.
Aces win.
Oh, and the valet ticket.
Thank you.
Sir.
-Thank you.\N-Thank you, sir.
No wonder he was\Nin such a foul mood.
My mistake.
Can I give you a lift home?
That would really send him\Nover the edge.
I'm afraid I'm not that cruel.
Well, perhaps you're just\Nout of practice.
Perhaps.
Well, what about\Na drink at my place?
Your place?
-Is it close?\N-Very.
One drink.
Good evening, sir,\Nand welcome back.
Welcome to my home.
I'm having a hard time seeing\Nhow this is my fault.
It's your plan.\NAll I did was get you the man.
A man who was under surveillance\Nby the British Secret Service.
Which makes me wonder\Nif I can trust you at all.
Then don't. I couldn't care less.
But I do care about my reputation.
I have someone else\Nwilling to do the job.
He just needs the particulars...
...and payment.
You like married women,\Ndon't you, James?
It keeps things simple.
What is it about bad men?
You, my husband....
I had so many chances\Nto be happy...
...so many nice guys.
Why can't nice guys\Nbe more like you?
Well, because then they'd be bad.
Yes.
But so much more interesting.
What makes your husband\Na bad man?
His nature, I suppose.
The nature of his work?
A mystery, I'm afraid.
I'm also afraid you will sleep with me\Nin order to get to him.
How afraid?
Not enough to stop.
Can I ask you a personal question?
Now would seem\Nan appropriate time.
Does "ellipsis"\Nmean anything to you?
Should I ask him about it?
Perhaps later.
Yes, dear?
I'm on the last flight\Ntonight to Miami.
Don't wait up.\NI'll be back in the morning.
Okay, I understand.
See you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
Apparently he's on\Nthe last flight to Miami...
...so you have all night\Nto question me.
In that case...
...we're gonna need...
...some more champagne.
Good evening. Room Service.
Good evening. Can I get a bottle\Nof chilled Bollinger Grand Année...
...and the beluga caviar?
-With everything?\N-Yes, with everything.
-And would that be for two, sir?\N-What?
-For two?\N-No, for one.
Wait here.
There you go. Number 53.
Dr. von Hagens' Body Worlds\Ninvites visitors...
...to observe the body's various\Nlocomotive, digestive...
...nervous and vascular systems.
Please may I have your attention,\Nladies and gentlemen?
I believe it is something very special,\Nwhat we see here.
This is edutainment.
--fixed in dramatic\Nand athletic poses...
...that reveal the true-to-life spatial\Nrelationships amongst organs.
Hello.
Do not leave your vehicle unattended.
Welcome to Miami\NInternational Airport.
Curbside parking in front\Nof the terminal is restricted....
-Yes.\N-It's Bond. I need her now.
I'm afraid she can't be disturbed.\NCan I take a message?
Listen, you go and find her, tell her\Nto call Security at Miami Airport...
...because I think a bomb is about\Nto go off. Do it now.
-Sorry, can I put you on hold?\N-I thought you might.
Bond? What the hell are you up to?
I'll call you back.
-The Skyfleet S570 prototype.\N-What about it?
"The largest airplane in the world will\Nbe unveiled today at Miami Airport."
Oh, my God!
Bond? Bond!
His target is the Skyfleet prototype.
It's launching today.
I gotta go.
Stop! Stop!
Get moving!\NLet's go, let's go, let's go!
The puts expired. I'm sorry,\NI'm not sure yet how much you've lost.
One hundred and one million,\Ntwo hundred and six thousand dollars.
Someone talked.
-You got everything you need?\N-Yeah, I have.
I'm gonna get a few more photos....
Quite the body count\Nyou're stacking up.
She was tortured first.\NAs you'd already killed her husband...
...she must have been\Nthe only one left to question.
Did she know anything\Nthat could compromise you?
No.
-Not your name, what you were after?\N-No.
Dimitrios worked as a middleman.
Knew where to put his hands\Non weapons...
...and people who could use them.
He worked with anyone\Nwho had money.
For years he was involved with a man\Nwe knew as Le Chiffre...
...a private banker\Nto the world's terrorists.
He invested their money, gave them\Naccess to it wherever they wanted.
Oh, good. You're here.
Albanian, we believe.\NChess prodigy.
A bit of a mathematical genius\Nand liked to prove it by playing poker.
So you can keep an eye on me?
Yes.
When they analyzed\Nthe stock market after 9l11...
...the CIA discovered a massive\Nshorting of airline stocks.
When the stocks hit bottom on 9l12,\Nsomebody made a fortune.
The same thing happened\Nthis morning with Skyfleet stock...
...or was supposed to.
With their prototype destroyed, the\Ncompany would be near bankruptcy.
Instead, somebody lost over\N$ 100 million betting the wrong way.
You think it's this man Le Chiffre.
Which would explain how he could\Nset up a high-stakes poker game...
...at Casino Royale in Montenegro.
Ten players, $ 10 million buy-in,\N5 million re-buy.
Winner takes all.\NPotentially 150 million.
Good.\NThen we'll know where he'll be.
Do you want a clean kill\Nor to send a message?
We want him alive. Le Chiffre\Ndoesn't have 100 million to lose.
Has he been playing the stock market\Nwith his clients' funds?
They're not gonna be too happy\Nwhen they find out it's gone.
We can't let him win this game.
If he loses,\Nhe'll have nowhere to run.
We'll give him sanctuary\Nin return for everything he knows.
I'm putting you in the game...
...replacing someone\Nwho's playing for a syndicate.
According to Villiers,\Nyou're the best player in the Service.
Trust me, I wish it wasn't the case.
I would ask you if you could remain\Nemotionally detached...
...but I don't think\Nthat's your problem, is it, Bond?
No.
Don't worry about keeping in touch.
We'll know where you are.
You can stop pretending.
You knew I wouldn't let this drop,\Ndidn't you?
Well, I knew you were you.
Thank you.
I'm the money.
Every penny of it.
The Treasury has agreed\Nto stake you in the game.
"Vesper."
Well, I do hope you gave\Nyour parents hell for that.
Thank you.
Your boss must be well-connected.
I've never seen so much\Ngo out the door so quickly.
Or quite so stylishly.
May I ask you where it is?
Ten million was wired\Nto your account in Montenegro...
...with a contingency for 5 more\Nif I deem it a prudent investment.
I suppose you've given some thought\Nto the notion that if you lose...
...our government\Nwill have directly financed terrorism.
What looks good?
So you're telling me it's a matter\Nof probability and odds.
I was worried there was\Nsome chance involved.
Well, only if you assume the player\Nwith the best hand wins.
So that would be\Nwhat you call "bluffing"?
You've heard the term.
Then you'll also know that in poker\Nyou never play your hand.
You play the man across from you.
-And you're good at reading people?\N-Yes, I am.
Which is why\NI've been able to detect...
...an undercurrent\Nof sarcasm in your voice.
I'm now assured our money\Nis in good hands.
You don't think\Nthis is a very good plan, do you?
So there is a plan?
I got the impression\Nwe were risking millions of dollars...
...and hundreds of lives\Non a game of luck.
What else can you surmise,\NMr. Bond?
About you, Miss Lynd?
Well, your beauty's a problem.
You worry you won't\Nbe taken seriously.
Which one can say of any\Nattractive woman with half a brain.
True, but this one\Novercompensates...
...by wearing\Nslightly masculine clothing...
...being more aggressive\Nthan her female colleagues...
...which gives her a somewhat\Nprickly demeanor...
...and ironically enough, makes it\Nless likely for her to be accepted...
...and promoted\Nby her male superiors...
...who mistake her insecurities\Nfor arrogance.
Now, I'd have normally\Ngone with only child...
...but, you see, by the way you ignored\Nthe quip about your parents...
...l'm gonna have to go with orphan.
All right.
By the cut of your suit,\Nyou went to Oxford or wherever...
...and actually think\Nhuman beings dress like that.
But you wear it with such disdain...
...my guess is\Nyou didn't come from money...
...and your school friends\Nnever let you forget it.
Which means you were\Nat that school by the grace...
...of someone else's charity,\Nhence the chip on your shoulder.
And since your first thought about me\Nran to orphan...
...that's what I'd say you are.
Oh, you are.
I like this poker thing.
And that makes perfect sense...
...since Ml6 looks\Nfor maladjusted young men...
...that give little thought\Nto sacrificing others...
...in order to protect\NQueen and country.
You know...
...former SAS types with easy smiles\Nand expensive watches.
-Rolex?\N-Omega.
Beautiful.
Now, having just met you...
...I wouldn't go as far as calling you\Na cold-hearted bastard.
No, of course not.
But it wouldn't be a stretch\Nto imagine.
You think of women\Nas disposable pleasures...
...rather than meaningful pursuits.
So as charming as you are,\NMr. Bond...
...I will be keeping my eye\Non our government's money...
...and off your perfectly formed arse.
You noticed?
Even accountants have imagination.
How was your lamb?
Skewered.
One sympathizes.
Good evening, Mr. Bond.
Good evening, Miss Lynd.
-Hotel Splendid, sir?\N-That's right.
-Thank you, sir.\N-Thank you.
It's just last-minute details.
Apparently we're very much in love.
Do you usually leave it to porters\Nto tell you this sort of thing?
Only when the romance\Nhas been necessarily brief.
I'm Mr. Arlington Beech,\Nprofessional gambler...
...and you're\NMiss Stephanie Broadchest--
-I am not.\N-You're gonna have to trust me on this.
Oh, no, I don't.
We've been involved\Nfor quite a while...
...hence the shared suite.
But my family\Nis strict Roman Catholic...
...so for appearances' sake,\Nit'll be a two-bedroom suite.
I do hate it when religion\Ncomes between us.
Religion and a securely locked door.
Am I going to have a problem\Nwith you, Bond?
No, don't worry. You're not my type.
Smart?
Single.
Welcome to the Hotel Splendid.\NYour name, sir?
James Bond. You'll find\Nthe reservation under Beech.
-Welcome, Mr. Bond.\N-You sign that, dear.
You represent the Treasury.
Thank you. Enjoy your stay.
I will. Thank you.
Very funny.
Look, if Le Chiffre\Nis that well-connected...
...he knows who I am\Nand where the money's from.
Which means he's decided\Nto play me anyway.
So he's either desperate\Nor he's overly confident...
...but either way, that tells me\Nsomething about him.
And all he gets in return\Nis a name he already has.
And now he knows\Nsomething about you.
He knows you're reckless.
Take the next one.
There isn't enough room for me\Nand your ego.
Mr. Bond?
-It was left for you.\N-Thank you.
I love you too, M.
My name is Mathis. Rene Mathis.\NI'm your contact here.
Does he know\Nwe've been watching him?
Le Chiffre? I don't think so.
Probably because there's no "we."\NJust me.
I'm afraid if you get\Ninto trouble here...
...the cavalry won't be\Ncoming over the nearest hill.
Le Chiffre arrived yesterday...
...and spent the time reestablishing\Nold relationships.
The chief of police and he\Nare now quite close.
That's him, with the mustache.
Over my left shoulder.
Well, that could make life\Nquite difficult.
Yeah, and quite possibly shorter.
He's not a very subtle man.
I thought about trying to buy\Nhis services, but we frankly...
...couldn't afford to outbid Le Chiffre.
I hate to say it...
...but the accountants seem\Nto be running Ml6 these days.
Oh, not that I have anything\Nagainst accountants.
Many of them are lovely people.
So I decided that it was cheaper\Nto supply his deputy...
...with evidence\Nthat we were bribing the chief.
It's amazing what you can do with\NPhotoshop these days, isn't it?
I think your odds are improving,\NMr. Bond.
Yes?
For you.
Something you expect me to wear?
I need you looking fabulous.
So when you walk up behind me\Nand kiss me on the neck...
...the players will be thinking\Nabout your neckline...
...and not about their cards.
Do you think you can\Ndo that for me?
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
I have a dinner jacket.
There are dinner jackets\Nand dinner jackets.
This is the latter.
And I need you looking like a man\Nwho belongs at that table.
How--?
It's tailored.
I sized you up the moment we met.
-Good evening, sir.\N-Good evening.
Thank you.
And you must be\NMr. Bliss' replacement.
Welcome, Mr. Beech.
Or is that Bond?\NI'm a little confused.
Well, we wouldn't want that,\Nwould we?
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome.
As you know, the game is no-limit\Nhold 'em poker.
Five communal cards,\Ntwo in the hole.
Monsieur Mendel here represents\Nthe Basel Bank, Switzerland...
...holding the stakes.
You have each deposited\N$ 10 million buy-in.
A further buy-in of 5 million\Ncan be made by electronic transfer.
The money will remain in escrow\Nuntil I return...
...and the winner of the contest\Nenters his or her password...
...into the encryptor...
...whereupon the entire sum\Nwill be wired...
...to any bank account\Nin the world you nominate.
Mr. Bond?
We proceed alphabetically.
Please be so kind as to enter\Na password of your choice.
Six letters or more.
High card for dealer position.
It's Signor Gallardo.
Mr. Kaminofsky is\Nthe small blind, $5000...
...and Mr. Fukutu, the big blind,\N$ 10,000.
Well, enjoy the game.
Four players.
It's your bet.
Check.
Bet. Fifty thousand.
Call.
Fold.
Fold. Heads up.
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
Bet. One hundred thousand.
Weren't you supposed to enter\Nso the others could see you?
Was I? Forgive me.
Good luck, darling.
It's up to you, Monsieur Bond.
Monsieur Bond?
Oh, I'm sorry. What was the bet?\NA hundred thousand?
Call.
Hello.
I suppose I don't have to tell you\Nhow beautiful you look.
Half the people at that table\Nare still watching you.
Champagne.
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
Bet. Two hundred thousand.
Monsieur, you have been called.\NShowdown, please.
A full house to Monsieur Le Chiffre.\NDeuces full of nines.
Mr. Bond?
Fold.
Send the barman over, please.
A dry martini. Wait.
Three measures Gordon's,\None of vodka...
...half of Kina Lillet,\Nshake it over ice...
-...then add a thin slice of lemon peel.\N-Yes, sir.
-You know, I'll have one of those.\N-So will I.
Certainly.
My friend, bring me one as well.\NKeep the fruit.
That's it?
Anyone want to play poker now?
Someone's in a hurry.
Would you excuse me?
You taste nice.
-I thought we dispensed with covers.\N-No.
We dispensed with one that was\Nof no use and created another that is.
-Is he watching?\N-Yes.
Good.
This is me in character pissed off\Nbecause you're losing so fast...
...we won't be here past midnight.
Oddly, my character's feelings\Nmirror my own.
Check.
-You know, that's not half bad.\N-Up to you.
I'm gonna have to think up\Na name for that.
It was worth it to discover his tell.
What do you mean?
The twitch he has to hide\Nwhen he bluffs.
-Bluffs? He had the best hand.\N-Which he got on the last card.
The odds against were 23-to-1,\Nand he'd know that.
When he did his first raise\Nhe had nothing.
Winning was blind luck.
-Did you get the bug?\N-Yes.
Bet. One hundred thousand.
Thank you.
It's your play, Monsieur Fukutu.
Maybe he can actually pull this off.
Call.
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
Ladies and gentlemen,\NMesdames, Messieurs...
...we've now been\Nplaying for four hours.
It's time for a short break.\NWe will resume play in one hour.
Well, I think I'll report\Non the evening's frivolities.
So?
You want to do what to me?
You've lost me completely.
You just said you can't wait\Nto get me back to the room. Come on.
So, what's so damn important?
I'm sorry.
Where is my money?
-Good evening.\N-Good evening.
You're holding a parcel for me.
Thank you.
Do you think you can lose that kind\Nof money and no one would notice?
Your money is safe.
Open that.
You'll have it tomorrow.
All of it.
I would take a hand for this betrayal,\Nbut you need it to play cards.
Hold out your arm.
Hold out your arm, my beauty...
...or I will take your head.
Go to the room. Wait for me there.
Stairs.
Not a word of protest.
You should find a new boyfriend.
Go find Mathis.
Tell him I've hidden the bodies here\Nand I want him to get rid of them.
Do that now. Go. Go, go!
You changed your shirt, Mr. Bond.
I hope our little game\Nisn't causing you to perspire.
A little.
But I won't consider myself to be\Nin trouble until I start weeping blood.
Ladies and gentlemen, if everybody's\Nready, let's continue the game.
It's like there's blood on my hands.\NIt's not coming off.
Here, let's see.
That's better.
You cold?
Yeah.
Here.
You have any trouble\Nwith the bodies?
Less than some.
Being dead doesn't mean\None can't still be helpful.
That'll keep Le Chiffre\Nlooking over his shoulder.
He'll be wondering who's gonna\Ncome for him next.
How's our girl?
Melted your cold heart yet?
Call.
Fold.
And call.
Three players.
Three hundred grand.
Bet. Three hundred thousand.
Call.
And call.
Three players.
Check.
Monsieur Bond?
Bet. Five hundred thousand.
Look. It's the tell. He is bluffing.
My God, James was right.
It's up to you.
Raise. One million.
Seems someone knows\Nsomething I don't.
Fold.
Heads up, gentlemen.
It's up to you.
Two.
Re-raise. Two million.
And it's up to you.
I'm all in.
Well, it's 14 million\Nand 500,000.
It's up to you, Monsieur Bond.
Bond will have to go all in\Nto call his bluff.
-Call.\N-Call.
Gentlemen, showdown, please.
Full house. Kings and aces.
Monsieur Le Chiffre.
It's four jacks.\NMonsieur Le Chiffre wins.
You must have thought\NI was bluffing, Mr. Bond.
Please.
We will now break for one hour.
When we return,\Nthe big blind will be 200,000.
Good game.
Well, I'm gonna need the other\N5 million to buy back in.
I can't do that, James.
Look, I made a mistake.
I was impatient, maybe I was arrogant,\Nbut I can beat him.
-I'm sorry.\N-Sorry?
Sorry?
Try putting that in a sentence.
"Sorry Le Chiffre's gonna win...
...continue funding terror and killing."\NThat kind of sorry?
You lost because of your ego,\Nand that same ego can't take it.
That's what this is about.
All you're going to do now\Nis lose more.
Then you're an idiot.
-I'm sorry?\N-I said, you're a bloody idiot.
Look in my eyes.
I can beat this man, you know that.
Get your hand off my arm.
Vodka martini.
-Shaken or stirred?\N-Do I look like I give a damn?
-James.\N-Get the girl out.
Funny game, right?
Sorry, I should've introduced myself,\Nseeing as we're related.
Felix Leiter, a brother from Langley.
You should have a little faith.
If you keep your head about you,\NI think you have him.
Had. Excuse me.
You're not buying in?
No.
Listen, I'm bleeding chips.\NI'm not gonna last much longer.
You have a better chance.\NI'll stake you.
I'm saying I'll give you the money\Nto keep going.
Just one thing. If you pull it off,\Nthe CIA bring him in.
And what about the winnings?
Does it look like\Nwe need the money?
Shall we up the blinds?
Why not?
Bet.
Raise.
And fold.
Excuse me, please.
Call.
Raise.
Raise. Five hundred thousand.
-Fold.\N-Thank you.
Fold.
Thank you.
Wins.
Deal me out.
Sorry, sir. You are the big blind.
Small blind, please.
-Who is it?\N-It's 007.
Bond's been poisoned.\NHe's going into cardiac arrest.
Stay calm and don't interrupt.\NBecause you'll be dead...
...within two minutes\Nunless you do exactly what I tell you.
I'm all ears.
Remove the defibrillator\Nfrom the pouch.
-Do we know what it is yet?\N-We're still scanning.
Attach the leads to your chest.
Ventricular tachycardia. Digitalis.
What do we give him? The kit\Nhas amphetamines, antihistamines...
...hydrocortisone. Adrenalin?
-As soon as it reads charged--\N-Lidocaine. That'll work.
Bond, don't push the red button yet.\NDo you hear me? Don't push it.
His heart's gonna stop.
There's only time for one charge\Nbefore he passes out.
Take the blue combipen, Bond.\NMid-neck into the vein.
That'll counteract the digitalis.
You're going to pass out\Nin a few seconds.
You need to keep\Nyour heart going.
Push the red button now, Bond.
-Bond, push the damn button!\N-Do it now!
-You okay?\N-Me?
-Thank you.\N-You're welcome.
-Now get yourself off to a hospital.\N-I will do.
As soon as I've won this game.
You're not seriously\Ngoing back there?
I wouldn't dream of it.
Bet. One million.
-All in.\N-Call. All in.
Gentlemen, showdown, please.
Two pair. Aces and sevens.
Queen plays. Wins.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That last hand, it nearly killed me.
Gentlemen, with this chip exchange,\Nwe enter the final phase of the game...
...which means no more buy-ins.
The big blind is now\N1 million dollars.
Four players.
It's your bet.
-Monsieur Bond?\N-Check.
-Check.\N-Twenty-four million in the pot already.
Check. And check.
All check.
Four players.
-Check.\N-Check.
All in. Six million.
Bet. Six million. All in.
Five million. All in.
Bet is 6 million.
Raise.
Twelve million. Heads up.
Forty million, 500,000. All in.
Raise. All in.
Well, I think I will call you\Non that one.
Call.
One hundred and fifteen million\Nin the pot.
Gentlemen, showdown, please.
Flush. Ace, king, queen.
Full house. Eights full of aces.
A higher full house.
Aces full of sixes.
Monsieur Bond.
Five and seven of spades.
A straight flush.
Four to the eight.
The high hand.
Monsieur Bond wins.
-For you.\N-Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
-He's all yours.\N-Much appreciated, brother.
You know,\NI think a celebration's in order.
You were almost dead an hour ago.
Come on, I'm famished.
Thank you.
Mathis says the Americans\Nhave made contact with Le Chiffre.
They're going to extract him\Nbefore dawn.
You know, I think\NI'll call that a Vesper.
Because of the bitter aftertaste?
No. Because once you've tasted it,\Nthat's all you want to drink.
-I thought that was quite a good line.\N-It was a very good line.
But you're laughing at it.
-Not so much it as you.\N-Well, that's fine then.
I figured out what that is.
It's an Algerian love knot.
Really? I thought it was\Njust something pretty.
No, you didn't.
Someone gave that to you.
He's a very lucky man.
You can switch off so easily,\Ncan't you?
It doesn't bother you,\Nkilling those people?
Well, I wouldn't be very good\Nat my job if it did.
I don't believe you.
You've got a choice, you know?
Just because\Nyou've done something...
...doesn't mean\Nyou have to keep doing it.
Why is it people who can't take advice\Nalways insist on giving it?
You think I can't take\Nmy own advice?
I think something is driving you.
And I think I'll never find out\Nwhat that is.
Mathis needs me.
Good night.
Congratulations again.
Mathis.
I'm afraid your friend Mathis\Nis really...
...my friend Mathis.
Wow..! You've taken good care\Nof your body.
You know...
...I never understood\Nall these elaborate tortures.
It's the simplest thing...
...to cause more pain\Nthan a man can possibly endure.
And of course...
...it's not only the immediate agony,\Nbut the knowledge...
...that if you do not yield\Nsoon enough...
...there will be little left\Nto identify you as a man.
The only question remains...
...will you yield in time?
I want the money.
Miss Lynd will give me the account\Nnumber, if she hasn't already.
So all I need from you\Nis the password.
The password, please.
I've got a little itch...
...down there.
Would you mind?
No! No! No!
No. To the right.\NTo the right. To the right!
You are a funny man, Mr. Bond.
Yeah!
Yes, yes, yes.
Now the whole world's gonna know\Nthat you died scratching my balls.
I died?
-I died?\N-Yes.
Because no matter what you do,\NI'm not gonna give you the password.
Which means your clients\Nwill hunt you down...
...and cut you into pieces of meat\Nwhile you're still breathing.
Because if you kill me...
...there'll be nowhere else to hide.
But you are so wrong!
Because even after I slaughtered\Nyou and your little girlfriend...
...your people would still welcome me\Nwith open arms...
...because they need what I know.
The big picture.
Give me the password...
...and I will at least let her live.
Bond. Do it soon enough\Nand she might even be in one piece.
You really aren't going to tell me,\Nare you?
No.
So I think...
...l'll feed you\Nwhat you seem not to value.
I'll get the money.
Tell them I'll get the money.
Money isn't as valuable to our\Norganization as knowing who to trust.
Francesco.
Vesper.
No.
Not him.
Not Mathis.
No.
I'll get the doctor.
Not him.
Any ideas?
-What?\N-Why they left the two of you alive.
Where is she?
Sleeping.
Well, I'm supposed\Nto get you to drink this.
It's just odd...
...killing everyone else\Nbut leaving you and her untouched.
Almost as if someone\Nwas trying to tell us something.
Get a look at the killer?
No.
Shame.
Drink up.
Anything else you remember?
Anything that can help us?
Help us?
Or help you?
Hello.
You all right?
I can't resist waking you.
Every time I do, you look at me as if\Nyou haven't seen me in years.
It makes me feel reborn.
If you'd just been born...
...wouldn't you be naked?
You have me there.
You can have me anywhere.
I can?
Yeah. Here, there,\Nanywhere you like.
Does this mean\Nthat you're warming to me?
Yeah. That's how I would describe it.
It's just that not so long ago...
...I would have described\Nyour feelings towards me as....
I'm trying to think\Nof a better word than "loathing."
I'm afraid I'm a complicated woman.
That is something to be afraid of.
-Hello.\N-Oh, perfect timing.
Monsieur Mendel.\NHow are things in Switzerland?
My apologies,\NI do not mean to rush...
...but 120 million\Nis a large sum of money.
It certainly is. You didn't bring\Nany chocolates with you?
I'm afraid not.
If you would type in\Nthe account number.
And now the password.
You can do that.
I would if I knew what it was.
V-E-S-P-E-R.
The funds have been transferred.
Sorry for disturbing you.
-Auf Wiedersehen.\N-Auf Wiedersehen, Herr Mendel.
You know, James...
...I just want you to know\Nthat if all that was left of you...
...was your smile\Nand your little finger...
...you'd still be more of a man\Nthan anyone I've ever met.
That's because you know\Nwhat I can do with my little finger.
-I have no idea.\N-But you're aching to find out.
You're not going to let me\Nin there, are you?
You've got your armor back on.
That's that.
I have no armor left.
You've stripped it from me.
Whatever is left of me....
Whatever is left of me...
...whatever I am...
...l'm yours.
I suppose M won't miss me\Nfor a couple of days.
She'll be too busy sweating Mathis.
Mathis?
Remember I told you\Nabout Le Chiffre's tell?
Well, Mathis told Le Chiffre.
That's how he wiped me out.
Same goes for the implant. Can't say\NI'm too sorry about losing that.
I can't believe it.
No, neither could I.
I thought he had my back.
But there you go, lesson learned.
Does everyone have a tell?
Yes.
Everyone.
Everyone except you.
I wonder if that's why I love you.
You love me?
Enough to quit\Nand float round the world with you...
...until one of us\Nhas to find an honest job.
But I think that's gonna have to be you.\NI've no idea what an honest job is.
You're serious.
Like you said...
...you do what I do for too long...
...and there won't be any soul\Nleft to salvage.
I'm leaving with\Nwhat little I have left.
Is that enough for you?
-Come on.\N-No. No.
No, stop it. Stop.\NI have to get to the bank.
What's the time?
How much do we need\Nto float for a month?
I've got plenty.
No, I want to pay for my half\Nof our aimless wanderings.
You stopped wearing the necklace.
Yeah. It was time.
Time enough to get over someone?
To realize sometimes\Nyou can forget the past.
Though apparently not\Nyour employer.
Back in one month.
Come on. I'll get the money...
...you get supplies.
I'll see you back here\Nin half an hour.
-Hello, M.\N-I got your note.
Yes?
We'll talk about that later.
Right now I have a lovely man\Nfrom the Treasury here...
...wondering if you're ever\Ngoing to deposit the winnings.
That's a shame.\NI didn't think they'd miss it.
Yes. Well, I told them not to worry.
So you'll be depositing it today.
On my way to the bank right now.
James Bond for Mr. Mendel.
Hello.
Mr. Mendel? I'm having trouble\Naccessing the funds in my account.
It was transferred\Nto the account number...
...your company gave us, Mr. Bond.
It appears the funds\Nare being withdrawn as we speak.
-Where?\N-the Venice branch, of course.
St. Mark's Square.
Is there a problem, Mr. Bond?
I'll kill her!
Allow me.
I'm sorry, James.
She had a boyfriend.\NA French Algerian.
They were very much in love.
He was kidnapped\Nby the organization behind Le Chiffre.
And they blackmailed her, threatening\Nto kill him unless she cooperated.
We should've picked up on it...
...but sometimes\Nwe're so focused on our enemies...
...we forget to watch our friends.
How are you doing?
She left her cell phone.
She must have known I'd check it.
She knew you were you.
-Well, at least this clears Mathis.\N-No.
-No?\N-No.
We just proved that she's guilty,\Nnot that he's innocent.
It could've been a double blind.\NKeep sweating him.
You don't trust anyone,\Ndo you, James?
No.
Then you've learnt your lesson.
Get back as soon as you can.\NWe need you.
Will do.
If you do need time....
Why should I need more time?
The job's done,\Nand the bitch is dead.
James...
...did you ever ask yourself\Nwhy you weren't killed that night?
Isn't it obvious?
She made a deal to spare your life\Nin exchange for the money.
I'm sure she hoped\Nthey would let her live.
But she must have known\Nshe was going to her death.
And now we'll never know\Nwho was behind this.
The trail's gone cold.
-Hello.\N-Mr. White?
We need to talk.
Who is this?
The name's Bond.
James Bond.