♪ Hah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Hah ♪
♪ Huh ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Time is truly wastin' ♪
♪ There's no guarantee, yeah ♪
♪ Smile is in the makin' ♪
♪ We got to fight ♪
♪ the powers that be? ♪
♪ Got so many voices ♪
♪ Saying all the same, yeah ♪
♪ Killing up all around me ♪
♪ Faces full of pain ♪
♪ I tried to play my music ♪
♪ They say my music's too loud ♪
♪ I tried talking about it ♪
♪ I got the big runaround ♪
♪ And when I rolled ♪
♪ with the punches? ♪
♪ I got knocked on the ground ♪
♪ By all this bullshit ♪
♪ going down, hey? ♪
♪ Time is truly wastin' ♪
♪ There's no guarantee, yeah ♪
♪ Smile is in the makin' ♪
♪ We got to fight the powers ♪
♪ that be? ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪? Fight, fight the powers ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
Okay...
Huh?
Oh, my God, it means:
"Cover me, go left."
Read the manual,
why don't you?
Wait for my three count.
And one, two...
Unbelievable.
FBI! Freeze! FBI! Hands
on top of your head!
Don't move! Get 'em up!
Okay, calm down, okay, man?
On your head! Hey,
calm down, tough guy.
Surprise.
We've checked everywhere.
There's nothing.
Well, place is clean, Ashburn.
Looks like your theory
has a few holes in it.
Let's roll, boys.
So you think it's clean, huh?
Oh, here we go. Yeah,
that's what they...
that's what they said last year
right before I arrested
the Red Falls Killer.
What are those?
Barbecue spareribs?
Is that what that is?
I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong.
Or...
maybe I'm not.
Yeah. Airtight.
Dipped in wax.
I respect that.
I especially like the
meat to distract the dog.
And while that may have fooled
the loudest breather
in the world,
it did not fool me.
And, unfortunately, it's
not what I'm looking for.
So why don't we just
cut to the chase?
Are there guns in this house?
I don't know anything
about any guns.
Interesting.
Maybe I'm wrong. You know?
Mm, wait for it.
Maybe these guys are...
are right for a change.
Stranger things have
happened, right, guys?
Mm, that's a trap.
Meteors, comets.
Somebody married Pete,
and he can't even
count to three. Uhuh.
See? Right there?
So frustrating.
You know, they
loved these houses
during the Prohibition Era.
You guys know what
prohibition is, don't you?
Yeah, selling your
ass for money?
Really? Really?
No. No, it was, uh, alcohol.
People loved to drink it, even
though they weren't supposed to,
and these houses had
all these little
nooks and crannies where
they could hide it.
Like this one.
Is there something behind me?
There is, isn't there?
Fuck.
Now you can roll.
Gentlemen.
Nice work, dick.
Jesus.
Let's go. Ooh...
Hard to believe she's single.
Oh!
Immediately below that, you
feel a little crease...
Wow, that's pretty
impressive, huh?
Do you see that? Look at that.
We'd want to make an incision
right through there.
That's pretty amazing, huh?
Pretty amazing.
Pumpkin!
Here, kitty, kitty.
Are you at the
neighbor's again?
Pumpkin!
Here, kitty, kitty.
Go on home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
There you go.
Pumpkin, I told you
to stay away from
that weird lady.
Yo, taxi!
Mmhmm.
No, no, no, o lo lo...
lo siento.
No, hay a poder
llegar temprano,
llamar de Los vecinos
y diles que...
Lo siento. Perdón.
Oh, boy.
Wife doesn't like you
working late, huh?
What do you want?
Oh, just, uh, letting you know
that I have been
observing the agents,
overseeing what
they've been up to,
you know, keeping
an eye on them.
Yeah. Supervising.
Supervising. Yes, sir.
Look, Ashburn...
I haven't made any
decisions yet.
Oh... of course not.
Every... everyone
deserves a shot.
I don't know if you are the
right person for this position.
I'm s... I'm sorry, what?
What? I'm confused.
Walk with me.
Sir, I don't... I
don't understand.
I've closed more cases
than any agent here.
Should I not have done that?
You are a solid agent.
There are many other
solid agents.
Well, none of them have closed
the Red Falls Killer case.
Ashburn, it's no secret
that none of the other
agents like you.
What?
I've gotten countless
complaints of arrogance
and competitiveness,
showmanship.
Just give it a rest.
All right.
We've got a situation in Boston.
The Feds picked up chatter
on a guy moving in.
Simon Larkin.
We don't know what
he looks like,
where he comes from, nothing.
We believe this guy is
doing the legwork for him.
Julian Vincent, nasty
son of a bitch.
Murder, extortion.
This is his M.O.
The problem with guys
like that is that
everyone's too scared to talk.
Pack your bags. I'm
sending you to Boston.
You know how to get
inside people's heads.
You want to find
Larkin, get to Julian.
You do well with this, we
can talk about the job.
♪ Wooh! ♪
♪ She's got stickers ♪
♪ on her locker? ♪
♪ And the boy's number's there ♪
♪ in Magic Marker? ♪
♪ I'm hungry ♪
♪ and the hunger will linger? ♪
♪ I eat 16 saltine crackers ♪
♪ Then I lick my fingers ♪
♪ Well, every morning ♪
♪ I deliver the news? ♪
♪ Black hat, white shoes... ♪
Hey, Rojas sent me over.
He said you were really nice.
Yeah, baby, what are
you looking for?
What's your name? Champaz.
What's yours?
Champaz? Did your Mom
give you that name?
Not exactly.
Hey, Mullins.
Captain wants to know
when you're coming in.
Hey, you know what?
Tell him I'll be there
sharply at, uh,
gofuckyourself o'clock.
Okay? If there's no traffic.
Thank you.
That seems kind of expensive.
Expensive?
Can you break a hundred? I
got a hundred right here.
No, baby, I'm not going
to break a hundred.
All right, let me see.
I don't think I have that.
Wow.
My God, do you have,
like, a discount?
Hey, what's going on here?
Okay, I don't want any
drugs, all right?
Oh.
No. Hi. How you doing?
Are you trying to get a...
a deal on my girl here?
Are you her pimp?
No, we're just friends.
Isn't that right?
Okay, well, it's... I think
this is just kind of...
between her and I, so let's...
Am I kind of invading
your space here?
Kind of. I don't
want to do that.
Let me see if this
will help you.
All right, look, I...
I just wanted to...
Oh.
Well, it... it's, uh...
it's a good thing I didn't
get the drugs from you.
Yeah, can you imagine that?
That would have been...
That would have been crazy.
That would have been bad.
Yeah, right?
Whew!
You'd better wipe that brow.
Listen, um... Thanks.
I got to ask,
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, whatever...
What was... what was
actually going on here?
Oh, we were just, um...
She looked kind of
sad, so I just...
I kind of thought I'd help her
out and give her a ride home.
That's nice, like
a Good Samaritan.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Were you depressed?
Was he giving you a ride home?
Yeah, I was kind of
cheering you up.
Yeah, good for you.
You know who else is pretty sad?
Frank over here.
Right, Frank, you get sad 'cause
you shit and piss yourself?
You having a sad day, Frank?
Hey, maybe you can put him
in the back of your car...
You want to shit and piss
all over this guys car?
You know what, let's
open up the...
Frank, you want to shit your
pants and get in the...
Oh, good, it's open.
I can put, uh, Frank in there.
Okay.
He can shit and piss himself...
Until he's happy.
I got some towels. I
can put some towels...
Does that sounds good?
Yeah, sure.
Why don't you let me see your I.D.
there? Oh, come on, please.
Um... Yeah, hey, let me
just take the whole thing.
I don't... Yeah, it's good.
It's... I got it.
Oh, good.
You know what?
I got nervous that
maybe you didn't have
a wife and a whole
bunch of kids, but...
but luckily, you do.
What's your wife's name?
Her name is Bella.
Oh, Bella. Good.
Hey, can I borrow your
phone for a minute?
My... yeah, my...
my battery's out.
Why do you want to
borrow my phone?
Because I asked you
for your phone.
Give me your fucking phone.
Shut your mouth.
Can't you just, like, g
give me one chance here?
Yeah, I'll give you one chance.
Hello?
Yeah, who's this?
Is this Bella?
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
That's... Don't do that.
Don't do that.
Ow! My God! Don't do that.
Yes, this is Officer Mullins.
God!
I'm here with your husband.
God, what are you, Spock?
No.
No, he's not been in an
accident, unfortunately.
I just, uh... II do have him
here with a known prostitute.
God! She's lying!
Bella, she's lying!
Oh, that's not the
first time, huh?
God. Yeah, that's him.
He's crying 'cause I'm
breaking his fucking hand.
God. Oh, she said
do it harder.
All right, Bella.
Ow! God! That's for Bella.
Well, you got to go with
your instincts, Bella.
Yep, you're welcome.
Yep, she's probably going to
burn your shit today, so...
Come on, look, you don't
understand, all right?
She just had a baby. There's
a lot going on down there.
I'm not going to touch that.
Why don't you take your, uh,
seat belt off for a minute?
Oh, come on, please...
come on. Yeah.
No, you seem like
a reasonable guy.
You look like you got...
Take your fucking belt off.
And you look like you
got some compassion.
Listen, I love... I love
the sound of a guy that,
after his wife gives him
his fifth fucking child,
complains about
her messy vagina.
And then you don't want
to fucking touch her!
Get out of the fucking car. I
can unlock the door for you.
What the fuck, man? Get
out of the fucking car!
Get out of the fucking car!
Are you kidding me?
Come on! Get up
against the car.
What is your problem? You
asked for my phone...
Turn around. You
want to do that?
Do you want to do that? It's hot!
The car is hot!
Good! I hope it burns
your fucking dick off!
Hey, it's Rojas, my
favorite asshole.
Yeah, look what I found.
Oh, no, did I take some
of your business away?
That's a real shame.
Lady, I don't even know
what you're talking about.
I just stand on this corner,
and I just do my
"sodukas," okay?
Oh, is that right? First of
all, it's "soduko," dumb-ass.
And you want to
tell me that you're
just here coincidentally,
right in the...
right in the middle of
all the prostitutes?
Lady, tell me this... why are
you so obsessed with me?
You should be ashamed
of yourself,
trying to break down a
successful black man.
You racist?
And don't play that race
bullshit card with me!
Nine out of ten guys I
fuck are black guys.
Lady, what I think
you need to do...
you need to go down the road,
take a vacation, okay?
And go get your groove back.
Lady, just relax, chill, okay?
What is that?
Take off.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I'm not a part of this!
Shut up! Shut up!
Stop! Oh! Oh!
Oh, my God!
♪ Yeah, I was right all along ♪
♪? Yeah. ♪
Oh, my God!
Oh, it's on!
She's crazy!
♪ Yeah. ♪
Come on, please let me out.
I get really carsick.
Please, please, please, please
Oh, no, that's terrible.
No, come on. Oh, my God!
I got him now. I got
him, I got him.
You are a meth head!
Oh, my God!
Hey, look who's here.
Oh!
You just hit him!
♪ So what you waiting for? ♪
Yeah, you better run.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
I got him. I got him!
Oh, God!
You piece of shit,
I said stop.
I said... I said stop!
I said stop! Just get off me!
You're crushing my balls!
I hope they fucking rupture!
Lady, get the fuck off of me!
You're going to fucking...
What the hell is
wrong with you?
Bella, I'm sorry!
Let me go! Hold still,
you piece of shit!
Ow! My leg, lady!
Let me go!
No! No!
Lady, what the hell
is wrong with you?
I'll tell you what the
hell's the matter with me.
It's you, piece of shit.
Son of a bitch.
Stop moving!
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone!
Get off me! Shit.
Get off me!
Shit.
Yeah.
Man, lady, what the hell
did you throw at me?
A watermelon. A watermelon?
Ah, hell, no!
See, I told you
you was a racist.
Yeah? I tried to hit you with my car.
What's that make me?
Yeah, let's see what you got in...
Oh, look at this.
Look at this. Not
even my birthday.
Hey, man, you planted
that shit on me, man!
Yeah, I planted it, yeah.
You planted that on me!
I'm innocent!
Shut up before I feed you watermelon.
Get up.
Levy?
Yeah. Federal Agent
Sarah Ashburn
from the New York field office.
Hi. How are you?
I'm going to need all your files
on all known drug
dealers of the area.
Right. We heard you were coming.
Actually, I was expecting you.
Ah.
I'll show you to your desk.
Oh, that won't be necessary.
I won't be here long.
Okay. Okay. So I can carry these.
Thank you.
Where is it?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey! Ashburn!
Ashburn!
Oh! Ooh. Oh, God.
You okay? What? What is it?
What is it? Okay.
Lowend dealer just brought
into the East Boston precinct.
All right. Name's
Terrell Rojas.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Good. Thank you very much.
Good... good luck out there.
It's not about luck, pal.
Not about luck.
Wow.
That was almost cool.
Almost.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ain't going to
fucking park today?
All right.
Here we go. Finally.
Hey! I'm moving in there!
No, don't...!
Hey, hey, hey! No, get
back in your car.
Hey! Hey!
Hey, asshole!
Goddamn it.
FBI.
Hey, you need to sign in.
Come on. Let's go.
Captain Woods?
Christ. I'm sorry?
Uh, how can I help you?
Special Agent Sarah Ashburn.
We got intel recently
that you brought in
a dealer by the name
of Terrell Rojas.
Uh, yeah, but Detective Mullins
isn't back from lunch yet.
I'm sure he won't mind.
Well, he's a she, and we're not
really allowed to go
near her collars.
Let me tell you what I think.
I think that every second
we're standing here
is interfering with the
federal investigation.
So, if you'd be so kind
as to show Mr. Rojas to
an interrogation room.
Thank you.
Special Agent? Yes.
This way. Okay.
Special Agent?
Shit.
You are looking at
possession with intent,
which is a class D drug charge,
chapter 94C, section 32A.
I had a joint and a few
little bags of coke.
Since when is that shit illegal?
The answer to your
question is always.
And with your priors,
you are looking at 25 years
and some pretty stiff fines.
Who the hell cares about fines?
That's 25 years!
Never mind.
Let's see what you
make of these.
Huh? What do you
make of these?
What I make of them is
that somebody doesn't want
somebody else selling
on their turf.
But you're still here.
And you're alive. Why is that?
Who you working for? Nobody.
Who you working for? Who
you working for? Nobody.
Nobody! If I tell
you, that's my ass
chopped up into a million
motherfucking pieces!
Goddamn it.
Fucker.
God.
Push!
This motherfucker!
Everybody's got to
fucking park in my spot.
Goddamn it!
Shit!
Suitwearing, God...
Ow! Fuck!
God.
Yeah, I said I'm...
fucking parking there.
That doesn't... Steal my
goddamn fucking space.
I don't want you to do time.
I don't want you to get
chopped up into little, tiny,
mothereffin' pieces.
Oh.
I can protect you.
I can.
But you got, you
got to help me.
I can help you.
You're gonna help me? Yeah.
Tell me where I can find Julian.
I don't deal with him like that.
I get my stuff from this bitch
named Tatiana on Newkirk Avenue.
Can you describe her to me?
Well, she got brown eyes.
Okay.
Mm, she got some
bigass "breastses."
Big breastses. Okay.
Can you maybe be a little
bit more specific?
Uh... like...
her breastses is like this.
Okay. Thank you.
That's a shame.
Don't.
Oh, haha, oh, yeah!
We're at a comedy party, yeah.
Move the fuck out of my way.
Get a room.
Tim, you still owe me 40.
Yeah, tomorrow it's 60.
Fucking dickweed.
Why is the cage empty?
What have I told you about
moving my prisoners?
He's in interrogation.
Why would he be in interrogation
when I'm standing right here?
Theythey came and got him.
Who's "they"?
Better be two of me.
Is it two of me?
It was a lady. She was...
I'm a lady. Did I
come and get him?
No, no, it was a different
lady, She was nice.
I'm fuckin' nice. No, no.
Why was she nice to you?
She made me give her the keys.
I'm gonna make you
fucking bend over,
and I'm gonna reach up your
ass into your pocket and get
the keys to your house.
And then I'm gonna
drive there,
come in your front fucking door
and kill you in your sleep.
I think I have a clear idea
of what we're looking for,
and I appreciate your time.
Wow, lady, you're on
a real fuckin' roll.
Excuse me? I...
Yeah, no, I won't excuse you.
I just spent the last 30 minutes
thinking of different
ways to kill you.
I... I'm... I'm sorry,
when did we meet?
What is this, your lawyer?
I'm... What are you,
insurance salesman?
Do you sell those shitty suits?
I'm Special Agent Sarah Ashburn.
How can I help you?
You can get all of
that, get it up,
and get it the fuck out of
here, 'cause this is my room.
Were you, were you about to be,
uh, questioned by a detective?
I am a detective,
and that's my perp. Ah.
Ah, I... I understand now.
Well, um, Detective,
Mr. Rojas will be continuing
on with me at this point.
No.
It's a jurisdictional issue.
No, not gonna happen. And
so, uh, youryour efforts
areare duly noted. Thank you so much.
Oh, great.
And if you're okay
with everything,
could you justjust
maybe close the door
on the way out?
I'll shut the door on you.
Will you lay down here and
put your head in the door?
And I'll slam it about
157,000 fucking times.
Aw, shit, girl, you better run.
You need to shut your mouth.
Run like you on fire.
You need to be quiet.
You're gonna get up,
and we're gonna
settle this outside.
Okay, now I'm... I won't
be going outside.
You're gonna get up and
you're gonna come outside.
No, ma'am. Not going outside.
Fine. We'll do this inside.
Can somebody please
remove this person
from the interrogation room?
We're good!
Mental illness is nothing
to be ashamed of.
It runs in many families.
I'm gonna hit you.
You're not gonna hit me.
Please don't.
I'm gonna hit you and knock
all your little buttons.
Do not point your finger...
I'm gonna hit you there...
No, do not put your
finger in my...
Stop touching my buttons,
stop touching...
Well, stop wearing buttons.
Don't you... Don't you move
those fucking hands again.
I'll get that stupid barrette.
H Hey, hey!
I'll take that barrette right
out of your fucking hair!
Hey, stop! Oh,
stop, stop, stop!
Hey, both of you, my office now.
Nope. Not in there.
There is nothing I
can do, Mullins.
The FBI has jurisdiction.
Maybe they're in here. Maybe
they're in here. Aw, come on.
Nope. Stop. Will you stop?
Nope, they're not in there.
Let me see.
What is she doing?
They're not under there.
She's looking for my balls.
Oh.
Hey, if anyone sees
the captain's balls,
let me know!
They're about this
big, but a lot tinier.
They're like a pea, or like
a, like a ball bearing,
or like, if you've ever
seen a mouse ball,
about half that size.
Incredibly tiny.
They're like really, really
tiny, little girl balls,
if little girls had balls.
So if you find little,
tiny, girl balls
that are so fucking tiny and
shriveled up, let me know,
'cause I'll put them right
back up his scrotum!
Knock it off, Mullins.
How about you do
something for once?
What do you want me to do?!
Uh, I'd like you to have my
back and stop being so goddamn
disappointing like
everybody else.
Oh, well, that was professional.
Oh, is that not professional?
Here.
Let me, let me be professional.
Let me help you
pick up your bag.
That's very mature.
Let me just straighten
that shit up.
Oh, wait, hey, hey!
Good news! Good news!
I found his balls!
Yeah, in a clear sack!
Yeah, enjoy that.
Shove those back up there.
Cop of the Year!
Keep it up!
This job is destroying me.
You know how old I am?
Uh, uh, 58?
I'm 43 years old.
Mmhmm, mmhmm.
Well, I always, see,
I always round up.
I have a fiveyearold son
who calls me Grandpa.
So, uh, anywho, uh,
sir, if, um...
if you could just, you know,
keep her away from me,
that would be...
be very helpful.
She stole your keys, didn't she?
Yes, she did. Do you know
where I can find her?
She's probably at O'Flanagan's.
It's a bar down the street.
Now, it's a little divey.
You might want to wear a vest.
♪ Okay, I'm Rambo, I ramshack ♪
♪ I'm next to that cheese ♪
♪ like rat traps? ♪
♪ On top of that green ♪
♪ like grass ass? ♪
♪ That's over y'all head ♪
♪ like snapbacks? ♪
♪ I get it where I fit in, ♪
♪ put up then I put in? ♪
♪ Tryin' to find an ass I can ♪
♪ put my fucking foot in? ♪
♪ Run this shit, ♪
♪ no, I run this shit? ♪
♪ Don't give one fuck, ♪
♪ bitch, I done this shit...? ♪
Sir, is this... is
this place open?
Is there a door...?
Oh, wow. Wow, okay,
so there is.
Could you, um, could you
point it out to me?
With... with your fin...
with your finger. Please.
Thank you. Thank
you very much.
♪ Here I come again, now, baby ♪
♪ Like a dog in heat... ♪
Hand them over.
Give me the keys. Now.
Oh, my God.
Did you drop something?
Apologize. Apologies.
You are so concerned about
taking down a guy like Rojas
when we have just wasted
all this time, when I could
have stopped a drug lord
who is far more dangerous and
supplies to people like Rojas.
Bullshit. Oh, really?
Who? Oh.
Okay, you want to see
some bull feces?
I think I said bullshit,
is what I said.
Here you go. Here's
some bull poopoo.
How's this for bull feces?
How does that look? Huh?
See that?
Oh, come on. I got a kid here.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm, I'm very
sorry, very sorry.
Wait a minute, this is a bar.
This is a b...
No, absolutely not.
Nononononono. Nonononono.
Why do I not know who
Simon Larkin is?
Uh, that would
probably be because
the FBI knows
more than you do.
Uh, anything that's happening
in my neighborhood,
I have a right to know.
Uh, no, you actually don't.
You want to know.
And you do not have the
clearance that would allow you
to read everything that
is on this file, okay?
Okay, all right!
You know, when
bad shit happens
in my neighborhood, I get a
little passionate about it.
I shouldn't have
read your files.
I went too far.
Well, I... I accept
your apology.
But you need to understand
that this is a highly
important case
and the information is
highly, highly sensitive.
Therefore, we have these
clearances that mean...
I don't have the clearances.
I don't have the
clearances, right?
I mean, you're...
you are, wow, FBI.
Yes. I mean, you are...
you're a goddamn
angel of the law.
Well, I... that's a little...
You know, I want you to spread
those wings out and just soar.
While I appreciate
the sentiment...
Hey!
It's certainly not...
Watch it.
You watch it.
I'm a federal agent.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
Well, guess what, you dick.
I'm a federal agent, too.
I work at The Post Office.
Well, I... I appreciate
the work you do for us
down on the ground.
Thank you. Thank you.
Bet your ass you do.
I can see no one will be
getting their mail today.
Wow.
Good burn. Good burn.
You got burned, you
big drunk paddy!
Kiss my cunt, you twat!
Yeah. So we are...
Hey. We are good?
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, America thanks you.
And I, it.
And it, you.
Thank you.
Whoaoa.
Yes, okay.
Good day.
Dumbass.
All prisoners, clear the yards.
So how you been, Jason?
You want to talk
about Simon Larkin?
Uh, I never heard of him.
Don't fucking lie to me.
You're my goddamn brother,
I know when you're lying.
I'm just a lowlevel guy.
Okay? I heard of Larkin, but,
you know, I never met him.
Yeah, well, he's a
goddamn animal,
and I'm trying to keep
him from meeting you.
What, are you gonna
storm through Boston
and take down a drug lord?
Yeah, I might.
Have you met me?
Yeah, unfortunately.
Yeah, shut up.
Look, I get out
tomorrow, okay?
I... I'm coming home.
I'm gonna be fine.
I promise, all right?
Oh! Jesus!
Never approach me if
I'm not expecting you!
Cheese and rice, what
are you, an animal?!
Okay, you know what?
You said you would
stay off my case,
and where do I find you?
Right here.
Right here in front of
Tatiana's apartment.
What? I live here.
Oh, okay, that's hilarious.
Yeah, okay, you know
what's not funny?
That you stole a
confidential FBI case file.
Oh, that's funny, I don't
remember any of that.
I'm gonna say this
one more time.
Stand down, Officer.
Fuck off, Officer.
Oh, okay, guess what?
Now you've really done it.
I'm gonna call my boss.
Yeah, you do that,
tattle tits!
Fucking narc!
Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
Hale.
It's Ashburn, sir.
I'm gonna need authorization
to suspend a police officer
from my investigation, sir.
Ashburn, why is working
with local authorities
a problem for you?
Sir, it's not.
I understand how this might
sound coming from me,
but I... I think this individual
might actually be
mentally unstable.
According to her captain,
she grew up on those streets
and she knows them
better than anyone.
That seems like an asset
to our investigation.
Nonono. Sir, I...
Just work with her.
Just show me you can do this
or forget the promotion.
Well, sir, no need, no need
to take someone's badge.
I think I can, uh...
I think I can work
something out, sir.
All right. Thank you.
Byebye.
You know, uh...
I just, I think just...
I think you and I
got off on the wrong foot.
Oh. I don't know Boston,
and you obviously have
a a lot of resources
and a lot of knowledge about
the area thatthat could be,
you know, could be useful.
Probably very.
So, uh, maybe we can
work together on this.
Yeah, I don't need your
help to take down Larkin.
You know, you wouldn't even
have known about Larkin
if it wasn't for me, so
obviously the FBI can
get information that
you can't, okay?
And there's a lot more
where that comes from... a lot.
Maybe I just need
to hear a little.
"I need your help, Mullins."
No, I won't be doing that.
Okay, well, get your
ass back in your car.
Okay, this is ridiculous, okay?
I'm an FBI agent,
you're a police officer.
It's not...
"I need your help, Mullins."
I need your help, Mullins.
Oh, God, what is... is
this a whisper party?
I want that third
floor to hear it.
"I need your help, Mullins."
And then maybe give me a
little echo on that "Mullins."
I need your help, Mullins!
Mullins, Mullins...
Just move, move, move!
God.
Even in that, you're annoying.
I will work with you,
as long as we're clear
that this is my case.
That's actually not correct.
This isn't your... Awesome.
Glad you see it my way.
Careful of the car.
Goddamn it.
Stand down. I got it.
If you just, if you just let go.
I got it.
I think I have it, just...
Just let me...
I got it. Geez.
Oh, shit.
Ma'am, you, uh...
Just go. Just go.
Okay, now let me take
the lead on this.
I'm a trained interviewer.
"Interviewer"?
What are you, fucking
Barbara Walters?
I just thought we were
gonna go in there
and bring in some heat on her.
I'm sorry, w what is...
what does that even mean?
What does that mean?
Me and you, we're the heat.
We go in there, we
interrogate her,
we scare the shit
out of her...
See, we don't say
"interrogation."
It's, it's much
too aggressive.
Rule number one: Catch more
with sugar than a stick.
That's a horrible
fucking saying.
Okay, well, what we like to
do isis create aa genuine
personal interest
in the subject,
allowing them to open up. But
from then, I'm going to...
Oh, God... uh, perform instant
personality assessments
based on the MyersBriggs
theory, uh,
Thematic Apperception
Tests, and a few...
well, a few others I won't,
I won't bore you with.
Oh, my God, well, that's...
I am balls deep in boredom.
All right, as long
as you don't do
that whole goddamn long
explanation again,
we'll try it your way first.
Okay.
Only 'cause you're older.
Oh, my God.
Tatiana Krumova.
I'm Special Agent
Sarah Ashburn,
and this is Detective Mullins.
Detective Mullins.
And we'd like to ask
you a few questions,
if you could give us a moment.
Oh, shoot, you know, now is bad.
Oh. I'm making butter.
Oh. Oh, that's...
How about other time?
Well, if you could... How
about right fucking now?
How's that? How's that?
Right fucking now.
Well, Tatiana, thank you.
This is, this is
very kind of you.
So...
how long have you lived here?
I've lived here
since I moved in.
Shit.
Okay, that's very,
very helpful.
Okay, we'll get a
little more specific.
Uh, what do you do
for a living?
I know what this asshole
does for a living.
What you know, asshole?
Okay, sugar, no stick.
It is Bulgarian, is it not?
No, I'm fucking French.
Oh, Jesus.
Tatiana...
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Nice bullshit Bulgarian.
Okay, you know what? That
was perfect Bulgarian.
I mean, I don't understand
what you're talking about.
Why I go to jail when
I don't do shits?
Ah, okay.
So she did understand
what I was saying,
she just didn't
understand the context
in which I said it to her.
Oh, sweet God.
Okay, okay, all right,
Rosetta Stone, you're done.
God.
Oh, Jesus.
How many porns have been
made on this couch?
Oh, this couch not of
your satisfaction?
You're not comfy?
I'll get comfy. When
my foot's up your ass.
Wow.
That'll make me really comfy.
Stop.
Don't poke me. Don't poke me.
Listen, Tatiana, I want
to get really real.
You ready to get
real, Tatiana?
Let's get real.
Okay, we both know you've been
blowing shit up
your nose all day.
Man, I get it.
There's nothing more
I'd love to do than
slip into my camisole, put my
feet up, have a little smack.
Real good time, maybe
a couple cold ones,
a little chip and dip,
watch some cartoons.
I'd get a big bowl
of fucking coke, I'd just
put my face right in it,
cut it with a little Ritalin.
Heaven on fucking earth, right?
Sure. I'd camp out all week
for tickets to that show.
WhWhatwhat is this,
Training Day?
All fucking week, I'd
camp out for that.
But you, you piece of shit,
you've been rolling
deep for a long time,
and now it's time you open
up that goddamn mouth
and tell us what
we want to know.
You got good point.
I tell you what.
I open my mouth.
You get the fuck
out my house now!
How's that for open mouth?
Fuck out! Get fuck out!
Yeah. I'll get the fuck out.
All right.
You should really stop
smoking, 'cause, uh...
it's an awfully bad habit.
You're leaving half your
lipstick in the ashtray.
I had a, uh, great
aunt that lost
most of her teeth
to, uh, smoking.
Good to know. A lot
of fistfights, too,
but, uh, mostly smoking.
You know what?
We're gonna get
out of your hair.
So we're just gonna...
What? That is not front door.
Put your hands where I
can fucking see them!
Don't fucking move.
What is this, your drug mule?!
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my goodness.
That's my mother!
Huh? Do you have balloons
of horse up your ass?!
You break my fucking door!
Stand down, Officer.
Who closes the door
to take a shit?!
Get out! Humans do.
Get out now. You get out.
D Don't touch underpants!
Thank you.
Get out, bull in China shop!
Out of my house!
What the fuck's wrong with you?!
Wow, you are just all
stick and no sugar.
Did you get the
cigarette or not?
Uh, uh, yeah, yeah,
ofofof course I did.
Yeah.
I snagged these matches, too.
I think our guy likes
to go to Club Ekko.
Okay, hold on.
Come on. Really?
Yes, yes, really.
Let's find out, shall we?
All right, hang on.
That couch was disgusting,
I need to wash my hands.
Wait a minute, you do,
you do live here?
That's what I said.
Oh.
Wow, your windows are all...
all boarded up.
Yeah, I've got the glass,
I just don't have the, you
know, the window blankets.
The curtains? You mean,
you mean the curtains?
Whatever. Okay?
That's just my family.
That's...
Oh.
Yeah, it's sweet.
You want something to eat?
I didn't finish my submarine
sandwich from the other day.
Oh, God, no, thank you.
Thank you.
Well, I'm sorry I don't have
poached eggs in rubies for you.
No, I... I don't, I
don't mean to be rude,
but one could catch aa MRSA
infection in here, that's all.
Yeah, what part of
that wasn't rude?
Just for your, for
your own wellbeing.
I mean, for example, that door.
That door has absolutely
no way of locking.
Someone could barge
in at any moment.
It's not safe.
No one's coming in here,
'cause they know I keep
this fully stocked.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I know.
A Marlin 1894 CB?
Yeah.
Is that a FNPS 90?
Yeah. Nice one.
You have all this
in your house?
Yeah. You didn't even
mention my baby.
Look at this.
Oh, oh. Wow, wow.
My little pride and joy.
Okay.
This little beauty could
vaporize an aboveground pool,
if you didn't want the
pool anymore, you know?
No kidding. Pretty, huh?
Yeah, how do you, how do you
refuse that sales pitch, huh?
You don't, unless
you're an asshole.
Wow.
Haven't seen one of these
since, what, World War II?
No, God, that's...
occasionally ticks.
Put it back slowly.
Okay, okay. Slowly!
I'm sorry.
Like, half that speed.
That's... God, okay.
Half that speed.
Stop sha... Put
your pinky down.
I got it on eBay.
It was supposed to be
bigger and different.
It doesn't matter.
I'm gonna "bad feedback"
his ass though.
All right, ladies.
Here's the DNA results
from the book of matches
and the cigarette butt
you got from Tatiana's.
We pulled two sets of prints.
First one's a real nut job.
Look at this:
Reckless driving,
assault, arson.
Oh, God. Really?
Who the fuck is this guy?
He's my assistant. What...
Uh, you know I'm
an agent, right?
Arson? It was a drug house.
God, I... I really feel the need
to finish reading your files,
because this is just, um...
I feel the need for you to
stay out of my business
so I don't punch you in the teeth.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
All right, what did you find
out about the cigarette?
Okay. Hank LeSoire.
Local businessman.
Got tons of ties to the
drug world, black market,
as well as prostitution rings.
Coowner of Club Ekko.
Well, it looks like we
found our distributor.
Can you, can you back
that up, please?
Back up to which one? That.
Hey! I'm not into you.
Your breast is invading my space.
It's just...
Well, keep your finger
out of my areola.
Well, contain your areola.
There. Now we're even.
Well, he looks like a
real Chatty Cathy.
Did you tap the phone?
I haven't been able to.
Guy gets a new prepaid
every other week. Yeah.
By the time I can get
his phone number
and hack in, he's
got a new one.
Well, let's get a bug into the
phone this guy does have.
I want to know what
he's saying this week.
Yeah, just get a court
order and a bug,
and we'll just do it ourselves.
Right.
If you're gonna
boss me around,
you can at least buy
me dinner first.
No. Okay. Cool.
I'll get that to you ASAP.
You gotta work on your game.
That was weak.
What? I thought I
was being charming.
I don't know what
to say to that.
Now I just feel bad for you.
Okay, so LeSoire
coowns Club Ekko.
Let's get over there and
start surveilling it
and figure out how to
get a bug in his phone.
Tell me everything
you know about it.
It's just a shitty
club downtown.
I've never been inside of it,
but there's always a line
of awful people
around the corner,
and they've called PD a couple
of times to break up fights...
Oh, shit.
What's wrong?
Justjust don't look, don't look...
don't look!
Just act like we're talking.
Hey, Shannon.
Hey, Robin.
I really enjoyed our
night together, Shannon.
You just disappeared on me.
Yeah, I know. I was there.
Well, can I take you to dinner
or a movie or something?
God, buddy, do you not
hear how pathetic
everything out of
your mouth sounds?
I mean, there's a girl
out there for you,
but it's not, it's not me.
Maybe it's her.
Her lady business is
like an old dirty attic.
It's full of broken
Christmas lights
and, like, doll shoes and shit.
Why don't you clean
that out for her.
Uh, that's a,
that's a misrepresentation
of my vagina.
Oh, wow, what was that about?
You sleep with a guy one time,
and he wants to get
married to you.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
♪ More than a feeling ♪
♪ More than a feeling? ♪
♪ When I hear that old song... ♪
Who is, who is that?
My Mom.
Ortiz settles into
the batter's box.
Verlander with the pitch
and a ground ball
right side through the legs
of Cabrera into right field.
Pedroia is headed
for second base.
He slides and he is...
How about I tell you a little
something about myself?
Oh, God. Let's see.
I went to undergrad at Yale.
I have been with the
Bureau for about 12 years.
Um, up for a promotion.
See, I... I caught the,
um, I caught the Red...
the Red Falls Killer.
Yeah, I remember thinking
that guy was innocent.
Yeah, he's been in
jail for 11 months.
That would make me
a horrible person,
if any of what you said was
actually factual, so...
Well, you can just tell
the judge you fucked up.
I w... I... I... I didn't,
eh, I did not "F" up.
Listen, don't get your
panties in a wad.
Just... They're not
wadded, I'm just... my...
I'm intuitive, I
say what I feel.
I'm usually right. Oh.
Take it or leave it. Oh, I
didn't, I did not know.
Okay.
Hey, say hi to Tommy.
It's Tommy.
All right, there's our guy.
I... I see him as well.
♪ Daft Punk is playing ♪
♪ at my house, my house? ♪
♪ I'll show you the ropes, kid, ♪
♪ show you the ropes? ♪
♪ Got a bus and a trailer ♪
♪ at my house, my house? ♪
There he is, it... What?
Over there.
♪ I'll show you the ropes, ♪
♪ kid...? ♪
We got to get past
those bodyguards.
We're not gonna have to,
'cause he's gonna come to us.
Come on. What?
Excuse me! Step aside, please.
All right.
This is, this is
gonna go fast.
When I, when I pull the alarm,
the crowds are gonna head
towards the two exits.
He's gonna head towards
the nearest one,
which is northeast, I will
bump into him in the crowd.
I will grab the cell, place
the bug within the phone,
tell him he dropped his phone.
It's, it's, uh, something I
like to call a "cop drop."
Yeah. Got it.
Okay, here we go.
My God, there are absolutely no
wires attached to this thing.
Now, what is that? What,
is that gum or is that...?
No, that's Silly Putty?
I mean, why is it...? Don't
touch it, it's a condom.
All right, he's on the move.
Okay, we got to get
out there and shake
our asses like the
rest of the foxes.
Ah, oh, yes, yes, yes,
dancing to get close to him...
that is a fantastic idea.
Okay, here we go.
Jesus, don't do it.
Don't, don't. What?
What, why are we...? Don't
do anything you're doing.
But, but he's over that way.
Just... let's go
find a bathroom.
I told you, I don't have
to use the bathroom.
Did I ask you about
your bathroom habits?
You are killing us out there.
You don't fit in.
Take off that fucking jacket.
Well, this is a, this is a good jacket.
This is...
Really? 'Cause you look like
you're gonna set up a table
and do their fucking taxes.
Take off your jacket.
My God, this is ridiculous...
why...?
Your shitty jacket? My God.
Shhshh! Zip it.
Okay, jacket's off,
okay, jacket's off.
No, no, I can't watch whatever
process is about to happen.
Now unbutton your buttons.
I'm a federal agent.
I don't... Yeah, I know,
and you look like one.
Oh, God. You think you're
gonna bump into him
and he's not going to
think something's up?
Fine, fine, how's that?
Is that good, is that good? Can we go?
Can we please go?
I don't know how it's happening.
I think it's getting worse.
I... my fear is that I'm
gonna put you in a bikini
and you'll still look like
a fucking bank teller.
Okay, do you have to use
that language, do you?
I'm trying to make a point.
I'm saying your face and
whatever is underneath
this shitty outfit is maybe
not terrible. Oh, okay.
I'll have you know I
dress appropriately.
I, I, I like to...
I got it, I got it.
It's when this...
your big flapping mouth...
starts running,
and then you put
th this getup on top of it,
and it's, it's just a...
it's a boner killer, and
I'm gonna help you.
What are you doing, what are
you doing, what are you doing,
what are you doing? Now, I
just want you to shut up.
Oh, my God, just...
Oh, my God. Would you shut up?
I, I only brought five
of these to Boston.
Then, I'll, I'll cut
the other four.
God, that's terrible fabric.
This was... Just get
that off your wrist.
This was one of
my favorite ones.
Well...
God, just take it
off, take it off!
Just give me a second,
I'll take it off!
Okay, I, I look like
I've been attacked.
That's not my fault.
What, oh, it's my fault?
I'm gonna...
Let me even out the bottom.
Okay, would you just stop
carving up my clothes?! Stop!
I'm making shorts!
Everybody likes shorts.
Oh, my word.
Jesus, hold still.
Oh, please, just...
W... hey. That feels
awkward, weird.
Just don't touch that area.
Well, don't duck down.
You're gonna suck
my hand up there.
It's... will you pull...?
Stop pulling my pants off.
Jesus. What?
What are those?
What? What are those?
Stop, stop it.
They're my Spanx, they
hold everything together.
Why, what's gonna f...
come fucking popping out?
Nothing! It just
keeps everything
where it's supposed
to be, like in...
Shit, like medically?
No, no, not
medically, just to...
Uh, just keeps it right
where it's supposed to be.
You got to, you got
to vent that furnace.
Okay. That's a lot of
compression and heat.
It gets plenty of
ventilation, thank you.
My hand's a foot off and it's on fire.
Okay, okay, well, then
why don't you cut
these shorts shorter
because no one can
see my cervix yet?
Go ahead. I'll
cut 'em shorter.
No, I'm... stop it,
we're finished.
Okay, let's just do you now.
Come on, let's just...
I, I don't need,
I don't need that to...
What do you mean?
I put out my sexuality
through motion.
When this starts
going, it's all...
You'll get it.
So I have to look like this and
you get to look like that?
I know, it's not fair.
Oh, my God.
We got to tackle the helmet.
It's got a real...
style memory, huh?
Shit, you got to... you got
to flip that shit over.
Bend over. Why?
You look like Darth Vader.
Just flip it over.
God Almighty. God, just...
I gotta just finger tease
the shit out of this.
You're doing what?
You're finger...?
I'm going to finger tease it.
What is that? What
does that mean?
Not what you want it to mean.
♪ Now I lay me down ♪
♪ to sleep...? ♪
Hit it!
♪ I just can't find ♪
♪ the beat...? ♪
What are you looking at?
I like how your friend's shorts
make me feel in my shorts.
I am sorry, that was much
cruder than I meant it to be.
I stand corrected
on the shorts.
Let's proceed.
Oh, God, we're dead.
Ah, one o'clock, one o'clock.
Mm, yeah. Let's do this.
All right.
Get in there, get in there.
How do you, how do you get in?
I don't know how you...
How do you get in? In,
back, back it in.
Yeah, baby, yeah, let's go.
Get in there. Whoa.
Get your hands in, get your
hands in and get the phone.
Okay, Pinky. Yuck!
Do the fucking cop drop.
I'm trying to! Do the
fucking cop drop!
Oh, baby. I can't do
it from this position!
♪ Stoplight... ♪
No, no, no, no!
Okay, coming in one more time.
Get her away, get her away.
Aah! I got her, I
got her, I got her!
You're like a fucking gnat!
Picture time! Yes!
Damn it, can somebody
get my phone?
I got it, I got it, I got it,
I got it, I got it, I got it!
Let go, let go, let
go, let go, let go.
Thanks a lot, bro, and
close a couple buttons.
You Ahole. Ahole! Club policy.
Whoa, Jesus.
There we go. God bless.
I got it, I got
the orange one.
Oh, my God, I need,
I need some water.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
My God,
I will fucking kill you,
I will fucking kill you.
Oh, where is he, where is he?
Get in there, get in there, go.
Okay, coming one more time.
Get her away, get her away.
Oh, my God.
Jesus, there's
too many of 'em.
Hey, all right, hi, hi.
Your moves are weird as shit.
I got it. Aah!
Yeah? You have really soft hair.
And I love it.
Oh, yeah, oh, it's
the shampoo move.
Use your boobs.
Oh, yeah, uh, okay.
Use your boobs!
You see these, see these?
Oh, my God, yeah.
Yeah, look at 'em, look at 'em.
Oh, my... oh, my God.
I'm looking, I'm liking.
Shake it, yeah, shake it.
Oh, yeah. Shove him in
there, shove him in there.
I'll get her, I'll get her.
Get her away.
Hey, what is this?
What's going on, girl?
Whoa, yeah!
No. There we go.
Dave! Oh, God, back it in.
Am I in, am I in?
Get in there, get in there.
Whoa, please.
Hi. Hi.
You know, you're the
first chick over 40
to give me a boner.
Great, great.
Want to go get a drink?
Okay, yeah.
Maybe, maybe.
It's the only reason girls
hit on me, I think.
Oh, sorry, yeah. You know?
'Cause every night,
the hottest chicks...
they come in here,
they're like,
"Hey, there's LeSoire."
Short skirts, too much
makeup, just looking
like fucking gremlins, right?
Oh, I hate that.
Don't feed 'em, don't feed
'em after midnight, right?
Yeah. They turn
into more sluts.
Fuck it.
Give me a whiskey.
I just noticed that
lion, that lion.
It's just... that is amazing.
Fuck, who the fuck keeps
putting lions in the back?
Fourteen dollars.
Fourteen dollars?!
I Is it magic fucking whiskey?
Do, do I get a
motorcycle with it?
Is it gonna be served
in Jesus' shoe?
Can I sit on your lap?
Obviously. Okay, all right.
Yeah, let's... I like
where this is going.
Me, too, Me, too.
I love foam. My
nephew knows Seal.
Trying to get Seal
to come up in here.
Oh! I would love to, oh!
We're having a, uh...
Yeah? big foam party later.
Oh, I look forward...
Hey, hey!
Oh, shit... I'm plastered.
So sorry.
Fuck, get up.
Let's go. God, I am so sorry.
Hey! Come on, honey, get up.
Drunk bitch.
Get her the fuck out of
here, guys, come on.
Oh, God, she holds her
liquor like a fiveyearold.
I'm so sorry. Let's go.
I'm sorry. All right,
sweetheart, you're out.
I'm a pony! Time to go. Sorry.
I'm a pony! I'm so sorry.
Get her the fuck out of... yeah,
take her home. Come on, pony,
let's go. Hey, I got to drive
the school bus tomorrow.
It's my shift. What the
fuck are you talking about?
It's my shift! Here we go.
Come on, sweetheart, go. I
didn't get your number.
It's 21... 22... I'll
find you, I'll find you.
Oh, pretty nice, right? Wooh.
I have to say, that
was pretty awesome.
It really was, man.
Put 'er there. Put 'er there.
Yeah... no, put
'er, put 'er there.
Oh.
Aah! Don't do that.
What? You just make it odd.
I'm trying so hard not
to lash out at you,
and you make it
really fucking impossible.
What was that about?
We got company.
Oh, shit.
Hold on,
I can lose 'em. Do you
want me to take the wheel?
No, I was a precision
driver at Quantico.
They thought I was the
instructor, I was that good.
Oh, shoot.
Lose 'em! I'm... What do you
think I'm trying to do?
Let me steer it, I... Stop
it, stop it, I got it.
Hold on.
Ha!
And that, that is how
you lose a tail.
Nicely done. Yes.
I'm surprised.
Our friends are back.
I got it, I got it, I got it, tag out.
What are you doing?
I'll show you how I stop a tail.
Just tell me what
you're doing.
Watch out!
Aah!
FBI! Drop your weapon!
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
Special Agent Garrett, DEA!
Drop it!
No, seriously, what
the fuck are you?
What are you, fucking deaf?
I just told you.
DEA. Drop your fucking gun!
Now!
Shit.
I'm, I'm very sorry
about earlier.
I just thought you
were an assassin
'cause of your weapon.
And because you
look evil as shit.
Yeah, I get it, all right?
I'm an albino, so I look
like a bad guy, right?
No, no, that's not... Yeah.
That's not what we were...
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I'm DEA. Hmm.
And let me tell you something.
Two months we been
sitting on that club,
and then you two come
in here one night
like a couple of
fucking amateurs,
and you almost blow the whole thing!
All right,
obviously you have no idea
who you're speaking with.
I'm Federal Agent
Sarah Ashburn...
Yes, I am sure your
credentials are
quite impressive, as is your
choice of wardrobe there.
Nice hot pants. You
might want to try
shshaving above the
knee next time.
Are you giving beauty tips?
Do you own a fucking mirror?
Listen to me, all right?
This whole "female
professionals"
"in the workplace" thing, man,
I'm fine with it, all right?
But here's the problem, all due
respect, with you people...
is that you get all excited,
you let your
emotions take over,
your hormones kick in, you're
riding the cotton pony.
The next thing you know, you're
complimenting the bad guy
on his fucking couch!
Oh, well, all due respect
to you, who's your wife,
a fivepound bag of flour
with a hole in it?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
listen, ma'ams,
we've been cramped inside this
van for two months, all right,
and we're not gonna let you
swoop in from out of nowhere
and take all the credit.
I don't want to see you two
anywhere near this case.
We have got informants
everywhere.
We've got surveillance
We do not need the two of you
coming in with your estrogen
flying at full speed,
sticking out in the
middle of broad daylight,
fucking things up for us.
'Cause the two of
us are gonna bring
these guys in. Shit.
Fuck you, chalk balls.
Not even on your
birthday, sweetheart.
That's right, keep walking.
This isn't over.
Okay?
And FYI, women were b...
we were born
with hair on our legs. Yeah.
You don't have to stop.
Well, what are you doing?
Whoawhoawhoawhoa whoawhoawhoa!
Get...
Okay, do you want to tell me
what was wrong back there?
Nothing. I saw your face when you
were looking at the footage.
It looked like you saw
someone you knew.
Possibly your brother?
You did not read that
from my fucking face.
You read my file, didn't you?
God, you're an asshole.
Okay, yes,
I read your file, but
it is my job to know
everything about a case,
including who I work with.
I don't like that.
We should talk
to him tomorrow.
Where is he?
Probably at my parents'.
Well, then, let's go
to your parents'.
I can't... no, I can't
go to my parents'. Why?
I'm the one that
put him in jail.
Okay, never mind.
It's not like I
liked doing it.
You know, he got mixed up with
a lot of really bad people
and then he started... he
started using that shit,
and I just had to get
him out of there.
You know, iironically, a lot
of people become addicted
when they're in... in prison.
I think it's like 80,
85% of the inmates
require treatment.
I hate you.
Yeah, I know, I'm sorry.
But I... you know, I
actually wasn't finished.
I was going to say...
Why can't you just be quiet?
What the "F"?
These are cloth, they're nice.
I could have shot you.
Oh, I'm sorry,
do you not like someone
invading your privacy?
Oh, come on.
I, I glanced at your file.
You broke into my home.
I care about who I'm
working with, too,
and it's a little
uncomfortable
that you feel the need
to travel with trophies.
Okay, well, it's, it's
not what you think.
They moved me up here, they
rented this apartment, and,
and this is all my stuff.
These four shitty, sad boxes...
this is it?
This is your life?
Yes.
Oh, God.
I don't think that could be any
sadder if you threw it all
in the trash bag and started
dragging it behind you.
Oh, my word, you,
you use coffee filters for
toilet paper at your house.
I'm buying 'em anyway,
They have a dual purpose.
That's not what they're for.
Yeah, real fancypants.
I see it, I see it in here.
Looks like you were pretty
cool in high school, huh?
Yes, yes, III
was, but what...?
Because you weren't.
You know what that girl's not?
That girl's not cool.
My favorite part is, you
only have two signatures,
both by teachers.
Mrs. Burke said, "Have
a good summer."
That's a personal touch.
And then my real
favorite is this one.
"It'll get better."
Yes, fine.
Okay, now we're even.
Okay.
I see you have a cat.
Yep.
Is he around? 'Cause
I'd kind of like to,
you know, pet him and stuff.
He ran away, uh, when
I was in New York.
Oh, God, that kind
of tears me up.
Yeah, it was, um, it was a loss.
That cat got one look
at your shitty life
and said, "No fucking
thanks, man.
I am out of here."
I'm still
kind of just grieving a
little bit about it.
That fucking tabby is an
asshole, that's what he is.
Fuck you.
Fuck you... that's what
I say to that cat.
Goddamn it.
Oh. Such a shitty,
shitty little life.
Even the... you can't
even keep a cat.
Ah, you know, that just
hurts a little bit.
That's just the grief.
No, not the grief.
It's just the, the pounding
a little bit, just...
Oh.
All right, well, don't be
a dick about it, but...
Well, thank you for that.
That was...
All right, let's hit
the road, okay?
I gotta change.
What's the matter
with your pantsuit?
It's, it's pajamas.
Well, excuse the
shit out of me.
I didn't realize you
slept in a fucking tux.
W... Go ahead, get
your top hat.
You could get a
girlfriend and get a job.
You don't swear at me.
This is the place
where you're supposed
to be civilized. Okay,
stop yelling at everybody.
Okay? For once in your life,
be a mother. I don't know
why your whole family
is jealous of me, then.
Be a mother for once
in your life, just...
Some chicken?
Oh, great, this asshole.
All right, just take it easy.
Hey, Pop.
Hey, pork chop.
Ah, well, well, well,
look who it is.
Yeah, the rat's back in the house.
Nice.
What, did you come back
to arrest somebody else?
Hey, you know, I saw Ma threw
a can of, uh, Diet Coke in
the garbage the other day.
She didn't even recycle it.
Dad here... he's splicing cable
off the neighbors next door.
Hey, come on, now, Mark.
Maybe you should start
fingerprinting him, huh?
That'd be a good call, and maybe
get yourself some stripes?
Petey over here, how
many, how many songs
you download illegally off
the Internet... 5,000?
Ten, 20,000. 20,000.
Mikey stole a laptop
from his work the other day.
Stole? I fucking worked
there for six weeks.
I deserved to fucking take it.
Exactly... no health insurance.
That balances out, but not you.
You'll probably call in the
fucking SWAT team, won't you?
Uh, actually she could,
'cause these are
horrible examples.
Here are the nuggies.
All right, here we go.
What kind of an animal throws
her own brother in jail?
This kind of animal,
right here.
Shut up, shut up.
How about keeps him
from killing himself?
I was the only one that
got him off the street.
None of you fucks did.
You should never
arrest your family.
Who the fuck are you?
That's Gina.
Well, tell Gina I'm going to
strangle her at the table.
Hey, she is my best friend.
You touch her, you got
to go through me first.
Who the fuck are you?
I'll kill you and kill her
with your fucking dead body!
Okay, everybody calm down.
Shannon's right.
This one has no business
chiming in on a family matter.
"This one"? What,
why are you talking
about my girlfriend like that?
She wears sweatpants
to your mother's
dinner, that's why.
Those are her
classy sweatpants.
They don't say "Insert
Here" on the ass.
Her ass is hanging out!
Look at her, look at her
breasts at the table!
Welcome home.
Hey.
What, you here to arrest me?
I hope not.
You selling Bibles?
No, she's... Ashburn.
Let's go, let's go.
We need to talk. Go.
Sit down.
Really?
Okay, enough,
enough, all right?
Get your hands off me.
Uh, that is, uh,
that's one of the,
uh, better Jesus sportsthemed
paintings I've seen.
That's very good, nice.
What are you doing
at Club Ekko?
What are you, my mother?
What, were you following me?
How do you know I was there?
'Cause I know
everything, that's why.
Are you already working
for those guys again?
No, no, this guy Julian...
he sent for me
because he wants me to
start working for him,
but I told him, "No",
"I'm getting a straight
job," and it's fine.
We're... everybody's cool now.
Wewe... parted amicably.
Are you a "knock"?
I'm sorry? Are you a knock?
A knock. I d... I'm sorry,
I don't know what that is.
A knock. A knock.
Am I speaking fucking Japanese?
Yeah, listen to him.
I'm gonna sound
it out for you.
Are you or are you not...
a knock?
A fucking knock.
Like Johnny Depp
in 21 Jump Street.
Ah, I see, I see,
okay, aa narc.
A knock, yes. Ah, yes, yes...
no, I...
What are you...
what was I saying?
I was missing the "R"
when you were saying...
I heard "knock", but
apparently there's a "C."
He said, he said
"knock." I said,
I said fucking "knock," right?
Wow.
Why are you wearing a
longsleeved flannel?
It's hot out.
Eh, I'm, I'm a little
fluey, I was...
It's nothing. You
want, you want me
to break that thumb?
Please don't...
Want me to break that thumb?
No, no, no.
Mercy, mercy, mercy.
Straighten that arm.
Uh, it looks worse than it is.
Itlt's not a big deal.
This guy Julian, you know,
they don't want me to stop
working, they like me.
You tell me where I can
find Julian right now.
No, just stay out of it.
They're fucking maniacs.
They'll chop you up oor
gun you down or worse.
Okay, we're... Jason, tell
me what you fucking know.
I don't know anything.
I, I... ouch!
D D DDon't.
Okay, Sal, Sal Natale.
I'll rip it open.
Okay, you know Sal Natale?
Of course I know Sal Natale.
He was going to steal
this huge shipment
they got coming in,
so they popped him.
He's in the trunk of his Caddy
under the Charles
River Bridge.
I want you to stay
in this house.
If I catch you out
of this house,
I'm gonna hurt you
worse than them.
What are you, what, what
are you doing here?
What are you doing? No, I'm
a, I'm a federal agent.
I'm a special agent, and I...
Special, like retarded?
Well, we don't use that word.
We say "special needs," but
II have a very high IQ.
Are you a boy or a girl?
That's a fair question.
Uh, I'm, I'm female.
No kidding.
All woman.
From the getgo?
Um... No operation?
Um...
From birth, yes.
How you get that close
a shave on your face?
I need to go, but I'll
be back to, um...
Get back to the airport?
Yeah, nice knowing you.
To... uh, yeah, thank you.
Yep, that's Sal Natale, all right.
Hmm.
Bullet hole through the head.
That's unusually
civilized for them.
Oh, they cut out
his tongue, too.
Ah, there you have it.
They like to send a message.
Did you find the tongue?
Sure. Yeah.
Shoved it up his anal cavity.
Mmm. Ooh, that's
a weird message.
Yeah. The tip of the tongue
was sticking out of the rectum,
so it made it appear as if
his buttocks were giving
the police the raspberry.
Did they draw googly eyes or
anything on his butt cheeks?
No.
Seems like kind of an
opportunity missed.
That would have been funny.
Well, II feel that they were
just trying to be
tongueincheek.
God, don't do that.
Uh, where are his belongings?
Any clues as to where
the body was killed?
No. We're still looking
for their base camp.
Well, if there's anything on him
that will tell us,
I will find it.
Huh. What is that, coke?
I don't think so.
It's more like a coating.
Same traces found on all
the victims' shoes.
All of them had...
Epoxy powder coating. Right?
That's right. Yeah.
And each sample was made
up of the same ingredient,
which probably
means that they...
They were all
killed, same place.
Exactly.
I checked it out. Wow.
There are three places that
have this kind of powder.
Paint factory. Yes. Yeah.
I think we all know that.
Well, it's...
Take a look at this.
This one right here is
centered in the location...
Where all four... Where
all four dead...
bodies were found. Yeah.
dead bodies were found.
Right.
That's what I thought.
This one shut down years ago,
owned by a man by the
name of Leif Sa...
Saggle... Sagglemint.
Sambertineson?
Samber... Old Sagglemint.
Santino.
Santino. Santino. Oh, Santino.
Is that a derivative
of Sagglemint?
Get me the address to
that paint factory ASAP.
Excuse me, Ashburn? Um, I was
wondering if you would...
Okay, this is a little awkward.
Uh, it's nothing
personal, but as a rule,
I... I make it a point
not to date my coworkers, so...
thank you.
I was wondering if you would
not talk to me in that tone.
Oh. Oh! Yes, of course.
That's a little different.
Of course, yeah.
No, I... I wouldn't.
Why would I?
Why would you, really?
I wouldn't.
Just, we should go to
the paint factory.
Well, are we clear here?
'Cause I don't...
It got real awkward
between you guys.
No, it's... I think
we're all good, right?
Uh, we're... We're
really good.
Same page. Yeah.
'Cause I don't want any bad...
I think we are.
We're all good, right?
Okay, here we go.
Let's go to the paint factory.
She doesn't want
to date coworkers,
so spread the word. Shut up.
♪ Caught my man cheatin' ♪
♪ Now I'm rolling through ♪
♪ the West Side? ♪
♪ 'Bout to burn this fucking ♪
♪ house down, like I'm Left Eye? ♪
♪ Rest in peace ♪
♪? Like I'm Left Eye ♪
♪ 'Bout to burn this ♪
♪ motherfucker down? ♪
♪ Like I'm Left Eye ♪
♪ Heard my man is cheatin' with ♪
♪ another bitch at my house...? ♪
What is that shit?
Stop it.
Just cover me and go right.
Well, then, say that.
Stop making me
want to shoot you.
I don't know what
your problem is,
but we told you...
stay out of the city.
I don't know what it is.
Are you, uh... you deaf?
Shh.
Do you not, uh... do
you speak English?
I got to do something
with you, man.
Look, Julian.
I'm sorry.
I'll sell for you guys,
whatever you want me to do.
I'm just trying to
make some extra money.
Okay? You can't blame
me for that, right?
Relax. I totally get it.
Thank you, man.
I'm not going to shoot you.
Okay.
It's cool, man. Thanks. He is.
Wait, wait, hold on,
hold on, hold on!
Shit.
All right, if...
if we grab Julian,
I can get into his head
and we'll have
Larkin by tonight.
Two against two. I
like those odds.
I'm going to call for backup.
It's already here.
Oh, hey. Shit.
I was looking for you.
Um, I forgot to
get your number.
Cool. Yeah.
Uh, it's 1800
givemeyourfuckingguns.
That's... that's, uh...
that's... that's too many numbers.
Okay.
Met these disasters at the
club the other night.
Now they're both here.
You think you might
have been bugged?
Give me a break.
What the fuck?
Think you're hot shit?
Guess what? You guys look
even older in this lighting.
Come on. Fuck you.
Fuck you! It's not "fuck me."
It's "fuck you."
You know why?
Because I'm about
to fuck you up.
Pick it up.
Do it.
Give me a reason to
shoot you in the face.
How long is this going to take?
I don't know. Maybe 12
hours, hopefully less.
I have... I have to find
out what drives him.
We could just go in there and
beat him with a phone book.
No, no, no. For so many
reasons, no, okay?
You just need to be
patient, all right?
It is crucial... crucial
that you remain patient.
It's also crucial
that you stop wearing
that stupid barrette. What
are you doing? What...?
Don't... Just leave it. What
is the problem with this?
I mean, you have
one on your head.
Yeah, on top of my head,
like a normal person.
What is the difference?
Just move on.
Okay, if you enter that room,
you could break the bond
that we have created, okay?
Just please, please,
trust me on this one.
Okay, do you understand
how important this is?
Yeah, I do.
And you will be patient?
I will.
Okay. All right.
Hello.
Coffee?
I drink a little more coffee
than I probably should.
I... Aah!
Oh, my...
Where's Larkin?
You couldn't wait ten seconds?
Ten seconds? What's so funny?
You thinking you're
going to make me talk.
Yeah, you're talking
right now, dumb-ass.
You know, you look like one
of the Campbell's soup kids
who grew up and
became an alcoholic.
Oh, surprisingly catty.
You're a fucking genius.
I asked you to stay outside.
I need to go tough on him.
Oh, uh, are you not
already doing that?
No. I'm doing good copbad cop.
You know, I can hear you.
Shut up.
Just, please, don't
do anything crazy.
I'm not going to
What am I going to
do that's crazy?
I'm a police officer. Huh?
I mean, what, am I
going to shoot you in the dick?
Oh, my God.
You said nothing crazy,
and that is a nono.
Nono!
Turn around. I need you
to pass a polygraph.
Put it away. Turn around.
No! Don't worry. She's
not going to do it.
She's not going
to do anything.
Oh, okay, so you
want to just...
you just want to go and gamble
with your scrotum
and your testicles?
Okay, gamble away.
Just go to the corner.
I'm in it.
I'll tell you what
we're going to do.
We're going to play
a little game.
Okay? I'm going to take
out these bullets.
Except for this one, 'cause
this is my favorite.
I'm going to keep that in there.
And then you're going to
tell me where Larkin is,
and you're going to
tell me where and when
that shipment is
coming in, okay?
Right now.
I'm going to kill you
and everyone you know.
Aah! God, no.
Yeah, that's not what I
fucking asked you, is it?
Hey, straight arrow, take the
gun out of this one's hand.
Oh, now you want me
to save your scrotum?
When is the shipment coming in?
I don't know.
Hey, hey, all right!
ThThere's a shipment
on Wednesday.
Where? II don't know.
I swear. I swear to
God, I don't know!
Tell her! Just tell her where it is!
I swear to God!
I don't know! Jesus Christ,
don't shoot me in the dick!
I don't know! It's going
to be on Wednesday!
That's four shots! Don't
take any more shots!
Don't shoot my dick off!
No! Just tell her
where it's coming in!
Honest to God, I don't
know where the drop is!
Don't shoot me in the dick!
Hey! Enough! Stop it!
Hey! Hey!
You brought Julian
and LeSoire in?
What are you, out of
your fucking minds?
Wasn't too smart.
Oh, okay, so you're
not supposed
to arrest someone when
they commit murder
and then turn around
and try and kill you
at the same time?
Yeah, you wanted us
to keep them on the street?
Yeah.
You shouldn't even
have been there!
Larkin is the big catch
here, not those two.
Now we're never going to be able
to bring these fucking guy...
Enough. Craig, calm the hell down.
We can all hear you.
Yeah, dogs can hear you.
Yeah, of course
dogs can hear me.
Yep. God, are you okay?
'Cause you... you
look really pale.
It's a genetic condition!
Ashburn, come here.
Fucking snow cone.
Oh, I get it.
That's a good one,
'cause I'm really white.
Can I have a moment
with my agent, please?
I'm good.
All right. I'm going to
be right over there.
Right there.
Thank you.
Ashburn, why didn't
you alert anyone
once you found evidence
on Julian's whereabouts?
Sir, it was an unconfirmed lead.
I wasn't going to waste anyone's
time until I knew it was real.
Just give it a rest.
I want you to stand down
while I figure out
how to repair
all this shit with the DEA.
Sir, no, please. I...
I swear, I've...
I've been doing everything that
you sent me out here to do.
I... we've been doing
such good work.
I know. I know you are.
It's just...
I don't know, it's...
never easy when
you are involved.
Fuck that guy. Yeah, yeah.
Right? If you're not in trouble,
you're not doing your job.
Yeah.
We should go get a drink.
Right? What's the point of
being a cop if you can't
get one drink at the
end of the night?
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, II said just...
I just want one.
Yeah, oh, no, no. Here.
It is one. It is one.
Sometimes he just... he
likes to do this thing,
he pours them in three
little glasses,
but it's one.
All right. Here we go.
Fair enough.
Let's loosen that up.
Okeydokey.
There you go. There you go.
Keep a pace. Okay.
Don't spit that shit out.
It's not free.
Let's go.
Keep that in.
Hey. Ooh.
Yeah. Hey. How you doing?
I haven't heard from you.
Shit.
No. Yeah, you haven't.
Well, then, I mean, did I
do something wrong or...?
Okay, here we go.
It's not you, It's me.
Uh, I'm still working on myself,
so I can't be a part of two
until I'm a better one.
Okay, don't. You don't
have to do that.
Uh, wait, I still...
my favorite's coming.
Oh. You make me want
to be a better woman.
Okay, you know what? I
thought we had a good time.
Yeah, I... we did
have a lot of fun.
And now we're
going to move on.
Let it go. Okay.
All right. Cool. All right.
Hey. Hey, no hard
feelings, all right?
Oh...
Okay.
Okay, hit it.
Hit it. Okay. Okay.
Bye. Bye. That's good.
I don't know how
else to say it.
It's pretty clear. Yeah.
That's why you don't...
you don't feed strays.
Yeah.
Can we get two more?
Shots?
Six.
We should just get one
more of these, right?
I don't know, Mullins.
It's hard.
I know we're not
supposed to say this,
but being a woman in
this field is hard.
Well...
Men are just so intimidated
by me, which is, like, why?
And then you put your
personality on top of that,
and it is... Mmhmm.
It is off putting.
You know, I was, uh... I was
actually married for...
for six some years... same guy.
Was he a hearing man? Yes.
Yeah, he didn't, uh...
he didn't understand
how much the job meant
to me, so I thought it'd
probably be best
to just be alone
rather than to, you know,
compromise the work.
I get that. Yeah. Yeah.
It's kind of weird that it
does get lonely a little bit.
You know, and it's...
it's hard to make
female friends.
Yeah.
I hung out, you know...
really just with my...
my brothers and stuff
growing up, and... Yeah.
They just kind of all turned
out to be terrible people.
So that's kind of a bummer.
Your f... your family loves you.
I mean, in their own
unique... unique way, but they...
you know,
theythey love you, and
that's a wonderful...
Very unique.
That sounds like
it's coming from...
somebody that's an only child.
No, I...
I was actually raised with a
lot of children, so I had...
With the children?
What, in a circus?
Uh, no, just in...
in the houses.
Oh, my God.
You're a foster kid.
Yes, I was.
Oh, my God. Yes.
No... Jesus, that
clears up a lot.
Foster... foster kid.
That makes sense.
That's a tough go of it.
No, it was totally fine.
There was a lot of benefits
Toto being a foster kid.
Yeah? Yeah, oh, yeah.
You had...
on Christmases, there was
thisthis local drug store
it would sponsor... sponsor us
and give us little baggies of,
you know, toiletries, and stuff.
On Thanksgiving... Oh, shit.
We would... we would
hit these different
puttputt golf courses.
It was, you know, you'd
meet all kinds of
other kids. Other sad kids?
Yeah, no. No, no, no.
Oh, Jesus.
That is the saddest series
of images I've ever heard.
No, I don't think
it affected me...
I mean, in the long
run, at all, At all.
You're probably fine. You
know, I can see how maybe
it was, you know,
like, a little bit,
but not anything that's...
A little bit.
Maybe it has? Maybe it has.
May...? Oh, God.
Oh, God, my life. Yeah. Okay.
Ugh. Oh, God.
All right. Yep.
All right. Let it out.
That's it. Oh, God.
Good for you to start
working through it.
I don't feel well.
Oh, Jesus. I don't feel well.
I don't...
I... Wow. Well, you're not
making me feel great.
All right. Get it, get it.
Blow it out.
Really let it go.
You've got more than that.
You've got more than...
Oh!
Good job. Hey.
Oh, God, I don't feel well.
Good job. Do you
want some Jãger?
Oh, God. Oh, God, I feel sick.
Can we have two Jãgers?
Let's hear it!
♪ Dig. ♪
This is for you.
♪ The chills that you spill ♪
♪ up my back? ♪
♪ Keep me filled with satisfaction when ♪
♪ we're done? Oh, yeah, pump it. ♪
♪ Satisfaction of what's to come ♪
♪ Pump it, and pump it, and pull it. ♪
Sex walk.
♪ I couldn't ask for another. ♪
Look at it, look
at it, look at it!
Look at it. Giving
it to you, and...
♪ Your groove, I do deeply dig ♪
♪ Higher. ♪
♪ No walls, only the bridge ♪
♪ My supper dish, ♪
♪ my succotash wish? ♪
"My name...
♪ I couldn't ask for another ♪
♪ "... is Detective Mullins. ♪
You'd better lay
your ass down."
I smell bacon. I smell bacon.
I smell bacon.
♪ No, I couldn't ask ♪
♪ for another? ♪
Ooh, ooh.
♪ Groove is in the heart. ♪
Biscuits are done.
Big finish. Big finish.
Yes!
Yeah! Let's do it again.
Let's do it again.
No!
Stop playing this song. Why?
Because you played it
26 fucking times. Hey!
She's a foster kid. Yeah.
She got, like, Q tips and...
tampons and shit
for Christmas.
Yeah. She's had a horrible,
Yeah. Yeah! Fucking,
miserable life.
Look at her! Yeah!
All right. Play
the goddamn song.
Don't you fucking swear at us.
Ooh...
Oh, are we going to... Yes.
You celebrate your music.
Okay. Okay.
Everybody, get up.
Come dance! Come on!
Get up, you fuck!
Wooh! Get on.
Look, it's a frenzy.
We started a frenzy.
You're covered in nuts.
You're having a bad dream.
♪ Groove is in the heart. ♪
Uhuh.
♪ Groove is in the heart... ♪
What happened? Huh?
Let's give them...
let's give them a
little something...
Hold... God, hold still.
♪ Spin me around ♪
♪ till I fell asleep? ♪
♪ Then up the stairs ♪
♪ he would carry me.? ♪
♪ Girl, you're every woman ♪
♪ in the world to me? ♪
I love this place.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, to this... to this place.
To this place.
♪ Girl, you're every woman ♪
♪ in the world to me? ♪
♪ You're my fantasy ♪
♪ You're my reality ♪
♪ II don't feel it. ♪
I don't feel it.
Keep it up.
♪ Girl, you're every woman ♪
♪ in the world to me? ♪
♪ You're everything I need ♪
♪ You're everything to me... ♪
Oh, crap.
Oh, f...
Hey. Hey.
How long have we been here?
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Oh, crap.
Okay, focus.
Uh, you know what?
Here's this.
This counts as something.
That's it.
I'm all in.
Hey, how's it going?
Jesus, you've got to get
a mint in that Dumpster.
Oh, God.
Was I smoking
cigarettes last night?
Yeah, you kept taking them out
of people's mouths
and smoking them.
Oh, God, that's so nasty.
It was pretty gross. Why
is my jacket in the pot?
Oh, yeah, don't worry about it.
I'll get it right back.
All right, let's
see what you got.
Oh, shit.
That's great. Good evening.
That's great.
There you go.
I didn't think you were
going to care that much
about your jacket.
You didn't care at all when
you gave away your car.
Who did I give it to?
To Wayne. Who's Wayne?
Wayne. He just
walked out of here.
You were sitting on
his lap all night.
You had your tongue
down his throat.
What?!
Oh, God.
Feels like we've
been hibernating.
Didn't bother you last night.
Oh, Jesus, ten
missed messages.
Will you just... will
you get him, please?
Hey, Wayne! Ashburn wants
her underwear back!
I do not!
You cannot take that car.
It's government property.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I pay taxes, so
fuck the government!
Let's not, okay?
Wayne, get out of the
car, you asshole.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit, Wayne.
God, your first boyfriend.
You two were electric.
How did Julian escape?
Federal marshals transferring
him got ambushed.
We're not sure whether Larkin's
men followed the marshals
or if they got information
from the inside.
Yeah, you don't think
it's a little obvious?
Oh, fuck you!
I know when I smell a
fucking albino rat.
If you want to be pointing
a finger around here,
why don't you point it
right back at yourself?!
All right, yeah.
No, because if
you two hadn't
brought Julian in,
then Larkin would've never even
known that we were onto him.
And then this whole
case wouldn't be
the giant mixedup bucket of
shit that it is right now.
So fuck you and your
albino prejudice!
Now Larkin knows who you are,
and Julian's angry as shit.
If I were you, I would
get out of town.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Ashburn, he's right.
This isn't a choice.
No! No way!
You're not my boss,
Puss In Boots.
And even if you were my boss,
you still couldn't stop me.
I have more invested in this
case than any of you assholes.
And now you fucked it up, didn't you?
Mullins.
Yep, thanks.
That's another fuckedup
area of my life.
Thanks for bringing it up.
No, this was just
emailed to me.
Okay, fine. I guess
I'm out of line, huh?
Yeah, I'm gonna step back and
see what you assholes can do.
Yeah, go USA. Let's go.
We got to get my
family out of there.
They're gonna kill them.
You know, let me
just talk to Hale.
The FBI can arrange
everything.
No! Are you kidding? We got
a mole in there somewhere.
And I'm assuming it's
the fucking albino,
but we don't know.
Could be Levy.
It could be somebody
from my own precinct.
It could be your
boss, Puss In Boots.
We are going in there by
ourselves and doing it now.
Are you with me or not?
Okay, okay.
This is bullshit.
Why should we uproot our lives
'cause you're an asshole?
Go. Hey, don't talk
to her like that.
It's not her fault.
Are you sure you want
to bring everyone?
No, but it'd be like Schindler's List.
Dad! Come on!
We cannot fit that in the car!
I don't want them to take
my treasures. Jesus.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I'm
hoping, I'm hoping it's Vegas.
I thought you were outside.
Say byebye.
'Cause I'll get my boobs
done if we go there.
Say byebye. Say byebye. Say byebye.
No, no, no, no.
I'll call you when I get there.
Ow.
You are so rude. I know.
I'm so sorry.
This is my house. Can
you just go outside.
No, where are you going?
Outside.
I'll be right there. Outside.
Holy shit, I can see
through your shirt.
Oh, God, are you serious?
Oh, my God.
What are you doing
with the bat?
Just let 'em try to come over here, Shan.
Just let 'em try.
They're not going to throw softballs at you...
they're going to shoot you, moron.
Get your bag. Oh, would you get
over yourself, for Christ sake.
Bring it on, motherfuckers!
Not you, Mrs. Amendola.
Hi. Can I drive? Hi.
No, but if you could
make your way around...
Why don't you get
out and I'll drive.
But if you could make your...
I'm a really good driver.
Mullins!
Your Mom, your Mom.
Our lives are in danger.
Ma! Ma!
I may have to change my name.
Hey, come on.
What are you doing?
So if you get a call
from someone named Carla, it's me.
Stop! God Almighty!
When did you become such
a fucking princess?
You make it impossible.
You hear this?
All right, seat
belts, everyone.
Come on, buddy.
Right in here, buddy. No, no.
Highly allergic.
What the fuck is this?!
That's my puppy. I got him four months ago.
Highly allergic.
I named him Kevin Garnett.
No. No.
You're an asshole. You got to
see the cock on this thing.
We're going to a motel.
We're not bring... Move.
We're not bringing this
fucking horse to a motel.
We got to get Gina. For what?
Because you put her
fucking life in danger!
Nobody gives a shit about her.
If I'm going, Gina's going.
Get in there. I'm not
going unless we get Gina.
Just get in. We're
getting Gina.
Move your feet!
I'll chop them off.
Thank you. Shut up!
We're going to Gina's!
Everyone put your seat belt on.
God, I hope a truck
hits us and we all die.
Oh, God.
What the fuck is
this girl doing?
Could she go any slower?
Could she physically
go slower?
Go get your girlfriend,
for God's sake.
Um, okay, please.
She's fine, Ma!
I forgot my curling
iron, Mrs. Mullins!
Come on, Gina!
Get in the car!
What the fuck?
I got you the rollie so
you could roll the bag,
so get over here!
You kidding? You
bought me a bag
for Christmas so that I
could carry my own luggage?
Gina, come on. Let's go.
I'm gonna get you a
dicksucker for Christmas,
so I don't have
to do it no more.
Go get her! I'ml'm going!
Jesus Christ! Gina!
You really... you
didn't say that.
Oh, that got your attention.
Go on, go get her.
Come on, Pete,
just break up with this
girl, for fuck sakes.
This'll help. Come on,
you're making a scene!
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go, you assholes. Okay?
Let's go, Mark! You think
you're man enough?
Come on! You fucking
man enough?
Knock it off!
Just knock it off!
I got this, I got this!
Come on.
Hey, assholes! Get in the car.
You animals! Whoa!
Get in the car!
Did she just pull out a gun?
You know what happens now?!
You don't get this one! No.
So, uh, Jason, your
family seemsseems nice.
Yeah, we, uh, we
have our good days.
But my makeup is in that one!
I'll rip your
fucking pants off!
If we just knew where
that shipment was
coming into, we would have,
we would have Larkin and
we would have Julian,
they would both be there,
and we could get them.
I'm just happy that Jason, you
know, is out of there for now.
Yeah.
It's a shame, though.
Having your brother
on the inside
would be a, would
be a coup for us.
That's what you want to say?
'Cause you're saying
that out loud.
Okay, you know what, Mullins?
You would say exactly the same
thing if it wasn't your brother.
We're done talking about this.
So, if it was just some
random drug dealer,
you wouldn't send him back in?
If it was someone like,
I don't know, Rojas,
you wouldn't...
We're not talking about
Rojas, are we? Okay.
We're talking about Jason,
my brother, you fuckwit.
Okay, you know what?
We all have
a lot to lose if we
don't catch Larkin.
Yeah, what do you have to lose?
I have a lot. Yeah?
Some bullshit promotion?
You don't give a
shit about my family
or if Jason gets out
there and gets killed.
I feel that you're
not being honest.
Because nobody, nobody
forced your brother
to get involved with drugs.
You're an asshole for that.
Okay, you know what?
That's not helping either.
See, I'm trying to
create a dialogue.
Note that I am starting my
statements with "I feel."
I feel... Oh, I feel
like you're an asshole.
You know what I feel?
I feel that you have
worn that shirt
every single day this week, and
I feel that you turning it
inside out does not
make it a new shirt.
Well, I feel like it does.
Oh, really? Okay, well,
I feel I disagree.
Must be nice.
What? What? Must
be really nice
for you to just know everything.
To be so much smarter
than everybody else.
I... I don't profess
to know everything,
but I do know quite a bit.
And what I know is accurate
and scientifically proven,
and I just share that
information with you.
If you have a problem with that,
tune me out like
you always do.
Help! He's choking!
Okay, I've got it, I've got it.
He's choking, help!
Sir. Somebody call
an ambulance!
Okay, I got it. I got it.
Call...
Check his mouth,
check his mouth!
Nothing in there!
Okay, all right.
Let's lay him down.
Sir, just relax.
Everything will be just fine.
Let me get his head back.
Okay? Yeah, okay.
He's choking. You're
gonna be okay.
I need a, I need a knife
and a straw please!
I need a knife and
a straw please!
Why do you need a
knife and a straw?
Why? I need them
'cause I'm gonna
perform an emergency
tracheotomy.
What?! I'm gonna need
a glass of vodka.
Vodka! It's a Denny's!
Uh, for sterilization...
hot water.
Do you know what you're doing?
Have you done this before?
Technically, technically,
no, but I've been,
I've been doing some
research, and I feel
fairly confident I know how.
Fairly confident?
Jesus! He's still choking, you know.
It isn't time to stop.
Okay, sir, what I'm gonna do
is I'm gonna find your...
Oh, God, don't, please don't
put that in there. Shh.
Stop touching me... so, the
cricothyroid membrane...
I think, I think
it's right here.
I'm gonna make a small incision.
Please don't do that.
Let go of my hand, let go of
my hand, let go of my hand.
I'm gonna make a
small incision.
The reason I'm doing this...
Oh!
Oh, God.
Is because you're choking.
I'm gonna cut in...
Wow, okay, just a
little bigger.
Wow, okay, that goes in
deeper than I thought.
I'm gonna insert my fingers in here
because what's happening is...
Don't put your
finger in there.
Don't put your finger in there.
Wow, that feels a lot different.
There's the membrane, okay?
It's a fucking horror show!
Don't put your
fingers in there!
Sir, what I'm gonna do
is I'm going to insert
the straw in the hole.
And it's gonna allow the
oxygen to get to your brain.
Now if you give it one moment,
you're gonna feel the oxygen
flow into your brain.
There we go.
That's not oxygen!
Jesus Christ, that's not oxygen!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
That's a lot of blood.
What are you doing to him?
Oh, my God, ah! Oh, Jesus!
Oh, my God, there's
so much blood!
I don't know what I'm doing!
Stop crying! You did this!
Is the ambulance coming?!
You're fucking killing him!
I'm so sorry! I got it, I
got it, I got it, move!
I'm so sorry! What
are you doing?
So much blood!
You asshole! Oh, my God!
You probably could have just
pulled the piece of pancake
out of his throat.
He's alive, isn't he?
You know what? I have a cut
on my arm from earlier.
Do you think I
should amputate it?
You know you're not a
real doctor, right?
Yeah, neither are you.
Okay.
Yeah, byebye. You're
a reckless person.
See you later. Yeah, thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Byebye. Not you.
Oh, my God.
Ashburn.
Why don't you have
your own phone?
Who am I, the Queen of England?
I don't know, does the Queen of
England only wear sweatpants?
Fuck you. You... "F" you.
This is Mullins. Hey,
Shan, I left, all right?
I couldn't sit there anymore.
What are you talking about?
Where the hell are you?
Look, I talked to them,
and everything's
fine, all right?
Nothing's weird, we're good.
Nonono, nonono!
It doesn't work that way, Jason.
They know you're my brother.
Yeah, but they also know
you arrested me,
and I made it seem
like I hated you.
That's good, right?
Itit doesn't work that way.
What's happening?
Shut up for a minute.
Look, I know where the
shipment's going to, all right?
Okay, I don't give a
shit about the shipment!
What shipment? Just get
your ass back here now.
Let me talk... Look,
I'm gonna stick around
and work it or they're gonna
know something's weird.
Get off me. No, it's my phone.
Please trust me... I... I'm trying
to do the right thing here.
Are you, are you kidding me?
What?
Jason, Jason. Ow.
Jesus Christ. Jason! Ow!
Let go of my vest.
Shan. Ow. Jason, it's Ashburn.
What the fuck is going on?
Give it to me.
What have you got?
Don't talk to her! Look,
the shipment's coming
into the Boston Harbor
Shipyard at 11:00.
Okay. It's a big freighter,
tons of guys, all right?
No, I got it, I got... They're
gonna be heavily armed,
so you got to be
careful, you hear me?
Okay, okay. God, get off!
The ship is called the, uh,
"S.S. Tank" or something
like that, all right?
I promise we'll be there.
All right, II got to go.
Thank you.
I'll break your fucking arm!
God! Okay, take it easy.
Just take, just take it
easy, just take it easy.
Just...
Jason? Jason?
Shit!
You just made my
brother a dead man!
No, no, he's gonna be fine.
Mullins, I swear,
he'll be fine.
We'll... we're gonna
have thethe full power
of the, uh, the Boston FBI
down on that terminal
tonight, I promise you.
He's gonna be fine.
It really is a good thing.
You'llyou'll thank me.
Shut up!
All right. Ship's coming in.
Time to lock and load.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Police. Put your hands up.
FBI!
Get your fucking hands in the air!
Now!
Let's see them!
Boat's clean.
It'sit's not clean.
We found a joint in that
girl's purse. If...
Oh, now, this is
really a mess.
Sir, we just, we just have
to hit the streets again.
We hit the streets, a and
if the shipment came in...
Ashburn, enough.
It's over. I'm sending
you back to New York.
Sir, sir, nononono,
please, please.
I'ml'm telling
you, I'm so close.
I'm so close, and this was
just a little hiccup.
No, it wasn't a hiccup.
Lo siento.
Don't...
Don't even... Oh, God.
Uh, um, sorry.
Uh, Detective Mullins...
have you seen her?
Oh, hospital.
Some kind of family emergency.
Oh, God.
He's in an induced coma.
They shot him and left
him out in the street.
I'm so sorry, Mullins.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, he was
trying to move on.
He had a job interview.
I... I saw the résumé.
It was a terrible résumé.
He... mentioned prison,
and in "special skills,"
he said, "Keeping
it real," but he...
he was trying.
How'show's your
family holding up?
Well, they're not talking to me.
Blame me more now than ever.
It's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
Damn it, I should have
handled it by myself.
So that's it?
I'm not your, I'm not
your partner anymore?
No, you're not.
You're another fucking
disappointment.
I just want you to know
that I'm gonna find
the man responsible for this.
Hey, Shan.
Uh, that was wicked rude.
♪ You can live your life ♪
♪ In a crowded city ♪
♪ You can walk along ♪
♪ A crowded street ♪
♪ But the city really ♪
♪ Ain't no bigger ♪
♪ Than the friendly people ♪
♪ Police! Put your hands up! ♪
♪ Friendly people that you meet? ♪
♪ Really? ♪
Ugh, God.
♪ But it don't do ♪
♪ Too much good to be talkin' ♪
♪ Brother, when there ain't no ♪
♪ Ain't nobody listenin'. ♪
Hi.
Hey.
I'll give these back to you.
Thank you so much for your help.
Anytime.
Hey...
We're gonna miss
you around here.
Oh, I don't think so.
I might.
Oh...
You did a good job out there.
Just keep your fingers
out of guys' necks.
It's nasty.
Bye.
All right, if anybody
has any questions,
you come to Adam or myself.
That's all we got.
All right.
We sent out alerts to
airports, train stations.
DEA's gonna take the lead
on this one, all right?
Now, although this is
a joint task force, we're also
working with the Boston PD.
Right. Adam and I are gonna be
handpicking all the officers
so we don't wind up with this.
Ooh, ooh.
All right, any questions?
Hey.
Hey, that's not right.
No, it's not.
No, that officer that
you're making fun of,
the one that you're all laughing
at, has more integrity,
more commitment, more
courage and more guts
than anybody in this room.
Yeah. But less
mental stability.
Okay, okay, so, um,
justjust to be clear,
what does mental
instability look like?
Keeping people safe?
Protecting the community?
Getting the job done?
Is that what it looks like?
Well, then great.
If that's what mental
instability looks like,
sign me up for the crazy house.
That officer right there
is a better law
enforcement officer
than anybody in this room.
Myself included.
She is better than you,
she is better than you,
and she's definitely
better than you.
What are you doing?!
Are you texting?
Are you playing a game? What?
What is it? Put it away.
Put it away. God, you
guys are just...
What is, what is the
matter with you?
You're such, you're
just such jerks!
You're just such...
You're just a shitjerk!
You're just a
shitjerk dickfucker!
You're a shitjerk
dickfucker assholer!
And you all can just
go fuck yourselves!
Not... sorry, senor, not you.
Pardon, please.
Just, all you fuckers!
Get on the ground!
You are under arrest! Put your
hands where I can see them,
and tell me where
the fuck Larkin is!
Hey.
I think it'd be much more better
if you put your hands up.
"Much more better"?
Drop the gun and take a
grammar course, you idiot.
Who the fuck are you?
Me and her?
We're the fuckin' heat.
All right.
We've got some scumbags
to visit, huh?
Yeah, we do.
Get up, asshole.
Let's go.
♪ Ooh. ♪
Where's Larkin?
What? I don't even
know who that is.
Where is he?! I told you,
I don't know who
the fuck that is!
Really? Okay, so it's clean?
Clean? You not
finding anything?
Nothing in here?
Really, you...
Right, okay, hhold on a second.
How about this?
Right there!
Got your pizza.
Got your pizza, mister.
Just a minute, Lou.
Fresh hot pizza.
Get on your knees!
What the fuck is this?
Get down on the ground!
Where's your stash? I
don't have anything yet.
I'm waiting to get some
from a new distributor.
Who's your new distributor?
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh. ♪
Oh, shit, man.
Guess who.
Surprise. Hey,
man, come on, man!
Listen, I don't know
what y'all doing here!
I'm out the game.
You know what I hate? Drugs.
I'm a different man.
This is not mine.
I just bought that
refrigerator the other day.
This must have been in there.
We want to know where all
this new shit is coming from.
Where is Larkin?
Bitch, which part of "I'm
out" do you not understand?
I'm out!
You want to interview him?
Mm, no.
No, I think I have
something better in mind.
Oh, shit!
I don't know shit! Come on!
I don't know, you're getting
awfully heavy, Rojas.
Yeah, lie to me again.
I want to feel your body sliding
through my delicate hands.
I don't know shit!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I can't, I can't hold you.
No, I don't want to die!
I don't want to die!
Okay, okay!
It's at a warehouse
on Summer Street!
I'm almost disappointed.
Get me up!
All right, let's pull him up.
No, wait, I'm not
kidding anymore.
I really... I can't lift him up.
What?!
No! I can't lift him.
Shit, I've only done
this one other time,
and it was a really tiny hooker!
Lift my ass up!
You ain't fucking putting
nobody over no rails
you can't fucking lift them out!
Okay, okay.
Uh... just tuck your head
and relax your body.
Lady, what the fuck?!
God... Crap. Crap.
Get me up! Let me out!
Thankthank you again.
Thank you.
That was on me.
I take that.
I hope this ain't my car.
This my car? This my car?
Oh, shit!
My 2003!
Let's load up.
♪ Hey, I can be the answer ♪
♪ I'm ready to dance ♪
♪ when the vamp up? ♪
♪ And when I hit that dip, ♪
♪ get your camera? ♪
Nonononono.
Yes, yes. No, no, you
said that thing ticks.
Yeah, but not for days.
♪ The bitch ♪
♪ who wants to compete? ♪
♪ And I could freak a 'fit, ♪
♪ that pump with the peep? ♪
♪ And you know what your bitch ♪
♪ become when her weave in? ♪
♪ I just wanna sip that punch ♪
♪ with your peeps? ♪
♪ And sit in that lunch ♪
♪ if you're treating? ♪
♪ Kick it with your bitch ♪
♪ who come from Parisian? ♪
♪ She know where I get mine from ♪
♪ and the season...? ♪
Are you hungry?
I got a sandwich
I didn't finish.
Is that the same sandwich
you offered me a week ago?
It's cheese.
Cheese doesn't go bad.
♪ Ayo, ayo ♪
♪ I heard you're riding with ♪
♪ the same tall, tall tale, tall? ♪
? Telling them you
made some Made some?
♪ Saying you're grinding, ♪
♪ but you ain't going nowhere? ♪
♪ Nowhere ♪
♪ What you goin' do ♪
♪ when I appear? ♪
♪ Wwhenwhen I premiere ♪
♪ Bitch, the end of your lives ♪
♪ are near? ♪
♪ This shit been mine, mine ♪
♪ What you goin' do ♪
♪ when I appear? ♪
♪ Wwhenwhen I premiere ♪
♪ Bitch, the end of your lives ♪
♪ are near? ♪
♪ This shit been mine, mine ♪
♪ This shit been ♪
♪ mine, mine.? ♪
Baby formula. Yeah.
Cartels have been
smuggling cocaine
in baby formula for years.
Two of them, two of us.
I like those odds.
Boston PD! FBI!
Get down on the ground!
That's right,
that's how we roll.
Come on.
You guys all coming back
from break at the same time?
Unfortunate.
You guys get less attractive
everytime I see you.
Put the fucking guns down.
No, thanks.
Nice entrance, Teen Wolf.
What?!
You look like a Ninja Turtle, all right?
Take it easy.
I've held someone at gunpoint for
72 hours before... let's go.
Wewe need to do what
he says, all right?
What?!
It's the, it's the best thing.
What are we gonna do, shoot
our way out of this?
Okay, just put the
gun in the bag.
No, get your...
hold your gun up.
Just give them the bag and
give them everything! Come on!
Goddamn you.
I thought you had my back.
Put it in the bag
and slide it over, now.
It's in the bag!
Slide the bag over. Sorry.
I guess you and her
are engaged now, huh?
What?!
Well, 'cause you just gave me
a ring, motherfucker!
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Oh.
Get up. Get up already. Ow.
Oh, God.
No, no, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Pull it out.
Okay, that feels broken.
It's out!
Nice work.
How many of you are there?
Really?
Hey...
How funny.
This is like when you
were interrogating me,
only now you're tied up
and I got all these knives.
You know, I don't like, uh...
I don't like to shoot people.
I like cutting people up.
It's kind of what I do.
That's athat's a... I like that one.
It's... That's a good one.
It's a good choice, It's small.
a small one.
You like this?
Not too flashy.
This is actually a
oystershucking knife.
Either of you ladies need
your oyster shucked?
Not at the moment.
Not me. Not me.
You know, I got to tell you,
I've done this a... lot of
times to a lot of people,
but you two... you're gonna
be the most fun. What?
Larkin's here.
Larkin. Upstairs.
The fun'll have to wait.
The boss is here.
Can you, uh, please excuse
me a second, ladies?
Sure. Take...
Yeah, take your time.
whatever time you need.
Okay, cool. Cool.
Oh, also, um...
would you mind
holding this for me?
Well, mymy hands are
tied, but I can...
Oh, okay. Let me help you.
Ooh! Jesus!
Thanks.
Fuck! Fuck! FF... Shh.
Fuck, fuck, fuck! Shh...!
Breathe through the pain.
Yeah, do that.
Do that, do that.
Breathe it out, breathe
it out, Oh, my God.
Breathe it out. Okay, Mullins.
Oh.
If we should perish in here...
We're not gonna. All
right, just shh...!
I know I'm not very good with
my feelings... oh, God...
but I need to tell
you something, okay?
Okay, you are...
you are smart,
you are smart and
you are intuitive,
and you're the best cop
I'vel've ever worked with.
Oh, God.
You, too. Thank you.
You were right... I went back
and looked at the evidence,
and I think the Red Falls
Killer is innocent. Oh...
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Did you happen to
mention that to anybody
before you put yourself in a
lifethreatening situation?
No, no, I didn't!
No, I didn't!
Jesus! Good luck.
You're taking that to
your grave, probably.
Fuck, the other leg!
Oh, God. I got it. I got it.
You can move your chair,
too, you know? Just...
I am moving my chair!
Just grab the knife.
Grab the knife.
Take it. Take it.
Take it, just take it.
I'm sorry.
I got it!
Waah!
Shh. Shut up. Waah! Waah!
Shut up. Just come on,
come on, all right?
I am doing it as
fast as I can.
It's almost there, it's almost
there, it's almost there.
Whew... Come on. Got it!
Hurry up, hurry up...
hurry up, hurry up.
What? Somebody's coming up.
Got to put it back in. What?!
I got to put it back in,
and I'll put my hands
behind my back,
and then when he gets
close to me, I grab him.
But you got to shut up and
let me put it back in.
Okay, just put it
in, put it in...
Oh, my God, what are you...?
Jesus!
Sorry, it doesn't go
in that fuckin' easy.
Just... just... Just
shut up, shut up.
Ow! Motherfucker.
Oh... I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
I'll pretend... I'll pretend
to keep my hands tied.
Shut up! Shut up!
Oh, no, Scoob!
Velma and Daphne got captured!
Ah, I never thought I'd
be happy to see you guys.
Come on, we got to get
her to the hospital.
Did you guys call this in?
Yeah, I sent a fuckin'
owl with a note.
How did you even
know we were here?
We followed you. I
knew you weren't
gonna give up that easily,
especially not after
they greased your
shitbag brother.
Fuck you. You know, it takes
a lot more than Larkin
to take down a Mullins.
Wait, JaJason's not dead?
Come on, Adam. Larkin
is on his way.
What is this, a Q and A?
Can we fuckin' do this later?
Yeah, wait... did he
talk to the police?
Did he see Larkin?
Well, how was she
supposed to know? He's been in a coma.
Can you please
continue untying my leg?
That's too bad.
Where is he? Is he
at Boston General?
Why, are you gonna send
him fuckin' flowers?
Why are you so...
Oh, my God.
You piece of shit.
You guys are working
with Larkin.
I really wish you
hadn't said that.
Said what?
Oh, God! Oh, God. Shit!
God, that felt good.
God, it wasn't the albino.
I feel bad.
Yeah, no, he wasn't
working for Larkin.
He just wanted
you off the case
'cause he's a
misogynistic asshole.
Why are you doing this?
You getting some kind of,
what, a payoff, is
that what it is?
I was, in the beginning.
Six years dealing
with these lowlives,
making shit money.
Ah.
You're Larkin.
Holy shit.
♪ Tada! ♪
Get it? Right?
Makes perfect sense.
Uh, well, now I'm bragging,
but it's very nice
having a second income.
I heard shots. What the...?
Aw, the albino?
That guy was hilarious.
Boss, I don't think that
was such a good idea.
Yeah, well, you spend three
years in a van with him
and you'd kill him, too.
We'll pin it on LeSoire.
I've got to go to the
hospital to finish Jason.
You deal with these two.
No loose ends. Mmhmm.
Fuckin' rat.
We told you to stay
out of the way.
Goodbye.
You fuckin' rat!
See you, buddy. Don't
call me buddy.
He's actually a great guy.
All right, uh...
let's have some fun.
I've been waiting to
do this a long time.
Campbell's soup...
you're up first.
Please don't hurt us.
I didn't mean to say
that shit I said.
Please don't hurt us.
Aah! God!
Come on!
Son of a bitch!
Mullins, gun at 2:30! Mullins!
Get...
Get off! Don't!
You take one step, and
your partner gets it.
Oh. Ah.
Shit!
Nice.
Oh, my God... Oh, my God.
Look at me. Oh, God.
Look at me. Are you okay?
Oh, God,
I think I'm gonna throw up.
My God, it was a
really bad headbutt.
Yeah. Yeah. It was good.
But you're gonna feel it.
Go, go, go. Get
yourself untied.
And then we're gonna
go get Jason.
Okay, got it?
Why won't they answer my phone?
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, dickfucker!
Damn it, get off
the fuckin' phone!
Useless!
We got something.
I got it. I got it. Get
her on the stretcher.
No, no, I got it.
I got it! I got it,
I got it, I got it.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Oh, crap.
There you go. Oh, crap.
All right, got to turn.
Call 911.
You won't shoot me?
Well, just... yeah,
call it, call it.
Where's my brother,
you asshole?
Okay, you know, it's that kind
of language from your family
that forced us to move him to
the east wing of the hospital.
I don't know why...
Move, dipshit!
Jason, I'm coming!
What the fuck?
Come on, come on.
Stupid, stupid chair!
Screw it.
Eee... Eee...
Eee...
Shit. You know,
it's amazing what a little air
in the bloodstream does
to the human heart.
You may not want
to watch this.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
I just want you to know that...
I get it.
I get it. I mean,
I've been on the...
Eee... Eee... I've been on
the job a long time, and...
you just see so many
bad things and...
and bad people, and you...
you just start to
wonder if, you know,
is anybody good
anymore, and...
I just want you to
know that, you know,
you don't have to do this.
You don't have to do it.
I know.
But I do, because I have plans
that don't involve me going to
prison with people I put there.
So say goodbye
to your Mick brother.
Wait, wait, wait!
Drop it, or I'm gonna
fire this weapon.
Or I inject...
Oh, you shot him in the dick.
Twice.
Oh, shit!
I took a page right out
of your book, partner.
Oh, God, but I've
never done it.
I just... you know, I
just aim it at it.
I don't actually do it.
That's ffuckin' crazy.
What about Julian? I
take the bullets out!
What? I mean, I just use it
as a tactic to scare him.
I mean, Jesus, I'm
not fuckin' crazy.
Oh, my God, don't make me feel about it.
God! No, no, I know.
Hey, no, come...
Ooh, watch that leg.
You did good, little buddy.
You saved my brother's life.
Doing good. Thank you.
Yeah. Shit.
Internal Affairs
is going to open
a toptobottom investigation
of every department now.
Nice work.
Well, it was... it was
a team effort, sir.
Yeah. We put out
an APB on Julian.
Oh, don't bother,
He's in the trunk.
Oh, and, uh, sir...
uh, we're gonna have to reopen
the Red Falls Killer case.
Good for you.
I don't know.
I thought that would feel
good, but it felt awful.
You know, that's
probably gonna...
just keep feeling bad.
I'm glad you did it.
Should we be leaving the hospital?
Oh, shit. No.
Probably not. Probably not.
Spin it, spin it.
Okay, did it, did it.
Now, let's... let's
take this one though.
Okay. Is that clean?
Let's get you up here.
I'll get you...
It's clean enough.
Oh, my God, that smells. Get
off the leg, get off the leg.
Like several people
died on here.
Oh, my... Let me just sit.
Let's get your legs up.
No, I don't need
to be on my face.
You know, you can help the process.
Ow! God!
Not clean. Inchworm it up.
Come on. Come on. Okay,
okay, that's good.
Just flip me.
Get off the leg,
get off the leg,
off the leg.
Don'tdon't fall off.
Oh, my God. Okay.
Okay, I want this place
locked down, people.
Nobody goes in or out
without talking to me.
I want you three
stationed at each end
of the east wing. Let's go.
All right, let's clear
this hallway, people!
Let's go! What are you...
You two, get the
press out of here.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm good, I'm good.
Yeah, I knew you would be.
I'm good, too.
Excuse me.
You see this woman right here?
This is one of the best
agents in the FBI.
You make sure she's
well taken care of.
All right?
That was...
that was... that was
interesting, right?
I would look into that.
Yeah...
Oh, God! What is that?
All right. All right, let's go.
Oh, Christ.
Um, you actually
have to stay here.
Why? All right, well, just...
do what you can
to save that leg.
Oh, I'm not a doctor.
All right, fucktard,
I know you're not a doctor,
but tell it to the doctor.
How about that?
All right, I'll wait
right here for you.
Throw out that sandwich.
I'll bring you that sandwich!
No!
Throw it out!
You got it, buddy.
For outstanding service,
Officer Shannon Mullins.
There you go, Shan!
That's what I'm talking about!
There you go, Shannon!
Hold it up! Hold it up! Yeah!
Take out the gun.
Just a little snooze, man.
I'd like to cake toast to Jason.
Cake toast.
Yeah! To Jason. Yeah, dude.
May I have your
attention, please?
I wanted you to have this...
it was your grandmother's.
Aw. She would've been
very proud of you
taking care of your brother.
Yeah, that's...
that's awesome.
Take a picture.
Come on, take a picture. Oh, my God.
Are you serious?
"Dunkin' Jesus"? Yeah.
No cell phones.
How about now?
Oh, different story? Oh,
come on back. Jesus.
Ashburn. Hey, it's me.
Hey!
So, uh, you getting all
settled in your new digs?
Yeah, yeah, they're pretty...
pretty sweet.
Who needed that
promotion anyway?
I'm glad I stayed around where
all the action is, you know?
We got a lot of scumbags
we need to take down
here in Boston, Mullins.
Yeah, we do, right?
Hey, uh... Yeah.
Did you get that
package I sent over?
Oh! God, I haven't even opened it yet.
I'm sorry.
It's crazy, 'cause your Dad
sent me something, too, so...
It's, like, the
Mullins' gift day.
Hold on.
Oh. Okay.
I signed... signed it in front.
Does that mean you broke
into my house again?
Maybe, maybe not, right?
Yeah, it's amazing how that door
just opens up all by itself.
Okay, I see it.
That's very funny.
No, I know. I was just kidding.
Just look at the...
look at the back.
Oh, you wrote
something else mean
and profanityladen in the back?
Okay, here it is.
Well...
don't make it weird.
Later, nerd.
Takes a nerd to know a nerd.
Okay. You made it weird.
Bye. Bye.
I left my baby in the car.
Hi.
Hey. There's, uh,
there's been something
I've been thinking about a lot,
and it's been bothering me,
and... well, I got
you something.
Oh. Okay. Oh.
I found your friend.
Pumpkin!
Awesome, right?
I drove all the way
to New Jersey,
and I was up and down these
streets and looking all over,
and, you know, I was
just about to give up,
and I was over by
your old place.
All of a sudden I hear
this little Bell,
and I thought, wait a minute.
I looked in your neighbor's
window, and I saw
this asshole sitting
right on the couch.
I said, "You are
coming with me",
even if you don't want
to go back with her..."
Oh, he fought you, huh? Yeah.
Yeah, he fought me.
Wow. Pretty hard,
but I'm just glad
that, you know, I could
kind of make this...
reuniting... Yeah. Oh, wow.
What a surprise this is. Huh.
What a surprise, huh?
Look at where you are.
This was never your cat, was it?
Yeah, no, no, no, it isn't.
Goddamn it, put him in the box.
Put him in the box.
Oh, can you... can
you put him back?
I... well, do I have a lot of choice?
Well, can you...
make sure he's got...
lot of water?
Just don't. He
likes to snuggle.
Don't make me put the
cat down and punch you.
Subtitle improved by SELVAHEMA
♪ It's no use, ♪
♪ we're gonna have to fight? ♪
♪ Thrown your words round ♪
♪ a thousand times? ♪
♪ Like a child ♪
♪ who can't empathize? ♪
♪ You don't speak the language, ♪
♪ you don't read my signs? ♪
♪ You wanna know ♪
♪ what I really think? ♪
♪ what I really believe? ♪
♪ There's a fire burning ♪
♪ up in here? ♪
♪ See the smoke ♪
♪ coming out of my ears? ♪
♪ Oh, no, we both know ♪
♪ More trouble's gonna find us ♪
♪ if we're all alone? ♪
♪ I wanna show you ♪
♪ what I really mean? ♪
♪ But you're always ♪
♪ on the outside looking in? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ Come inside, ♪
♪ lie down in my head? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ I just wanna have you ♪
♪ up in my head? ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, heyhey ♪
♪ Look through my eyes, ♪
♪ I'm your binocular? ♪
♪ And everytime you'll get ♪
♪ a shock, you'll learn? ♪
♪ What's it like to be ♪
♪ in my dimension? ♪
♪ I'll be the center ♪
♪ of your attention? ♪
♪ Come listen ♪
♪ to all the sounds I hear? ♪
♪ The quiet prose ♪
♪ and the crack of the snare? ♪
♪ Make your Mark ♪
♪ on my territory? ♪
♪ Carve your name ♪
♪ in every cavity? ♪
♪ Oh, no, we both know ♪
♪ More trouble's gonna find us ♪
♪ if we're all alone? ♪
♪ I wanna show you ♪
♪ what I really mean? ♪
♪ But you're always ♪
♪ on the outside looking in? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ Come inside, ♪
♪ lie down in my head? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ I just wanna have you ♪
♪ up in my head? ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, heyhey ♪
♪ Look through my eyes, ♪
♪ I'm your binocular? ♪
♪ And everytime you'll get ♪
♪ a shock, you'll learn? ♪
♪ What's it like to be ♪
♪ in my dimension? ♪
♪ I'll be the center ♪
♪ of your attention? ♪
♪ Oh, no, we both know ♪
♪ More trouble's gonna find us ♪
♪ if we're all alone? ♪
♪ I wanna show you ♪
♪ what I really mean? ♪
♪ But you're always ♪
♪ on the outside looking in? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ Come inside, ♪
♪ lie down in my head? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ I just wanna have you ♪
♪ up in my head? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ Come inside, ♪
♪ lie down in my head? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ I just wanna have you ♪
♪ up in my head? ♪
♪ Oh, want a piece ♪
♪ of my mind? ♪
♪ Emphatic and erratic ♪
♪ at the drop of a dime? ♪
♪ Oh, want a piece ♪
♪ of my mind? ♪
♪ Climatic and dramatic, ♪
♪ like Jekyll and Hyde? ♪
♪ Oh, you want ♪
♪ to read my mind? ♪
♪ Emphatic and erratic ♪
♪ at the drop of a dime? ♪
♪ Oh, want piece ♪
♪ of my mind? ♪
♪ Dada, dada, dada, dada, ♪
♪ dadadada? ♪
♪ Like the blood ♪
♪ running through my veins? ♪
♪ This is my DNA ♪
♪ and my chemistry? ♪
♪ But from the pews ♪
♪ of the congregation? ♪
♪ You'll never know ♪
♪ the real salvation? ♪
♪ You wanna know ♪
♪ what I really think? ♪
♪ what I really believe? ♪
♪ There's a fire burning ♪
♪ up in here? ♪
♪ See the smoke ♪
♪ coming out my ears? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ Come inside, ♪
♪ lie down in my head? ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come into ♪
♪ my head? ♪
♪ I just wanna have you ♪
♪ up in my head? ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ahooh ♪
♪ Oh, want a piece ♪
♪ of my mind? ♪
♪ Climatic and dramatic ♪
♪ like Jekyll and Hyde? ♪
♪ Oh, want a piece ♪
♪ of my mind? ♪
♪ Emphatic and erratic ♪
♪ at the drop of a dime? ♪
♪ Oh, want a piece ♪
♪ of my mind? ♪
♪ Dada, dada, dada, dada, ♪
♪ dadadada.? ♪