AMERICAN MINISTRY OF MAGIC
NEW YORK, 1927
You'll be glad to be rid of him, I expect.
We'd be more than happy to
keep him here in custody.
Six months are enough.
It's time for him to answer
for his crimes in Europe.
President Picquery, Mr. Spielman, sir.
Prisoner is secured and ready
to travel.
You've thrown everything at him, I see.
It was necessary.
He's extremely powerful.
We've had to change his
guard three times, he's very... persuasive.
So we removed his tongue.
Grindelwald! Grindelwald!
The wizarding community worldwide owes
you a great debt, Madam President.
Do not underestimate him.
Mr. Spielman, we found
his wand hidden away.
Abernathy?
And we found this.
No more silver tongue, hmm?
You have joined a noble cause, my friend.
I know. I know. I know, Antonio
So needy.
FANTASTIC BEASTS: THE CRIMES OF GRINDELWALD
Subtitled by Clarity.
BRITISH MINISTRY OF MAGIC
THREE MONTHS LATER
They're ready for you, Newt.
Leta...
What are you doing here?
Theseus thought it would be good if I
became part of the Ministry family.
Did he actually say the
words “Ministry family”?
That sounds like my brother
Theseus was disappointed you
couldn't come to dinner.
Any of the nights we've asked you.
Well, I've been busy.
He's your brother, Newt.
He likes spending time with you.
And so do I.
Oi, you! Hop in, Pick.
Why do strange creatures love you so much?
- Well, there are no strange creatures...
- Only blinkered people!
How long did you get in detention
for saying that to Prendergast?
You know, I think it was a month that time.
And I set off a Dung bomb under his desk
so I could join you, do you remember?
No, I actually don't remember that.
Hello.
Theseus. We were just talking
about Newt coming for dinner
Really? Well...
Look, before we go in there I
It's my fifth attempt, Theseus.
I know the form.
This isn't going to be like
the other times. This is...
Just try and
keep an open mind, will you?
- And maybe a little less.
- Like me?
Well, it can't hurt.
Come on. Let's go.
Hearing commences...
You want an end to the ban on your
traveling internationally. Why?
Because I like to
travel internationally.
Subject uncooperative and evasive on
reasons for last international trip.
It was a field trip.
So I was collecting material for
my book on magical beasts
You destroyed half of New York.
No, that's actually factually
incorrect on two counts
Newt!
Mr. Scamander...
it's clear you're frustrated
and, frankly, so are we.
In the spirit of compromise,
we'd like to make a proposition.
What kind of proposition?
The committee will agree to lift
your travel ban under one condition.
You join the Ministry.
Specifically, your brother's department.
No.
I-that isn't my kind of...
Theseus is the Auror...
I think my talents lie elsewhere.
Mr. Scamander. The wizarding
and non-wizarding
worlds have been at peace
for over a century.
Grindelwald wants to see that peace
destroyed.
And for certain members of our
community his message is very seductive.
Many pure-bloods believe it
is their birthright to rule
not only our world but the
non-magic world as well.
They see Grindelwald as their hero,
and Grindelwald sees this boy
as a means
to make this all come true.
I'm sorry. You're talking about
Credence as if he were still here.
He survived, Newt.
He is still alive.
He left New York months ago.
He's somewhere in Europe. Where
exactly, we don't know, but...
And you want me to hunt Credence down?
To kill him?
Same old Scamander.
What's he doing here?
Taking on the job you're too soft to do.
Is that it?
Travel documentation denied.
Newt!
You think I like the idea of
Grimmson any more than you do?
Listen, I don't want to hear how
the ends justify the means, Theseus.
I think you're gonna have to
pull your head out of the sand!
Okay, right, here we go. What a selfish...
irresponsible...
You know, the time is
coming when everyone's
everyone's gonna have to pick a side.
Even you.
I don't do sides.
Newt.
C'mere.
They are watching you.
Well, gentlemen.
I assume this means
I have the job.
PARIS, FRANCE
Chérie?
Who's there?
This will be suitable
after a thorough cleanse.
I want you to
go to the circus now.
Give my note to Credence,
begin his journey.
When we've won, they'll flee
cities in the millions.
They've had their time.
We don't say such things out loud.
We want only freedom.
Freedom to be ourselves.
To annihilate non-wizards.
Not all of them. Not all.
We're not merciless.
The beast of burden
will always be necessary.
[London, UK]
Ventus.
Dumbledore.
Were the less conspicuous
rooftops full, then?
I do enjoy a view.
Nebulus.
How was it?
They're still convinced that
you sent me to New York.
You told them I didn't?
Yes.
Even though you did.
You told me where to find
that trafficked Thunderbird,
Dumbledore. You knew that I
would take him home and you
knew I'd have to take him through
a Muggle port.
Well, I've always felt an affinity with
the great magical birds..
There's a story in my family
that a phoenix will come to any
Dumbledore who is in desperate need.
They say my great-great grandfather had
one, but that it took flight when he died,
never to return.
With all due respect, I
don't believe for a minute
that's why you told me
about the Thunderbird.
Credence is in Paris, Newt.
He's trying to trace his real family.
I take it.
You've heard the rumors
about who he really is?
No.
The pure-bloods think he's
the last of an important French line,
a baby whom
everyone thought lost
- Not Leta's brother?
- That's what they're whispering.
Pure-blood or not, I know this...
An Obscurus grows in the absence of love
as a dark twin, an only friend.
If Credence has a real brother or sister
out there that can take its place,
he might yet be saved.
Wherever Credence is in Paris, he's
either in danger or a danger to others.
We may not know who he is yet,
but he needs to be found.
And I rather hoped you might
be the one to find him.
What's that?
An address of a very
old acquaintance of mine.
A safe house in Paris,
reinforced with enchantments.
Safe house? Why would I
need a safe house in Paris?
One hopes you won't, but
should things at some point
go terribly wrong,
it's good to have a place to go.
You know, for a cup of tea.
No, no, no, absolutely not.
I'm banned from international
travel, Dumbledore.
If I leave the country, they will put
me in Azkaban and throw away the key.
Do you know why I admire you, Newt?
What?
More, perhaps, than any
man I know?
You don't seek power or popularity.
You simply ask, is the thing
right in itself?
If it is, you do
it, no matter the cost.
That's all very well, Dumbledore,
but, forgive me for asking,
why can't you go?
I cannot move against Grindelwald.
It has to be you.
Well, I can't blame you,
in your shoes I'd probably refuse too.
- What...?
- It's late.
- Good evening, Newt.
- Wait. No!
Oh, come on.
Dumbledore.
Bunty!
Bunty, the baby Nifflers are loose again!
Well done
I'm so sorry, Newt.
They must have picked the lock while I was
cleaning out the Augureys
Not to worry.
I've fed nearly everyone,
Pinky's had his nose drops, and
And Elsie?
- Elsie's droppings are nearly normal again.
- Wonderful.
You can clock off now...
- I told you to leave the Kelpie to me.
- That wound needs more ointment.
I don't want you losing fingers over it.
Seriously, you go home now, Bunty.
You must be exhausted.
You know the Kelpie's easier with two.
Perhaps you should take off your shirt?
Don't worry, I'll dry off quickly enough.
Someone needed to let off some steam.
Ointment, Bunty?
You bite Bunty again and
there'll be trouble, mister.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
But I want you to go home now, Bunty.
- Shall I call the Ministry?
- No, I want you to go home. Please.
If you could just give it to me...
Honey, if you could just give it to me.
- He doesn't care. Hold it.
- If you could just give it to me.
Hey...
NEWT! Get over here, you maniac.
We hope you don't mind, Newt?
We let ourselves in...
it's raining
out there-cats and dogs!
London's cold!
But you were supposed
to have been Obliviated!
I know!
It didn't work, pal.
I mean, you said it, the potion
only erases bad memories.
I didn't have any.
I mean, don't get me wrong, I had
some weird ones...
but this angel...
this angel over here, she filled
me in on all the bad parts.
And here we are, I guess, huh?
This is wonderful!
Is ...Tina?
Tina?
Oh it's just us, honey.
Me and Jacob.
Why don't I make us some dinner, huh?
Yes!
Tina and I aren't talking.
Why?
Oh well, you know, she
found out about Jacob and
I seeing each other and
she didn't like it,
cause of the “law.”
Not allowed oops, not
allowed to date No-Majs,
not allowed to marry them blah, blah, blah.
Well, she was all in a tizzy
anyway, 'cause of you.
Me?
Yeah, you, Newt.
It was in Spellbound.
Here-I brought it for you-
Newt Scamander with
fiancée, Leta Lestrange...
brother, Theseus
and unknown woman.
No. Theseus is marrying Leta, not me.
Oh!
Oh, oh dear.
Wah.
So Tina read that, and she started dating
someone else.
He's an Auror. His name's
Achilles Tolliver.
Tolliver?
Anyway... We're real
excited to be here, Newt.
This is a, oh
it's a special trip for us
You see, Jacob and I,
we're getting married.
I'm marrying Jacob!
You've enchanted him, haven't you?
What?
I have not.
Will you stop reading my mind?
Queenie, you've brought him
here against his will.
Oh, that is an
outrageous accusation.
Look at him. He's just happy.
Then you won't mind if I...
Please don't!
Queenie, you've got nothing to
fear if he wants to get married.
We can just lift the enchantment...
and he can tell us himself.
What you got there?
Whatchu gonna do? Whatchu gonna do with
that, Mr. Scamander?
Surgito.
Congratulations on
your engagement, Jacob.
Wait, what?
Oh no, you didn't.
Queen. A second.
Queenie!
It's very nice to see you.
Where the hell am I right now?
Uh, uh, London.
Oh! I always wanted to go here!
Queenie!
Oh Queenie, honey.
Well, I'm just curious, when were you going
to wake me up? After we'd had five kids?
- Why is it wrong to want to marry you?
- Okay.
To wanna have a family?
I just want what everyone
else has, that's all.
Okay, wait..
We talked about this,
like, a million times.
If we get married and
they find out, they're
gonna throw you in
jail, sweetheart.
I can't have that.
They don't like people like me
marrying people like you.
I ain't a wizard. I'm just me.
They're really progressive here, and
they'll let us get married properly.
Sweetheart, you don't need to enchant me.
I'm already enchanted!
I love you so much.
- Yeah??
- Yeah.
But I can't have you risking
everything like this, you know?
You're not giving us a choice, sweetheart.
You're not givin' me a choice.
One of us had to be brave, and you
were being a coward!
I was being a coward?
If I'm a coward, you're...
Crazy!
I didn't say it...
You didn't have to.
No, I didn't mean it, sweetheart.
Yeah, you did.
No!
I'm gonna go see my sister.
Fine. See your sister.
- Fine.
- No! Wait!
Queenie! No! Queenie!
I didn't mean it.
I didn't say nothing.
PARIS
My dear Queenie,
what a beautiful city.
I'm thinking of you, Tina.
Hey, Newt?
Down here, Jacob.
I'll be with you in a second.
I got my own problems.
BUNTY! DON'T FORGET TO
GIVE PATRICK PELLETS.
Queenie left a postcard.
Tina's in Paris looking for Credence.
Genius!
Queenie's gonna go straight for Tina.
Okay, we're going to France, pal!
Hold on. I'll get my jacket.
I've got it.
Oh. Beautiful.
BUNTY, GONE TO PARIS. HAVE
TAKEN NIFFLERS WITH ME. NEWT.
Nagini.
Credence.
I think I know where she is.
We escape tonight.
Hey.
I've told you to stay away from her, boy.
Did I say you could
take a break?
Clean out the Kappa.
And you, get ready!
Next in our little show of
freaks and oddities...
I present to you...
a Maledictus!
Once trapped in the jungles of Indonesia,
she is the carrier of a
blood curse.
Such Under-beings are destined,
through the course of their lives...
to turn permanently into beasts.
But look at her. So beautiful, yes?
So desirable.
But soon she will be trapped
forever in a very different body.
Every night, when she sleeps...
mesdames et messieurs...
She is forced to become...
Over time, she will not be
able to transform back.
She will be
forever trapped in the body of a snake.
Credence!
Pack it up!
Paris is done for us now.
The boy with the Maledictus,
what do you know about him?
He's looking for his mother.
All my freaks think they can go home.
Okay, let's go.
Look, I think we were both at the circus
for the same reason, monsieur ...?
Kama. Yusuf Kama.
And you think right.
- What do you want with Credence?
- The same as you.
- Which is?
- To prove who the boy really is.
If the rumors of his identity are
correct, he and
I are distantly related.
I am the last male of my
pure-blooded line.
And so, if the rumors are correct, is he.
Have you read The Predictions
of Tycho Dodonus?
Yeah.
But that's poetry, not proof.
If I could show you something better
more concrete, something
that proves who he is
would the Ministries of Europe and America
let him live?
They might.
Then come.
So...
Credence Barebone.
Nearly destroyed by the woman who
raised him.
Yet now he seeks the mother who bore him.
He's desperate for family.
He's desperate for love.
He's the key to our victory.
Well, we know where the boy is, don't we?
- Why don't we grab him and leave!
- He must come to me freely...
and he will.
The path has been laid,
and he is following it.
The trail that will lead him to me,
and the strange and glorious
truth of who he is.
Why is he so important?
Who represents the greatest
threat to our cause?
Albus Dumbledore.
If I asked you now to go to the school...
where he is
hiding and kill him for me,
would you do it for me, Krall?
Credence is the only entity alive...
who can kill him.
You really think that he
can kill the great...
can kill Albus Dumbledore?
I know he can.
But will you be with us
when that happens, Krall?
Will you?
Jacob, that man Tina's been seeing...
Don't worry, she's gonna see you.
And she'll see the four of
us together, it'll be just
like New York all over again.
Don't worry about it.
- Yes, but he's an Auror, Queenie said?
- Yeah, he's an Auror. So what?
Don't worry about him.
What do you think I should
say to her, if I see her?
Oh, well, it's best not
to plan these things.
You know, you just say
whatever comes to you in the moment.
She has eyes just like a salamander.
Don't say that.
Nah, look, you just tell
her that you missed her.
Right, and then you
came all the way to Paris just to find her.
She'll love that.
And then, tell her you're losing
sleep at night for thinking of her.
Just don't say
anything about no salamanders, all right?
Right. Okay.
Hey, hey, hey. It's gonna be all right.
We're in this together, pal.
Okay, I'm gonna help you out. I'm gonna
help you find Tina, find Queenie,
and we'll all be happy again.
Just like old times.
Who is this guy?
He's the only way I can leave the
country without documentation.
Now, you don't suffer from
motion sickness, do you?
I don't do well on boats, Newt.
You'll be fine.
Stir your stumps-it leaves in one minute!
Fifty Galleons.
No, we said thirty.
Thirty to go to France,
twenty not to tell anyone, I seen Newt
Scamander leaving the country illegally.
Price of fame, pal.
Ten seconds.
Jacob.
Seven.
Six
Four.
Three.
Two. One.
I didn't like that Portkey, Newt.
So you keep saying.
Follow me.
Confundus.
Come on. That'll wear off in a few minutes.
Appare vestigium.
Accio Niffler...
Get looking. Oi! Get looking.
That's a Kappa.
That's a Japanese water demon.
Tina?
Tina?!
What have you found?
And we're licking the dirt now.
Revelio.
Newt... what made those?
That is a Zouwu.
It's a Chinese creature. They are
incredibly fast and incredibly powerful.
They can travel a thousand miles in a
day
and this one could take you from one part
of Paris to the next in a single leap.
Oh, good boy.
Jacob, she was here.
Tina stood here.
She has incredibly narrow
feet, have you noticed?
Can't say that I have.
Then someone came towards her.
Avenseguim.
- Follow that feather.
- What?
- Jacob, follow the feather.
- Follow the feather.
Where is he? Ah, Accio Niffler.
Let go of the bucket!
Bienvenue Au Ministère
des Affaires Magiques.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you just said at all.
Welcome to the French Ministry of Magic.
What is your business, please?
I need to speak to Tina Goldstein.
She's an American Auror working
on a case here.
We have no Tina Goldstein here.
No, it's... I'm sorry there
must be some sort of mistake.
See, I know she's in Paris,
she sent me a postcard.
I brought it, I can show it to you.
Maybe you
can help me find her here?
It's just in here.
Oh rabbits!
If you can just wait one moment!
I know it's in here somewhere.
I definitely packed it. Where?
One second.
Please.
Could we at least stop
for a coffee, or like a...
Not now, Jacob.
This way. Come on.
Pain Au chocolat? Half a
croissant, or like, a bonbon?
This way.
Jacob!
Jacob?
Madame?
Tout Va bien, Madame?
She's home.
Qui est là?
C'est votre fils, madame.
Qui êtes-vous?
Are you Irma?
Are you ...? Are you Irma Dugard?
I'm sorry. Your name is
on my adoption paper.
Does this make sense?
You gave me to Mrs. Barebone in New York.
I am not your mother.
I was only a servant.
You were so beautiful baby.
And you are a beautiful man.
I have missed you.
Why didn't they want me?
But why is your name on my adoption
paper?
I took you to Mrs. Barebone
because she was supposed to look after
you.
She's dead.
How did the boy take it?
He's sensitive.
The Ministry won't be happy
when I tell them I've missed.
- They know my reputation..
- Listen to me...
The disapproval of cowards
is praise to the brave.
Your name will be written in glory
when wizards rule the world.
And the clock is ticking faster.
You watch over Credence.
Keep him safe.
For the greater good.
You know what I miss about Queenie?
Everything.
I even miss the
stuff that drove me nuts.
Like the mind reading.
I was lucky to have someone like her
even interested in anything
I thought.
You know what I mean?
Sorry?
I was saying, you're sure the guy
is here that we're looking for?
Definitely. The feather says so.
- Is that the guy we're looking for?
- Yes.
Sire.
Err... bonjour. Bonjour, monsieur.
Oh wait, no, sorry!
We were just wondering if
you'd come across uh, a friend of ours...
Tina Goldstein.
Monsieur, Paris is a large city.
She's an Auror..
When Aurors go missing, the
Ministry tend to come looking. So...
No, now I suppose it would probably
be better if we just report her absence.
Is she tall? Dark? Rather
Dark rather...
- intense?
- Beautiful.
Yeah, what I meant to say-
she's very-very pretty!
I think I saw someone like this last night.
- Perhaps if I showed you where?
- If you wouldn't mind. That would be...
- That would be lovely.
- Sure.
Tina?
- Newt!
- Expelliarmus!
My apologies, Mr. Scamander!
I shall return and release you once
Credence is dead!
Kama, wait!
You see, either he dies... or I do.
No, no, no.
Oh no. No, no, no.
Well, that's not the best
start to a rescue attempt.
This was a rescue attempt?
You've just lost me my only lead.
Well, how was the interrogation
going before we turned up?
Newt!
Well done, Pick.
- So, you need this man, you say?
- Yeah.
I think this man knows where
Credence is, Mr. Scamander.
Well, that'll be the Zouwu.
Come on, Newt, get out of there!
What were the three biggest
mistakes that you made last time?
Caught by surprise, sir.
What else?
Didn't parry before counter-curse, sir.
Very good. And the last one...
the most important one?
Not learning from the first two.
This is a school, you've no right
I'm the Head of Magical Law Enforcement and
I have the right to go wherever I please.
Out of here.
Go with Professor McGonagall, please.
He's the best teacher we've got.
- Thanks, McClaggan.
- Get out!
Come, McClaggan.
Newt Scamander is in Paris.
Really?
Cut the pretense. I know
he's there on your orders.
If you'd ever had the
pleasure to teach him, you'd
know Newt is not a great
follower of orders.
You've read The Predictions
of Tycho Dodonus??
Many years ago.
“A son cruelly banished
Despair of the daughter"
- Return.
- Yes, I know it.
There's a rumor this prediction
refers to the Obscurial.
They say that Grindelwald wants.
A highborn henchman.
I've heard the rumor.
And yet Scamander appears wherever
the Obscurial goes, to protect him.
Meanwhile you have built up quite a
little network of international contacts.
However long you keep me and my
friends under surveillance...
You're not going to discover
plots against you, Travers.
Because we want the same thing:
the defeat of Grindelwald.
But I warn you,
your policies of suppression and violence
are pushing supporters
into his arms.
I'm not interested in your warnings!
Now, it pains me to say it, because
Well, I don't like you.
But...
you are the only
wizard who is his equal.
I need you to fight him.
I cannot.
Because of this?
You and Grindelwald were
as close as brothers.
We were closer than brothers.
Will you fight him?
I can't.
Then you have chosen your side.
From now on, I shall know
every spell you cast..
I'm doubling the watch on you
and you will no longer teach
Defense Against the Dark Arts.
Where's Leta? We
need to go to Paris!
Theseus.
Theseus, if Grindelwald calls a rally...
don't try and break it up.
Don't let Travers send you in there.
If you ever trusted me...
Theseus!
Even Lestranges makes me feel sick.
You know she stays here every vacation.
Her family don't actually
want her home.
I don't blame them,
she's so annoying.
- Did you see her last week?
- Oscausi!
Professor McGonagall!
Lestrange has done it again!
Lestrange, stop running!
- Lestrange! Disobedient children! Stop!
- She needs to come back!
Shame on the House of Slytherin.
A hundred points! Two
hundred!
Get back here, right now!
Stop! Stop it! Stop it! You stop
it! Get back!
Miss, it was Lestrange. She's horrible!
Scamander... why aren't you packing?
I'm not going home.
Why not?
He needs me.
It was hurt.
What is that?
A raven chick.
Isn't Raven your family emblem.
Yes it is.
All right, Newt.
Be brave.
That's an unusual one.
So Mrs. Scamander fears what more
than anything else in the world?
Having to work in an office, sir.
Go ahead, Newt.
Riddikulus!
Well done.
Good job. Leta?
It's only a Boggart,
it can't hurt you.
Everyone's scared of something
I've been looking forward to this.
I don't want to talk about it!
They know me, or they'd hide.
They only nest in trees with wand quality
wood,
did you know that?
And they have very complex social lives.
If you watch them for
long enough, you realize.
Hello, Leta.
This is a surprise.
Finding me in a classroom?
Was I such a bad student?
On the contrary, you
were one of my cleverest
I said bad, not stupid.
Don't bother answering.
- I know you never liked me..
- Well, you're wrong.
I never thought you bad.
You were alone, then. Everybody else did.
And they were right.
I was wicked.
Leta, I know how painful the rumors
about your brother Corvus must
be for you.
No, you don't. Not unless you
had a brother who died too.
In my case, it was my sister.
Did you love her?
Not as well as I
should have done.
Never too late to free yourself.
Confession is a relief, I'm told.
A great weight lifted.
Regret is my constant companion.
Do not let it become yours.
Oh No, thank you.
Well, you've been real kind, but...
my sister Tina's
probably worried sick about me...
you know, banging on all the doors
and things...
so I think I'd better be going.
But you haven't met your host.
Oh, are you married?
Let's say... deeply committed.
You see, I can't tell
if you're making a joke
or if you're just...
French.
Hey, knock it off.
You stay right there.
I know what you are.
Quennie.
We are not here to hurt you.
We only want to help you.
You're so very, very far from home.
Far away from everything you
love. Everything that was comfortable.
I would never see you harmed, ever.
It is not your fault that your
sister is an Auror.
I wish you were working
with me now towards a
world where we wizards
are free to live openly,
and to love freely.
You are an innocent.
So go now.
Leave this place.
Hey, Newt, buddy.
Tina's up here. She's all by her lonesome
and maybe you want to come
up and keep her company?
I've been looking for food, and
I ain't found any. So, I guess I'm
gonna go upstairs and try my
luck in the-I dunno-the attic!
You're all right.
Relaxio.
Okay.
She's responded well to the Dittany.
She was born to run, you see.
I think she's just lacking in confidence
Mr. Scamander, have you got anything in
your case that might help revive this man?
I need to question him.
I think he knows who
Credence really is.
The scars on his hand suggest
an unbreakable vow...
- an unbreakable vow.
- Unbreakable vow. I noticed that too.
Lumos.
What was that?
There must be a water dragon in that sewer
they carry these
parasites, you see. They...
- Jacob?
- Yeah?
In my case, in the pocket there,
you'll find a pair of tweezers.
Tweezers?
- They're thin and pointy...
- Thin, little pointy things.
Yes, I know what tweezers are.
You might not want to watch this...
I can handle it.
Come on.
Oh come on.
Jacob, will you take that for me?
Calamari..
I must kill him.
Who?
Credence?
It may take him a few hours to recover.
The parasite's poison is quite strong.
I'll have to go back to the
Ministry with what I've got.
It was nice to see you
again, Mr. Scamander.
Hey, hold on one second, will you?
Well, hold on!
Wait! Tina!
You didn't mention salamanders, did you?
No, she just ran.
I don't know...
So you chase after her!
Tina. Please, just listen to me-
Mr. Scamander, I need to
go talk to the Ministry.
And I know how
you feel about Aurors.
I may have been a little strong in the way
that I expressed myself in that letters.
What was the exact phrase? “A
bunch of careerist hypocrites”?
I'm sorry, but I can't admire people
whose answer to everything that
they fear or misunderstand is “kill it”!
I'm an Auror and I don't...
Yes, and that's because
you've gone middle head!
Excuse me?
It's an expression derived from
the three heads of the Runespoor.
The middle one is a visionary.
Every Auror in Europe wants Credence
dead-except you. You've gone middle head.
Who else uses that
expression, Mr. Scamander?
I think it might just be me.
It's Grindelwald. He's
calling his followers.
It's too late.
Grindelwald's come for Credence.
He might already have him.
It's not too late.
We can still get to him first.
Where are you going?
The French Ministry of Magic.
That's the last place Credence would go!
There's a box hidden
at the Ministry Tina.
It's a box that can tell
us who Credence really is.
A box? What are you talking about?
Trust me.
You wanna come out?
Just for a little while?
Credence.
- Shh.
- What do you want?
From you?
Nothing.
For you?
Everything I never had.
But what is it you want, my boy?
I want to know who I am.
This is where you will find
proof of your true identity.
Come to Père Lachaise tonight and
you will discover the truth.
Father... why did you make me ...?
Wait!
I'm afraid we keep no food in the house.
Are you a ghost?
No, no, I am alive,
but I am an alchemist,
and therefore immortal.
You don't look a day
over three-seventy-five.
Hey, sorry we didn't knock.
No, no matter.
Albus told me some
friends might be dropping in.
Nicolas Flamel.
- Jacob Kowalski.
- Oh.
- I'm Sorry.
- It's alright.
I didn't.
Ah!
At last, we see some developments!
I've seen one of these before.
It was at the fair.
There was this dame there, and she
had a veil.. I gave her a nickel and
she told me about my future.
And she missed out on quite a bit actually.
Wait a minute! I know him. That's that kid.
That's Credence
Jesus.
Hey! That's Queenie! There she is
Hi, baby!
Where is this? Is this-is this here?
Yes. This is the Lestrange tomb.
It lies in the cemetery of Père
Lachaise
I'm coming, baby. Stay right there.
Thank you, thank you, Mr. Flamel!
- Ahh!
- Ooh no. I'm sorry! I'm sorry, okay?
Oh-look after
Mr. Tentacles for me.
- Oh no. I'm sorry, I gotta go.
- Please, you must not go to the cemetery!
Oh dear
- What's happening?
- Exactly what he said would happen.
Grindelwald rallies at the cemetery
tonight, and there will be death!
- Then you gotta go!
- What?
I haven't seen action
in two hundred years...
Flamel, you can do this. We believe in you.
The box is in the ancestral
records room, Tina.
So, three floors down.
Is that Polyjuice?
Just enough to get me inside.
- Who...?
- That's my brother, Theseus.
He's an Auror.
And a hugger.
What's happening?
Grindelwald's rallying. We don't know
where, but we think it's tonight.
- Be careful.
- Of course.
- Promise me you'll be careful.
- Of course, I'm going to be careful.
Listen, I want you to hear this
from me.
They think that Credence boy
might be your missing brother.
- My brother is dead. He died..
- I know. I know.
How many times, Theseus?
And the records, the
records will prove that,
okay?
- They can't lie.
- Theseus.
I want every person at
that rally arrested...
- If they resist...
- Sir-forgive me but if we go in too heavy,
- don't we run the risk of adding to the.
- Just do it.
I don't suppose you can Disapparate on
Ministry premises in France, can you?
No.
Pity.
- Newt.
- Yes, I know. I know there's-
Emergency! Emergency! A
tracked wizard, Newt
Scamander, has entered
the Department of Magic!
Newt!
That's your brother?
Yes, I think I may have
mentioned in my letters
that we have quite a
complicated relationship.
Newt, stop!
- Does he want to kill you?
- Frequently.
He needs to control his temper!
I think that might have been
the best moment of my life.
Quennie?
Queenie, honey?
Don't.
Don't move.
Puis-je vous aider?
Yes, this is Leta Lestrange.
And-I'm her...
Fiancé.
In you go.
Thank you.
Tina, about that fiancée business...
Sorry, yeah. I should
have congratulated you.
- No, that's...
- Lumos.
Lestrange.
Tina, about Leta...
Yes, I've just said, I am happy for you.
Yeah, well, I don't.
Please don't be happy.
Uh, no, no. I'm sorry. I don't...
Uh, obviously, I obviously I
want you to be.
And I hear that you are now.
Uh, which is
wonderful. Sorry.
What I'm trying to say is,
I don't want you to be happy
that I am happy because I'm not...
happy.
Or engaged.
- What?
- It was a mistake in a stupid magazine.
My brother's marrying Leta,
June the sixth... I'm supposed
to be best man Which is
sort of mildly hilarious.
Does he think you're here to win her back?
- Are you here to win her back?
- No, I'm here to...
you know, your eyes really are.
Are what?
I'm not supposed to say.
Newt, I read your
book, and did you...
I still have a picture
of you-wait, did you read?
I got this...
I mean, it's just a picture
of you from the paper.
It's interesting because
your eyes in newsprint...
See, in reality they
have this effect in them, Tina,
it's like fire in water, in dark water..
I've only ever seen that.
I've only ever seen that in...
Salamanders?
Come.
Lestrange.
Records moved to Lestrange
family tomb at Père Lachaise.
Circumrota.
Hello, Newt.
Hello, Leta
Hi.
Oh no.
What kind of cats are those?
These aren't cats.
They're Matagots.
They're spirit familiars.
They guard the Ministry.
- But they won't hurt you...
- unless you attack them.
- Stupefy!
- Leta!
- Reverte!
Accio!
Ascendio!
Okay. Wait.
Come on.
All right. All right.
Wait.
Move back!
Move! Out of the way!
If you are looking for Credence, me too.
Stop!
Yusuf?
Is that really you?
My little sister .?
So, he's your brother?
Who am I?
I don't know.
I'm tired of living with
no name and no history.
Just tell me my
story-then you can end it.
Your story is our story.
Our story.
No, Yusuf.
My father was Mustafa Kama.
A pure-blood of Sénégalese descent
and most accomplished.
My mother, Laurena,
was equally high-bred-a noted beauty.
They were deeply in love.
They knew a man of great influence, from a
famous French pure-blood family.
He desired her.
Lestrange used the Imperius
Curse to seduce and abduct her.
I tried to prevent it but he attacked me.
That was the last time I ever saw her.
She died, giving birth to a
little girl.
You.
The news of her death
drove my father insane.
With his dying breath, my father
charged me to seek revenge.
Kill the person Lestrange
loves best in the world.
I thought at
first it would be easy.
He had only one close relative
You.
But...
Say it.
He never loved you.
He remarried not three
months after her death.
He loved her no
more than he had loved you
But then...
his son, Corvus, was born at last.
And that man who had never
known...
love was filled with it.
All he cared about was little Corvus.
So... this is the truth?
I am Corvus Lestrange?
- Yes.
- No.
Realizing that Mustafa Kama's
son had sworn revenge,
your father sought to hide you
where I couldn't find you.
So he confided you to his servant,
who boarded a ship for America.
- He did send Corvus to America, but...
- His servant, Irma Dugard,
was a half-elf...
Her magic was weak and
therefore left no trace I could follow,
I had only just discovered
how you had escaped
when I received news I never expected.
The ship had gone down at sea.
But you survived, didn't you?
Somehow, someone had
pulled you from the water!
A son cruelly banished
Despair of the daughter.
Return, great avenger
with wings from the water.
There, stands the despairing daughter.
You are the winged raven returned
from the sea, but I
I am the avenger of my family's ruin.
I pity you, Corvus,
but you must die.
Corvus Lestrange is already dead.
I killed him.
Accio.
My father owned a very strange family tree.
It only recorded the men...
The women in my family
were recorded as flowers.
Beautiful.
Separate.
My father sent me to
America, along Corvus..
Irma was to pose as a grandmother
with two grandchildren...
Corvus never stopped crying.
I never wanted to hurt him.
I only wanted to be free of him
Just for a moment.
Just a single moment.
They want us to put on life jackets!
You didn't mean to do it, Leta.
So it wasn't your fault.
Oh, Newt.
You never met a monster you couldn't love.
Leta, do you know who Credence really is?
Did you know, when
you swapped him?
No.
Queenie?
They're pure-bloods.
They kill the likes of us for sport!
- Quennie.
- Jacob.
Honey, you're here! Hi!
Hi, dear, do not.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry,
I never should have done it, I love you so
much.
- And you know that I love you, right?
- Yeah.
- Good, now let's get the hell out of here.
- Oh, wait. Wait a second.
I just thought maybe we could hear him
first.
You know, just listen, that's all.
What are you talking about?
It's a trap.
Yeah.
Queenie-the family
tree-it's all been bait.
We have to find a way
out of here, right now
You go find the others.
What are you gonna do?
I'll think of something.
My brothers, my sisters, my friends:
the great gift of your applause
is not for me...
No. It is for yourselves.
You came today
because of a craving
and a knowledge
that the old
ways serve us no longer.
You come today because you crave
something new.
Something different.
It is said that I hate Les Non-Magiques,
The Muggle.
The No-Maj.
The Can't-Spells.
I do not hate them. I do not.
For I do not fight out of hatred.
I say the Muggles are not lesser, but
other.
Not worthless,
but of other value.
Not disposable,
but of a different disposition.
Magic blooms
only in rare souls.
Oh, and what a world we could
make, for all of humanity...
We who live for freedom,
for truth.
And for love.
It isn't illegal to listen to him!
Use minimum of force on the crowd.
We mustn't be what he says we are!
The moment has come to share
my vision of the future.
That awaits if we do not rise up
and take our rightful place in the world.
Not another war.
That is what we are fighting!
That is the enemy.
Their arrogance.
Their power lust.
Their barbarity.
How long will it take before they
turn their weapons on us?
Do nothing when I speak of this.
You must remain calm
and contain your emotions.
There are Aurors here among us.
Come closer, brother wizards! Join us.
Do nothing.
No force.
They have killed many of my followers.
It is true.
They confined me
tortured me in New York.
They had struck down their fellow
witches and wizards...
For the simple crime of seeking the truth.
For wanting freedom...
Your anger, your desire
for revenge is natural.
No!
Take this young warrior back to her family.
Disapparate. Leave.
Go forth from
this place and spread the word.
It is not we who are violent.
Aurors, join me in this circle.
Pledge to me your eternal allegiance.
Or die.
Only here shall you know freedom.
Only here shall you know
yourself.
Play by the rules.
No cheating, children.
He knows who I am.
He knows what you were
born, not who you are...
Credence!
Queenie. You gotta wake up!
Jacob, he's the answer.
- He wants what we wants.
- No, no, no.
Why?
This has all been for you, Credence.
Walk with me.
Honey, no!
Walk with me!
You're crazy.
Not!
No! Queenie, don't do it!
Queenie!
Mr. Scamander.
Do you think Dumbledore will mourn for you?
Grindelwald! Stop!
Leta...
This one I believe I know.
Leta Lestrange.
Despised entirely amongst wizards.
Unloved, mistreated...
yet brave.
So very brave.
Time to come home.
I love you.
Go!
I hate Paris.
Together! In a circle,
your wand into the earth.
Or all Paris will be lost!
Finite!
I've chosen my side.
Oh come here. I've got you.
I've got you.
I think it's best if he
speaks to him alone.
Is he frightened of me still?
You need to be careful ..
He's not sure he made the right choice.
Be very gentle with him.
I have a gift for you, my boy.
Is it true about Leta?
Yes.
I'm so sorry.
It's a blood pact, isn't it?
You swore not to fight each other.
How in the name of Merlin
did you manage to get?
Grindelwald doesn't seem to understand the
nature of things he considers simple...
Can you destroy it?
Maybe.
Would he like a cup of tea?
He'll have some milk.
Hide the teaspoons.
You have suffered the most
heinous of betrayals,
most purposely bestowed
upon you by your
own blood. Your own
flesh and blood.
And just as he has celebrated your torment,
your brother seeks to
destroy you.
There is a legend in your family that
a phoenix will come to any member
who is in dire need.
It is your birthright, my boy.
As is
the name I now restore to you.
Aurelius.
Aurelius Dumbledore.
We will go down in history together
as we remake this world.