-[dogs barking]
-[minion] Stop-ah!
Stop-ah!
[panting]
-[chuckles]
-[ball squeaking]
-[barks]
-Uh...
Illumination!
[hip-hop music playing]
[bicycle bell rings]
[kids chattering and laughing]
[Max] Ah, kids.
-[barking]
-Everybody loves them, right?
-[boy laughing]
-You probably love kids.
Hey!
I gotta admit...
[kids chattering]
I don't.
That's me, by the way. I'm Max.
I'm the little dog right there,
grateful I'm not being
piled on by a horde of children.
[laughs] Wait for me!
Ugh! Can you believe that?
[chuckles] Having a kid looks like fun.
Nah, man. It ain't fun.
I'm telling you,
once the humans bring a kid home,
your life ain't the same.
-[barking]
-[screaming excitedly]
[scoffs] Seen it a billion times.
It changes you.
[Max] Now, I thought I never had to worry
about any of that,
but then one day...
-[gasps]
-[grunting]
-...my owner Katie...
-Hey.
met Chuck.
Are you okay?
Oh...
Uh... Yeah.
[laughs]
-[Max] A little while later...
-[Chuck] Hi, guys!
...they're married.
-[Max] Which-- It's great.
-[dogs barking]
Chuck is really-- He's a good guy.
[Max barks]
-But then something happened.
-Aw...
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[Chuck snoring]
[baby cooing]
[Max] Katie and Chuck
had a kid of their own.
His name's Liam.
[Liam cooing]
At first, he slept all the time.
Dreaming about, you know,
whatever it is that babies dream about.
Who's a cute little baby?
[Max] He had his place...
-You little cutie pie.
-[Chuck cooing]
...and I had mine.
Things seemed
like they were gonna be fine.
-[Liam babbling loudly]
-What?
Until he started talking.
[grunts]
And eventually, he started crawling.
[whimpers]
Sort of.
And suddenly, my own home
wasn't safe anymore.
-[giggling]
-[Busy Bee squeaking]
There was a tiny monster taking it over.
[Liam laughing]
Now, I did my best
to keep a safe distance.
[yells]
[laughing]
[babbling]
[Max] But then one day,
Liam did something I never expected.
Max!
I love you, Max.
-[Max] And from then on...
-[giggles]
...everything was different.
Duke and I, we became
like role models to him.
[Max and Duke laugh]
What can I say? The kid's a fan.
-We try to be a good influence.
-[whining]
[laughing]
Whoa! [grunts]
And we help him out whenever we can.
[giggling]
This kid gets us.
-[barks]
-[laughing]
-[both barking]
-Bubbles!
[Max] Yeah, we have fun.
Bubbles!
[Max] And by the way,
I'm still not a kid person.
I'm talking about this kid.
This is my kid.
He's perfect.
And I'm never gonna let
anything bad happen to him.
But I got to say,
keeping Liam safe is a full-time job.
-[gasps] Ah.
-[gasps]
-[Max] No, no, no.
-Ah...
-[giggling]
-Uh...
[both gasp]
[laughs]
-[babbling]
-All right.
[chuckles nervously]
Hey. Uh, hello.
Everything's cool.
Uh, we don't...
We don't want any trouble.
-[kid yelling]
-[horn blares]
-[steam hissing]
-[Max] Liam?
You okay there, buddy?
Was the world always this dangerous?
-[thunder crashing]
-[gasps]
[thunder rumbling]
[grunting]
-[Liam mumbles indistinctly]
-Huh?
Good doggy.
[sighs]
[upbeat jazz music playing]
[snoring]
Hmm.
[groaning]
[yelps]
-[purrs]
-[groans]
[grunts]
[meows]
-[meows loudly]
-[groans]
[gagging]
[yelps] No, no, no!
No.
[gags]
-[sighs]
-[meows]
Morning, Snowball!
Who's the best bunny
in the whole wide world?
-[toothbrush whirring]
-[Molly imitates whirring]
[sniffing]
[bubbling]
[TV playing indistinctly]
[superhero on TV] Take that, evil-doer!
Off into the sun with you!
Yeah! [mimics explosion]
Ears up.
[triumphant music playing]
[laughing]
[imitates whooshing]
I'm calling this meeting
of the Super Hero Animal Friends to order!
Commander Horsey, please read
the minutes from our last meeting.
Thank you.
Now remember, everyone,
crime is out there.
-We have to be ready!
-[Molly's dad] Come on, Molly. Time to go.
Oh, I'm gonna be late for school!
Captain Snowball,
you're in charge while I'm gone. [kisses]
First of all,
I want to welcome White Thunder
back from the washing machine,
who was put in there with a red blanket,
and henceforth will be known as
Pink Thunder.
Okay, I'mma go check the perimeter.
[yells]
[sniffing, grunts]
Good morning, New York City!
[vocalizing Superman theme music]
[Max] Snowball.
Hey, Snowball, what are you doing?
What's it look like I'm doing?
I'm looking for crime, Tiny Dog.
I'm doing superhero stuff.
[mimics web shooting, laughing]
Let me tell you something.
Anybody comes in here looking for trouble,
oh, they gonna meet my partners.
I'm talking about Paw and Order.
[growls and screams]
Uh-huh. Okay, well,
you do know that your owner
is just playing superhero, right?
You're just wearing
some superhero pajamas.
Ha! Tiny Dog, you so naive!
Point me in the direction
of any animal who needs my help
and stand back!
[exclaiming]
-Death blow!
-[metal clangs]
[Kung-fu grunts]
Okay, okay, I got it.
So, uh, did your kid leave for school yet?
Yeah, yeah, no, she's got a quiz today.
Advanced spelling. She'll ace it though.
You know,
she writes her answers down in ink.
That's how confident she is.
That sounds really smart,
but you know what?
Liam is smart too.
In fact, I heard Katie say
that Liam's head circumference
is in the 80th percentile.
Oh, that's cool. That's a lot of head.
Hey, quick question.
Is he still peeing everywhere?
Can't control his bladder?
Yeah, he's-he's peeing.
But every pet knows,
if you pee on it, you own it.
And Liam, he's just thinking ahead.
Yeah, well, you still better train him
before preschool starts.
You don't want Liam to get a reputation
as one of those pee-pee kids.
Yeah, totally! Wait, preschool?
Yeah. He's around that age.
The baby bird is leaving the nest, TD.
No, no. Baby bird is staying put.
He doesn't need preschool.
He'll, you know, [grunts]
stay home, with me, where it's safe.
[Duke] Hey, Max.
It's, uh, no big deal,
no need to overreact,
but, uh, Liam just left.
Wait, what? Where did he go?
I don't know.
They never tell the dog specifics.
Okay, okay, okay.
-[grunting]
-[toys squeaking]
This is Homebase to all units!
The package has left the building.
Does anyone have eyes on him?
I don't see him. Over.
[grunts]
Well, he's not in this bag of chips.
-Over!
-Okay. Keep--
Wait a minute.
Why would he be in a bag of chips?
[Norman on walkie-talkie] Homebase,
this is Eagle Eye. Don't you worry.
[yelps]
I had eyes on the package
as soon as he left the building. Over.
-[toy car beeping]
-[Liam giggling]
[grunting]
Subject is safe and sound,
enjoying what looks to be
a cookie shaped like a moose.
-Here you go. Nom-nom.
-[Norman] No, wait.
It's a reindeer. [sniffing]
Okay, thanks, Norman.
[grunting]
Scratching again there, buddy.
[grunts] I just...
I really don't like it
when they take him out without me.
[Katie] Hey, Duke!
-Ooh.
-[toy squeaking]
-[barks]
-What's this?
Oh, I know this! It's a ball!
-Go get it!
-[barking]
Hey, Maxie! What say we go for a walk?
[panting excitedly]
You know, I got to say, this is nice.
-Good to stretch the legs.
-[dog whimpering]
No, I don't wanna go to the vet!
The vet! No! No, no, no!
Oh, not cool! You tricked me!
-Maxie, come on, boy.
-[whining]
[whimpering]
You've been so stressed lately,
but this vet is gonna help you.
-Let's go, buddy.
-[whines, barks]
[door bell tinkles]
[Muzak plays softly over speakers]
-[whimpering]
-[sighs]
-[grunts]
-[whines]
-All right.
-[parrot squawking]
[whimpering]
Aw...
[whines]
-First time here?
-Uh, yeah.
Oh, Dr. Francis is the best
veterinarian in the business.
You're gonna love him.
He specializes in behavioral disorders.
-Behavioral disorders?
-Yeah.
But I don't have a behavioral disorder.
I mean...
[stuttering] I mean, I worry a little,
sure, but it's a dangerous world.
You'd be crazy not to... To worry.
Yeah, I'm fine, too. [chuckles]
It's my human that's nuts.
I mean, you know, I...
I bring her a dead bird,
she throws it out. [chuckles]
I bring her a dead mouse,
right in the garbage.
Is nothing I do good enough
for you, Mother?
[yowling, hissing]
-[hesitantly] Okay...
-[wheel squeaking]
I run, and I run, and I run,
and I run, and I get out,
and I've gone nowhere. Nowhere!
Uh...
My owner always says,
"You're such a good dog,"
and I feel like a good dog,
but what if deep down I'm a bad dog?
What if I'm a bad dog, huh?
[chuckles nervously]
[both] We start fires.
[screaming]
Max?
Come on.
I know, buddy.
It's just until we can get
this scratching thing under control, okay?
[gasps]
Busy Bee!
[grunts]
[straining]
[grunts, blowing air]
[groans]
[sighs]
[grunting]
-Max! Max!
-[exclaims]
Max! Max! You're never gonna believe it.
Oh, hey, I like your cone.
Listen, I heard Chuck tell Liam
that we're going on a trip!
Really? We're going in the car?
We're going in the car!
-[Max] Car! Car! Car!
-[Duke laughing]
Man, you know, life is funny.
One minute
you're getting fitted for a cone,
and the next, you get to go in a car!
Oh, I feel like that's very specific
to you, but totally! [chuckles]
-Yeah!
-[muffled] This is incredible!
I'll be right back.
Chloe?
[spring twangs]
Chloe, I'm going on a trip and I--
-[spring twangs]
-Oh...
I was wondering if you'd--
Will you watch my Busy Bee while I'm gone?
-Oh, hey, Max. Were you saying something?
-Ugh.
Yeah. I was wondering if you could--
Oh, God! Okay. Never mind.
What's that stupid thing on your head?
Gidget?
Gidget, are you home?
-[steam hissing]
-[gasps]
[grunts]
Mmm. Oh, hi, Max.
Do you want to join me?
Oh, you know what?
I really wish I could, but get this.
I'm going on a trip!
Wow! Really?
Yeah, it's a big deal!
I was wondering, could you
watch my Busy Bee while I'm gone?
[gasps] He is so cute!
I know. It's my favorite toy
in the whole world.
And that little face?
[chuckles] His little face.
Oh, and, and ready?
[Busy Bee squeaks]
Oh, wow! I love him!
Oh, I just... I just love him immediately.
It's like we're his parents.
It's like you're the dad and I'm the mom,
and we're in a relationship
and this is our baby. [chuckles]
-[hesitantly] Well...
-It's exactly like that! Exactly!
It's-- Okay, yes.
Yes, that's exactly what it is.
Uh, so, you'll watch Busy Bee
while I'm gone?
Max, you go, have a great time,
and I want you to know I have got this.
Thanks, Gidget! See you later!
I will defend Busy Bee with my life.
-[squeaks]
-[giggles]
["Me and Julio Down
by the Schoolyard" playing]
-[barks]
-[all chuckling]
Come on, Duke! Go!
Yes, yes, yes! How we doing, Liam?
-Whoo-hoo!
-"Whoo-hoo" is right!
[barks]
[chuckles] Okay.
-Yes!
-Here we go!
-Oh, wow!
-Whoo-hoo!
-Hey, man!
-I'm in a car!
Us too!
I love the car!
-It's the best!
-[laughing] Yes!
[Duke barks]
[slurping]
[giggling]
-Okay, come on, guys. Let's be quick.
-All right. Here we go.
[Liam laughing]
[Katie] Oh, no, no, no.
This way, buddy. Come on.
[Liam] No!
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[sighs]
[Busy Bee squeaking]
-[waves crashing]
-[seagulls squawking]
-[Busy Bee squeaking]
-[both chuckling]
-[both] Mmm...
-[Gidget kissing]
-[squeaking]
-[grunts, exclaims]
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
[gasps]
-[squeaking]
-No, no, no!
[grunting]
No!
[squeaking]
Gidget, what have you done?
[panting]
Huh?
[woman speaking indistinctly on TV]
[gasps] A-ha!
Okay.
-[squeaks]
-Huh?
-[squeaking]
-[meows]
[cats snarling]
-[hisses]
-[meows angrily]
[squeaking]
[cats meowing]
[shudders]
-[squeaking]
-[snarling]
-[honks]
-[yowls]
-[meowing]
-[fabric tears]
[yowls]
[yowling]
[squeaks]
-[cats snarling]
-[Busy Bee squeaking]
[hisses]
-[cat meows]
-[yowling]
Oh, dear, sweet Busy Bee.
[Busy Bee squeaks]
Yeah, I'm gonna be the first bunny
with washboard glutes.
I'm not even sure what glutes are,
but mine are gonna be shredded.
-[straining]
-Oh, yeah, yeah. That's, uh...
-That's fascinating.
-Let me tell you something.
[grunts] Criminals are gonna take
one good look at my glutes...
[exhales] ...and they just gonna give up.
Oh! Okay, this is obviously glued
to the floor.
[dog] Excuse me, rabbit, cat.
Do any of you know Captain Snowball?
Yeah, uh... Yes! Yes, we do.
And here we go.
Oh, good!
My name is Daisy
and I really gotta talk to him.
A poor, defenseless animal needs saving.
What? Are you saying...
Yes. I need Captain Snowball
for a top-secret rescue.
All right, well, I got to go.
But nice meeting you.
Uh, what was it again?
Okay, you don't listen. It's Daisy.
[Snowball] Whatever. Okay, I've...
I got to get the dude
to get the stuff to do the things...
Bye-bye.
Mmm-hmm.
That was weird.
Oh, sister, it's gonna get way weirder.
[Snowball grunting]
It's snow time, baby!
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[chuckles menacingly]
Help!
Anybody hungry? [yells]
[all] Huh?
[Snowball grunting]
[yelling]
[screams]
Oh, Snowball!
-[yelling continues]
-Uh...
Is he okay?
Not in any way. No.
[Snowball grunting]
Hello, citizens!
Who is that? Mmm-mmm-mmm.
I'm Captain Snowball.
I hear one of you needs my help.
-Ooh, that's me.
-Ah, very good.
New dog, tell me your story.
Okay. Well, it all began
when I was on my way back from vacation.
Our humans were safely stowed
in the overhead compartment,
and we were going
through our owners' stuff.
[chuckles] Humans always
blame the airline.
What do you got?
I'll trade you two socks
for a pair of workout shorts.
Are they clean or dirty?
They ain't clean.
[sniffing]
Nope. They're nasty.
[metal rattling]
[Daisy] And then, I heard a noise.
-[grunting]
-[rattling continues]
[grunts]
[growling softly]
-[chains clanking]
-[tiger cub groans]
-Now, I don't speak wild animal...
-[roars weakly]
...but from what I gathered,
he was a scared,
adorable tiger cub named Hu.
This poor baby kitty
was being held against his will.
Whoa.
-That is unbelievable.
-I know, right?
No, I mean I literally
don't believe a word of it.
No offense. Or do take offense.
I'm good either way.
Um, pardon me.
Offense is very much taken.
That story happened, and it gets worse.
After the plane landed, I saw Hu again.
[Hu groaning]
[Sergei yelling indistinctly]
He was being brought to his new owner.
You clowns are taking too long!
-[Daisy] And this guy...
-Time is rubles!
[Daisy] Y'all, this guy was pure,
concentrated circus evil.
That tiger needs Captain Snowball!
-Daisy, let's go.
-Yeah!
-[grunts] Let's free that tiger.
-Or die trying!
-Well, I mean...
-I mean, we might.
-Um... Huh?
-Probably you.
You wearing a bright suit.
Everyone's gonna notice you.
I'll be fine.
[whimpers]
[chickens clucking]
Hey, guys, we're here.
Oh, yay!
[Duke snoring]
[chicken clucking]
[laughing] Hey there!
There's Uncle Shep.
-Welcome to the farm.
-[both laugh]
-Where's my little man?
-[Liam laughs]
-[sheep bleating]
-[cows mooing]
Oh! Wow!
-Look at this place.
-Yeah, it's--
-[laughs]
-[gasps]
Oh, so many smells
I've never smelled before!
My nose is so confused! And happy!
[laughs] Come on, Max. Let's go explore.
[laughing]
-Yeah!
-Uh, wait up.
[laughs] Oh!
Hey, cow. Moo!
[bell tinkles]
You're a cow. You're supposed to moo.
-[laughs]
-Woof, woof.
-What?
-Oh, I'm a dog.
I'm wagging my tail like an idiot.
[panting]
[laughing] Okay, dude, not cool.
Oh, are you gonna throw a ball?
Oh, please throw a ball.
And I would chase it because
my brain is the size of a rat turd.
[laughing] Okay.
-Yeah, I get it. You made your point.
-[Max sighs]
Oh, look! I'm peeing on a tree.
-Okay. Yeah, great. Leaving now.
-I now own this tree.
-All right.
-I guess I'll just stare at the door
until you come back.
[Max] Oh, I miss New York.
[Duke] Maybe a break from the city
is just what you need.
This place is...
What?
[snarling]
-[screaming]
-[gobbling]
[Max] No, no, no!
[screams]
Duke! What did I do? What did I do?
[howls]
-[gobbles]
-[mooing]
Huh?
[growling]
[gobbling]
Whoa.
-[triangle tinkling]
-[gasps]
Dinner's on!
Chloe! I need your help!
[whispering] Chloe.
Oh. Uh... Oh.
Uh...
Chloe? Chloe, are you okay?
Shh.
Sorry. Uh, I'm just-- I'm-- [sighs]
Real quick.
Why is there a lampshade on your head?
[chuckles] Listen, Gidget, baby.
I got to be honest with you.
My owner might have given me
a little bit of catnip.
[chuckling] Whoa.
[laughing]
Oh, okay. Gotcha. That's great.
-Um, listen.
-It is great, Gidget.
-Everything is great.
-All right.
[purring]
-Do you hear that?
-Hear what?
It's like a tiny... Uh, like a tiny motor.
[purring]
It's like a humming sound.
-[purring continues]
-I'm not-- Don't know what you're--
Oh, Chloe, you're purring. [chuckles]
-That's you.
-What? That's me?
Like, as in the sound
is coming from inside of me?
-Yep.
-Oh.
I wonder what other sounds I could make.
[meows]
It's just, Max trusted me
to look after his Busy Bee, and then...
[purrs loudly]
Uh, Chloe, would you listen?
[meowing]
Wow, please stop.
[growling]
Are you finished?
[squeaks]
This is important! I lost Busy Bee.
I got to get it back,
but to do that, Chloe,
[sighs] I need you
to teach me the way of the cat.
[grunts]
Here we go. I'm gonna get you.
[grunting]
-[barking]
-[Uncle Shep chuckles]
-Max! Come on. Try to catch a firefly.
-I'm just--
That sounds great,
but I think Liam wants me near him.
-You know, he's a little freaked out...
-[sighs]
...being in this weird place.
I think he'll be okay.
-And this one is a jumper.
-[panting]
-Oh, okay. Just one.
-[chuckling]
-[grunting]
Yes! I-- [spits]
[groaning, exclaims]
[gasps]
[blabbering]
[dog growling]
[exclaims] Oh, hello.
Dog's got two things in this life.
His water bowl and his dignity.
You take one, you take the other.
I, uh... I didn't know this was your bowl.
What? The cone blocking your view?
It's got my name on the side.
We are so sorry, Mr. Chicken.
Name's not Chicken.
Do I look like a Chicken to you?
-No. No, sir.
-No, not... Not even a little.
Name's Rooster.
Oh, okay. I'm Max and this is--
Hey, what's that kid doing in the cage?
Something wrong with him?
He's got the fever?
-[cooing]
-[croaks]
That's-That's Liam. He-He likes to run.
-So, let him run.
-Well, Liam's super-fast.
[chuckling] We blink and he's up a tree.
So then, your kid's up a tree.
What's the problem?
-Well, he could fall.
-He might.
And then he hurts himself.
Oh, so, he got really high up
in this hypothetical tree?
I--
Kid gets hurt,
he learns not to do it again.
You know how many
electric cords I've chewed?
Like, multiple cords?
One. It shocked me.
I walked backward for a week,
but I never chewed a cord again.
Well, that is great for you,
and it explains a lot,
but I like to protect Liam
from everything.
[scoffs] Well, that's you.
And you're wrong.
-[scoffs] Can you believe that guy?
-Yeah. He was cool!
-No, he wasn't.
-I know. He wasn't cool at all.
Come on.
[Chuck] Let's get this guy inside.
[Katie] Thanks.
Whoa, hold up there. Dogs sleep outside.
-Uh, pardon?
-Huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay. Wait, wait.
Let's talk about this like rational--
All right, we're here.
In record time, too,
thanks to the Bunnymobile.
Oh, yeah!
Stealth mode! Let's go!
[thunder rumbling]
[grunting]
[grunts, exclaiming]
-[gasps]
-[thunder crashes]
[screaming]
You are jumpy.
I meant... [screams] That's cool!
Or... [screams]
Look at that thing
I'm not scared of right there.
Or... [screams]
There's a candy wrapper on the ground.
See? It's just a thing I do.
[screams softly]
-[whip cracks]
-[Sergei] Come on, you stupid tiger!
[whip cracking]
-There he is! Let's go!
-[grunts]
[Sergei] We don't have entire night!
[whip cracking]
[Hu groaning]
Let's go!
-[groaning]
-You're wasting Sergei's time!
[whimpering]
-We gotta do something! [gasps]
-[whip cracks]
[Hu shrieking]
[men shouting indistinctly]
Come on.
[whimpers]
We try again tomorrow.
If tiger does not do trick,
tiger will become rug.
[growls softly]
Do not let tiger out of your sight.
[wolves growling]
[groaning]
It's okay, Hu.
It's me, Daisy. From the plane.
[purring]
[chuckling]
Hey! Step away from the tiger.
Mind your business, wolf!
-[snarling]
-[all growling]
Oh...
[Daisy grunting, exclaiming]
[wolves snarling]
-[wolf whimpers]
-[snarls]
[grunting, yelling]
[lock clinks]
[grunts]
[snarling]
-[wolf barking]
-[screaming]
-[Daisy grunts]
-[wolves snarling]
Ha-ha!
[screams]
[growls, barks]
[Snowball panting]
[grunts]
-Oh! [screaming]
-[carnival music playing]
-[grunts]
-[bell dings]
Whoa! [screams]
Ah! Oh!
[growling]
-[screams]
-[snarling]
[laughing]
-[growls]
-[screams]
[screaming, grunts]
[whimpering]
Oh, I'm gonna die! Gonna die! Gonna die!
[screaming] Huh?
[grunts]
-[machinery whirring]
-[growls]
Huh?
[muffled] I got the keys. Let's go!
What?
I said I got the keys. Come on, let's go.
Uh, all right. Yeah, of course.
[whimpering]
[yelps]
[creaking]
[chuckling]
-[laughs] Heck yeah!
-[both] Boom!
-You know what I learned today?
-Hmm?
-Wolves are jerks.
-[chuckles]
[snarling]
[snoring]
[whimpers]
[grunting]
[whispers] Duke.
[snoring continues]
Psst! Duke!
I think we should check on Liam.
-Duke!
-I finally caught you, tail.
[groans]
[sighs]
-[bird chirping]
-Huh?
What's that?
[chirping]
-[rustling]
-[whimpers]
[cawing]
Okay. Okay.
[croaks]
[hoots]
-What?
-[chitters]
-[bellows]
-[whimpers]
-[chirping]
-[snoring]
-[whimpers]
-[munching]
-[gobbles]
-[farts]
[howling]
[screams]
[sighs]
[snarling softly]
[rustling]
[gasps]
-[snarling]
-[screams]
Wait, wait, wait. No.
Please, you don't want to eat me.
-I'm skin and bones! No, no, no!
-[Rooster barking]
[barking]
-[gasps]
-[barking]
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[chuckles sheepishly] Thanks.
He, uh, got the jump on me.
I guess he--
I couldn't see him because of the cone.
-Then get rid of the cone.
-Oh, man, I would.
I would, but my therapist says I need it.
Oh! Oh.
Okay. Well, that makes sense.
Yeah, it's a medical device.
These doctors-- [screams]
There, you're cured.
Hallelujah.
Not a fan. I am not a fan of the farm.
[Chloe] Okay, tail...
[giggles]
...ears and voilà.
Whoa! Gidget, you look so much like a cat,
it's crazy! [chuckles]
-Yeah! Who knew? So easy.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on. It's gonna take
more than fake ears and a sock, okay?
-You gotta learn how to act like a cat.
-Okay.
Okay, Gidge,
I'm going to throw some situations at you,
and you're just gonna, you know,
you're gonna react like a cat.
Gotcha.
Fetch.
-Yes!
-I'm gonna get it!
-Gidget! Stay.
-[gasps] But...
No! Cats don't care about fetching.
Fetching is for dopes.
[Mel laughing] Yes!
You're above that, because you are a cat.
Mmm.
[screams and grunts]
-Whoa! [whines]
-[exclaims in disgust]
You see,
dogs land like the clumsy oafs they are.
-Meanwhile, cats land on their feet.
-Really? How do--
[screams]
[grunts and gasps]
Yes! I did it! I landed on my feet!
-Yes!
-[muffled] Nice work!
[groans] Seriously, guys,
I think I broke something.
You gotta. It's a fact of life.
Absolutely not. Never gonna happen.
Guys, I found treats!
Oh, Mel... Ugh.
Okay, Gidget, eat Sweetpea.
-What?
-[chirps quizzically]
Cats eat birds. It's nature.
-Yeah, I'm gonna pass.
-[Chloe] No, no, no.
You used your one pass on the litter box,
so you have to do this.
-But...
-Bu-bu-bu-but do it!
You're seriously gonna
make her eat Sweetpea?
[whispers] No, of course not.
I'm just freaking her out.
-[Sweetpea chirps]
-[both gasping]
Okay! What's next?
Gidget, no! That's...
Bad dog! Bad cat-dog!
-[exclaims]
-[squawking]
-[chirping angrily]
-[grunts] Oh.
Sorry.
-Up!
-[grunts]
And tail in the face.
Okay, touch the butt to the cup.
[Mel laughs]
Walk on keyboard.
There you go.
Coffee on computer! And down!
-Nice.
-Yes! You got it!
Gidget, you're as close
to a cat as a dog can get.
[laughs]
[gasps] Cool! Now turn me into
a chinchilla! Can you do that?
-[chuckles]
-[chittering]
["Fantastic Voyage" playing]
Oh, yeah! First mission in the bag.
It was easy. Too easy?
Maybe. Maybe it was.
Hey, big fella! What did I do?
I just rescued a tiger.
No, I'm not even trying to brag.
I'm just telling you what happened.
See, that's the thing about being awesome.
When you awesome and you just tell
the truth, it sounds like you bragging.
Let me know when you finish
tooting your horn,
'cause we got to find a safe place for Hu.
Uh, what? What are you talking about?
-[metal clattering]
-Ahh!
[purrs]
Oh, yeah. That guy. Yeah.
Uh...
Yeah.
Oh, I got it! I know a guy
whose owner is never home.
-Yeah, we can just take him there!
-Sounds like a plan!
Super bunny powers activate!
Wait out here, buddy.
[grunting]
We'll be right back, okay?
[purrs]
[Pops singing]
♪ I'm a puppy, cute and sweet ♪
♪ Beg real nice and get a treat ♪
Hip, hip, hip,
Hip, hip, hip.
Hey, Pops.
-Who's that?
-[puppies] Bunny! Bunny! Bunny!
Uh... [screams]
I'm a hero! I need you to respect that!
All right. All right.
Ten-hut!
[groans]
Puppy school is in session!
Puppy school?
Now, the daily pledge. I promise...
[all] I promise...
...to listen to Pops.
[all] ...to listen to Pops.
And learn how to be adorable,
wide-eyed and loving.
[all] And learn how to be adorable,
[Pops] To get what I want, when I want it.
[all] To get what I want, when I want it.
Okay, now, Pops' quiz!
Myron has hidden socks all over the room.
Now, what do we do with human socks?
-Ooh! Me, me!
-Go ahead, Princess.
-We hide them, Mr. Pops.
-Correct-a-rooney!
And why do we do hide them?
Not knowing where one sock is
messes with the humans' minds.
Heck yes, it does!
Always keep them guessing!
Now, go find those socks!
What? Okay, all right. Okay.
Hey, Pops! What...
Okay, that's enough. Hey. What's going on?
Yeah. My owner got a new puppy.
My name's Tiny!
Nobody cares!
I was teaching Tiny
how not to be anyone's sucker.
Word got out,
suddenly, every puppy in the tri-state
area is scratching at my door.
Yeah. Oh!
-Professor Pops?
-Yes, Pickles?
I gotta make a poop.
Oh! You know where to do that.
Find a shoe.
-[chuckles]
-[laughs]
This is so sweet.
-Yeah, they're good--
-[Hu growls]
Holy cheese and crackers! What is that?
Myron! Horn!
[air horn blares]
No, no, no! Look, look. It's okay!
This beautiful creature is Hu,
and the good news
is he's staying with you!
Get that tiger out of here
before he does any more damage!
But we don't have
anywhere else to take him!
Well, he ain't staying here!
[puppies] Kitty, kitty, kitty!
Don't get attached!
That thing is out!
[all] Aww.
Oh! Pickles, did you poop in a shoe?
I pooped in a boot!
Your owner won't find it for weeks!
[chuckles]
[sniffling]
-Are you crying?
-What? No! You're crying!
But I'm just so proud of Pickles.
[clears throat]
Mr. Pops, please,
can the tiger stay with us?
Please?
[all] Please?
-[puppies whining]
-Argh!
Myron, look away!
[Hu whines]
[Pops] Oh, flap-doodle!
Okay, fine, one night.
[all cheering] Yeah!
-I taught you guys too well.
-[sniffling]
[blows nose]
[chattering]
[grunts angrily]
[whimpers]
[wolves whimpering]
I give wolves one job.
Guard white tiger.
And you wolves, you blow it.
Maybe I should make juggling
monkey head of security.
What say you, Little Sergei?
[squeals and chatters happily]
Yes, you are so smart.
And then there's this one.
-You're the worst wolf ever.
-[whines]
I swear, I-- [gasps]
[snarls]
What this?
[sniffs]
-This from thief of tiger.
-[sniffing]
-Yes, smell.
-[wolves sniffing]
[wolves barking]
[wolves growling]
You bring that tiger back!
And if you don't, that one...
[whimpers]
...will be a new coat for Little Sergei.
[chatters excitedly]
[all howling]
[all barking and snarling]
Oh, this is good.
You should really try this.
[babbling softly]
Max, book, book, book!
We're turning it again.
Oh, I'm sorry, Liam. We can't read.
Well, wait a sec.
There's no reason we can't
figure this one out together, right?
[giggles]
This first page,
there's a little girl in a red hood,
skipping through the forest
[gasps] with some food.
-Look at that! She's got food!
-[laughs]
[mimics munching]
[Max] And look at that.
She brought the food over to...
Hmm. Say, who is that?
Oh! Looks like her grandma!
Oh, I'll bet you're right.
Oh, that is sweet. She...
[Max and Duke scream]
So, Grandma had a pet wolf!
They had a great visit,
the little girl went home.
No one got eaten. The end!
[laughs nervously]
[Rooster] No, no, no.
That's not how the story goes.
Oh, we got this, thanks.
That wolf was gonna eat the little girl.
Nope! Thank you, Rooster!
-He already ate Grandma...
-[Max groans]
...and then he assumed
the old lady's identity.
-[gasps] No!
-Hey! Don't freak out my kid.
Take that, Mr. Wolfy! [blows raspberry]
Kid seems fine to me.
You're the one who's scared of everything.
I am not! I'm-- Tell him, Duke!
Yeah, yeah.
Max isn't scared of everything.
[stammers] I can think of, um...
Yeah. Yeah, well, there's a few...
-There's a few things.
-Okay, thanks.
You bet.
[all meowing softly]
Okay, this is it. You good to go?
Roger that.
[squeals and grunts]
Uh...
[meowing angrily]
That's a good kitty.
[growling]
-[hisses]
-[meows]
[indistinct chatter on TV]
-[fabric tearing]
-[meowing]
[whimpering]
-[Busy Bee squeaks]
-[gasps]
Busy Bee!
[squeaks]
[grunts]
-[gasps]
-[meows]
Whoa.
[grunting]
[gasps]
Oh, boy.
[snoring]
[exhales]
Okay, come on, Gidget.
[squeaks]
[gasps]
[snoring continues]
-[grunts]
-[squeaks]
-Uh...
-Huh?
-[roars]
-Oh! [screams]
Norman, now!
You got it, sister.
Huh?
[muffled screams]
[grunting]
[roars]
Busy Bee!
[squeaking]
[roars]
[cats meowing]
Whoa! Okay! Time for plan B!
Engaging plan B!
[all gasp]
[gulps]
She caught the red dot!
[all] Huzzah!
["La Marseillaise" playing]
[squeaks]
She is the Chosen One.
All hail the queen!
[all] Hail the queen!
All hail Queen Gidget. [screams]
[snarling]
[barking]
[snorting]
[barks]
Hyah!
[Rooster barking] Get in there! Faster!
Max, did you see that?
-Uh, yeah.
-So cool!
Oh, it's not that big a deal.
[Rooster grunting]
Move! Hyah!
Move it!
Oh, man!
Hey, look. That big guy got out.
We better get Rooster.
No, no. No need for that. I can handle it.
Hey, mister! Back inside! Come on!
Yep!
-[grunting]
-You're doing great!
Go underneath him!
Let's go!
I think he moved a little!
Don't you ignore me.
[grunting]
Oh, come on!
[Duke] Yep. Uh-huh.
Now go and do the front. No! No, back.
Now go to the side.
Max, Rooster nips at the cows
to get them to move.
Really?
That sounds drastic, but...
Okay, pig, you asked for this.
[squealing loudly]
Whoa!
[screaming]
[grunts]
[bleats]
[groans]
-Hey, Max. You okay?
-Yeah.
-What's going on?
-Don't worry. I'm fine.
-You let all the sheep out!
-I did?
Hey!
Get back in there. Come on.
Wait a minute. Where's Cotton?
Oh, he went into the woods.
[groans]
You. Come with me.
Where are we going?
We're gonna go get Cotton back.
Oh. Great.
-Come on, Duke.
-Oh!
-Duke, sit!
-Yep.
This is just you and me.
Oh, boy.
Come on.
Oh. Heh. Super.
Goodbye!
[whimpers]
[croaks]
Cotton! Where are you?
[grunts]
Come on. Hurry up!
Uh...
Okay.
[Rooster] Just jump!
Yeah.
[screams]
Ow, ow, ow.
[groans] Ow, ow!
Scent's getting stronger. Cotton's close.
[groans]
Oh, boy.
I can do this.
[panting]
I got it. I got it.
[screaming]
Ugh!
[grunting]
Rooster...
You know what? Just go on without me.
-Oh, you're not giving up.
-Yeah, but...
-[Cotton bleating]
-Follow me!
[panting]
[echoing] Cotton,
what are you doing down there?
There's apples in this tree!
All right, just don't panic.
Oh, man.
-Max is coming down to save you.
-Wait, what?
That tree can't support my weight.
You get down there.
[eagle screeches]
[stammers] I can't do that.
Sure you can.
Think of this as a game of fetch.
Now, go fetch the sheep.
No, no, no.
[stammering] It's too high
and I'm too afraid.
Max, here's a trick.
The first step of not being afraid
is acting like you're not afraid.
[chuckles nervously]
So, are you scared?
-No.
-Are you scared?
No! No, I'm not!
Now you're talking! Go get Cotton!
Hurry!
Okay. Okay.
[echoing] Hey.
[breathes deeply]
Okay.
[whimpering]
[screams]
Oh, no!
Listen, uh, Cotton, walk toward me, okay?
Okay, sure! But my leg is stuck.
His leg is stuck!
Well, unstuck it.
[sighs]
[whimpers]
[yelps]
-[whimpering]
-[branch cracks]
Hold on!
[Cotton] Whee!
-Okay, Cotton, listen, we gotta-- [yelps]
-[branch cracks]
Hurry up!
Ooh!
Whoa!
Ahh!
Come on!
[groaning]
[grunting]
[gasping]
[screams]
[whimpering]
[panting] Okay.
We're alive.
Yup.
[chuckling]
Yeah, we-- Oh, no!
Phew!
Yeah, we are!
-[sheep bleating]
-[distant barking]
[gasps] Max?
[chuckling]
Max!
-Get back in your pen, Cotton.
-Okay!
-No. Other way, Cotton.
[humming]
So, how did it go? What happened?
You know, it was pretty intense!
Tell him, Rooster!
You know, some stuff happened.
Now it's over.
Wow!
He can really tell a story.
Right?
[snarling]
[sniffing]
We are getting closer.
[wolves growling]
So there I was,
surrounded by nasty wolves.
-You asking was I scared?
-No one asked anything.
You just walked up to us
and started talking.
I was scared,
but I saved that tiger anyway.
Am I a hero? That's not for me to say.
-Boo-Boo? Boo-Boo, are you listening?
-I am.
Stop digging for a second, Boo-Boo,
and maybe you'll learn something.
As I was saying...
[stammering] Wolf!
Duh! That's what I've been talking about.
Wolves. [scoffs]
[wolves growling]
-Oh.
-[screams]
-[grunts]
-[wolf grunts]
[panting]
Uh...
[screaming]
[crashes]
[yelps]
[sniffing]
There!
[wolves growling]
[barks]
[gasps]
[chuckles nervously]
Where is the tiger?
Oh! There he is!
Huh?
What?
Hey!
So long, suckers! [blows raspberry]
[rock music playing]
Hah! Take that!
Now this is training! Okay?
Keeping my reflexes sharp.
Hah! Flawless Victory! Oh!
You were just beaten by a rabbit,
and you don't even know it!
-[microwave dings]
-Ooh! My pizza rolls!
[window shades rattling]
What's that?
Ah! Oh.
[Pops] Oh, hello, Snowball.
Hey, Pops. What's, uh, what's going on?
Oh, you know,
just returning your giant tiger.
Oh, fun fact. He trashed my apartment!
This thing ate a flat screen
like it was a pita chip!
For shame!
Oh, now you've done it. Pickles is pissed.
Uh...
Are you sure that's my tiger?
'Cause I don't know if that's a--
-Let's go, class.
-Hmph!
Oh, come on, old man, don't do this.
Wait, wait, wait. Please!
[purring]
Hey.
-How you been?
-[meows softly]
[purrs and yawns]
I'mma go get back to my pizza rolls,
and I'll come back
and check on you in a bit, okay?
[purrs]
-Problem solved.
-[Gidget] Snowball?
Puffy Dog?
What are you doing in Max's apartment?
Nothing.
Why are you hanging out
with every cat in the universe?
Uh... You know. Just because.
Mmm, okay.
Okay.
[gasps]
Uh, hey, Rooster.
Hey, kid. Good job today.
Yeah? Well, I got to admit,
I feel pretty good.
I'm not so nervous around the farm,
or you,
or the turkey who won't stop following me.
[gobbles]
[Max] Yeah, I see you,
you weirdo.
[chuckles]
Anyway, I heard Katie say
we're leaving tomorrow, and--
[Rooster howling]
You want me to...
Do you want me to go?
[chuckles] Just what we do out here.
-You want to join me?
-Yeah! Okay! Cool.
[grunting]
You ready to try?
[both howling]
Come on, kid. Deeper.
Deep from your gut.
Right. Okay, got it.
[chuckles]
There you go.
[both howling]
[cockerel crowing]
[snoring softly]
Huh?
Wow!
[chuckles]
[barking]
All right, come on, guys.
[babbling]
-Huh? What do you think?
-Max, so cool!
Hey, where'd Max go?
And who let this super cool cowboy
in the car?
-Whoo-hoo!
-[all laugh]
-[Katie] Bye, Uncle Shep.
-Goodbye now! So long!
-Bye, Rooster!
-And thank you!
[grunting]
Bye.
[gobbles]
Mind your business, turkey.
[stammers] I'm having a moment.
[gobbles]
Okay, moment's over.
There we go, buddy.
[yawns]
-[door closes]
-[sighs]
-Good to be home.
-So good.
[sighs]
[yelps]
-Shh.
-You "shh."
[Hu purring]
Huh?
Snowball?
[gasps]
Oh, hey, what, uh...
Hey, Tiny Dog!
What are you doing
with a tiger in my apartment?
Well, what are you doing home
from your trip so soon, hmm?
I mean, as long as we pointing fingers.
Hey, hey, hey.
We don't have time for this!
We are trying to hide Hu
before the circus wolves get here.
Circus wolves?
You do know I have a life
when you're not around, right, TD?
-Yeah, okay, but--
-Captain Snowball! They're here!
What?
-[gasps] Wolves!
-[gasps]
[Snowball] Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no, they gonna kill us, Hu!
Oh, this is bad! [sobs]
Well, at least we die together.
[continues sobbing]
Keep it together, boy.
[sniffles] Okay, okay.
We need a plan.
Daisy, let's hide Hu on the roof.
Tiny Dog, where are you going?
Yeah, I'm not sure,
but I guess I'm gonna
try and find my inner Rooster.
What?
[panting] Okay. Okay.
[grunts]
[both snarling]
[barking]
[wolves growling]
[whimpering] Huh?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[whines]
[screaming]
-[panting]
-[Sergei laughs]
Puny little coward.
[grunts]
Hurry up, Hu!
All right, let's hide him in the--
[screams] Oh.
Oh, it's just this weird little guy.
Why don't you just go back
to wherever you belong, Bonzo,
because I don't wanna-- Oh!
-Ow, ow, ow!
-[laughing]
Ow, ow, ow! [screams]
[snarling]
[gasps] Run, Hu!
[Daisy yells and grunts]
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[wolves snarling]
[roars]
[groaning]
[laughs wickedly]
-Huh?
-[growling]
Oh, pretty little dog, I like you.
You will join my circus as a cannonball.
[barking]
[grunts]
-Mongrel has to learn.
-[whining]
Stupid tiger!
[gasps]
[Sergei laughing wickedly]
[groaning sadly]
[Sergei] Pathetic. Let's go!
We have a train to catch.
[groans]
[truck engine starts]
Daisy! Hu!
What? They are in a truck!
What are we gonna do, TD?
Whoo-hoo! Whoa!
[laughing]
-[gasps]
-[tires screech]
Attention! This is Captain Snowball!
Me and Tiny Dog need backup!
We read you loud and clear! Over!
[Snowball] We are headed to the circus!
This is urgent! Over!
Copy that!
Busy Bee, Mommy's gotta go save Daddy.
Again.
Cats! Let's do this!
-["La Grange" playing]
-[cats meowing]
[all meowing]
[Cat Lady] Are my babies hungry?
Oh, dear.
[engine revs]
Ah! Whoa!
Buckle up, everyone!
Hang on, Max! We're coming!
Floor it!
-[meows]
-[tires screeching]
[whooping]
Hurry up, you clowns!
[laughs]
Let's go, let's go!
Sergei have new toy!
Training is going to be a lot more fun.
[laughs]
All right,
let's get this show on the tracks!
[engine powers up]
[yelling, laughs]
[yelps]
[panting]
Snowball!
Come on, jump!
-[yells]
-[grunts]
Guys, what's your location?
They're on a train headed northbound.
-Over.
-Roger that, Norman! We're on it.
Go right here!
[all meowing]
You hang back, TD!
Captain Snowball is on the... [yells]
Snowball!
I'm fine!
[train horn blows]
Yeah.
Can you find a way to get back up here
-or is there--
-[snarling]
[gasps]
[wolves gasp]
-What?
-[yells]
[wolves snarling]
Tiny Dog!
[Daisy grunting]
What was that? Hello?
[gasps] Daisy!
Snowball!
Oh, thank goodness.
Get me out of here. I'm stuck.
Okay, okay, look. Huh?
[screeches]
Ah!
[grunting]
[yelling]
-[yells]
-[growling]
[exclaiming]
[gibbering]
[bell dings]
[screams]
[both grunting]
-[grunts]
-[screams]
[both grunting]
Body blow.
[yelling]
[grunts and gasps]
-This ends now, monkey.
-[knuckles cracking]
[whimpering]
-[laughs]
-[groans]
[wolves barking]
Whoa!
Guys!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[yells] Whoa!
[wolves grunting]
[groans]
[sighs]
You still there, monkey? Huh?
-[chattering]
-Oh, no! He's here!
He's here! And on fire! [screams]
Hey! Get me out of here!
-[screams]
-[chatters]
[screaming]
[growling]
[gasps and blows]
Snowball! The fuse!
I got it! I got it!
[chatters and screams]
[screams]
Whoa!
[gasps]
[grunting]
[growling]
-Ahh!
-[laughs]
[screams]
[grunts]
-[whimpers]
-[grunts]
Say goodbye, monkey!
Uh-oh.
[screaming]
[panting]
Oh. Huh?
[screaming]
Oh, no!
[both grunt]
[groans]
[panting]
[horn blowing]
[sniffs]
[grunts]
Whoa! Huh?
[growls]
All right, doggy. Bring it.
Whoa! [screams]
Tiny Dog!
[yells]
-[Snowball yelling]
-[blows landing]
Get away! Get off me!
Go away!
[screams]
[groaning]
My God!
-[yells]
-[Sergei screams]
[wheels screech]
[engine stops]
Come on!
-[Sergei] stop!
-[all gasp]
You are going nowhere.
-I've had enough.
-[clicks]
[all whimper]
This ends here and now!
[groans]
[hip-hop music playing on car stereo]
-Hi, Max!
-Gidget!
Uh... That was a bad guy, right?
[laughs]
Yes.
-Uh, hey.
-[purrs]
Okay. All right, all right, all right.
["It's Gonna Be A Lovely Day" playing]
[groaning]
[chuckling]
[Sergei screams and grunts]
[groaning]
[screams and coughs]
-Whoo-hoo!
-Yeah!
Whoo!
[Max] Okay, so, things got back to normal.
[meows]
I mean, mostly.
[mumbles]
-[roars]
-[gasps and screams]
You know what they say.
When life closes a door,
it opens a cat lady's window.
-[purrs]
-That's a good kitty!
Ooh! [laughs]
[objects clatter]
[Max] Because everything changes.
Good morning, Snowball!
Nothing stays the same for long.
The minute you're used to something,
the minute you think,
"Oh, this is how life is,"
-life finds a way of surprising you.
-Aww.
Ah!
Hey, man, what is going on? What?
This is awesome!
Wow!
[Katie] Come on, buddy!
-[Chuck] This is gonna be fun!
-Whoo-hoo!
[Max] You never know
what life is gonna throw at you.
[chuckles]
And you have two choices.
Run from it...
-[cooing]
-Boo! [laughs]
...or run at it.
It's a big day.
And from this point on,
nothing is gonna be the same.
Wow!
[Max] But I'm gonna be brave.
And I'm gonna help Liam be brave.
[laughs]
Because he's my kid,
and I want him to see the world.
The big, scary, incredible world.
[sighs]
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
[both sobbing]
[blows nose]
Wait!
[laughing]
My doggies.
[Max] Always.
Bye-bye, Mama and Dada.
Bye, Snowball. Bye, Mr. Bear.
[door closes]
["Panda" playing]
[Snowball rapping]
♪ Panda ♪
♪ Panda, Panda, Panda
Panda, Panda ♪
♪ Listen
Hey! ♪
♪ I got broads in Atlanta ♪
♪ Twisting rope, drinking Fanta ♪
♪ Credit cards and the scammers ♪
♪ Hitting off licks in the bando ♪
♪ Black X6, Phantom ♪
♪ Wait and see
Looking like a panda ♪
♪ Listen!
Hundred scammers ♪
♪ Black X6, Phantom
What you see, panda ♪
♪ Pockets swole, Danny
Selling bar, candy ♪
♪ Man, I'm the macho like Randy ♪
-[music stops]
-Snowball, I'm back!
[chuckles] Mmm!
[music continues]
♪ Panda, panda, panda ♪
[Rooster] Okay, moment's over.