My name is
Captain James Tiberius Kirk
of the United Federation of Planets.
I am appearing before you
as a neutral representative
of the Fibonan Republic.
I bring you a message of goodwill
and present to you esteemed members
of the Teenaxi Delegation,
a gift from the Fibonan High Council
with the highest regard.
What's wrong with it?
Uh, excuse me?
Why don't they want it anymore?
Uh, well, this was once
a piece of an ancient weapon,
and now they offer it as a symbol of...
Of peace.
In the Fibonan culture,
to surrender a weapon
is an offer of truce.
How did they come by it?
They told me
they acquired it a long time ago.
So they stole it, then.
No, they, um... Well, I don't know.
You don't know the Fibonans like we do!
Yeah, that's very true.
Your Excellency, this gift...
They're a crowd of untrustworthy thieves
who want to see us murdered
in our own beds!
This beloved artifact
is a symbol of trust and peace.
They want to chop us into pieces
and roast us over a fire!
No, no... I don't think that's true.
And eat us!
What?
Scotty! Get me out of here!
- That was quick.
- Scotty!
There's quite a bit
of surface interference, sir.
Scotty!
Get it off of me!
I ripped my shirt again.
How'd it go?
Captain, did you manage
to broker a treaty with the Teenaxi?
Uh... Let's just say I came up short.
Will you, uh, log that and put it
in the vault, Spock? Thank you.
Jim, you look like crap.
Thank you, Bones.
You got that little vein popping out
of your temple again. You okay?
Never better!
Just another day in the fleet.
Captain's Log, Stardate 2263.2.
Today is our 966th day in deep space,
a little under three years
into our five-year mission.
The more time we spend out here,
the harder it is to tell
where one day ends
and the next one begins.
It can be a challenge to feel grounded
when even gravity is artificial.
But, well, we do what we can
to make it feel like home.
The crew, as always,
continues to act admirably
despite the rigors of our extended stay
here in outer space.
And the personal sacrifices
they have made.
We continue to search
for new life forms
in order to establish firm diplomatic ties.
Our extended time in uncharted territory
has stretched the ship's
mechanical capacities.
But fortunately
our engineering department,
led by Mr. Scott,
is more than up to the job.
The ship aside,
prolonged cohabitation has
definitely had effects
on interpersonal dynamics.
Some experiences for the better,
and some for the worse.
As for me, things have started to feel
a little episodic.
The farther out we go,
the more I find myself wondering
what it is we're trying to accomplish.
If the universe is truly endless,
then are we not striving
for something forever out of reach?
The Enterprise is scheduled
for a reprovisioning stop at Yorktown,
the Federation's newest
and most advanced starbase.
Perhaps a break from routine
will offer up some respite
from the mysteries of the unknown.
Sorry I'm late.
Keenser's leaking
some kind of highly acidic green goo,
and Scotty's terrified
he's gonna sneeze on the warp core
and kill us all.
What the hell are you drinking?
Uh, I'm pretty sure
it's the rest of that Saurian brandy
we picked up on Thasus.
My God, man, are you trying to go blind?
That stuff's illegal.
Besides, I found this in Chekov's locker.
- Wow.
- Right?
I mean, I always assumed he'd be
- a vodka man.
- A vodka guy, exactly.
I wanted to have
something appropriate for your birthday.
Uh, that's in a couple days.
You know I don't care about that.
I know. I know you don't like
celebrating it on the day
because it's also the day
your pa bit the dust.
I was being sensitive.
Did they teach you about
bedside manner in medical school?
It's just your southern charm.
- Oh, yeah. That's good.
- Ooh.
Lordy!
Are you gonna call your mom?
Yeah, of course. I'll call her on the day.
I'm one year older.
Yep, that's usually how it works.
A year older than he ever got to be.
He joined Starfleet because he...
He believed in it.
I joined on a dare.
You joined to see
if you could live up to him.
Uh, you spent all this time
trying to be George Kirk
and now you're wondering
just what it means to be Jim.
Why you're out here.
To perfect eyesight
and a full head of hair.
Kirk here.
Captain,
approaching Yorktown base.
I'm on my way, Mr. Sulu.
Let's keep this birthday thing
under wraps, huh?
Yeah, you know me. Mr. Sensitive.
Wow. That is impressive.
Aye, she's a beauty, isn't she?
What a damn monstrosity!
Couldn't we just rent
some space on a planet?
Showing geographical favoritism
among inducted Federation worlds
could cause diplomatic tension.
Oh, you don't think that looks tense?
Looks like a damn snow globe
in space just waiting to break!
Oh, that's the spirit, Bones.
Spock!
Do you have a moment?
Of course, Nyota.
I think you should have this back.
After all, it belonged to your mother.
It's not in the Vulcan custom
to receive again
that which was given as a gift.
You guys break up?
What'd you do?
A typically reductive inquiry, Doctor.
You know, Spock, if an Earth girl says,
uh, "It's me, not you,"
it's definitely you.
Excuse me. Commander Spock?
May we have a moment of your time?
This is wonderful!
You know I've never been here?
What I hear is that
the bars here are excellent.
I'm so glad you guys could come.
Thank you for bringing this
to my attention.
Live long and prosper.
IFF alert on incoming vessel.
Unidentified. Non-Federation.
Attention, unidentified vessel.
You are not authorized for approach.
Power down and await instructions.
Unidentified vessel, please comply.
Speak normally.
Language analysis complete.
Is this working?
We were on a science mission
inside the nebula.
Our ship suffered a critical malfunction.
I took an escape pod
before the ship crash landed
on a nearby planet.
We need a ship
capable of navigating the nebula.
You must have someone
who can help us.
We tracked her stranded ship
to a sector of uncharted nebula,
here at 2-1-0 mark 14.
- Uh, long-range scan?
- No data.
The nebula is too dense.
It's uncharted space.
Well, the Enterprise does have
the best navigational system in the fleet.
She could handle it.
The only ship here
with more advanced technology
is still under construction.
But it's not just the
ship that I'm sending.
- I'll gather the crew.
- Captain.
Starfleet command
sent me your application
for the Vice Admiral position
here at this installation.
Yes, ma'am. Um...
If I may, I would
recommend Commander Spock
replace me as Captain of the Enterprise.
He is an exemplary Starfleet officer.
He'd make a great captain.
It isn't uncommon, you know,
even for a captain,
to want to leave.
There is no relative direction
in the vastness of space.
There is only yourself,
your ship, your crew.
It's easier than you think, to get lost.
- It's not about...
- I'll bring it up with the General Council.
We'll discuss it when you return.
Ma'am.
- Mr. Spock.
- Captain.
- I was thinking...
- Perhaps there...
- No, please.
- Captain, after you.
I insist.
After this mission,
we should, uh, sit down.
There's something
I need to talk to you about.
I as well have something to share.
We make a good team. Right?
I believe we do.
I insist.
Lieutenant Uhura,
open a ship-wide channel.
Yes, Captain.
Attention, crew of the Enterprise.
Our mission is straightforward.
Rescue a crew stranded on a planet
in uncharted space.
Our trajectory will take us
through an unstable nebula,
one which will disable
all communications with Starfleet.
We're gonna be on our own.
The Enterprise has something
no other ship in the fleet has,
you.
And as we've come to understand,
there is no such thing as the unknown,
only the temporarily hidden.
Kirk out.
Mmm. Readings indicate
cloud density diminishing, sir.
This is Altamid.
My ship is stranded here.
Approaching Altamid. Class-M planet.
Massive subterranean development.
But limited to no life forms
on the surface.
Proximity alert, sir!
We have an unknown ship
heading right for us.
- Lieutenant Uhura, hail them.
- Yes, Captain.
No response.
I am picking up some kind of signal.
They're jamming us.
Magnify, Mr. Sulu.
What is this?
Shields up! Red alert!
Fire at will.
Sir, our phasers
are having minimal effect
and our torpedos
can't track their movements!
Fire everything we've got.
Captain, we are not equipped
for this manner of engagement.
Shield frequencies have no effect, sir!
They took out the dish!
Shields are inoperable!
- Warp us out of here, Mr. Sulu.
- Yes, sir.
Why the hell aren't we moving?
I can't engage the warp drive, sir!
Scotty, I need warp now!
I cannae, sir! The nacelles, they've...
They've gone!
Security, engage
all emergency procedures.
Active protocol 28 Code One Alpha Zero.
All personnel to alert stations.
Sir, I have hull breaches
in levels 12 to 15,
6, 9, 31 and 21, sir.
Captain! There's a chance
I can reroute the energy reserves
from the warp core
to the impulse engines.
If we can get back into the nebula,
maybe we could lose them.
Do whatever you have to, Scotty.
Wee man! Let's go.
Fit the plasma conduits
and stand by to reroute on my mark!
- Captain.
- Go, Spock.
I have identified the individual
who appears to be
leading the attack party.
He infiltrated the archive vault
and removed the artifact
from our mission on Teenax.
Hold your distance until...
Spock!
You two, with me.
Sulu, you have the conn.
Yes, sir.
My God.
What the hell?
Doctor?
Doctor, we must evacuate now!
Captain
Kirk.
Yes! We are at 100% impulse.
Great work, Mr. Scott!
Maximum impulse towards the nebula.
Aye.
Kirk to Bridge.
We are losing
the inertial dampeners!
Systems are failing ship-wide, Captain.
Emergency bulkheads are sealing,
but structural integrity
is at 18% and falling, sir!
Abandon ship, Mr. Sulu.
Sound the alarm.
Abandon ship. All personnel.
We need to give those pods
a chance to escape.
Can you lead those ships away?
Impulse engines are still trying
to draw power from the warp reserve.
We cannot move
until the saucer is separated.
I'll handle it.
Aye-aye, sir.
Abandon ship.
All personnel evacuate immediately.
You okay? Oh, my God.
Get him up. Help him up.
Got you.
We've got to get you guys
to an escape pod. Go.
Go! Ensign Syl.
I need your help.
Yes, sir.
My God.
Spock, they're taking the crew!
Abandon ship.
All personnel evacuate immediately.
Are you okay?
The saucer should be free by now!
I know, Mr. Sulu.
The Captain should be there!
All personnel evacuate immediately.
Impulse engines drawing power
from auxiliary generators.
Captain!
How many of the crew
are still aboard the saucer?
None.
But if I'm reading this correctly,
the intruders are taking them.
Captain,
we are caught in the planet's gravity.
We cannot pull away.
Get to your Kelvin Pods.
- Yes, sir.
- Aye, Captain.
Come on, let's go!
Let's go.
Come on.
Chekov!
You knew. You knew we'd be attacked.
You don't understand.
Captain! Captain Kirk!
Yes. I lied.
Our ship was attacked.
Chekov, check the comms for survivors.
- Aye, Captain.
- Who is he?
His name is Krall.
He took my crew. Like he took yours.
How did he know so much
about the Enterprise?
All I know is that if I did this,
he would set them free.
Chekov, are you picking
anything up on those scanners?
Nothing, sir.
- What if they...
- No, no.
He was taking them.
We have to find that saucer.
Even minimal scanning systems
will have more range than a tricorder.
Aye, Captain, it's possible.
Captain.
I was protecting my crew.
What is your name?
How do you know our language?
I know your kind.
I am Lieutenant Nyota Uhura
of the U.S.S. Enterprise.
And you have committed
an act of war against the...
Federation!
Federation is an act of war.
You attacked us.
Your captain...
Why did you sacrifice yourself for him?
He would have done the same.
And if he made it off of that ship,
he will come for us.
I am counting on it, Lieutenant Uhura.
I can't believe it.
My God, Spock.
God...
Sit down over here.
Okay. Okay, sit. Easy.
Okay.
Now, just try and relax.
You're gonna be okay.
The forced optimism
in your voice suggests
that you are trying
to elicit a sense of calm in order to...
I'll cut the horseshit.
Doctor, I fail to see
how excrement of any kind
bears relevance on our current situation.
Whoa, whoa,
what the hell are you doing?
We must keep moving, Doctor.
Spock, this thing's punctured
your iliac region!
Time is a critical factor.
That's exactly what I'm trying to tell you.
Look, if I can't take this out,
you're gonna die.
Okay? If I take it out and can't stop
the bleeding, you're gonna die.
I can see no appeal in either option.
Believe it or not, neither can I.
So, if I remember correctly,
the Vulcans have their hearts
where humans have their livers.
That is correct, Doctor.
That explains a thing or two.
You know, you're lucky.
An inch to the left...
And you'd be dead already.
I just don't get it, Spock.
I mean, what did they attack us for?
I mean, they do all this for some
doodad that the tiny critters didn't want?
It is unwise to trivialize
that which one
simply does not understand, Doctor.
We can safely assume
it is more important than a doodad.
I think you just managed
to insult me twice, Spock.
Okay.
All right, Spock, I just got one question.
- What's your favorite color?
- I fail to see the relevance.
Ow!
Yeah. They say it hurts less
if it's a surprise.
If I may adopt a parlance
with which you are familiar,
I can confirm your theory
to be horseshit.
We got to get out of here.
Come on.
You're kidding me, aren't you?
Hello there.
My name is Montgomery Scott.
And, uh, who might you be?
Watch it, sonny.
I'm pretty handy
when I want to be, all right?
Don't come back!
We certainly showed them, eh, lassie?
That's Starfleet property, okay.
You cannae just take it.
Uh, but I'm feeling generous today,
so have at it.
Where you get that?
- Is that English?
- I learn it from my house.
- Where you get that?
- It's my Starfleet insignia.
What does it mean?
Means that I'm an officer of Starfleet.
Uh, engineering division.
- Engineering?
- That's right. I fix things.
I know what is engineering.
You're not with those bastards
that killed my ship, are you?
I'll take that as a no.
He is Krall. Him and his
bees.
They search the stars
for a death machine.
They're the reason why you here.
Why we are all here.
Even those three scunners?
They have fallen from the sky,
like me and you.
Come with me. Now!
Wait, no... Hang on a minute, lassie.
I'm having a difficult day here.
I've got to find my crewmates.
I will help you find your mates.
And then you will help me.
With what?
You want me to fix something?
Yes. You help me, and I help you.
All right, well, things being as they are,
I doubt I'll get a better offer today,
so, lead the way.
Good.
I am Jaylah.
- And you are Montgomery Scott.
- Aye, Scotty.
Come now, Montgomery Scotty.
All right, hold up.
The Enterprise.
She may not even have power
to the Bridge, Captain.
She still has a few tricks up her sleeve.
I'd bet on it.
McCoy to Enterprise. Come in.
McCoy to Enterprise.
Hey, take it easy there, Spock.
That was just
a temporary fix back there.
I understand, Doctor.
Fascinating.
Ominous. Dark. Dangerous.
We're going in.
Intriguing.
These symbols are the same as those
depicted on the artifact
taken in the attack.
You think it came from here?
It would seem so.
Damn it, Spock.
Easy. Easy.
Hurry.
- Are we there yet?
- Stop asking that.
- Sorry.
- This is the way. Come.
And watch your steps.
You do not want to set off my traps.
Oh.
That's clever.
What is this place?
- This is my house.
- Your house?
Hold on a minute. Is this a ship?
I help you find your friends
and you help me fix it.
So I can leave this planet forever.
Wait a minute. Is this your ship?
No, Montgomery Scotty.
It's yours.
Oh, my good Lord.
Captain,
it looks like there is power.
All right,
let's get to the Bridge and find the crew.
The console is intact, Captain.
I will try to reroute power to it.
Work fast.
Once we get this place lit up,
we're gonna draw a lot of attention.
What do you think,
can you find them?
Aye, Captain.
I am reconfiguring scanners
to modulate for the crew's signals.
You're with me.
I left something behind.
That is one heck of a cold.
Nice job, Keenser.
All right, we got about 15 minutes
until the next guard rotation. Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on.
This is the Magellan Probe.
The Federation was using these
to find a way through the nebula.
What's he using it for?
What do you see?
He's been piggybacking
the subspace links between the probes.
Can we use it to send a distress signal?
I can try.
It's sent.
He's accessed the Yorktown database.
What?
He's got Starfleet data files, ship logs,
including the Enterprise.
He's been watching us this whole time.
Captain,
the artifact was on the ship
the whole time?
I couldn't afford to get caught with it,
so I hid it in here.
Tell Krall I have the Abronath.
Do you believe
every sad story you hear?
Not every.
Put the phaser down.
Please.
You get it, Chekov?
Aye, Captain, I have traced
the location of her call.
What does Krall want with this thing?
To save you
from yourselves.
Captain!
- You all right?
- Aye, Captain,
but we are trapped!
Can you get this thing started?
Are you intimating
that we should engage the thrusters?
I am open to other suggestions.
Okay.
- There is a problem.
- What?
The fuel is primed,
but I cannot get it to combust.
Oy, Captain, we are basically
standing on a very large bomb.
If you miss
the combustion compressor...
I'm not gonna miss, come on.
Do you even know what
the combustion compressor looks like?
It's square, right?
No, sir, it's round.
That's what I said.
Run!
Go!
Chekov!
Chekov! Move!
You think you know
what sacrifice really means?
Federation has taught you
that conflict should not exist.
Ha!
But without struggle,
you would never know who you truly are.
You have no idea who we are.
But you'll soon find out.
You mean the distress signal
you thought you sent?
The coordinates were altered.
Your rescue ships
will be stranded in the nebula
and your base left vulnerable.
You're going to attack Yorktown.
Millions of souls from every
Federation world holding hands.
It's a perfect target.
You're wrong. There is strength in unity.
The strength of others, Lieutenant,
is what has kept me alive.
No!
Spock.
Spock, wake up, damn it!
I am entirely conscious, Doctor.
I'm simply contemplating
the nature of mortality.
Feeling philosophical, huh?
Massive blood loss will do that to you.
You asked me why
Lieutenant Uhura and I parted ways.
I became concerned,
in the light of Vulcan's demise,
that I owed a debt of duty to my species.
You thought you should be off
making little Vulcans, huh?
Yeah, I can see
how that would upset her.
I intended to discuss it with her further,
but I received some news
which affected me unexpectedly.
What news?
Ambassador Spock has died.
Oh.
Spock, I'm so sorry.
I can't imagine what that must feel like.
When you've lived as many lives as he,
fear of death is illogical.
Fear of death
is what keeps us alive.
I want to live as he did.
That is why I decided
to redirect my efforts
and continue his work
on New Vulcan.
You're leaving Starfleet?
What did Jim have to say about that?
I could not find the time to tell him.
Well, I can tell you
he's not gonna like that.
Hell, I don't know
what he'd do without you.
I mean, me on the other hand,
I'd throw a party, but...
My God, you're getting delirious.
How far are we
from the coordinates of that call?
Still a ways, sir.
- Captain?
- Yeah.
When did you begin to suspect her?
Not soon enough.
How did you know?
Well...
I guess you could say
I've got a good nose for danger.
Run!
Is that music?
Where on earth is that coming from?
There.
I plugged the little box in the power cell
and the little mouths make it sing.
That's very clever.
Music's a bit old-fashioned for my taste,
not to mention very loud and distracting,
but, aye, well played.
I like the beats and shouting.
Oh, you do?
- Switch it off.
- Ach, you're okay.
Switch it off!
Someone set off one of my traps.
Shh.
Captain?
- You know these men?
- Aye, lassie.
- That wee man there is Pavel Chekov.
- Hello.
And that handsome bastard
is James T. Kirk.
They're my mates.
It's good to see you, sir.
What is she doing, Scotty?
Don't hurt them. No, don't!
Hit her!
- You're free, James T.
- There we go.
Mr. Scott.
Who's your new friend here?
She sure knows
how to throw out a welcome mat.
- This is Jaylah.
- I do not know what is a welcome mat.
- You find anybody else?
- No, sir.
I'm sorry, you're the only ones.
What the hell happened up there, Jim?
Why were we attacked?
They were after the artifact
we brought back from T eenax.
- Did they get it?
- No.
- Have you got it?
I had to get it off the Enterprise,
put it on a shuttle.
- You hid it in a shuttle.
- Yes.
And no.
This is the U. S. S. Franklin, sir.
Can you believe it?
First Earth ship capable of warp 4.
Went missing in the Gagarin
Radiation Belt in the early 2160s.
I remember that
from the Academy.
Captain Balthazar Edison.
One of the first heroes of Starfleet.
How the hell did his ship end up here?
There's a lot of theories, sir.
Surrendered to the Romulans.
Captured by a giant green space hand.
This far out,
it's got to be a wormhole displacement.
Can she fly?
She's missing a few driver coils
and the EPS conduits are fried,
but Jaylah has done a marvelous job
of getting the ship's systems
back online.
- Thank you, Montgomery Scotty.
- Pardon me.
Mr. Chekov,
can you plug in the coordinates.
See if you can track the crew's location
from the ship's sensors.
Aye, Captain.
- He likes that seat.
- Mr. Scott.
- Tour.
- Yes, the mess hall.
- Jaylah, if you will.
- Yes.
No clue
what happened to the crew, huh?
No, sir. They'd be dead
a hundred years by now.
Is that a...
That's a PX70!
Wow.
My dad used to have one
when he was a kid.
My mom said he'd put her
on the back of it, drive her nuts.
Sir.
Um...
So you're telling me
this thing's been here this whole time
and no one's ever noticed it?
She's rigged up
image refractors.
Here.
So, like some sort of
holographic camouflage.
Aye, sir.
Captain!
I have intercepted a weak
communications transmission, sir.
It's a Starfleet frequency.
Can you lock on to the signal?
Yes, but how do we get to them?
I have an idea, sir.
But I'm gonna need your permission.
Why would you need my permission?
Because if I mess it up,
I don't want it to be just my fault.
McCoy and Spock to Enterprise crew.
Come in, Enterprise crew.
Anyone.
Come on, Spock.
Come on, you can make it.
Leaving me behind
will significantly increase
your chances of survival, Doctor.
Well, that's damn chivalrous of you,
but completely out of the question.
It is imperative that
you locate any surviving crew.
And here I was thinking you cared.
Of course I care, Leonard.
I always assumed
my respect for you was clear.
The dialogue we have had
across the years has always...
It's okay, Spock.
You don't have to say it.
Well, at least I won't die alone.
Well, that's just typical.
Come on, you bastards!
Oh.
Good to see you in one piece, Doctor.
Oh, am I?
I feel like my innards
have been to a barn dance!
Aye, well, these old transporters
were only ever used for cargo,
but a few modifications
seem to do the trick.
I thought it best
to beam you one at a time, though.
- You know, in case you got spliced.
- Oh.
I couldn't imagine a worse scenario.
Good to have you back. You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. He's hurt.
I am functioning adequately, Captain.
In a pig's eye, you are!
Captain, we discovered
that the stolen artifact
appears to have
come from this planet.
Damn it, Spock.
Are there any medical supplies
on this thing?
This way.
All right. Lie down. Come on.
There you go.
How are we gonna get out
of this one, Spock?
We've got no ship, no crew.
Not the best odds.
We will do
what we have always done, Jim.
We will find hope in the impossible.
Let's get you patched up first, okay?
No, Captain.
You must focus your efforts
on helping the crew.
Well, that's why
I need you around, Spock.
These things are from the dark ages.
Bones.
I'm pretty sure this is a protoplaser.
Should stop the internal hemorrhaging.
At least that's my hope.
"The miserable have no other medicine
But only hope."
Death's door
and he's quoting Shakespeare.
Captain's Log, Stardate 2262.18.
The mission, routine investigation...
If the universe is truly endless...
What seemed so clear to me
two years ago now seems,
well, far away.
You will tell me where it is!
Now!
Stop! Stop!
Let him go
and I will give you what you want!
No! Syl, don't!
Lieutenant, unity is not your strength.
It is your weakness.
We should wait
until we're absolutely sure.
No, we have to get the crew back now.
Chekov has the coordinates that can
lead us to Krall's base, so we go!
With respect, sir, how do we know
that Krall was at the base
when she called him?
Even if he was, we don't know
that the crew is even with him.
Or if they're even still alive.
Mr. Chekov, can you reconfigure
the search parameters
in order to compensate for this formula?
Aye, Commander,
but what is this formula?
It is Vokaya, Mr. Chekov.
A mineral unique to Vulcan
which emits low-level radiation.
I will have to filter out
all other energy emissions.
Spock, what the hell would a Vulcan
mineral be doing way out here?
Where are you going with this?
Lieutenant Uhura
wears a Vokaya amulet
which I presented to her
as a token of my affection and respect.
You gave your girlfriend
radioactive jewelry?
The emission
is harmless, Doctor.
But its unique signature
makes it very easy to identify.
You gave your girlfriend
a tracking device.
That was not my intention.
I'm glad he doesn't respect me.
Huh.
I am detecting
a very trace amount of Vokaya.
Does the location match the coordinates
you acquired from Kalara, Mr. Chekov?
It is a match, sir.
Its presence suggests that Lieutenant
Uhura and thereby the rest of the crew
are being held
at Krall's base of operation.
Can you beam them out?
No, sir. There is some
geological interference
that is blocking the transporter signal.
Well, I guess we're gonna have to go in
and break them out
the old-fashioned way.
You cannot go to this place.
Everyone who goes there, he kills.
You've...
You've been there? You've seen it?
Well, why didn't you
say something, lassie?
Because I know you will
ask me to take you there.
If your friends are there,
then they will die, just like my family.
And I will not go back
to that death place!
Aye, but if you've escaped,
then you can show us
the way in and the way out.
No! This is not the deal we made,
Montgomery Scotty.
If you choose to do this,
you are on your own.
Wait.
Let her go.
She's lost people, too, Captain.
Look, that's our friends out there,
lassie. Right?
We cannae just leave them behind.
Now, we could really use your help.
We just need you to be brave, is all.
When we were in that place,
Krall would come and take someone.
There were screams.
I can still hear them.
And we would not see
that person again.
We did not know who would be next.
My father planned an escape.
But we were seen
by the one they call Manas.
My father fought him so I could get out.
He was brave and Manas killed him.
What you want is impossible.
Look, maybe it's not.
Right. My wee granny used to say,
"Ya cannae break a stick in a bundle."
You're part of
something bigger now, lassie.
Right? Dinnae give up on that.
'Cause we'll sure as hell
never give up on you.
That is what being part of a crew
is all about.
Is that what you believe in, James T.?
All I know is we stand
a better chance with you.
The digging machines uncovered
a tunnel that goes into the crater.
That's how I got out.
So that'll be our way in.
An away team will beam
to the other side of the tunnel,
follow it to Krall's base,
get inside the building
and break out the crew.
Uh, Captain, we cannot lock
onto anyone inside the crater
in order to beam them out.
Oh, I could rig up pulse beacons
as pattern enhancers.
That'd get the signal out of the crater.
- All right.
- How many people can
the Franklin transport at a time?
Uh, with a wee bit
of modification, 20 max,
but I'm not sure
how long it would hold out.
Bones, Mr. Chekov, Jaylah,
you're with me on the away team.
Mr. Scott, modify that transporter
and then do everything you can
to get this ship operational.
Captain, Mr. Chekov's technical acumen
makes him more valuable
aboard the Franklin with Mr. Scott.
It is thereby logical
that I would replace him.
Why is that logical, Spock?
You just got back on your feet.
Lieutenant Uhura is in that facility, Jim.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Understood.
But his soldiers are everywhere.
We won't pass unseen.
What we require is a diversion.
I think I have an idea.
This is Abronath.
It was used by the Ancient Ones
as a weapon.
But when they could not
control its deadly power,
they split it into two
and ejected the halves into space,
hoping it would be lost forever.
But I am grateful.
I have spent lifetimes searching for it,
only to have you
find it for me.
The poetry of fate.
The world that I was born into
is very different from yours, Lieutenant.
We knew pain. We knew terror.
Struggle made us strong.
Not peace. Not unity.
These are myths
the Federation would have you believe.
Those are strong words.
You might even believe them,
but there's something else
going on with you.
Something underneath.
Uhura!
Wait.
What are you doing with her?
You already got what you wanted!
Let her go!
Syl!
No, please!
Let her go!
Manas, it's time.
The Federation has pushed
the frontier for centuries.
But no longer.
This is where it begins, Lieutenant.
This is where the frontier pushes back.
This way.
Where is she?
I've got to admit,
that's a hell of a distraction.
Your friends are over there.
Come on.
Go!
Commander. Uhura, they took her.
Get the remainder of the crew to safety.
Come on, let's go! Move!
- Stay in the circle.
- Come on! Hurry!
I've got them, Mr. Scott!
Okay, Mr. Chekov, increase the signal.
We're gonna grab them 20 at a time.
- Aye.
- Let's hope this doesn't get messy.
Energize!
Spock.
What are you doing here?
Clearly, I am here to rescue you.
Let's go.
Good to see you, wee man.
Ten seconds until
the transporter's recharged, Doctor.
- Wait for my signal.
- Doctor!
Damn it, man,
we're not leaving without them!
Come on. Let's go. Move!
Let's go! Come on!
We're ready for you next,
Captain. Just turn on your beacon.
Scotty, do you have everybody?
Aye, sir. Everyone
except you and Jaylah.
Hit the beacon and we'll grab you.
Captain, your beacon!
- There it is!
- Energize.
Jaylah, now!
Okay...
Let's never do that again.
I agree, James T.
You all right?
Captain! This thing he has...
Yorktown. He's gonna destroy Yorktown.
You take my house
and you make it fly.
Scotty, can you get this thing started?
Started, yes.
Flying, sir, that's a different thing.
These old vessels,
they were built in space.
They were never supposed
to take off from atmosphere.
Make it happen.
They're called starships
for a reason, Captain.
You're telling me this now?
Because I didn't want
to disappoint you, you know,
in case you didn't make it back.
- How thoughtful, Mr. Scott.
- Captain.
He's launching.
The attack on Yorktown
may be just the beginning.
Armed with this bio-weapon,
he could rid it of all life
and use the base's advanced technology
to attack an untold number
of Federation planets.
Then we're just gonna have to
get this thing flying.
We cannae just jumpstart it, sir!
Okay! All systems online.
Dilithium chambers
at 70% and climbing.
Primary support engines standing by.
Mr. Sulu.
You can, you know, fly this thing, right?
You kidding me, sir?
Fantastic.
Scotty, how we looking?
Ready as she'll ever be, sir.
That's what I like to hear. All right.
Bones, where are we with the crew?
I could use a functioning med-bay,
but otherwise we're secure down here.
Mr. Sulu, we have to achieve
terminal velocity
in order for the stabilizers
to provide lift.
Are you sure this drop
is high enough to do that?
We'll find out.
Call it, Mr. Sulu.
Aye-aye, Captain.
Mr. Chekov, be ready to hit
the forward stabilizers full on my mark.
- One quarter impulse.
- Aye.
One half impulse, Mr. Chekov.
Aye.
We should belt up. Go on. Go!
Easy, Mr. Sulu.
Let's not break her in half.
Any time, Mr. Sulu.
Now, Mr. Chekov!
IFF alert on incoming vessel.
No reply to all-frequency I.D. request.
Visual.
Red alert! Red alert!
Look how far they've come.
Please proceed
to designated safety zones immediately.
Please proceed to designated
safety zones immediately.
I'm picking up distress signals
from every frequency
coming from Yorktown.
Krall's already started his attack.
Mr. Scott, what kind of weapons
do we have?
Uh, we have pulsed phase cannons
and spatial torpedoes.
Great. Lock and load.
It does not matter.
You cannot defeat the bees.
Maybe, uh, maybe we lure them away.
How do we get Yorktown time
to get people to safety?
No, we are a horse and buggy
compared to those things.
We're barely holding together
as it is, Captain.
Captain, the flight patterns of bees
are determined by individual decisions.
Krall's swarm formations
are too complex not to rely
on some form of unified
cyberpathic coordination.
- I surmise that if we...
- Spock! Skip to the end.
What he's saying is that
if we disorient the swarm
we can kick its ass!
Precisely.
Scotty, can you beam me
onto one of those swarm ships?
Have you gone completely mad?
- Yes or no?
- No!
Yes!
Maybe.
Captain, my familiarity
of the interior of those ships,
however brief, makes me more qualified
for this away mission.
Spock, you're still hurt.
She's right, Spock.
I acknowledge
and respect your concerns.
Perhaps you would feel more confident
if I were accompanied by someone
with familiarity of both
the ship and my injury.
He's gonna love this.
You want me to do what?
- Come along, Doctor.
- Whoa! Wait a minute.
Why, you green-blooded ingrate.
This was your idea!
It's a good idea, Bones.
You know, next time
you have a piece of pipe
stuck in your transverse, call a plumber.
Just make sure you find a way
to break those things.
If it gets hairy,
I'll beam you straight back.
Energize.
You're gonna do great!
Damn it, Jim, I'm a doctor, not a...
You do realize the last time
I flew one of these things we crashed.
So don't blame me if we...
Hit something.
Spock to Franklin.
Spock, we read you.
Captain, from what I can ascertain,
the ships do indeed share
a cyberpathic link
which coordinates their actions.
Patching it through now.
That's what that signal was.
They weren't jamming us,
they were talking to each other.
Well, how do we get them
to stop talking?
What about electromagnetic focusing?
We could use the transporters,
disrupt their network.
The focus might be too specific.
If we could plant some sort of disruptive
communication signal inside the swarm,
it might adversely affect
their capacity to coordinate.
It would have to be
at a frequency they will not anticipate.
We could cause a chain reaction
that would wipe out the whole swarm.
Sir, a closed network like that
might be susceptible
to very high frequency.
VHF.
Radio. We can broadcast something
from the ship to drown out their link.
Something loud and distracting.
Loud and distracting?
I've got just the thing!
Do not break my music.
Break it? You're getting an upgrade.
Swarm ships are 60 seconds
from breaking through!
I've just got to reconfigure
the VHF output
into a multiphasic sweep.
Let me do it.
Let her do it.
You do it.
There, see? Simple.
All right. Captain,
we're ready to broadcast.
But the signal won't travel far.
We have to get closer.
- How close?
- Very.
Intercept course, Mr. Sulu.
Put us right in the middle of that thing.
Yes, sir.
My old friend.
The swarm ships are doubling back!
They are forming an attack wave, sir.
I think we got their attention.
Hold steady, Mr. Sulu.
Brace yourselves, everybody.
Spock, stand by
to drop out of formation.
- Scotty, you all cued up back there?
- Aye, sir!
Ready to broadcast at 577 megahertz.
Made your choice, lassie?
I have the beat and shouting.
Let's make some noise.
That's a good choice.
Faster, Doctor. We risk being
consumed by their trajectorial decay.
Damn backseat driver.
- Evade, Doctor!
- I see it, I see it!
Is that classical music?
Yes, Doctor, it would seem to be.
Lieutenant Uhura, make sure Yorktown
has the frequency to broadcast.
Sir, we now have
the disruption frequency.
Broadcast.
- You two all right, Spock?
- We are fine, Captain,
but there are still three ships
heading into Yorktown.
That's got to be Krall.
Keep on him, Spock.
Do whatever it takes to stop him
from using that weapon.
My house is breaking!
We've lost the polarization
of the hull plating!
I can reroute the power
from the dilithium chambers.
I need you.
And I need you, Jaylah. Let's go!
Do not lose them, Doctor.
You're more than welcome
to switch places with me, Spock.
Captain, intercepting
all three ships is an impossibility.
Get me a schematic of Yorktown!
There! Yorktown headquarters!
Mr. Chekov, can you do
a bioscan of Central Plaza?
Aye.
They are clearing civilians.
Bones, there's a city plaza coming up.
You gotta make sure Krall heads for it.
- Why?
- Just do it!
Sulu, get us up there.
Hold onto something!
- Great work, Bones.
- Thanks, Jim.
Now I've just got to
figure out how to land.
Captain, I have three hull breaches
from the impact.
Deck 3, the cargo bay,
and the engine room.
All right, Sulu, Chekov,
check the cargo bay and Deck 3.
We need confirmation
that the weapon has been neutralized
and Krall is dead!
Captain!
It's Krall.
We've seen him do this.
It's some kind of energy transference.
It physically changes him.
He must still be onboard.
We would have seen him leave.
Sulu, contact Yorktown security
and lock down the ship.
Let's go.
Push the frontier.
It's about damn time.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
All right, baby, let's go.
- It's about damn time.
- Push the frontier.
Captain!
- It's about damn time.
- Push the frontier.
...frontier.
It's him.
Scotty, I need you to link
into the Franklin database.
Find out what you can
about Balthazar Edison.
- The captai n of the Franklin?
- Yeah.
- Sir, he'll be long dead.
- No. He's not.
I don't know how, but Edison is Krall.
What'd you find?
His record goes back
way before the Federation even existed.
He was a major in
the United Earth Military Assault
Command Operation.
A lot of off-world combat.
He was a soldier.
Aye, sir.
And a pretty good one.
His military service came to an end
when MACO was disbanded.
- Why, what happened?
- The Federation, sir. Starfleet.
We're not a military agency.
They made him a captain
and gave him the Franklin.
- Scotty, bring up his logs.
- Aye, sir.
- Captain's Log...
- Last entry.
Captain's Log...
I don't remember the stardate.
All distress calls unanswered.
Of the crew,
only three remain.
I won't allow it!
The indigenous race
abandoned this planet long ago.
They left behind sophisticated
mining equipment
and a drone workforce.
They have some sort of technology
that prolongs life.
I will do whatever it takes
for me and my crew.
The Federation do not care about us.
You'll probably never see me again.
But if you do,
be ready.
Why has he not used his weapon yet?
'Cause he wants to find somewhere
to inflict maximum damage.
He needs a distribution system.
They have to circulate air here, right?
Aye, sir. There's an atmospheric
regulator at the core.
Lieutenant, contact Yorktown.
Make sure they shut it down
- until we find Krall.
- Yes.
How would he access the core?
Uh, well, there's a maintenance tower
at the station's gravitational nexus.
That's the only way.
Scotty, you get over there.
Make sure it gets shut down!
Lassie, you're with me.
Look, this thing
is impossible to shut down.
Aye, well,
we'll see about that.
Mr. Scott, why is that thing still on?
We're working on it, sir,
but as you can imagine
there's a lot of safety protocols
surrounding the thing that, you know,
- keeps everybody alive.
- Figure something out.
Be careful, Captain.
Gravity's gonna get a bit screwy
the closer you get to the center.
Maybe we should scan
the operational schematics,
- see if there's a back door.
- Right.
Lassie, I'm gonna need your eyes.
Stop!
What happened to you
out there, Edison?
Edison.
I have to say, Kirk,
I've missed being me.
We lost ourselves but gained a purpose!
A means to bring the galaxy
back to the struggle
that made humanity strong.
I think you underestimate humanity.
I fought for humanity!
Lost millions to the Xindi
and Romulan Wars.
And for what?
For the Federation
to sit me in a captain's chair
and break bread with the enemy.
We change. We have to.
Or we spend the rest of our lives
fighting the same battles.
You lost!
There's no way
you can make it back there.
Give up.
What, like you did?
I read your ship's log,
Captain James T. Kirk.
At least I know what I am.
I am a soldier.
You won the war, Edison.
You gave us peace.
Peace
is not what I was born into.
Scotty.
Captain, he's using
the gravitational slipstream
to carry him back to the center.
Nah.
No! No!
- What's that?
- The weapon's in the chamber.
Captain, we have to stop
the processor now
or everything breathing
in Yorktown is dead!
You can't stop it.
You will die.
Better to die saving lives
than to live with taking them.
That's what I was born into.
Scotty!
Captain,
I think we can redirect it.
There's a sealed construction hatch
that will let you vent the weapon
into space.
Now, we can override
the locks from up here,
but you will have to activate the hatch.
So I just hit a button.
It's not a button, sir.
It's a silver lever under a white panel.
- Got it!
- And there's four of them.
Once you've primed the hatch,
you'll have to exit
the chamber immediately.
If the hatch is open
when the processor cycles
and you're in it,
you're gonna get sucked into space.
What happens if the hatch isn't open?
You're gonna get sucked into a big fan.
With the weapon, and we all die.
Damn it, Jim, you won't
make it out in time!
The vent!
Get out of there, James T.!
Scotty, the last hatch won't open!
Scotty!
Work fast, Captain, time's running out!
He's not gonna make it.
No! No!
Manual override engaged.
Whoo-hoo!
What would I do without you, Spock?
For decades
the Federation taught that he was a hero.
I guess time will judge us all.
He just got lost.
You saved this entire base, Kirk.
Millions of souls. Thank you.
It wasn't just me. It never is.
Needless to say, the position
of Vice Admiral is yours.
No one deserves it more.
Vice Admirals don't fly, do they?
No. They don't.
Well, no offense, ma'am,
but where's the fun in that?
You didn't even
try to get our time out here reduced?
Why would I get it reduced?
Bones, we know our way
through the nebula now.
Can you imagine what we'll find!
Alien despots hell-bent on killing us?
Deadly space-borne
viruses and bacteria?
Incomprehensible cosmic anomalies
that could wipe us out in an instant!
It's gonna be so much fun.
By the way, where are we going?
I thought we were gonna get a drink.
I know you told me to keep it
under wraps, but, uh...
Happy Birthday!
Mr. Sensitive?
- There you go, laddie.
- Thanks, Scotty.
Everybody, raise a glass
to Captain James T. Kirk.
- Captain Kirk!
- Thanks, everybody.
- To the Enterprise.
And
to absent friends.
- Here's to that.
- Cheers.
All right,
let's get this party started.
Whose round is it?
Can I get three, uh,
Romulan ales for me?
I thought you had to
finish your mission report.
I do.
But I thought it would be more pleasing
to engage with you socially.
You old romantic.
Do you know that scotch
was actually invented
by a little old lady in Russia?
- Huh? Not many people know.
- Excuse me.
Uh, did you drink all those yourself?
I'm impressed.
Someone said it will take my edge off.
My edge is still not off.
All right, well, maybe this will help.
Captain pulled a few strings.
That is acceptance
into Starfleet Academy, if you want it.
They have a lot of rules.
Don't listen to them all.
Will I have to wear that uniform?
Afraid so.
Hey, Keenser.
Kevin. Still not wearing pants, I see.
I heard about Ambassador Spock.
Is that what you wanted
to mention that time in the turbolift?
More or less.
I trust your meeting with
Commodore Paris went well.
More or less.
You really want
to head back out there, huh?
Space, the final frontier.
These are
the voyages of the Starship...
...Enterprise.
Its continuing mission...
To explore strange new worlds.
To seek out new life.
And new civilizations.
To boldly go
where no one has gone before.