MOLLY: Max!
What are you doing up there?
MAX: You're the one who
wanted to take a break.
Break as in rest,
not break your neck
falling off the roof.
(DOOR OPENS)
Your dad used to sit up there.
Drove me nuts.
Did you run out here in the middle
of the night, or something?
You were eight weeks old.
I had my hands kind of full.
We're gonna clean it up.
It'll be great.
The cable guy comes tomorrow.
We should have Internet eventually.
(SIGHS) We're home, Max.
If you say so.
Hey, no more moving around.
Okay? We're gonna stay.
Right. For the ninth time.
Eighth.
I mean it this time.
I promise.
Hold, please.
You're a little warm.
Really? Really?
Sorry. I forgot. Habit.
Fresh start.
Right.
Fresh start number nine.
Hey, I can still
cancel the Internet.
(CHUCKLES)
MOLLY: Let's go, bud.
Boxes, boxes, boxes.
(MAN GRUNTING ON TV)
Your dad may have gone a bit
overboard with the stars.
I was actually thinking
he didn't put enough.
(CHUCKLES)
MOLLY: You okay?
Is that where it happened?
Um, yeah.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Now I'm gonna have to
call an electrician, too.
Babe, try not
to stay up too late.
First day of school and
everything. All right?
(MAN GRUNTING ON TV)
MOLLY: This bacon's not
gonna eat itself!
Hey, are you hungry?
I made you...
I'm good.
I'll see you tonight.
Okay.
MAN: (ON RADIO) In order
to amplify linking energy,
they developed a strategy
known as "mental fusion."
A practice that required not only
intense concentration, but...
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Crap.
Great.
MAN: (ON RADIO) They knew that
one warrior alone
could not produce
sufficient energy...
Ow! Ah!
GIRL: Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Don't be dead. Don't be dead.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
(PANTING)
Are you sure? (ECHOING)
What?
You okay?
Yeah, I...
I do this every year.
Um...
You're upside down.
GIRL: Sofia! Hurry up.
You're gonna be late.
Meet me here
after school, okay? (ECHOING)
I'll take a look at that bike.
MR. QUINN: "If you wanna find
the secrets to the universe,
"think in terms of energy,
frequency, and vibration."
Nikola Tesla.
Okay, start the water,
and begin the sound waves.
(HIGH FREQUENCY VIBRATION)
BOY: Awesome.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
And we have a new student.
Mr. McGrath. Max McGrath.
Here.
(BOYS CHUCKLING)
You're not
Jim McGrath's son, are you?
Um, yeah.
Uh, kind of. Yes.
GIRL: Oh, my gosh.
He was a remarkable man.
Where do I sit?
Now, this semester,
we are going to be diving
into the power of harmonics.
(CHATTER)
Hey.
You all right?
Yeah, I...
Hey, thanks.
SOFIA: Throw your bike
in the back.
Uh, this is a cool truck.
Thanks.
My dad and I restored her.
Really?
Don't look so surprised.
(CHUCKLES)
I might get offended.
Well, what do I know.
I drive a bike.
You named her, didn't you?
SOFIA: All right.
Good as new.
Thank you.
No problem. (ECHOING)
(RADIO SWITCHES ON)
Oh, that's weird.
And totally not my station.
Uh... (CHUCKLES)
Well, I will try to
stay out of
your way next time. (LAUGHS)
Oh, I'm sorry.
See you around,
Max McGrath.
MILES: Charlie Quinn. He was our intern.
(MOLLY LAUGHING)
Brilliant kid.
He was very good at bringing us
coffee at 2:00 in the morning.
MOLLY: Yes, he was.
Which happened
just about every single night.
Yes.
And I'm sure you...
Hi, hon.
Hey.
Wow, God, look at you.
MOLLY: You remember Miles,
don't you?
Yeah. Yeah.
No. No, you don't.
MILES: No, he doesn't.
He doesn't remember.
I am the guy who
used to send you
all the random
Christmas presents.
Right. Right, yeah, yeah, that Miles.
Of course.
Of course he remembers that.
You worked with my dad.
That's right.
MOLLY: Miles is gonna
join us for dinner,
so, why don't you
go get washed up?
Okay.
(HIGH-PITCHED VIBRATION)
SMITH: All right, here we go.
Come on.
LEE: I'm up three, man.
(PLAYING PING-PONG)
(LEE CLEARS THROAT)
LEE: (LAUGHS) It's 4-0. All right.
Here we go. You ready?
Come on.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
SMITH: I got you now.
What the hell was that?
MILES: I mean, we blacked
out about a 25-mile radius.
Fifteen.
No way.
How much?
It wasn't that much.
25-mile radius.
(MOLLY LAUGHING)
That's awesome.
The police didn't think so.
But your father of course,
as always a smooth operator,
he calmed them down.
He was a very
special man, your father.
(RUMBLING)
It's glowing.
It hasn't glowed in 16 years.
We have to...
So, you guys have just stayed
in touch all this time, then?
This is the first time we've met.
(LAUGHTER)
Actually, Miles is the one who
convinced me to come back home.
Really? Okay, wow,
so, I have you to blame then.
Mmm. It's all my fault.
It's amazing.
No, no, no, Smith, don't!
Smith.
LEE: What is it?
SMITH: Lee, call security!
Lee to security,
we have a breach.
Repeat, breach
in containment lab!
Subject is conscious. Repeat, the
subject is no longer in stasis.
Today was Max's
first day of school.
Really? How'd it go?
MOLLY: Mmm-hmm.
Uh...
It was okay. A few
more bruises than usual.
ARMED GUARD:
Go! Go! Go!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Shielding systems, engaged.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Stay down!
MAN: (ON RADIO)
Check high! Check low!
Up top on the vent! Up top!
Initiate Protocol Charlie.
Can you please stop doing that with
your chair? You're gonna break it.
Thank you.
All clear!
Watch the door!
Keep us sealed!
Keep us closed!
We got it.
(GRUNTING)
(GUN FIRE)
It's breached
the containment chamber.
So, what did you
do at N-Tek, then?
Mostly paperwork. Your father
was the true visionary, not me.
Miles rebuilt N-Tek.
He runs it now.
Well, our facility is nothing
like it was when Jim was there.
ARMED GUARD 1:
Behind you! Behind you! Down!
ARMED GUARD 2: Incoming!
It's breached the level.
(GRUNTS)
But everything
we're doing today
is based on your
father's vision.
Your father wanted
to save the world.
And we're just
following his lead.
MAN: (ON RADIO)
Don't let it get out!
MILES: He was right on
the edge of a breakthrough.
What happened?
Let's not go there right now.
It's such a long story.
No, it's fine.
We can talk about it.
What?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Miles was there
the night of the accident.
He tried to save your father.
(GRUNTING)
(GUARDS YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(DOG BARKING)
MOLLY: Make sure you're
not standing in water.
MOLLY: No, I don't have to
tell him. This isn't the time.
But he's not a kid anymore.
MOLLY: Yes. Yes, he is a kid.
Well, you'll be relieved to know
that we have plenty of SPAM.
MOLLY: Oh, thank goodness.
MILES: We love SPAM.
It never expires.
So, what did I miss?
Dessert.
Can I get you guys
anything from the kitchen?
If you ever want to
come by the office
and see what
your father created,
the door's always open.
Thanks.
I must say,
you do remind me of your dad.
Although a lot taller.
MOLLY: (CHUCKLES) A lot.
But you have his spirit.
And that's what counts.
Good night.
Bye.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You okay?
I'm going to bed.
(MAN GRUNTING ON TV)
REPORTER: Yeah, Bob, and
tonight the big question is,
was it a tornado that came through
this area or was it not a tornado?
Security camera footage seems to
show a funnel cloud in the sky.
(SYSTEM SHUTS DOWN)
What?
(KEYS CLACKING)
Come on!
Come... What?
What the...
No.
Off.
(MAN CONTINUES GRUNTING ON TV)
(CHUCKLES)
(RUMBLES)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
MOLLY: Max,
did you plug something in?
All right. All right.
Okay. Okay.
All right, you ready?
On.
(CHUCKLES)
This is freaking awesome! Ooh!
Off! Off, off, off!
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(BELL RINGING)
(CHATTER)
(POUNDING ON GLASS)
(MUFFLED) You like Thai food?
What?
You like Thai food?
I can't hear
what you're saying.
Tomorrow at 4:00,
the Thai place on Main Street.
What?
She said the Thai
place on Main Street.
Do you know where that is?
I'll find it.
Okay.
SOFIA: Tomorrow at 4:00, the Thai place...
(HEARTBEAT POUNDING)
Sweet!
Yeah!
(CLAMORING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey.
MOLLY: They're out
in force tonight.
MAX: Did you
find anything good?
MOLLY: Well, I didn't
find anything bad.
Hey, I unpacked the cutest
baby pictures of you today.
I'm gonna frame
the most embarrassing ones
and stick them
all over the house.
Wow, thank you.
What an honor that is.
(CHUCKLES) What can I say?
Although they'd
probably be safer
in the bomb shelter
in the basement.
Your dad was
nothing if not prepared.
For what?
The zombie apocalypse?
I heard you talking to Miles.
Why does everybody in this town
know more about Dad than I do?
What do you mean? I talk
about your dad all the time.
No, you don't.
I don't know
anything about his past
'cause you
never talk about it.
I don't know about his work,
or his family...
Or how he died.
(SIGHS)
Listen, bud...
I want you to
know your father.
I see so much of him in you.
He was such an amazing man.
But his story is
so complicated.
I just don't know if you're...
If I'm what?
Ready.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Hello? Mom?
Uh, sorry.
Hey.
You found it.
Yeah, sorry I'm late.
My phone kind of broke.
That's okay.
What is this?
Boba.
A what?
(CHUCKLES) Just try it.
Fair warning,
the texture's a little weird.
You get used to it. Mmm.
Mmm-hmm. Um-mmm.
No? (LAUGHS)
It's so good. Thank you.
It's such a treat.
No problem.
Frita.
What?
I named my truck Frita.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Frita. Wow, that is...
(LAUGHS)
Yes, and that's privileged
information by the way, so.
Oh, of course. You don't have to worry.
Your secret's safe with me.
Good. Because, you know,
I know a secret about you, too.
I know what
you're trying to hide.
What?
Well...
You haven't hooked up
with any of the cliques.
But you're
friendly with everyone.
You don't attract a lot of attention,
but you talk just enough.
So that people don't
think you're weird.
You're pretty
good at being alone.
Without being a loner.
Here, um,
put your number in my phone.
You should let me show you around
sometime, give you the tour.
Yeah. Maybe.
You'd better.
Um...
I... I think your phone died.
I just charged it.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Actually, you know what?
No, I, uh...
I got to go to
the bathroom really quick.
(FAUCET RUNNING)
No.
Off! Off!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, my God.
Watch it.
Max!
I got to go. I'm sorry.
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
JIM: Max!
(ALARM SOUNDING)
What?
MOLLY: Max, time to wake up!
(SCREAMS)
(THUDDING)
Mom!
No, stay back!
Stop! Stay away from me.
I'm warning you, stay back!
No, no, stop! I said stay away!
Okay, okay.
Max. Max.
What?
Wait, no, no, no. You said my name.
What did you just say?
Max, Max, Max.
MOLLY: Everything okay up there?
Max, Max.
What? What do you want?
Put down the weapon, Max.
Remain calm.
Oh, my God, you speak English.
What are you, some kind of a robot?
I am a parasitic,
silicon-based life form.
My name is, uh...
Hold on. It's one...
It's something that rhymes with...
I got this. Hold on. Uh...
Ak'stel.
Steel! He called me Steel.
Who did?
I don't remember,
but the important thing is...
I found you and now that...
Wait. Where are you from?
Ah. Good question.
I am from...
You're from space?
Yeah. I think so.
You're an alien?
Yes!
And you are Max McGrath.
Yeah.
I'm here to protect you from
everything that's trying to kill us.
Oh, my God. This is insane.
You had an insane
amount of energy. Wait!
Chronometer. Clock. Timepiece.
MAX: Energy?
Whoo! Cartography. Map.
Wait, wait, Steel.
What is this?
Oh, what is that?
MAX: What do you know
about my energy?
No, stop. No, stop.
What is this?
Stop! Stop! Steel! Steel!
Yes, Max?
MOLLY: Max, what are you
doing up there?
Oh, God, my mom is coming.
You have to hide.
Is "my mom" dangerous?
What? No, no, no! Come on!
STEEL: Cold hands!
Foul odor. You got to clean...
You got to clean in here, bud.
MOLLY: Max!
What's up?
Are you okay?
What's with all the yelling?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just... I had a bad dream.
Fell out of bed.
You were out cold last night.
You were already asleep when I got home.
Do you feel okay?
I'm fine. I... Growth spurt.
What is that noise?
Uh, nothing. It's just my
video games are going.
I need to get your laundry.
No!
I can do my own laundry
from now on. Okay?
You are so weird sometimes.
And you're gonna be late.
All right.
(GASPS) I had a dream, too, Max.
There was explosions and screaming.
Oh! Oh! I got it. I got it.
What are you doing? Get off me!
Why did you do that?
There was another buildup of
energy within you. I absorbed it.
MOLLY: Max!
You're welcome.
Okay, look, I'll just take you
back to where you found me,
and you can phone home,
or whatever.
No, no, no, Max. Listen, you
are gonna be generating
that tachyon energy for the rest of
your life. And that is all that I eat.
Without it, I would
actually starve to death.
After you, well...
After I what?
STEEL: Explode. So, yeah,
we are together forever.
All right, I want to know
everything that you know right now.
Okay.
Okay. Well, how about
the energy? The tachyon stuff.
Let's start with that.
Sounds good. Let's do it.
Where did it come from?
Uh, pass.
Did you do this to me?
No, I think
you did this to me.
You woke me up.
I was sleeping.
Is it gonna kill me?
Yes! If I'm not around.
Apparently, you don't realize
how lucky you were
that I was there
yesterday
to relieve you of
your excesses in energy
'cause you were
about to explode.
Explode. Right. I got it.
Jinx.
So, what? You're like some
kind of a space vampire then?
More like your space buddy.
Whoa. Heads up.
Excuse me,
Max, why are we hiding?
Because you're an alien.
They're gonna, like,
dissect you, or something.
Dissect. To cut open
a deceased organism for study.
But, Max, that doesn't make
sense 'cause I'm not deceased.
Good job, Max.
Now, watch this.
If we link together, Max...
No, don't, no.
It's okay. They didn't see us.
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Come on, move it!
Spread out! Find it!
Who were those guys?
They shot, like, real bullets at us!
They did seem angry.
Who wants to kill you?
Us, Max.
Who wants to kill us?
Oh, come on. You have to
remember something.
I don't know. I told you
everything I remember.
Wait, wait, wait,
I remember something else.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
HARKINS: The Ultralinks
are closing in!
(GROANS)
What was that? What was that?
I don't know.
I... I saw it, too.
I was in like a building.
It was like I was remembering,
but I saw you.
I saw a reflection of you.
I was you.
It was your memory. Why would
I see one of your memories?
See? I told you.
We are linked.
I feel like you're not
listening to me.
I heard a voice that
said something about...
I keep repeating myself.
It's getting old.
Ultralinks?
Is that what you are?
Ultralinks? No!
Max, those are very dangerous.
They destroy worlds.
They destroy everything. They don't...
They're coming. Okay, we
have to get out of here.
I can't go home.
Uh-huh.
Because you fear "my mom."
No, because guys with
guns are chasing us.
And because you
would freak her out.
Max, harsh.
We have to go somewhere
where they wouldn't attack us.
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
Hey.
STEEL: Hey.
Ow!
Don't, you can't do that.
Just being friendly.
Look, nobody can see you. Do you
remember the whole dissect thing?
That I do remember.
You have to be cool.
You understand?
I understand. But I cannot
control my temperature.
Ow!
I'm going to jail.
STEEL: As long
as I'm with you.
MS. BERNARDO: The integral measures the area
of the curve from point 'A' to point 'B'.
Copy these equations down,
this is all going to be on the final.
STEEL: The equations
are lies, Max!
This creature has no idea
what they're talking about.
Don't trust it.
I left my iPod on.
STEEL: No, you didn't.
Don't lie. (GRUNTS)
(BELL RINGING)
Are you crazy?
STEEL: (GASPS)
We've been attacked! Let go.
What'd you say to me?
I, uh, said
my backpack is heavy.
Stupid books. Am I right?
Freak.
STEEL: See, Max? I protected you.
Whoa! Incoming.
Max?
Sofia.
What happened to you yesterday?
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm so sorry that
I ran out on you like that.
My head just, um...
It felt like it was going to explode.
It was the boba, wasn't it?
No, I just...
I didn't want to leave you with the
impression that I was too cool.
But, uh, maybe I could
make it up to you?
Yeah? And just how
do you intend to do that?
Uh...
STEEL: Okay, this is boring.
Are you sure you're okay?
STEEL: It's cramped in here.
Yeah, I just...
STEEL: Come on, buddy.
Maybe we can talk
about this later. I have to run.
I'm really late
for my Zumba class.
(CHUCKLES)
STEEL: The girl creature
appears to cause
increases in heart
rate and respiration.
Perhaps you should
avoid contact with her.
Perhaps you should shut up.
STEEL: See?
She has made you angry.
Okay, we should be good here.
STEEL: I don't know, Max.
It seems like that girl creature
must have put out some kind
of mind control virus on you.
We should probably kill her.
What? No.
And her name is Sofia,
by the way. She's...
She's a cyborg.
She's, uh...
She's a war machine. A snail. An alien!
No, no, I'm an alien.
She's not dangerous.
Okay, okay.
Agree to disagree.
What are we gonna do, Steel?
We can't stay here all day.
Well, yeah, but perhaps
"my mom" can help us.
You claim she's an ally.
No, I can't dump this on her.
All my life, she's been like
insane about my health.
Taking me to
all these doctors.
If she knew what was
happening, she'd...
Oh! Excuse me one second.
Will you cut that out!
STEEL: No, it's okay.
No, I will not cut it out.
When you get worked up,
you generate energy.
Clearly, "my mom"
makes you upset.
No, she's just...
It just sucks.
What?
Everything that
happened with my dad,
she just kept moving us
from place to place.
Yeah. I know.
Yeah, no, I get it, right.
What's up?
Why am I telling you this?
Because I'm here for you, Max.
I'm here to protect you.
Which means
you can tell me anything.
Max?
You know, sometimes I just
wish my dad was still here.
That I could,
I don't know, talk to him,
or even know what
his laugh sounded like.
I don't even know him,
but I miss him.
I understand.
I don't even know where my
home is, but I miss it, too.
Right.
I'm sorry.
Nah, it's coolio. I was just kind
of going off your vibe anyway.
Although it could
help if you could
remember who was
trying to kill you.
Hey, us.
You.
All right, look, if you can just
remember something, I don't know.
Maybe more from the memory
that we saw, it might help us.
Um...
Here. Max, look.
What, this?
You remember N-Tek?
They attacked it.
They will come for us.
Wait, what?
The guys in the black vans?
No, the Ultralinks.
They always come for us.
Come on.
Uh, just... No trespassing.
Seriously?
All caps, Max.
Looks pretty serious to me.
Max, wait. Okay.
(WATER DRIPPING)
Okay, so, if you don't
remember any details,
how do we trigger
that memory thing that we had?
Does anything around here
remind you of anything?
STEEL: Yes!
What?
No, you go and then I'll go.
I thought you had something.
Steel, come on.
Oh! Don't move. I got you.
No, Steel, wait, no!
Will you stop!
Nah, I'm probably
gonna keep doing it.
How did you do that?
I didn't. We did.
I've been telling you,
if we work together,
we can
harmonize tachyon energy
so that it becomes far-cart-tar...
Turbo energy!
Turbo? Really?
Yes. Yes. It's very powerful.
The energy can enhance
your physical attributes.
Like how?
STEEL: Try moving.
Yes, that's very funny,
but fast.
Whoa!
Whoa, did you see that?
That was incredible!
Not bad.
Try something else.
That's impressive.
(CHUCKLES)
But, Max, do you know
what's even more impressive?
My knowledge of
battle strategy.
I have memorized volumes
upon volumes of extensive...
No way.
Uh, okay. We will get to
the strategy part later.
Concentrate.
(GRUNTS)
Okay!
We can come back to
this one if you want.
Yeah.
Whoa!
That was practice. Just do it
again and watch the landing.
Yes! Very, very nice.
(GRUNTING)
Whoo!
(GRUNTS AND CHUCKLES)
I blew stuff up before,
but I could never control it.
I mean, not like this.
See, Max.
We're a team. It works.
And you're sure
I'm not gonna die?
Mostly, but next, we could...
(SIGHS) I haven't even
shown you the best part yet.
(CHUCKLES)
Pretty cool, huh?
This is...
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
(SCREAMING)
STEEL: Hold on!
I gotcha, I gotcha, I gotcha!
Oh, yeah, that feels good.
MAX: Um, Steel, what is this?
STEEL: When we harmonize
energy, we create armor.
Steel, help!
STEEL: Hold on. Just relax.
MAX: Relax?
(BABY CRYING)
Steel, hold off the Ultralinks
while I power the core.
STEEL: You got it.
JIM: When they're all
in range, fire!
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
JIM: How did they get
through so fast?
STEEL: Mk'Rah!
That was my dad.
You knew my dad.
I guess I did.
How did you know my dad?
I don't... I don't know.
And that tornado, that must
have been the night he died?
That was no ordinary tornado, Max.
That was an Ultralink.
Steel! Steel!
Oh, everything looks
different. Yeah, wow.
MAX: Steel!
Yes!
Just seeing if anything
reminded me of anything.
Uh, coming. We're good.
No Ultralinks in there.
Hey, look, I'm in the kitchen.
(PHONE RINGING)
MOLLY: (ON RECORDING) You've reached
Molly McGrath. Please leave a message.
STEEL: What do we do?
Miles.
He was there that night.
Let's go talk to Miles.
Okay, so, apparently, my dad,
who I thought was a scientist,
knew you, an alien,
which is nuts.
And the two of
you were attacked
for some reason by
a wind-monster thing.
Actually, Max,
it's super, super scary.
See, Ultralinks can
manipulate the elements.
Air and wind and fire... So, that
night wasn't an accident at all.
They can control air itself
to create storms or tornados,
which is a kind of storm,
but also like...
So, my dad, he must have...
STEEL:...hurricanes or
tsunami or typhoon...
What, I don't know...
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(STEEL YELLS)
STEEL: Ow!
Sofia.
STEEL: Max,
we can still kill her.
Okay, I need you to be
quiet for a second, please.
It's like you actually
want me to run you over.
STEEL: No, we want you to go away.
Shh.
Did you just shush me?
STEEL: Danger.
What?
STEEL: Max, behind us!
Okay, uh, I got to go. Sorry!
This is not happening.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Max, we have
two vans in pursuit.
Okay. We need some
kind of, like, a plan.
Okay. Time to suit up.
No! No, no, no! We have to...
STEEL: What?
You don't like the suit?
We have to like split up.
Okay, if you can send them on like
a wild goose chase, or something,
then I can head to
N-Tek and talk to Miles.
I must protect you, Max.
Just buy me some time!
But, Max, what about my
knowledge of battle strategy?
For example,
in such a situation...
You don't care.
AGENT: All units,
we're completely disabled.
Fuck!
SOFIA: Hey!
Sofia! I'm not done
yelling at you yet.
Uh, look, now's not
really a great time.
I'm being really nice to you and
you keep flaking out on me.
Look, things are just really complicated
for me right now, so I just...
You should come with me.
What?
Uh, I'm super lost and I don't
really know where I'm going, but...
Where?
This place called N-Tek.
It's like right down the road.
N-Tek? That's 20 miles
away from here.
You gonna bike there?
Uh, good point. Let's drive.
Max!
Please.
Get in.
Are you sure
you're all right?
Never better.
It's a long story.
What's going on?
Um, my dad died here
when I was really young.
I didn't think moving back
would be a big deal, but...
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
So, I need a new
name for my bike.
(CHUCKLES)
Any suggestions?
Well, you want to name it
something child-friendly.
Child-friendly? Really?
Because it's a toy,
that's what you're saying.
You said it, not me.
Wow.
But, yeah.
Okay.
Well, you know what? Next time
we go out, we'll take the bike.
It's a classy ride.
You'll see.
Next time we go out, huh?
Yeah.
Max.
Miles.
I wasn't sure you would
take me up on my offer.
How you doing?
Hey, this is Sofia.
She goes to school with me.
I want to introduce you to her.
Hi, Sofia. How are you?
Miles Edwards. Good, thank you.
Official tour guide. Come on.
(CHUCKLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SOFIA: This is incredible.
Oh, thank you.
We're just trying to build
upon Max's father's work.
You know, when I first
met Jim 20 years ago,
he had such
a contagious energy.
It was inspiring.
I feel, uh...
I feel lucky to have
had him for a partner
even if it was for
too short a time.
Hey, can I talk to you?
Can we go somewhere?
Of course.
Go ahead. Have a seat.
Um, listen, I don't... I just need
to ask you one quick question.
Yeah. Have a seat.
No, no, I just...
Listen, I need to
ask you about my dad.
What exactly happened
the night that he died?
Max...
It's really not my place.
Miles, please.
I need to know.
Well, by the time I got there,
everything was gone.
And your father, he...
How should I say this?
Let me show you something.
You see this?
What is it?
It's a miniature
prototype of a power core.
It's a device that's capable
of harnessing energy
beyond anything that mankind
has ever attempted.
This was your father's dream.
So, then what happened?
Listen, your father was a dear
friend and a true genius,
but sometimes he tended to...
To leap before he looked.
And the energy that
he was playing with...
Wait. Wait.
I don't understand,
what are you saying?
That the accident
was his fault?
No, what I'm saying is that
sometimes we all have a tendency
to reach a little bit
too far for what we want.
Hey. You all right?
Breathe. It's okay. Come on.
(COUGHING)
Max?
Get him some water.
SOFIA: What's wrong?
MILES: Get some water
for him right now!
I have to go!
Max!
He has a habit of doing that.
You should look after him.
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
Dad?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(YELLING AND SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HORN HONKING)
Hey! Hey!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Hey! Get out of here!
Please, come on. Come on!
Hey!
(GASPS)
The car won't start!
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
You're welcome!
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(DOOR THUDDING)
(BULB SHATTERS)
(MAX BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(SCREAMING)
STEEL: Coming in hot, Max!
Steel!
STEEL: See, I told you we
should have stayed together.
I can't see!
STEEL: Oh, uh,
that's not right. Hold on.
Let's see, let's get a
little something going here.
Will you just pick one!
STEEL: Oh, I like this one.
Wait, where did it go? That was
that thing from the memory.
An Ultralink. What do we do?
STEEL: Well, Max, in the face of an
unknown enemy, hesitation is lethal.
What are you talking about?
STEEL: You see, Max, it's battle
strategy, for we don't have much...
(CREATURE GROWLS)
STEEL: Time.
Never mind!
(GRUNTING AND SCREAMING)
STEEL: Time to go.
Time to go now!
(GRUNTS)
Run faster, run faster, run faster!
Max, so much faster!
(SCREAMING)
What happened to the armor?
STEEL: The impact
de-harmonized us!
Why?
We have to
work together, Max!
Get down!
(BELL DINGING)
You missed.
Thank you for
pointing that out!
(STEEL YELLS)
Whoa!
No! No, no, no!
(GRUNTING)
STEEL: Max, hold on! Hold on!
Steel, help! Steel!
(SCREAMING)
STEEL: I got you!
Max, look up.
There! That's the Ultralink.
It's exposed.
Shoot it. Go turbo!
What? STEEL: Hurry, before
it reconstitutes the wind.
Concentrate. And fire!
(GROANS) We need
a cooler catchphrase.
Oh. Really?
I kind of like it.
What is that?
Uh, not sure.
Wait, that's you.
Why is that you?
I... I don't...
(GROANS)
Steel, hold off the Ultralinks
while I power the core.
STEEL: You got it.
JIM: What are you doing?
You've altered the power core!
Steel, please!
I trusted you! No!
You're one of them.
You're an Ultralink.
No. I mean, I guess that I am,
but I am not like them.
I can't trust you.
Max, the Ultralinks
are here to destroy the Earth
and your energy is the only
thing that can stop them.
Yeah, my dad had energy, too,
and you killed him for it.
STEEL: No, Max, I remember.
I fought alongside your father.
We used his energy to
fend off the Ultralinks
and now you and I
must do the same.
No, I can't do this.
I can't fight giant wind
monsters and talk to aliens!
Yes, you can!
Your father would...
No, my dad's dead!
Do you get that?
I don't have anybody.
I'm all alone!
No. Max, you are not. Max.
Stay away from me.
Max.
No, I said stay away from me!
(PANTING)
(INDISTINCT POLICE
RADIO CHATTER)
Mom.
MAN 1: He's here.
McGrath, stop! Move!
Stop!
Cut him off! Come on, come on!
MAN 1: Over there!
MAN 2: Come on!
Sofia!
Come on. Sofia!
Have you lost your mind?
Keep your voice down...
Oh, my God. What happened?
Were you in an accident?
Yes. I mean, no.
Technically, I was, but...
Let me take you
to the hospital,
or I don't know,
come inside, so I can...
I don't really have
time to talk about it.
I just really need your help.
Sofia...
What? Stop. No, no, no.
You're acting all crazy.
I will tell you everything.
I promise.
But right now, the people I love
are in trouble because of me.
What can I do?
I need a phone, your truck,
and a pair of rubber gloves.
Miles, it's Max.
Listen, I need your help.
They've got my mom and I don't
know where they're taking her!
MILES: Wait, Max, slow down.
Who has your mom?
I don't know. These guys with guns!
They were chasing me and...
It's happening again.
Wait, what's happening?
The storm tonight. You saw it.
It was an Ultralink, wasn't it?
Wait, you know about that?
Max, listen to me
very carefully.
The people that took your mom,
they don't want her. They want you.
This is a trap.
I don't understand.
Where is she?
The only place they could have
taken her is your dad's old lab.
The old N-Tek grounds.
Listen to me very carefully,
it's essential that we keep you safe.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
No, no, no! Come on!
Mom?
(WATER DRIPPING)
(RINGING)
Max, where are you?
Hi, uh, Mrs. McGrath?
Uh, yes.
It's Sofia. I'm a friend
of Max's. Is he home?
Uh, no. No, he's not.
Sofia, do you know where he is?
He came by to see me and he
borrowed my phone and my car,
but he was acting really weird
when we went to see Dr. Edwards
and he just ran out.
Mrs. McGrath,
is everything okay?
Yeah, uh, yeah.
Everything's just fine, Sofia.
I'll call you back.
Miles Edwards
ordered you to kill Steel?
Yes, ma'am.
That doesn't make sense.
Unless...
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
I am still the majority
shareholder at N-Tek.
So, the only person you
take orders from now is me.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
Now, go find my son!
(METAL CREAKING)
(ENERGY PULSATING)
Steel?
Steel!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Access granted.
Steel and I have seen this before.
It's a scouting party.
How many?
Half dozen maybe,
if we're lucky.
STEEL: Hurry, Mk'Rah.
We don't have much time.
They're forming
storm cells already.
MILES: These Ultralinks,
are they just like him?
No. They're nothing
like Steel.
He's risking his life to save
the Earth, just like us.
STEEL: Winds are picking up.
MILES: You're not
ready for this, Jim.
Yes, we are.
How long have we been
preparing for this day?
The machine will work.
We can stop them together.
STEEL: I've got strong winds
at the outer perimeter.
Steel will hold off the Ultralinks
while I power the core.
STEEL: You got it, Mk'Rah.
I'm clocking winds
at 90 miles per hour.
When they're all in range,
Miles, fire.
Here we go again, Steel.
STEEL: Here we go.
We should be ready to fire
within 20 seconds.
Two tornadoes have touched down.
These are big ones.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Energy source engaged.
Are you ready, Ak'stel?
STEEL: With you? Always.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Weapon initiating.
HARKINS: The Ultralinks
are closing in!
STEEL: They're through the outer walls,
but the chamber's holding.
We don't have much time.
Hurry, Mk'Rah.
JIM: How did they get
through so fast?
STEEL: Something's wrong. The outer
defenses have been sabotaged.
JIM: Steel!
(ELECTRICITY ZAPPING)
JIM: Miles, look out!
Behind you!
You're working with them.
Miles, what are you doing?
Steel.
JIM: Miles, please!
They call you rebel.
Did you know that? Did you know that?
JIM: Miles, listen to me.
Go for a walk.
JIM: No!
MILES: I chose
the wrong partner, Jim.
Miles. Miles,
why are you doing this?
You don't know what they are.
They'll consume everything.
I made a deal.
I eliminate you and the Ultralinks
let me have your energy.
I trusted you.
No! You trusted him!
You've lowered the defenses.
You've altered the power core!
And now
I'm going to drain you.
I am going to drain you of every
ounce of energy that you have.
No! No!
STEEL: Mk'Rah!
Steel!
STEEL: I can get you out.
Mk'Rah, listen. I can...
Steel, listen to me.
I'm going to
overload the core.
STEEL: No!
Yeah. If you go into stasis,
you'll survive the blast.
Once you wake up, get to Max.
Find him.
Dad.
Protect him.
He's the only
thing that matters.
No!
(SCREAMS) No!
You...
(GASPS AND GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
You're making
this so easy for me.
You know, at first,
I wasn't even sure
that you had begun to
generate the energy.
Till that little
monster woke up.
It was your father
who convinced Steel
to rebel against
the Ultralinks.
His own kind!
Thank you. Just what
I've been waiting for.
(GROANS)
The entire time I worked with
your father and his machine,
I was exposed to that energy
and it was exhilarating.
So, piece by piece
I built a suit that could
absorb the energy
like the Ultralinks do.
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
The Ultralink.
You wanted it to kill me.
To kill you?
I need you alive. Alive!
You're my very own source
of tachyon energy.
Now, step inside that core
like a good little battery.
And pick up where
your father left off.
You were supposed
to be his friend!
Your father was an alien, Max!
An alien!
You killed him.
Don't be so dramatic,
half-breed!
You think you're a warrior
like your father was?
You're nothing like him!
And you're all alone and you cannot win.
You are alone!
Now step inside that core!
Step inside the core!
Okay, okay!
I'm sorry, Steel.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Your father,
his name was Mk'Rah.
He was my friend.
We chose Earth to
protect together.
(GRUNTS)
(CORE POWERING UP)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
What are you doing?
That's too much energy!
Hey, you were wrong.
I'm not alone.
It's not possible.
MAX: Steel, now!
He trusted you.
We trusted you.
And you all made a mistake.
You want the power?
Then come and get it.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(WINCING)
It's over, Max.
STEEL: Come on, Max.
Let's get up.
MILES: Maxy, you can't
deny how good it feels.
STEEL: Max, we must avoid the claw.
It takes your energy and weakens our armor.
Yeah, I figured that out.
Now, what do we do?
STEEL: Stealth mode.
We have stealth mode?
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
You think merging
with that monster
will transform you
into some kind of hero?
You're no hero.
(YELLING)
Get away from the boy!
FEMALE AGENT: Harkins!
(GRUNTING)
Everybody get out!
(AGENTS YELLING)
He's too strong.
What do we do?
STEEL: Max, I remember.
Hello, Max. He's handsome.
(CHUCKLES)
Just like his dad.
But, uh, what will he be?
He'll be
whatever he wants to be.
(GASPS)
We're not running.
We're going back.
STEEL: Yes!
But we need a plan.
STEEL: Battle strategy.
A thirsty man is prone to drowning.
Come out, Max.
STEEL: Or...
Wait, is that it?
That's it.
STEEL: What's it?
We just have to
give him what he wants.
STEEL: Wait, what? Oh,
actually, that's really smart.
There's no one here
to save you. Come out.
Steel, will we survive it?
STEEL: I don't know, Max.
Ah! There's my boy.
Now, you can be smart,
or you can be dead.
I chose smart, your
father chose differently.
What about you, Max?
Well, I guess I have more in
common with my dad than I thought.
(GRUNTS)
You're just as
arrogant as your father.
You want the power,
then take it.
Steel, now! Go turbo!
STEEL: You got it, Max!
You idiot. You're giving
me everything I need.
You sure?
Because when I have too much
energy, I kind of explode.
This is for my father.
(SCREAMING)
(WATER DRIPPING)
Hey.
Steel.
Steel, come on, please. Hey.
Please.
You have to be okay.
I can't lose you, come on.
(GROANS) Ow!
(CHUCKLES)
(COUGHS)
See, Max,
we have fun together.
I still think
the armor feels weird.
I think it's all right.
We're like nesting dolls.
(LAUGHS)
AGENT: Clear.
There! Right here!
Now what?
Can you get up?
No. You?
No.
AGENT: D-06.
Secure the perimeter.
What do we do?
Let's hope
they're friendly.
MOLLY: Max!
Max.
Mom?
Max, are you okay?
STEEL: Careful steps,
careful steps.
Yeah.
Hey, I wanna
introduce you to somebody.
Steel, you're alive.
Hi, Molly.
We have a lot to talk about.
(CHUCKLES)
You totally married an alien.
Hey, what's wrong
with that?
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
MOLLY: The night your father died,
I didn't know what to do.
The whole town thought it was
an accident, a freak storm.
But I knew the Ultralinks
had come for them
and I was afraid
they would come for you, too.
So, I did the only thing I
could think of to protect you.
I ran. To different towns,
different doctors.
'Cause I didn't know if you
would blow up, or something.
I should have told you.
But I thought you were
too young to understand.
And believe me,
I never suspected Miles.
Yeah, just 16 years in a tank, Molly.
No big deal.
MOLLY: I said
I'm sorry, Steel.
If I had known
you were still alive,
you know I would have
never let that happen.
I would have kicked anyone's
butt who tried to hurt you.
STEEL: Aw!
So, it was Miles who suggested
we come back to Copper Canyon
in case the energy
manifested in you.
I was trying to help you.
And instead,
I almost got you killed.
I spent so many years
trying to hide this from you.
'Cause I was afraid
you'd end up like your dad.
But now I couldn't be
prouder that you did.
What's your name?
So, are there more
Ultralinks out there?
Yes.
Why do you think
I watch the stars so much?
Why haven't they come for me?
I don't know.
Maybe because
you didn't have the power yet.
But you're a threat now
and they'll come for you.
I thought I could
protect you, but I can't.
You know you're not exactly
making me feel any better.
But I do know
one thing, okay?
You will not have
to do this alone.
I love you, bud.
I love you, too, Mom.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
I've held on to
this for too long.
Now it belongs to you.
I don't understand.
You will.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Steel.
Show me.
He'll need to know where he
came from to know who he is.
(JIM AND MOLLY LAUGHING)
Thanks, Dad.
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey.
You're okay.
Yeah. (CLEARS THROAT)
Where have you been?
Uh, it's kind of
a crazy story.
Try me.
Listen, um...
I just came by to let you know
that you were right about me.
I'm used to being alone and I'm
actually pretty good at it.
Um, when I moved here,
I thought that
this was just gonna be
like every other
town I've lived in.
And then you showed up.
Uh, thank you for noticing me.
What's this?
Open it.
Uh, there.
(CHUCKLES)
We have a lot to talk about.
Uh-huh.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah. Uh, maybe
we could, I don't know,
go on that tour that you were
talking about in the car.
How's tonight?
Yeah, only if you
don't bail on me.
Never. Right.
Right. Uh-huh.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll see you later,
Max McGrath.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
STEEL: Okay, maybe it was
good we didn't kill her.
Yeah, you think?
Flight mode?
Flight mode.
I like flight mode.
MAX: (GROANS) Steel, this suit
seems tighter than usual.
Really? We're flying and you're
complaining about the suit?
MAX: Go right.
STEEL: Let's go left.
MAX: No. Let's go right.
STEEL: How about
your other right?
MAX: You know what?
Let's just go straight then.
STEEL: Okay.