Let go of me!
Okay, now I really have a wedgie.
Fred! Velma!
Can you guys hurry it up?
This ghost keeps grabbing...
Please!
Jinkies.
Fred. Come in, Fred.
-Fred! Can you hear me?
-Fredster here, Velms.
Shockingly, Daphne's been
captured again. That's okay.
When the Luna Ghost
rounds the corner with Daphne...
...Shaggy and Scooby will pop out
of the barrel...
You'll activate the conveyor belt,
spilling the oil onto the floor.
Just remember my plan.
Like, chill out, Scooby-Doo.
Stop shaking.
Me? That's you.
Right. It's me. Sorry.
Scooby-Doo, what are you doing, man?
Like, this is no time to...
Oh, boy.
Like, there's a ghost right behind me,
isn't there?
Run!
Go, Shaggy! Go!
-Run!
-Like, I'm trying, buddy!
Fred, now!
Hurry up!
-I got him.
-Look out!
Sorry!
-Sorry, Velma.
-I know, Fred.
-Where's the ghost?
-He's right behind us.
Skateboard!
Is he still after us, Scoob?
Banzai!
-Zoinks! Grab the hook!
-Hold on, Shaggy!
Daphne, are you okay?
I'm so over this
damsel-in-distress nonsense.
Where's Shagster?
-Like, I'm right here, man.
-Me too.
Scoob, that was fun. Let's grab
another skateboard and do it again.
Yeah.
There you go.
One for you.
Good-Iooking guy.
All right, nice to see you.
-Thanks for saving the factory.
-Pam, any comments?
This is a victory for any celebrity who
wants to make a quality action figure.
-What's the secret of your success?
-Teamwork.
I do a tremendous amount of teamwork,
and I always have a plan. Come on.
Yeah, my plan.
I knew from the start there was no
phantom. The Luna Ghost is, in fact...
-Old Man Smithers?
-The creepy janitor?
He wanted revenge after you
refused to go out with him.
How could you, Pam? I'm a lover-boy
of George Clooney-an proportions.
-Fred, how was the ghost able to fly?
-I can answer that. Watch.
These balloons fill with a highly
potent helium synthesis...
...giving the Luna Ghost...
...his weightless appearance.
I would have gotten away with it too,
if it weren't for you meddling kids...
...and your dumb dog!
I'll get you for this!
Scooby-Dooby-Doo!
Fred, I can't believe you took credit
for my plan again.
Some plan. That ghost pawed me
for an hour and a half.
It's not our fault you always
get kidnapped.
I don't always get kidnapped.
Can't believe you'd say that.
Oh, please.
You come with your own ransom note.
-My glasses!
-Who's helpless now?
I'm going to kill you, Daphne!
Watch the ascot!
You guys, look, I know I'm just
the dude that carries the bags...
...but we all play an important part
in this group.
I mean, we're just like a big,
delicious banana split.
Fred, you're the big banana.
Daphne, you're the pastrami and
gum-flavored ice cream. And Velma...
...you're the sweet-and-sour mustard
sauce that goes on top.
That sounds pretty good, doesn't it?
You know what, Shaggy? You've really
put it in perspective for me.
Thanks.
I quit.
-No.
-No way.
You can't quit. I was gonna quit in,
like, two seconds.
Now everyone will think
I copied off the smart girl.
Now, wait a minute.
Maybe I quit.
I do. Yeah, I quit.
I'm out of here.
Good riddance.
Don't...
No. Don't go.
Come on, you guys, don't do this.
Please don't go.
Do I quit?
No, Scoob...
...friends don't quit.
It looks like it's just you
and me for a while.
What now, Shaggy?
I guess we'll all just do
what we do best, Scoob.
This is primo.
Man, talk about toasted.
Man, the only thing I like better
than an eggplant burger...
...is a chocolate-covered
eggplant burger.
With hot sauce.
Yeah, just another beautiful day
in paradise.
I'm looking for a "Mr. Rogers"
and a "Mr. Doo." The detectives?
It's probably somebody looking for us
to solve some scary mystery.
Nobody home!
Quick, Scoob-o, grab the food-o,
let's scram-o.
I'm looking for a "Mr. Rogers"
and a "Mr. Doo."
Let's go!
I'm sorry, dude. I'd love to help you
out. You look like a really nice guy.
We're not detectives anymore.
I've been sent by Mr. Emile
Mondevarious to invite you...
...to his amusement park,
Spooky Island.
We don't go near places with "spooky,"
"haunted," or "creepy" in the name.
-Or hydrocolonic.
-Right, but that's for another reason.
But he'd like you to solve a mystery.
He'll pay you a fee of $10,000.
It's just, materialism
is not really our bag, man.
-Free airfare.
-No, thanks.
-Room and board.
And all you can eat.
All you can eat?
Fred?
Velma? Are you going this way?
-How have you...?
-Been?
-Yes.
-Great.
I'm on the lecture circuit
with my new book...
-...Fred on Fred: The Many Faces of Me.
-Jinkies, that's impressive.
And yourself?
I've been working at NASA, developing
hydropowered missile defense systems.
But, more importantly...
-...I'm on a journey of self-discovery.
-NASA?
Charter service to Spooky Island
will begin boarding momentarily.
What do you mean I can't have
seven carry-on bags?
-That's so economy.
-Crap.
Oh, no. I'm not talking to you guys.
-What are you doing here?
-Isn't it obvious?
We all received the same letter
from one Emile Mondevarious...
...the reclusive owner
of Spooky Island.
It's not fair. I was gonna solve
the mystery all by myself.
-And when you get caught?
-I'm a black belt now.
I've transformed my body
into a dangerous weapon.
It's true.
Far out. I guess we're, like,
all going to Spooky Island, man.
Where's Scooby?
Hello.
Sorry.
They don't allow big dogs
on the plane.
You've got to be kidding.
No one is stupid enough
to believe that.
Who's the ugly old broad?
-Say hello to Grandma.
-Aloha.
Flight 3774 to Spooky Island,
now boarding.
I wouldn't have agreed
to come if I knew.
Wait, just think about it
for one minute.
Mystery Inc. reunites. We'll be
a team again, just like the old days.
So come on...
...let's do that thing where we all put
our hands in, lift them up, and go:
Only if Fred and Velma do it.
People are watching, Shag.
Yeah, Scoob, "roo-hoo."
Come on, buddy.
Now that is a beautiful work of art.
Would you mind me taking a seat
there next to...?
To my grandma. That's my grandma.
Hi, Grandma. Like, no.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
Bless you.
I'm sorry. My allergies.
It's usually only dogs that do it.
-Maybe I'd better move.
-No, wait.
It's probably just
my grandma's perfume.
Yeah, even I sometimes get
a little allergic, you know. Oh, jeez.
I'm pretty sure Grandma wants to go
back and visit with her pal Velma.
Right, Grandma?
Okay.
Boy, oh, boy, those sure do look
like Scooby Snacks.
I know they're for dogs...
...but they're 100%% vegetarian,
and I love them.
Like, me too.
Far out. I've never met another person
who loves Scooby Snacks.
-Me neither.
-I'm Mary Jane.
-Like, that's my favorite name.
-Really?
No way.
Hello.
Grandma?
Velma, it's simple
behavior modification.
To cause a dog to discontinue any
action, flick it on the nose. Observe.
Scoob?
See?
Sit, Grandma! Bad, Grandma!
Don't eat the kitty!
Welcome to Spooky Island...
...the frightfully popular spring break
spot for college students.
Catch our Electrical Torture Parade.
It's a Dead World After All.
And the world famous Splatterhorn.
Scooby-Doo!
And the rest of Mystery Inc.
It's marvelous to see you!
How fanta...
I'm sorry.
That's the second time this week.
Thank goodness.
It's a new toy.
I'm just getting up to speed with it.
-Welcome.
-Thank goodness.
I was afraid I'd have
to lug those to the hotel.
That's what Spooky Island's about,
realizing your worst fears.
I'm Emile Mondevarious,
the owner of this amusement park.
-You seem less...
-Spooky.
...than we'd have guessed.
I can be pretty spooky
when called upon. I can go:
Claws and everything.
You wouldn't want to run into me
in a dark alley.
-So you're the one who brought us here?
-No.
What brought you here
was your insatiable appetite...
...for a juicy mystery.
The truth is,
Mystery Inc. is broken up.
That's the beauty of something broken.
It can be fixed.
Therein lies its potential.
And I need you to fix Spooky Island.
What's the problem?
I believe somebody's casting a spell
on the students.
Now listen and look around.
Notice any difference between those
arriving and those departing?
They look like sober, well-behaved
college kids.
Precisely.
They didn't before they came.
They've changed.
In other words, a magic spell.
Carol! Carol, how was the island?
Are you tricking on me?
It's me, Brad. We've known each other
since we were 3.
Back off my grill, son!
Carol, what are you doing?
I'm terrified. The young people
that come off that barge...
...the people I love the most,
they're in danger.
-I'm going to solve this one first.
-Not before I solve it first.
You'll look like total idiots
when you're captured and I save you.
Thank you. Marvelous.
Maybe we can celebrate later
by having a little spookapalooza.
Spookapalooza?
You haven't noticed anything unusual
since you started working here?
-Any weirdoes running around?
-No.
Welcome, dear victims.
My name is N' Goo Tuana.
This is my evil best pal, Zarkos.
You may recognize him from Telemundo
as the famous masked wrestler...
...Zarkos.
This enchanted island...
...is a thoroughfare
to the supernatural realm.
For centuries, it was home to creatures
who lived on the island undisturbed.
But then...
...ten years ago...
...Emile Mondevarious...
...antagonized these ancient beings
by building a theme park here.
The creatures are furious, my friends.
And I assure you...
...while you party...
...they plot...
...their revenge!
Do my friends frighten you?
They would, if it weren't
for the holographic projectors...
...there, and there and there.
What a smart little one.
Hello, Dead Mike's.
We got a "Mr. Doo" here?
I got a call for a "Mr. Doo."
Melvin Doo?
No, Scooby.
-Hello?
-Got a bag...
...of hamburgers here for you.
Just walk into the dark,
shadowy part of the forest...
...where no one can see you.
Okay.
-Want a stuffed thingy?
-Nobody can win those.
Fred says it's a worthless talent, that
I should've learned French instead.
I say you don't need to know what
" Voulez-vous coucher avec moi" means...
...to love that song.
I think being good at crane machine
is way cooler than French.
Voil.
Nobody's ever given me a stuffed
dismembered head before.
Excuse me.
Now I have to start my voodoo ritual
all over again!
Voodoo ritual?
-I was about to sacrifice this chicken.
-That chicken's not alive.
I know. What, did you figure that out
when you saw it didn't have a head?
What do you want?
Why you in the voodoo ritual space?
I'm looking for clues as to who's
behind the students' strange behavior.
Here's a clue:
Purple is a fall color.
-It's the middle of May!
-Pardon?
Do yourself a favor
and get off this island. Go home.
Go home before evil befalls
your skinny, aerobicized booty.
And whatever you do...
...do not, I repeat...
...do not go into
that Spooky Island castle.
-You want me to go to that castle.
-Didn't you hear what I said?
You knew I'd do the opposite
of what you said.
You told me not to go to the castle
so I would go...
...where you set a trap to capture me.
Unless...
...you knew I'd figure it out,
so you told me not to go...
...so I'd think you wanted me to go,
so I wouldn't go.
I'll find out what you're hiding
in that castle. You watch.
What in the world?
Hamburgers, where are you?
Hamburgers.
Thank you.
Shaggy!
It's been really nice.
Monster! Monster!
A monster?
Scooby-Doo, quit goofing around, man.
I guess I should go.
Bye, Scooby.
Bless you.
Shaggy. Scooby.
No way.
-Scoob and me don't do castles.
-Why not?
They have paintings that watch you,
suits of armor you think is a statue...
...but there's a guy inside who follows
you every time you turn around.
-How many times did that happen?
-Twelve. We're not gonna do it.
That's right.
Scooby?
Did you hurt your paw?
-Would you do it for a Scooby Snack?
-Oh, boy!
-And you'll be fearless?
-Fearless?
Hong Kong Phooey,
watch the fists of fury.
Here you go.
Thank you.
There's plenty more where that came
from. Let's go before someone sees.
You're not gonna stay out here alone,
are you?
No, thank you.
Oh, boy.
This place is, like, uber creepy.
Yeah, uber creepy.
The only thing missing
is a mindless zombie.
Fred, get back. I found this place.
I call dibs on its clues.
-I've already found some clues.
-What?
I followed some weird footprints here.
It might be dangerous for you.
If anyone messes with me, I'll open
a can of Chinese whoop-ass on them.
-What are you doing here?
-This ride was closed for construction.
It's the most likely place to hatch
a plan. And I wanted to scare Daphne.
Since we're all together,
let's split up and look for more clues.
-Daphne, you and l...
-Typical.
-What?
-Nothing.
-I was always picked last for the teams.
-Okay.
Daphne, exit through the entrance.
Velma and I will enter
through the exit.
And Shaggy and Scooby...
...do whatever you guys do.
Look at this, huh, Scoob?
It's like a medieval Sizzler.
Pinch me, I'm in heaven...
-It's an expression, Scoob.
-Sorry.
Velma, I never meant to...
Well, you know...
-...pick you last.
-Don't worry about it.
I know you.
All you care about
are swimsuit models.
Look, I'm a man of substance.
Dorky chicks like you turn me on too.
That's a compliment.
Yes! Yes!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, no!
And now for our dinner show.
What?
Watch out!
-I got a bad feeling about this.
-Me too.
And now for the main course:
You!
Feast on this.
Jinkies.
They're moving toward us. Run!
-We're trapped.
-Quick, try the bookcase.
-One of these has to open a passageway.
-Velma, this is a ride.
You got a better plan?
What do we do?
Do what we do best, Scoob:
Eat.
It's plastic.
So what? You drink out of a toilet.
So do you.
I'm not helpless.
I am helpless. I'm gonna die!
We made it, Scoob. We're alive!
That was weird.
Fred?
Are you all right?
The last book.
I don't feel so good.
Reminds me of the time we tried to eat
that guy in the hot-dog costume.
Looks like some kind of school.
In a spooky castle ride? Fishy.
Welcome to America.
I am using the language English.
-Shaggy, look.
-Let's check it out.
Oh, boy. Lights, camera, action,
huh, Scoob?
Now that you're a young adult...
...you'll need to learn societal dos...
...and don'ts.
Interaction between young
people is polite and casual.
Hey, sorry, bro.
I will crush your bones into dust.
Let's see how the situation
should be handled.
Remember, today's young people
have a language all their own.
Sorry, bro.
No big whoop, dog.
Catch that new vid on the box?
True dat. I'm up to sniznuff
on all popular trends.
Word.
It seems to be a brainwashing
facility of some type.
Wherever there's a brainwashing cult,
there's always a power-hungry leader.
-The Papa Smurf figure.
-Mondevarious.
Then why would he have
invited us here?
Jellybeans.
I'll have whatever he's having.
Are you challenging me?
Maybe.
Pull my finger. Too late.
-You're in trouble.
-Oh, boy.
I'm not stopping
till your fur is singed off.
We're here to solve a mystery.
Yeah, Scoob.
Let's get out of here.
Zoinks! Skedaddle!
-I found a neat and scary clue.
-Us too.
This is a brainwashing
facility for an evil cult.
Maybe this is the secret relic
thingy they worship.
We'll all be relics if we don't
get out of here.
I got a plan.
What's that smell?
Sir, they found the Daemon Ritus.
For your sake, they better not
have gone far.
It is time to summon
the big muchachos.
Like, oh, no!
Mystery Inc. You all seem rather
cheery. Good news, I hope?
Mr. Mononucleosis...
-Yes?
-We have hit a clue smorgasbord.
We have three suspects
as to who's behind this evil hooty.
N' Goo Tuana. He believes
your park's on enchanted ground.
The voodoo man, who tricked me
into going to the castle.
-And you.
-Me?
Let's split up.
We'll meet in a half-hour.
I'll interview employees to see
if they've noticed anything odd.
I'll translate these inscriptions
Daphne found.
I'll go research cults on the Net.
I'm a suspect?
Don't take it personally.
It's because you creep me out.
I see.
Fine.
Jinkies.
Hey. Your friends ditch you?
No, I always did the brainwork.
What's this?
I believe it's called
the Daemon Ritus.
Daemon Ritus? What's it for?
This describes
an old race of creatures.
It's reminiscent of Pandaemonous texts,
so I can make some of it out.
It looks like instructions
to some sort of secret ritual.
It is fascinating.
On the house. Nice sweater.
You really dig doing this, huh?
Like, clues and stuff.
Certainly.
Really focusing on a mystery
reminds me of the old days.
We were quite a crew back then.
That was the best time of my life.
Shaggy and Scooby...
What goofballs!
Kind of like they are today.
And Daphne...
So beautiful. She was the coolest girl
at Coolsville High.
Fred. He was so handsome.
And he really knew how to accessorize.
Sounds perfect.
Yeah, but every family has one nut.
Scrappy-Dappy-Doo!
Ghosts don't stand a chance with me.
Let me at 'em. I'll rack 'em.
I'll sock 'em.
For the thousandth time,
there's no such thing as ghosts.
Sure there are. When I find them,
I'll give them a dose of puppy power!
Oh, God. He's peeing on me.
That little egomaniac
had flipped his lid.
Scrappy, I told you,
no urinating on Daphne.
-It was an accident.
-You were marking your territory.
You don't have the scrote for this job.
Listen up, losers.
The time has come to appoint me
your unquestioned leader.
Either that, or I'm out of here.
What's the idea? You can't do
this to me. People adore me.
I'm as cute as a Powerpuff Girl.
I'll get my own show.
Puppy power, huh?
And he wasn't even a puppy.
He had a gland disorder.
Help me! Help me!
Monsters! Monsters!
This is the most embarrassing thing
you've done...
...since you cleaned your beans
at Don Knotts' Christmas party.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
There are no such things as ghouls,
ghosts, goblins or monsters.
Now listen up. There is absolutely...
...absolutely no such thing as...
Monster!
Fred!
Scooby...
Save Daphne.
My glasses.
I can't find my glasses.
Help me find my glasses.
Here they are.
Thank you.
Nice mask.
Bad breath.
Here.
Jinkies.
Velma!
Come on!
This is, like, the opposite
of what I wanted to do today.
Leave it!
Stand back, sir.
I'll protect you.
Mr. Mondevarious!
Daphne, go!
Scooby-Doo, where are you?
Running suitcase.
Run suitcase. Run...
Thank you.
-Where's Scooby?
-I hope he's okay.
-Right here. Scooby-Dooby-Doo!
-Hey, Scoob.
I have a sinking feeling these dudes
aren't brainwashed cult members.
What do they want with the students?
We need to follow them.
-Say what?
-Defeat them and save Fred and Velma.
Sort of like my plan: Get out of here,
let the creatures eat Fred and Velma.
No way. Fred and Velma
always figured out everything.
Now it's our turn.
For the first time, they're
the damsels in distress, not me.
-Help?
-Timber.
-Okay, I'm calling for help.
-No. I got this. I got this.
I don't got this.
-Coast Guard, Fitzgibbon.
-Hello, sir. We're on Spooky Island.
Our friends were...
...kidnapped.
We need someone here right away.
We do have a unit in the vicinity.
Can you meet them at the pier?
All right, they'll be right there.
"Our friends have been kidnapped."
-Something messed up is happening.
-Is the Coast Guard here?
What happened to the shattered windows
and busted walls?
Yo, Red. The ball.
Let's go.
Anyone else think this is strange?
-Okay, we need to split up.
-Why?
-We need to find Fred and Velma.
-I'll go this way.
And we'll go with you.
Come on, Scoob.
Fred?
Yo, the bitch was like, "What?"
And I was like, "Later on!"
What up, dog? And...
-...dog.
-Keeping it real.
-What happened last night?
-We got beats like it was the lizz-nizz.
-You know what I'm saying, G?
-No.
You hear that?
Get the dog.
-Damsel in distress.
-Let go of me. Help!
Hurry, get the door!
-Why is Fred in a bad mood?
-He's not in a bad mood, Scoob...
...he's a monster.
-Shaggy, bikes!
-I know, "yikes!"
No, bikes!
Scoob!
Shaggy, look out!
I just saw my friend Beth Ann.
Something's wrong with her eyes.
Like, hop on!
Like, what a drag!
Like, duck!
-Yes!
-That was great!
-Are you all right? You were great.
-You too.
-Scooby, what are you doing, man?
-Mary Jane is a man in a mask.
-Mary Jane is a man in a mask?
-Scooby.
What are you doing, man?
Step off, Scoob.
Shaggy, you're whipped.
I'm whipped? Yeah?
Why don't you say that to my face?
Okay, I will.
Your mommy eats cat poop!
No, Scooby-Doo,
your mom eats cat poop!
Bring it.
You want a piece of the Shagster?
-Feel the pain, Scoob.
-Okay.
Come on! Two shots! Two shots!
Me and you, me and you again.
I'll give you some right now, buddy.
Scoob!
I gotta save him.
You stay here, I'll be right back.
No, Shaggy.
I mean, it's too dangerous.
I've got to. He's, like, my best pal.
Friends don't quit.
Scoob?
Scooby-Doo...
...where are you?
Scoob?
Shaggy. Shaggy.
Shaggy!
Velma.
I'll save you.
Thanks, Shaggy.
Boy, am I glad to see you.
Let me go so I can return to my body.
Get out of here...
...before they steal
your protoplasm too.
I always knew you were a hero, Shaggy.
Jinkies!
-Hey, buddy.
-Shaggy!
Someone must have spiked my root beer
last night. Talk me down, man.
Fred, you're a frigging
protoplasmic head.
I know.
But I'm still the best-Iooking
protoplasmic head here.
How do you drive this?
The Darkopalypse's upon us.
Get what you need for the ceremony.
On your right. Your left.
I'm coming, good-Iooking!
-Thank you, you've saved me.
-Sorry, I'm looking for my friends.
But...
Put me back, Shaggy.
I'll figure a way out myself.
-Like, how?
-I don't know.
I'll use my tongue as an oar
and swim to the edge.
Sorry.
Yo, yo, you, yo.
What the...?
You could use a little sunlight.
That's one part of the mystery solved.
The creatures need our bodies
to survive in sunlight.
Like a human suit.
SPF 1,000,000.
But what are they doing here
in the first place?
Daphne, you okay?
Yeah.
-But I'm not Daphne!
-Fred?
I couldn't get to my body.
I didn't know where else to go.
It's not easy to steer
when you're pure spirit.
I can look at myself naked.
Oh, brother.
-Get your hands off me.
-Daphne?
-He planned this somehow, didn't he?
-Hey, good-Iooking.
Fred, you egocentric...
-Please tell me you guys are you.
-Fred keeps touching me.
Makes you nostalgic
for the homicidal creatures.
I stole this. I hope it helps.
The Daemon Ritus.
-I'm me again.
-Yippee for you.
Man, like, why am I wearing a dress?
Everyone remain calm.
Velma, what the heck's going on?
If I am correct...
...due to the instability of protoplasm
in the proximity of the Daemon Ritus...
...we're going to continue
randomly changing bodies until...
Jinkies!
...until the protoplasm realigns
with the correct bodies.
I'm Fred again!
Daph, what's wrong with you?
Don't you ever eat?
I'm me.
-I'm back.
-Like, me too.
Told you so.
-Oh, no.
-Let's go.
I guess that was the wrong ingredient.
Wait.
I know how to handle this guy.
Hey, you! What're you doing?
Yes. That is masterful.
I'm doing a voodoo ritual.
I need to get the right ingredients.
The only way to protect myself is
by blessing this dead Arnouki beast.
They're about to perform
their evil Darkopalypse ritual.
-Darkopalypse ritual?
-Right.
-That's what the ancient text describes.
-Don't open that!
They use the protoplasm
in the vat as an energy source.
And the leader needs to absorb a purely
good soul to complete the ritual.
Legend has it,
once the ritual is performed...
...the creatures will rule on Earth
for 10,000 years.
That's why I have this in my house.
To protect myself.
You have another one of those?
Those creatures are taking over
the world? That is so mean.
They can't do the ritual without a pure
human soul. Where will they get one?
I didn't say human.
Oh, boy.
Hello, puppy.
If the person behind all this
needs Scooby-Doo...
Then that person is the one
who brought Scooby here.
Scoobert. How are you, my friend?
Sit down, please.
Okay.
Scooby Snack?
Maybe one.
We'll need some more of those.
That's me!
It certainly is.
And that's because...why?
We love you, Scooby-Doo.
Unlike that alleged friend
of yours, Shaggy.
He wouldn't believe you about
that nasty girl Mary Jane, would he?
No.
But I believe you, my friend.
And that's why I've got
a very important job for you.
What's that?
That's a cat with a bobbing head.
Please don't touch it.
I would like you...
...to be a sacrifice.
A sacrifice?
If Mondorajagaga wanted Scooby,
why'd he invite the rest of us?
It doesn't matter.
We gotta, like, go save Scoob.
Our area of expertise is nut jobs
in Halloween costumes.
We're supposed to be heroes, man.
So I'm gonna do what I always do:
I'm gonna eat myself a Scooby Snack,
and I'm gonna save my best pal.
Velmster?
You think I'm gonna fall for that?
Giving me my own nickname?
Trying to make me feel like...
...part of the gang?
We could make a plan.
What can I do? The only thing
I'm good for is getting caught.
But you never let that
stop you before.
And if that's not a true hero,
then I don't know what is.
Let's get jinkie with it.
Okay, so we use the pulleys
to tip over the vat.
Daphne will open the air vents
and release the disco skull.
The light will refract off the skull...
The creatures will explode, I'll find
Scoob, and we'll have saved the world.
Oh, no. The ritual's beginning.
Quick. Attach this to the vat.
We're here to save you.
Shaggy, faster.
All systems go.
Wait, no!
Mystery Inc. rides again.
Quick, hide the Daemon Ritus.
Would you like another Scooby Snack?
Okay.
Scooby-Doo!
Yo, yo, yo. Yo, homedogs.
You forgot the next part
of the dance...
...where we do the Electric Slide,
you know...
Hurry up, Velma.
Welcome to my little
end-of-the-world party.
I've waited a long time
for this moment.
Thank you for returning
the ultimate party favor:
The Daemon Ritus.
And now, behold the sacrifice.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hello, thank you.
Thank you. Shaggy?
Let's run for it.
We gotta get out of here.
-I'm a sacrifice. Hello.
-A sacrifice?
Dude, that's not a good thing, Scoob.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
And I'm sorry I haven't been
a very good friend since we got here.
-But you gotta trust me now.
-You don't trust me.
I do trust you.
Now, look. Who's your best buddy?
-Shaggy.
-Right.
And who's my best buddy?
-Scooby-Doo?
-That's right.
You are. And we're like two trippy peas
in a far-out pod, man.
Best buddies trust each other.
Let's do what we do best.
Let's run out of here screaming
in fear like two lunatics, okay?
On the count of...
Let's make it five. One.
Two.
Hey, look at me!
The moment is at hand.
Through the Daemon Ritus,
I shall absorb the energy source.
And now, to complete
the transformation...
...I shall absorb the pure one.
Ultimate power shall be mine!
Nobody absorbs my pal!
Come on!
I'm free!
Look at me!
Get him!
Let's get the Daemon Ritus.
Get off my pincer!
Cowabunga!
Look, Velms. A man in a mask.
We love you, Scooby-Doo. We love you.
That alleged friend of yours, Shaggy.
I shall absorb...
Puppy power! I've outsmarted...
Scrappy-Doo.
Correction.
The new, improved Scrappy.
Because l, Scrappy-Dappy-Doo,
have absorbed enough energy...
...to rule the world
with my all-powerful army!
And I've brought you here,
puny, pathetic Mystery Inc...
...to witness my moment of triumph.
All I need to complete
my transformation is Scooby-Doo.
Me? Don't you mean Melvin Doo?
Seize them!
Like, let's get out of here!
Take that, pretty boy!
This is totally un-groovy, Scoob.
Scooby-Doo, where are you?
Yield to my puppy power!
-We gotta tip over the protoplasm vat.
-How?
The pincer. Come on.
You all need to step back,
because Fredster's got his groove on.
Got you! You look
so much bigger on TV.
You're done!
Come back here, you lazy beatnik.
-Crud.
-Told you so.
Like, wow!
Give me the dog!
Down! Sit! Bad Scrappy!
Let's finish this puppy! Now!
Not again.
Captured again, seorita?
Not this time!
-Now who's the damsel in distress?
-Me?
Straight up.
Mystery Inc., this ain't over!
Not by a long shot!
I'll rock you and sock you...
...and crush you like...
-Like, dude?
-What?
You're a bad puppy!
Come on, I can still take you.
Put them up, you mangy mutt.
Is that all you got?
-We did it!
-Yes, we did.
Cut it out.
Mr. Mondevarious, is that you?
Thank goodness!
Thank you! Thank you!
Velma! Thank you!
You're fogging up my glasses.
Two years ago, that little pest...
...turns up at a casting session
for our evil elves.
Next thing I know,
I'm stuck in a hole...
...and he's cavorting about
in a mechanical version of me.
But look, thank you so much.
What a delight. Fantastic!
Fantastic!
I love you, Shaggy.
I love you too, Scoob.
Now get off me, buddy.
Thanks. You saved my life.
Like, no problem.
And thank you, Scooby-Doo.
-My little schmookem-wookem.
-Shucks.
Fred, can you tell us
how you solved the case?
It all started when I was giving
a speech on my new book and...
And I think the Velmster
should take it from here.
Go.
Through the combined
intuitive powers of Mystery Inc...
...we've discovered the real villain
is, in fact, Scrappy Cornelius Doo...
...who sadly was corrupted
by the power of the Daemon Ritus.
Get over it!
So I got a little cranky.
It's no reason to freak out like a jerk
and try to kill all of humanity.
I would've gotten away with it too,
if not for you meddling sons of...
Now that Mystery Inc.
is back together...
...any comment on the Mud Bog Ghoul
who's been terrorizing London?
Whatever the case,
Mystery Inc. will be there.
Solving mysteries, man.
-Righting wrongs.
-Looking for clues and kicking butt.
How groovy is this, man?
Spooky Island finally came through
with its all-you-can-eat deal.
And there's nobody I'd rather
gorge myself with than you, Scooby-Doo.
-My best friend.
-You're my best friend, buddy.
You're beautiful like a beautiful
piece of pizza.
Zoinks! Them peppers is, like, hot.
-Wimp.
-Wimp? You think you can handle it?
Why don't you put your mouth
where your mouth is?
Okay.
Scooby-Doo, you feeling okay?
Here you go, dude.
-Like, how'd that taste, man?
-Delicious.
Well, let's get two more.
On the count of three.
One, two, three!