Everybody, heads up!
Heads up! Keep clear!
Keep it clear!
Okay, down!
Andale, si! Vamonos.
Keep it goin'!
Come on!
That's good, stay!
Slow it down.
No lo vayan a tirar!
Cuidado!
Traigala, traigala!
Okay, pushing team,
move in there. Move it!
Cuidado, vamos! I want
tasers on full charge.
Aaah!
Come on,
step back in.
Move it! Adelante! Puje, puje!
And push!
We're locked.
Loading team, step away.
Gate keeper!
Jophery,
raise the gate.
Aaah!
Block the opening!
Don't let her get out!
Aaah!
Work her back!
Shoot her!
Aaah!
Apuesto mil pesos
que se cae.
Hola, Juanito. Hola. Bienvenido.
What's this I hear
at the airport?
Hammond's not even here?
He sends his apologies.
We are facing a $20-million lawsuit
by the family of that worker,
and you're telling me that Hammond
can't even be bothered to see me?
He wants to be with his
daughter. She's getting a divorce.
I understand that, but we've been
advised to deal with the situation now.
The insurance company
- Okay?
The underwriters feel that
the accident has raised...
some very serious safety
questions about the park.
That makes the investors
very, very anxious.
I had to promise to conduct a
very thorough on-site inspection.
Hammond hates inspections.
They slow everything down.
Juanito, they'll pull
the funding. Jefe, jefe!
That'll slow him down more.
Encontramos otros mosquitos.
Seguro? A ver, muestrame. Si, venga.
Ooh! Aaah!
Watch your head.
If two experts
sign off on the island,
the insurance guys
will back off.
I've already got Ian Malcolm,
but they think he's too trendy.
They want Alan Grant. Grant?
You'll never get him out of Montana.
Luz, mas luz!
Why not?
Muchachos, echenme luz!
Si.
Why not?
Because Grant's like me.
He's a digger.
Que lindo eres.
Vas a ser-
Dr. Grant, Dr. Sattler,
we're ready to try again.
I hate computers. The feeling's mutual.
You'll get a reading from that.
Take a look.
Did it work?
How long does this take? It
should bring an immediate return.
You shoot the radar into the ground,
and the bone bounces the image back.
Bounces it back.
This new program's incredible.
A few more years'development, and
we won't even have to dig anymore.
Where's the fun
in that?
It's a little distorted, but I
don't think it's the computer. Oh.
Postmortem contraction of
the posterior neck ligaments.
Velociraptor?
Yes, good shape too.
It's five, six feet high, I'm guessing
nine feet long. Look at the extraordinary-
What'd you do?
He touched it.
Dr. Grant's not
machine compatible.
Hell, they've
got it in for me.
And look at the half-moon
shaped bones in the wrist.
It's no wonder these guys
learned how to fly.
No, seriously.
Well, maybe dinosaurs have more
in common with present-day birds...
than they do
with reptiles.
Look at the pubic bone, turned
backward, just like a bird.
Look at the vertebrae, full of air
sacs and hollows, just like a bird.
And even the word "raptor"
means "bird of prey. "
That doesn't look
very scary.
That kid's a pistol.
More like
a six-foot turkey.
A turkey, huh?
Oh, no.
Here we go. Okay, try to imagine
yourself in the Cretaceous period.
You get your first look at this
six-foot turkey as you enter a clearing.
He moves like a bird,
lightly bobbing his head.
And you keep still because you
think that maybe his visual acuity...
is based on movement, like T-Rex,
and he'll lose you if you don't move.
But no,
not Velociraptor.
You stare at him, and
he just stares right back.
And that's when
the attack comes.
Not from the front,
but from the side.
From the other two raptors
you didn't even know were there.
Because Velociraptor's
a pack hunter, you see.
He uses coordinated
attack patterns,
and he is
out in force today.
And he slashes at you
with this,
a six-inch retractable claw,
like a razor, on the middle toe.
He doesn't bother to bite
your jugular like a lion, say.
No, no. He slashes at you
here or here.
Oh, Alan.
Or maybe across the belly,
spilling your intestines.
The point is, you are alive
when they start to eat you.
So you know, try to show
a little respect. Okay.
Hey, Alan, if you wanted
to scare the kid,
you could have pulled
a gun on him, you know.
Yeah, I know.
Kids.
You want to have one of
those? I don't want that kid.
But a breed of child, Dr. Grant,
could be intriguing.
I mean, what's so wrong
with kids? Oh, Ellie, look.
They're noisy, they're messy,
they're expensive. Cheap, cheap.
They smell.
They do not smell.
Give me a break! Some of
them smell. Babies smell.
Cover the site!
Cover up the dig!
Tell them to shut down!
Shut down! Cut the machine!
Cover it all up!
Pull it over!
Just cut it,
will ya?
Cut it out!
Shut it down!
What?
What the hell do you think
you're doing in here?
Hey, we were saving that!
For today.
I guarantee it.
Who in God's name do you
think you are? John Hammond,
and I'm delighted to meet you
finally in person, Dr. Grant.
Mr. Hammond
- Well, I can see that my, uh,
50,000 a year
has been well spent.
Okay, who's the jerk?
Uh, this is our paleobotanist, Dr.
- Sattler.
Aha! Ellie, this is, uh, Mr. Hammond.
I'm sorry about the dramatic
entrance, Dr. Sattler,
but we're in a wee bit of
a hurry. Did I say "jerk"?
Will you have a drink? We won't let
it get warm. Come along, sit down.
Here, let me
- I'll just get a glass or two.
No, no, no, no,
I can manage this.
I know my way
around the kitchen.
Now, I'll get
right to the point.
Um, I like ya,
both of ya.
I can tell instantly
about people.
It's a gift.
I own an island off
the coast of Costa Rica.
I've leased it
from the government,
and I've spent the last five years
setting up a kind of biological preserve.
Really spectacular.
Spared no expense.
Make the one I've got down in
Kenya look like a petting zoo.
And there's no doubt our attractions
will drive kids out of their minds.
And what are those? Small
versions of adults, honey.
And not just kids, everyone.
We're going to open next year.
That is, if the lawyers
don't kill me first.
I don't care for
lawyers. Do you?
Oh, we, uh, don't know any.
I don't really know any.
Well, I do,
I'm afraid.
There's a particular pebble in
my shoe, represents my investors.
Says that they insist on outside
opinions. What kind of opinions?
Well, your kind, not to
put too fine a point on it.
I mean, let's face it.
In your particular field,
you're the top minds.
And if I could just persuade you
to sign off on the park,
you know, give it
your endorsement,
maybe even pen
a wee testimonial,
I could get back on
"shedual," uh, schedule.
Why would they care what we
think? What kind of park is this?
It's right up your alley.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you come down, just
the pair of ya, for the weekend?
I'd love to have an opinion
of a paleobotanist as well.
I've got a jet
standing by at Choteau.
Look, I'm sorry. This
is impossible. Yeah, we-
We just dug up
a new skeleton.
I could compensate you
by fully funding your dig.
And this is a very unusual
time. The timing is-
For a further three years.
Hmm?
Well, uh,
where's the plane?
Yeah, okay. Cheers. Cheers.
Okay.
Yo, Dodgson!
You shouldn't
use my name.
Dodgson, Dodgson!
We've got Dodgson here!
See? Nobody cares.
Nice hat.
What are you tryin' to
look like, a secret agent?
Well?
Seven fifty.
On delivery, 50,000 more
for each viable embryo.
That's 1.5 million, if you get
all 15 species off the island.
Oh, I'll get 'em all.
Remember, viable embryos.
They're no use to us
if they don't survive.
Oh! How am I supposed
to transport them?
The bottom screws open.
That's great.
Oh, my God.
It's cooled and
compartmentalized inside.
Oh, that's great! Customs can
even check it if they want to.
Let me see. Oh! Go on.
There's enough coolant inside
for 36 hours. No menthol?
The embryos have to be back
here in San Jose by then.
That's up to your guy
on the boat.
7:00 tomorrow night on the east
dock. Make sure he gets it right.
How are you planning
to beat security?
I've got
an 18-minute window.
Eighteen minutes, and your company
catches up on ten years of research.
Gracias, senor.
Don't get cheap on me,
Dodgson.
That was
Hammond's mistake.
So you two, um,
dig up dinosaurs?
Well-
We try to.
You'll have to get used
to Dr. Malcolm.
He suffers from a deplorable
excess of personality,
especially for a mathematician.
Chaotician, actually.
John doesn't
subscribe to chaos,
particularly what it has to say about
his science project. Codswallop, Ian.
You've never been able to sufficiently
explain your concerns about the island.
Oh,John,John. Because of the
behavior of the system in phase space?
A load, if I may say so, of
fashionable number crunching.
Is not. I do wish you wouldn't do that.
Dr. Sattler, Dr. Grant,
you've heard of chaos theory?
No. No? Non-linear equations?
Strange attractors?
Dr. Sattler, I refuse
to believe that you...
aren't familiar with
the concept of attraction.
Hmm! I bring scientists,
you bring a rock star.
There it is.
Bad wind shears.
We have to drop pretty fast,
so hold on,
'cause it can be just
a little thrilling.
Ya-hoo!
No, no, you need that piece
over here, and that piece-
Look, we'll have landed
by the time you get it right.
The full 50 miles of
perimeter fence are in place?
And the concrete moats, and the
motion sensor tracking systems.
Donald, dear boy, relax.
Try and enjoy yourself.
Let's get something
straight,John.
This is not
a weekend excursion.
This is a serious investigation
of the stability of the island.
Your investors, whom I
represent, are deeply concerned.
Forty-eight hours from now, if they're
not convinced, I'm not convinced.
I'll shut you down,
John.
In 48 hours, I'llbe
accepting your apologies.
All right, slow down.
Stop, stop, stop!
This shouldn't be here.
Alan, this species of
veriforman's been extinct...
since the Cretaceous Period.
I mean, this thing is humongous.
What? What?
Look at that.
Um, it's- it's a dinosaur.
Uh-huh.
You did it.
You crazy son of a bitch,
you did it.
Oh, Ellie, we could just tear up
the rule book on cold-bloodedness.
It doesn't apply.
They're totally wrong.
This is a warm-blooded creature.
This thing doesn't live in a swamp.
- This thing's got what, a 27-foot
neck? - The brachiosaur, 30.
Thirty feet.
We're gonna make a fortune
with this place.
How fast are they? Well,
we clocked the T-Rex...
at 32 miles an hour.
T- T-Rex?
Mm-hmm.
You said you've
got a T-Rex? Uh-huh.
Say again.
We have a T-Rex.
Oh.
Put your head
between your knees.
Dr. Grant,
my dear Dr. Sattler,
welcome to Jurassic Park.
They're moving in herds.
They do move in herds.
How'd you do this?
I'll show you.
G'day, g'day, g'day!
Now, the most advanced amusement
park in the entire world,
incorporating all
the latest technologies.
And I'm not talking just about
rides, you know. Everybody has rides.
No, we've made living biological
attractions so astounding...
that they'll capture the
imagination of the entire planet.
So what are you
thinking?
That we're out of a job.
Don't you mean "extinct"?
Well, now, why don't
you all sit down?
Uh, Donald,
sit down, sit down.
Ah, here.
Here he comes.
Well, here I come.
Yes.
Hello, hello. Say hello. Say hello.
Hello.
H- Hello.
Hello,John. Oh, yes, I've got lines.
Well, fine, fine, I guess.
But how did I get here?
Uh, uh, well,
let me show you.
First I'll need a drop
of blood, your blood.
Right.
Ooh! John, that hurt.
Relax, John, it's all part
of the miracle of cloning.
Hello,John.
Hello.
Cloned from what?
Loy extraction has never
recreated an intact D.N.A. strand.
Not without
massive sequence gaps.
Paleo-D.N.A.
from what source?
Where do you get a
100-million-year-old dinosaur blood?
Shhh!
What?
Oh, well, Mr. D.N.A.!
Where did you come from?
From your blood.
Just one drop of
your blood contains...
billions of strands of D.N.A.,
the building blocks of life.
A D.N.A. strand like me is a
blueprint for building a living thing.
And sometimes, animals that went
extinct millions of years ago,
like dinosaurs, left their
blueprints behind for us to find.
We just had to know
where to look.
100 million years ago, there
were mosquitoes, just like today.
And just like today, they fed on
the blood of animals, even dinosaurs.
Sometimes,
after bitin'a dinosaur,
the mosquito would land
on the branch of a tree...
and get stuck in the sap.
After a long time,
the tree sap would get hard...
and become fossilized,
just like a dinosaur bone,
preserving the mosquito inside.
This fossilized tree sap,
which we call amber,
waited for millions of years
with the mosquito inside.
Until Jurassic Park
scientists came along.
Using sophisticated techniques,
they extract the preserved blood
from the mosquito,
and bingo.:
dino D.N.A.
A full D.N.A. strand contains
three billion genetic codes.
If we looked at screens like these
once a second for eight hours a day,
it'd take two years to look at
the entire D.N.A. strand.
It's that long.
Since it's so old,
it's full of holes.
Now that's where our
geneticists take over.
Thinkin'machine super-computers
and gene sequencers...
break down the strand
in minutes.
And virtual-reality displays show our
geneticists the gaps in the D.N.A. sequence.
We use the complete D.N.A. of
a frog to fill in the holes...
and complete the code.
Phew!
And now, we can make
a baby dinosaur.
This score is only temporary.
It all has very dramatic music,
of course. Rum-pum-pum!
A march or something.
It hasn't been written yet.
And then, of course,
the tour moves on.
Well, lookie here!
Those hard-workin'cowpokes
you see behind the glass-
This is overwhelming,
John.
Are- Are these characters,
uh, auto-erotica?
No, no, no, we have no
animatronics here, no.
Those people are the real
miracle workers of Jurassic Park.
...D.N.A. in unfertilized
emu or ostrich eggs.
Wait a minute. How do you
interrupt the cellular mitosis?
Can't we see the unfertilized
eggs? Shortly, shortly, shortly.
Now, a whole team of
genetic engineers-
Can't
- Can't you stop these things? I'm sorry, it's kind of a ride.
One, two, three.
Uh-
You can't do that.
What?
Can they do that?
A reminder.:
The boat for the mainland
will be leaving at 1900 hours.
All personnel be at the dock no
later than 1845. No exceptions.
G'day, Henry.
Oh, good day, sir.
Oh. It's turning the eggs.
Oh, God.
Oh, perfect timing.
I'd hoped they'd hatch
before I had to go to the boat.
Henry, Henry, Henry,
why didn't you tell me?
I insist on being here
when they're born.
Come on, come on.
Come on, little one.
Come on.
Come on, little one, come on.
Come on, then.
Very good.
Push, push!
Very good!
Oh, God.
Push, come on!
Come on, then.
There you are.
There.
They imprint on the first
creature they come in contact with.
That's it!
Helps them to trust me.
I've been present
for the birth...
of every little creature
on this island.
Well, surely not the ones
that have bred in the wilds.
Yes. Actually, they
can't breed in the wild.
Population control is one
of our security precautions.
There's no unauthorized
breeding in Jurassic Park.
How do you know
they can't breed?
Well, because all the animals
in Jurassic Park are female.
Oh. We've engineered them that way.
There you are.
Oh, my God!
Look at that.
Blood temperature seems like
about high 80's maybe.
Wu?
Uh, 91.
Homeothermic? It holds that
temperature? Mm-hmm, yeah.
That's incredible.
Ooh.
But, um, again, how do you
know they're all female?
What, does somebody go out in the
park and pull up the dinosaurs' skirts?
We control their chromosomes.
It's really not that difficult.
All vertebrate embryos are
inherently female anyway.
They require an extra hormone given at the
right developmental stage to make them male.
We simply
deny them that.
Deny them that?
John, the kind of control...
you're attempting is, uh,
it's not possible.
If there's one thing the history
of evolution has taught us,
it's that life
will not be contained.
Life breaks free,
it expands to new territories...
and crashes through barriers
painfully, maybe even dangerously,
but, uh,
well, there it is.
There it is.
You're implying that a group composed
entirely of female animals will breed?
No, I'm simply saying that life,
uh, finds a way.
What species is this?
Uh... it's a velociraptor.
You bred raptors?
Dr. Grant, as I was saying,
we laid on lunch for you before
you set out into the park.
Our gourmet chef, Alejandro
- Oh. What are they doing?
Feeding them.
Alejandro's, uh, prepared a delightful
menu for us: Chilean sea bass, I believe.
Uh, shall we?
They should all
be destroyed.
Robert. Robert Muldoon,
my game warden from Kenya.
Bit of an alarmist, I'm afraid, but
knows more about raptors than anyone.
What kind of metabolism do they
have? What's their growth rate?
They're lethal at eight
months, and I do mean lethal.
I've hunted most things that can hunt
you, but the way these things move-
Fast for a biped?
Cheetah speed.
Fifty, sixty miles per hour, if they ever got
out in the open. And they're astonishing jumpers.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. That's why
we're taking extreme precautions.
The viewing area set down below
here... Do they show intelligence?
With their brain cavities, we assumed that
- They're extremely intelligent.
Even problem-solving intelligence;
especially the big one.
We bred eight originally,
but she took over the pride...
and killed all
but two of the others.
That one, when she
looks at you,
you can see
she's working things out.
That's why we have
to feed 'em like this.
She had them all attacking the
fences when the feeders came.
The fences are electrified,
though, right?
That's right, but they never
attack the same place twice.
They were testing the fences
for weaknesses systematically.
They remember.
Yes. Well.
Who's hungry?
More adventurous guests...
can opt for ourjungle river cruise or for a
close-up look at our majestic winged dinosaurs-
None of these attractions
are ready yet,
but the park will open with the
basic tour you're about to take.
Other rides will come on-line
six or twelve months after that.
Absolutely spectacular designs.
Spared no expense.
And we can charge anything we want: 2,000
a day, 10,000 a day. And people will pay it.
Then there's the merchandise. I can personally advise
- Donald. Donald.
This park was not built to cater
only for the super rich.
Everyone in the world has the right to
enjoy these animals. Sure. They will.
What, we'll have, uh,
a coupon day or something.
Gee, the lack of humility before
nature that's being displayed here,
um... staggers me.
Well, thank you, Dr. Malcolm, but I
think things are a little bit different...
than you and I feared.
Yeah. They're a lot worse.
Now wait a second. We haven't
even seen the park yet,
and you
- No, Donald, Donald. Donald, let him talk.
I want to hear every
viewpoint. I really do.
Yeah. Don't you see the danger, uh,John,
inherent in what you're doing here?
Genetic power's the most awesome
force the planet's ever seen,
but you wield it like a kid
that's found his dad's gun.
- It's hardly appropriate to start
hurling generalizations- - If I may.
Um, I'll tell you the problem with the
scientific power that you're using here.
Uh, it didn't require
any discipline to attain it.
You know, you read what others had
done and you took the next step.
You didn't earn the knowledge for yourselves,
so you don't take any responsibility...
for it.
You stood on the shoulders of geniuses to
accomplish something as fast as you could,
and before you even
knew what you had,
you patented it, packaged it and
slapped it on a plastic lunch box.
And now you're selling it.
You wanna sell it. Well-
I, I don't think you're
giving us our due credit.
Our scientists have done things
which nobody's ever done before.
Your scientists were so preoccupied
with whether or not they could,
they didn't stop
to think if they should.
Condors. Condors are
on the verge of extinction.
No! If I was to
- No, no.
If I was to create a flock of condors,
you wouldn't have anything to say.
Hold on. This isn't some species that
was obliterated by deforestation...
or the building
of a dam.
Dinosaurs, uh, uh,
had their shot,
and nature selected them
for extinction.
I simply don't understand this Luddite
attitude, especially from a scientist.
I mean, how can we stand in the
light of discovery and not act?
Oh, what's so great about
discovery? It's a violent,
penetrative act
that scars what it explores.
What you call
discovery...
I call the rape
of the natural world.
Well, the question is:
How can you know anything
about an extinct ecosystem?
And therefore, how could you ever
assume that you can control it?
You have plants in this
building that are poisonous.
You picked them
because they look good;
but these are aggressive living things
that have no idea what century they're in,
and they'll defend themselves,
violently, if necessary.
Dr. Grant, if there's
one person here...
who could appreciate
what I'm trying to do-
The world has just changed so radically,
and we're all running to catch up.
I don't want to jump to
any conclusions, but look,
dinosaurs and man, two species separated
by 65 million years of evolution,
have just been suddenly thrown
back into the mix together.
How can we possibly have the
slightest idea of what to expect?
I don't believe it.
You're meant to defend me
against these characters,
and the only one I've got on my
side is the bloodsucking lawyer.
Thank you.
Well. They're here.
You four are gonna have a spot
of company out in the park.
Spend a little time
with our target audience.
- Grandpa!
- Kids!
Wait! Careful with the
old man. We miss you.
Thanks for the presents. We loved
the presents. They were great.
Did you enjoy
the helicopter?
Yeah! It went down,
and we all went right up.
Now, kids, come away.
Not too close to the cars.
Aren't they lovely?
Aren't they glorious?
These will be your
transports for the afternoon.
No drivers.
No, no, no, no. No drivers.
They're electric. They run on this
track in the middle of the roadway.
Totally non-polluting. Top of
the line. Spared no expense.
It's an interactive
CD-ROM! Look!
You just touch the screen and
it talks about whatever you want.
Lex, darling, you're
all right in there.
Dr. Sattler, come with me. Dr.
Grant, come in the second car.
I'm gonna ride with,
uh, Dr. Sattler.
I read your book.
Well, that's...
that's great.
Do you really think that dinosaurs turned
into birds and that's where they all went?
Well, a few species may have
evolved along those lines.
They sure don't look
like birds to me.
I heard that there's
this, um, meteor,
hit the earth someplace in
Mexico and made this big crater?
Listen, uh-
Tim.
Tim, which car
were you planning on?
Whichever one you are.
Then I heard about
this thing in Omni...
about this, um, meteor
making all this heat.
And it made diamond dust. That changed the
weather, and they died because of the weather.
Then my teacher tells me about this
book by a guy named Bakker. He says-
She said I should ride with you
because it'd be good for you.
The boat is now loading.
Everyone must be on the dock
for the 1900-hour departure.
National Weather Service is
tracking a tropical storm...
about 75 miles
west of us.
Aye-yi-yi-yi. Why didn't
I build in Orlando?
I'll keep an eye on it. Maybe it'll
spring south like the last one.
Ray, start
the tour program.
Hold onto your butts.
And why did they
put the fiberglass thing?
I know.
What kind of dinosaurs
are we gonna see now?
Hey, lookit! A ghost, a ghost!
Aah! Oh, no. It's driving.
Turn in your fear at the door
and join the future, right?
Oh, God help us. We're
in the hands of engineers.
During most of your tour,
the appropriate information...
will be automatically selected
and displayed for you.
Hey, look! Simply touch the
area of the screen displaying...
the appropriate icon.
Are we gonna hit that?
Welcome to Jurassic Park.
What have they got
in there, King Kong?
The voice you're now hearing
is Richard Kiley.
We spared no expense.
If you look to the right,
you will see a herd of the first dinosaurs
on our tour, called Dilophosaurus.
- Dilophosaurus!
- Oh, shit!
One of the earliest carnivores,
we now know Dilophosaurus
is actually poisonous,
spitting its venom at its prey, causing
blindness and eventually paralysis,
allowing the carnivore
to eat at its leisure.
I can't see.
This makes Dilophosaurus...
a beautiful
but deadly addition...
to Jurassic Park.
Alan... where?
Damn.
Vehicle headlights are on
and they're not responding.
Those shouldn't be running off the car
batteries. Item 151 on today's glitch list.
We have all the problems of a
major theme park and a major zoo,
and the computers aren't
even on their feet yet.
Dennis, our lives are in your
hands, and you have butterfingers?
I'm totally unappreciated
in my time.
You can run this park from this room
with minimal staff for up to three days.
You think that kind of
automation is easy? Or cheap?
You know anybody who can network
eight Connection Machines...
and debug two million lines of
code for what I bid for this job?
If you can, I'd love to
see him try. I'm sorry...
about your financial problems,
but they are your problems.
Oh, you're right, you're absolutely
right. Everything's my problem.
I will not get drawn into another
financial debate with you, Dennis.
I really will not. There's
been hardly any debate at all.
I don't blame people
for their mistakes,
but I do ask
that they pay for them.
Thanks, Dad.
Dennis!
The headlights.
Yeah. I'll debug the tour
program when they get back, okay?
Okay? It'll eat a lot of compute cycles.
We'll lose part of the system for a while.
There's a finite amount
of memory.
You gonna compile for half an hour,
for crying out loud? Quiet! All of you!
They're approaching
the tyrannosaur paddock.
God creates dinosaurs.
God destroys dinosaurs.
God creates man. Man destroys
God. Man creates dinosaurs.
Dinosaurs...
eat man.
Woman inherits the Earth.
We'll try to tempt the Rex now.
Keep watching the fence.
What's gonna happen
to the goat?
He's gonna eat the goat? Excellent.
What's the matter, kid?
You never had lamb chops?
I happen to be
a vegetarian.
T
- Rex doesn't want to be fed. He wants to hunt.
Can't just suppress 65
million years of gut instinct.
Uh, uh, now, eventually you
do plan to have dinosaurs...
on your, on your
dinosaur tour, right?
Hello? H-Hello.
Yes?
I really hate that man.
See, the tyrannosaur, uh, uh, doesn't obey
any set patterns or, or park schedules.
The essence, uh,
of chaos.
Um, I'm still not clear on
chaos. Wh-What does that mean?
Oh, oh, it simply deals with, uh,
unpredictability in complex systems.
The shorthand is
the, the Butterfly Effect.
A butterfly can flap
its wings in Peking,
and in Central Park you get
rain instead of sunshine.
I go too fast. I did
a fly-by. I missed it.
Give me that glass of water. We're
going to conduct an experiment.
It should be still. The car's
bouncin' up and down, but that's okay.
Now, put your hand flat
like a hieroglyphic.
Say a drop of water
falls on your hand.
Which way is the drop going
to fall off? Which finger?
Thumb, I'd say.
Aha. Okay. Now freeze
your hand. Don't move.
I'm going to do the same thing,
start with the same place again.
Which way is it going to roll
off? Let's say back, the same way.
S- Same way.
Back the same way.
It changed.
It changed. Why?
Because tiny variations:
uh, the orientation of the hairs on
your hands, Hey, Alan, look at this.
um, the amount of blood distending
your vessels, imperfections in the skin-
Imperfections in the skin? Oh,
just... microscopic. Microscopic.
And never repeat and
vastly affect the outcome.
That's... what?
Unpredictability.
Right.
There.
Look at this. See?
I'm right again. Nobody could've
predicted that Dr. Grant would suddenly,
suddenly jump out of
a moving vehicle. Alan?
Alan! There's, uh, another example.
See, here I'm now by myself,
uh, er, talking to myself.
That's, that's
chaos theory.
Stop the program.
I told you how many times...
we needed locking mechanisms
on the vehicle doors?
Stopping park vehicles
and rebooting program.
We're on.
Will notify for resume.
I'll switch it
over to TelePromp Ter.
What about the circuit
integrities?
Screen says faulty sensor.
I'll call security.
We're a full go on that.
Looks good.
Like I was saying, there's this
other book by a guy named Bakker,
- and he says the dinosaurs died of a bunch of diseases.
- Where are we going?
You see something?
Is there anybody else who thinks
we shouldn't be out here?
His book was a lot fatter
than yours was. Really?
Yours was fully illustrated, honey. Hey.
You okay?
Hey, look at this.
Wait. Hey, watch.
Hey, come on.
Watch this.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Everybody stay here.
Timmy!
Hey, Timmy-
Oh, wow.
Okay?
Of course.
Don't be scared. It's okay.
Muldoon tranquilized her for me.
She's sick.
Oh, my God.
Hey! Hey, baby.
Hey, baby girl.
Yeah.
She was my favorite
when I was a kid.
Now I see her, she's the most
beautiful thing I ever saw.
It's okay.
Microvesicles.
That's interesting.
Thanks.
What are her symptoms?
Oh, imbalance, disorientation,
labored breathing. Right.
It seems to happen about every
six weeks or so. Six weeks.
These are dilated.
Take a look. They are?
It's okay.
I'll be damned.
That's pharmacological.
From local plant life.
Is this West Indian lilac?
Yes. We know they're toxic,
but the animals don't eat 'em.
Are you sure?
Pretty sure.
There's only one way
to be positive.
I'd have to see
the dinosaur's droppings.
Dino... droppings, droppings? Yeah.
Yep. Yep.
Yeah, I got that.
That storm center hasn't
dissipated or changed course.
We're gonna have to cut
the tour short, I'm afraid.
Pick it up again tomorrow where we
left off. Are you sure we have to?
It's not worth taking the chance. Well-
Sustained winds, 45 knots. Tell
them when they get back in the cars.
Ladies and gentlemen, last
shuttle leaving for the dock...
leaves in approximately
five minutes.
Drop what you're doing
and leave now.
Damn!
That is
one big pile of shit.
You're right. There's no
trace of lilac berries.
That's so odd,
though.
All right, so she's suffering
from Melia toxicity...
every six weeks.
Let's see.
Rats. Nada.
Every six weeks. She's, um... tenacious.
You have no idea.
You will remember to wash your
hands before you eat anything?
Doctors, if you please, I have
to insist that we get moving.
You know,
if it's all right,
I'd like to stay with Dr. Harding
and finish up with the trike.
Sure. I'm in
a gas-powered jeep.
I can drop her off at the visitor's
center before I make the boat.
Then I'll
catch up with you.
You sure? Yeah. I wanna stay
with her a little longer.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Now!
There's nothing I can do. The
captain says we gotta go, we gotta go!
You gotta give me the time. I did a test
run on this thing. It took me twenty minutes.
I could maybe push it to eighteen, but
you gotta give me at least fifteen minutes.
No promises!
Visitor vehicles are
returning to the garage.
So much for our first tour.
Two no-shows
and one sick triceratops.
It could've been worse,
John. A lot worse.
Anybody want a soda
or something?
I'm going to the machine. I thought, you
know, maybe I'd get somebody something.
I've had only sweets, and
I'm gonna get something salty.
I thought maybe
somebody would, uh-
Oh, I finished debugging the phones. I was gonna debu
- So I did.
You told me to, uh,
so I debugged the phones.
I should tell you the system
is gonna be compiling...
for, uh, eighteen
to twenty minutes.
Some of the minor systems might go on
or off, but it's nothing to worry about.
It's a simple thing.
You got any kids? Me?
Oh, oh, hell, yeah, three.
I love kids.
Hmm.
Anything at all
can and does happen.
Same with wives, for
that matter. You married?
Occasionally.
Uh, yeah,
I'm always on the lookout
for a future ex-Mrs. Malcolm.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
That's odd.
What? Door security
systems are shutting down.
Well, Nedry said a few systems
would go off-line, didn't he?
By the way, Dr. Sattler, um,
she's not, like, available, is she?
Why?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
You two are, uh-
Yeah.
Hey, what'd I touch?
Uh, you didn't touch
anything. We stopped.
Whoa, whoa. What the
hell? What the hell?
What now? Fences are
failing all over the park.
Find Nedry!
Check the vending machines.
Look at this workstation.
What a complete slob.
The raptor fences
aren't out, are they?
No, no.
They're still on.
Why the hell would he
turn the other ones off?
Access main program.
Access main security.
Access main program grid.
Uh, uh, uh!
You didn't say the magic word.
Uh, uh, uh! Uh, uh,
uh! Please! Goddamn it!
I hate this hacker crap! Call
Nedry's people in Cambridge.
Uh, uh, uh!
Phones are out too.
Uh, uh, uh! Where did the vehicles stop?
Their radio's out too.
Gennaro said to stay put.
Kids okay? I didn't ask.
Why wouldn't they be?
Kids get scared. What's
to be scared about?
It's just a little hiccup in the
power. I didn't say I was scared.
I didn't say you were scared. I know.
Boo!
Hey, where did you find
those? Under my seat.
Are they heavy?
Yeah!
Then they're expensive.
Put 'em back.
Don't scare me.
Oh, cool. Night vision.
Do you feel that?
Maybe it's the power
tryin' to come back on.
What is that?
Where's the goat?
Oh,Jesus!
He left us. He left us.
Where does he think
he's going?
When you gotta go,
you gotta go.
Dr. Grant?
Boy, do I hate
being right all the time.
Keep absolutely still. Its
vision is based on movement.
Turn the light off.
Turn the light off!
Turn- Turn it off!
I'm sorry!
You're the one
who turned it-
No!
Hey!
Oh, God.
- Hey-hey! Hey-hey!
- Ian, freeze!
Get the kids! Get rid of the flare!
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord be with me-
Aaah!
No! No! Aaah-
Dr. Grant! Dr. Grant!
Okay, Lex, I got ya.
I'm stuck!
The seat's got my feet!
I'll get you next.
You're okay. Dad! Dad!
You're all right.
Tim! Tim?
Don't move. He can't see us
if we don't move.
This way-
Wait, wait, wait!
Timmy? Timmy!
Tim!
Lex! Lex!
You're chokin' me!
Grab the wire!
"Keycheck space minus O, keychecks
off, safety space minus O."
He's turning the safety systems off. He doesn't
want anybody to see what he's about to do.
Look at this next entry. It's the
kicker. "White rabbit object. "
It did it all, but with the keychecks off,
the computer didn't file the keystrokes.
The only way to find them is to go through
the computer's lines of code one by one.
How many lines of code are
there? About two million.
Two million?
Yeah.
Robert, I, I wonder if perhaps
you would be good enough...
to take a gas jeep and
bring back my grandchildren.
Sure.
I'm going with him.
John. John?
The magic word, the magic word-
Uh, uh, uh!
I can't get Jurassic Park back
on-line without Dennis Nedry.
Should have been there
by now.
No damn good.
Oh, damn!
There's the road!
Winch this sucker off the thing and then
I tie it to that thing there and then I...
pull down this thing
here and I-
Oh. Oh!
My glasses!
I can afford more glasses.
Oh, geez!
You got time, you got time.
You can do it!
You can do it.
Come on, Dennis!
Hello?
Ha! Yeah, yeah,
that's nice. Gotta go.
Oh. Ah, nice boy.
Nice boy!
Nice dinosaur.
I thought you were one of your
big brothers. You're not so bad.
What do you want? You
want food? Look at me.
I just fell down a hill. I'm
soakin' wet. I don't have any food!
I have no food on me.
I have nothing on me.
Play fetch?
Look, see?
See stick?
Yeah, look, stick.
Look, stick! Stick, stupid!
Fetch the stick, boy!
You like the stick?
No wonder you're extinct.
I'm gonna run you over
when I come back down.
Aaah!
Timmy? Timmy!
Tim!
Now, Lex, listen, listen
to me. I'm right here.
I'm gonna look after you, but
I have to go help your brother.
So I want you to stay
right here and wait for me!
He left us.
He left us!
But that's not...
what I'm gonna do.
Okay?
Stay here.
Timmy?
Tim? You hear me?
I'm coming up.
I hate climbing. I hate
trees. Way too high.
Oh, goddamn tree.
Hey, Tim?
Tim?
Tim.
You okay? You okay? I threw up.
Oh. Oh, that's okay.
Just give me your hand.
Hey, Tim, I won't
tell anyone you threw up.
Just, just
give me your hand.
Here, I gotcha. Come on. Okay.
That's good. Over the wheel.
Don't pull me too hard.
No hurry.
Stand on the door.
Hang onto me.
Okay, I got you.
Okay.
Okay, that's not too bad,
right, Tim? Yes, it is.
Just like coming out of a tree house.
Did your dad ever build you a tree house?
No!
Yeah, me too.
The thing about climbing is, you never,
never look down! This is impossible.
How am I gonna do this? It's about
50, 50 feet- I'm gonna help you-
Oh, no.
Tim, go!
Oh! Go, go, go!
Go, Tim, go!
Faster, Tim!
Tim, jump!
Go, Tim!
Well... we're back...
in the car again.
Well, at least
you're out of the tree.
Where's the other car?
Where's the other car!
Alan!
Dr. Grant!
Grant!
I think this was Gennaro.
I think this was too.
I think
it's ahead of us.
It could be anywhere. With the fences down, it
can wander in and out of any paddock it likes.
He put a tourniquet on.
Ian. Ian!
Remind me to thank John
for a lovely weekend.
Can we chance
moving him?
Please chance it.
Ellie, come on!
Wait, wait.
The other car!
Dr. Grant?
Alan!
They're not here.
Anybody hear that?
It's a, um
- It's an impact tremor is what it is.
I'm fairly alarmed here.
Come on, come on, come on. We gotta
get outta here. Now, now! Right now!
Go, go, go!
Let's go!
Start the engine!
Must go faster!
Here it comes! Fifth
gear! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Get off the stick!
Bloody move!
Look out!
Down!
Think they'll have that
on the tour?
Are you hearing this?
Come on, Tim.
Come on, hurry up.
Let's, uh, get up this tree. Oh, no.
Come on, Tim, it's okay.
Try up here. I don't want to.
Okay.
Oh, man.
I hate trees.
They don't bother me.
Oh, yeah, well,
you weren't in the last one.
Hey, those are brontosauruses.
I mean, uh, brachiosaurs.
They're singing.
Shh, shh!
Don't let the monsters come over
here! They're not monsters, Lex.
They're just animals.
These are herbivores.
That means they only eat vegetables, but
for you I think they'd make an exception.
Tim. Oh, I hate the other kind.
The other kind just...
do what they do.
Ooh! Aah!
What's that?
What are you and Ellie gonna do now if you
don't have to pick up dinosaur bones anymore?
I don't know. I guess...
we'll just have to evolve too.
What do you call
a blind dinosaur?
I don't know. What do
you call a blind dinosaur?
Do-you-think-he-saurus.
What do you call a blind
dinosaur's dog? You got me.
A do-you-think-he-saurus'
Rex.
Alan?
Yeah? What if the dinosaurs
come back while we're asleep?
Well, I'll stay awake.
All night?
All night.
Hmph.
They were
all melting.
Malcolm's okay for now. I
gave him a shot of morphine.
They'll be fine.
Who better to get the children through
Jurassic Park than a dinosaur expert?
You know the first...
attraction I ever built when
I came down from Scotland...
was a flea circus,
Petticoat Lane.
Really quite wonderful.
We had, uh,
a wee trapeze and, uh,
a merry-go-
A carousel.
Huh.
And a seesaw.
They all move motorized, of course, but, uh,
people would say they could see the fleas.
"Oh, I can see the fleas, Mummy.
Can't you see the fleas?"
Clown fleas and high-wire fleas
and fleas on parade.
But with this place,
I wanted to show them something
that wasn't an illusion.
Something that was real.
Something that they could...
see and touch.
An aim not devoid
of merit.
But you can't think
through this one,John.
You have to feel it.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
Hiring Nedry was a mistake. That's
obvious. We're overdependent on automation.
I can see that now. Now, the next
time, everything's correctable.
John.
Creation...
is an act
of sheer will.
Next time,
it'll be flawless.
It's still the flea circus.
It's all an illusion.
When we have control again
- You've never had control. That's the illusion!
I was overwhelmed
by the power of this place!
But I made a mistake too.
I didn't have enough respect
for that power and it's out now.
The only thing
that matters now...
are the people we love.
Alan and Lex and Tim.
John, they're out there
where people are dying.
So-
It's good.
Spared no expense.
Go away! It's okay, it's
okay. It's a brachiosaur.
It's a veggie-saurus, Lex,
veggie-saurus.
Veggie.
Come on, come on, girl.
Come on.
Come on, baby.
Yo! All right!
I'm not letting go!
Looks like it has a cold. Yeah, maybe.
Can I touch it?
Sure.
Just think of it as...
kind of a big cow.
I like cows.
Hey, come on, girl.
Come on up here, girl.
Come on, up here.
God bless you!
Yuck! Oh, great, now she'll
never try anything new.
She'll just sit in her room and never
come out and play on her computer.
I'm a hacker! That's what
I said. You're a nerd.
I am not a computer nerd. I
prefer to be called a hacker.
Oh, God.
You know what this is?
It's a dinosaur egg.
The dinosaurs...
are breeding.
But, my grandpa said all
the dinosaurs were girls.
Amphibian DNA.
What's that?
Well, on the tour,
the film said they used...
frog DNA to fill in
the gene sequence gaps.
They mutated the
dinosaur genetic code...
and blended it
with that of frogs.
Now, some West African frogs have been
known to spontaneously change sex...
from male to female
in a single sex environment.
Malcolm was right.
Look.
Life found a way.
No, no, no, that's crazy.
You're out of your mind.
Wait a minute,
what exactly would this mean?
We're talking about a calculated risk,
which is about the only option left to us.
We will never find the command that Nedry
used. He's covered his tracks far too well.
I think it's obvious now
that he's not coming back.
So, shutting down
the entire system-
You can get somebody else,
because I won't do it.
Shutting down the system is the only
way to wipe out everything that he did.
Now, as I understand it, all the
systems will then come back...
on their original
start-up mode, correct?
Theoretically, yes. But we've never
shut down the entire system before.
It may not come back on at
all. Will we get the phones?
Yes, again,
in theory.
What about the
lysine contingency?
We could put that into
effect. What's that?
That is absolutely
out of the question.
The lysine contingency is intended to
prevent the spread of the animals...
in case they ever
get off the island.
Dr. Wu inserted a gene that creates a
single faulty enzyme in protein metabolism.
The animals can't manufacture
the amino acid lysine.
Unless they're completely supplied with
lysine by us, they slip into a coma and die.
People... are... dying.
Will you please
shut down the system?
Hold onto your butts.
Um.
It's okay.
Look. See that?
It's on.
It worked.
Wait a minute. What do you mean,
it worked? Everything's still off.
Maybe the shutdown tripped
the circuit breakers.
All we have to do is turn
them on, reboot the system:
telephones, security doors, half
a dozen others, but it worked.
System's ready.
Where are the breakers?
Maintenance shed,
the other end of the compound.
Three minutes, I can have power
back on in the entire park.
Just to be safe, I want everybody
in the emergency bunker...
until Mr. Arnold returns and the
whole system is running again.
I'm tired, I'm hot.
I'm dirty, my legs hurt.
Just keep going, guys.
The visitors center is just
about a mile over that rise.
Just... keep-
What is that?
Tim. Tim, can you tell me
what they are?
Gr- Ga, uh, uh,
gala-
Uh, gallimimus.
Are, are those, um,
meat-eating?
Um, meat-asaurusses?
Look at the wheeling.
Uniform direction changes...
just like a flock of birds
evading a predator.
They're, uh-
They're flocking this way.
I wanna go now.
Look how it eats.
Please! I bet you never look
at birds the same way again.
Yes.
Go now.
Okay. Keep low
and follow me.
Look how much blood.
Oh, God.
Something went wrong.
Something's happened.
Something's wrong.
This is just a delay.
All major theme parks
have delays.
When they opened Disneyland
in 1956, nothing worked. John.
But,John, if Pirates of
the Caribbean breaks down,
the pirates don't eat the
tourists. I can't wait anymore.
Something went wrong. I'm
gonna go get the power back on.
You can't just stroll
down the road, you know.
Don't let's be too hasty.
He's only been gone-
I'm going with you.
Okay.
Sorry.
This isn't going to be just like
switching on the kitchen light,
but I think I can follow this
and then talk you through it.
Right.
But, uh... it ought
to be me really going.
Why? Well, I'm
a- And you're, um-
- Look.
- Come on, let's go.
We can discuss sexism in survival
situations when I get back.
You just take me through this
step-by-step. I'm on channel two.
Right.
Oh, God.
The shutdown must have
turned off all the fences.
Damn it, even Nedry knew better
than to mess with the raptor fences.
Come on, this way.
I can see the shed
from here.
We can make it
if we run.
No. We can't.
Why not? Because we're being hunted.
Oh, God. In the bushes, straight ahead.
It's all right.
Like hell it is.
Run.
Towards the shed.
I've got her.
Go! Now!
Mr. Arnold?
John, I'm in.
Great. Now,
ahead of you
is a metal staircase.
Go down it.
Okay. Going down.
After 20 or 30 feet you come
to a T-junction. Take a left.
Have her follow the main cable. I
understand how to read a schematic.
I guess that means
the power's off.
That's not funny.
That was great.
Well, maybe, we could-
Damn it.
Dead end.
Uh, wait a minute,
wait a minute.
There should have been a right
turn back there somewhere.
Ellie, look above you.
There should be a large bundle of cable
and pipes all heading in the same direction.
- Follow that.
- Okay. Following the piping.
Timmy, I bet I could
climb over the top...
and be on the other side
before you could get to the top.
What would you give me?
Respect.
Come on, guys,
it's not a race.
I see the box.
It says "high voltage. "
Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
Good. Here we go.
Over the top.
Take your time, Tim.
That's good. Come on.
Find your footing.
Ellie, you can't throw
the main switch by hand.
You've got to pump up the primer
handle in order to get the charge.
It's large,
flat and gray.
All right,
here I go. Okay?
One, two,
three, four.
Okay. Charged.
Under the words
"contact position"...
there's a round, green button
which says, "push to close. "
"Push to close. "
Okay.
Push it.
Ah!
Now, Ellie, the red buttons turn
on the individual park systems.
Switch 'em on.
Timmy! You're gonna have
to jump! Get down now!
You crazy?
I'm not gonna jump.
Do what Dr. Grant says! Let
go! I'll count to three! One,
two, three!
Control room.
Tour.
I'm coming up. I'm coming up to
get you. Lex, I've gotta get Tim.
Okay. I'm gonna
count to three.
One,
two-
Timmy!
He's not breathing.
Mr. Hammond, I think
we're back in business!
Oh, my God!
Goddamn!
Oh, Mr. Arnold.
Clever girl.
Tim!
No, Tim!
Good boy,
good boy.
good boy, Tim.
Three.
Hello?
Okay. I'm gonna
have to find the others,
get you to a doctor.
Lex, you look after Tim. Hey! Yeah.
Your hair is
all sticking up.
Big Tim,
the human piece of toast.
I'll be back soon.
I promise.
Ellie!
- Run.
- Ellie!
It's just the two raptors,
right?
You sure the third one's contained? Yes.
Unless they figure out
how to open doors.
Timmy, what is it?
It's a velociraptor.
It's inside.
Follow me.
It's in there.
Control room.
We can call for help?
We gotta
reboot the system first.
The door locks!
Ellie, boot up
the door locks!
God!
No, boot up the door locks!
Ellie, get back!
Boot up the door locks!
You can't hold it
by yourself!
It's a UNIX system.
I know this.
It's all the files of the whole
park. It tells you everything.
Um, I gotta find
the right file.
Try to reach the gun!
I can't get it
unless I move.
Oh, this is it!
This might be the right file.
Wait. It's coming.
This isn't the right file.
Come on, Lex!
Oh!
You got it?
Yes!
You got it!
Yes! Yes, this is it! Yes!
What works? Phones, security
systems; you name it, we got it.
- Grant?
- Mr. Hammond, the phones are working.
The children all right?
The children are fine.
Call the mainland. Tell 'em
to send the damn helicopters.
Gonna cut through the glass!
Grant!
Move! Quickly!
Tim, move!
Tim, let go. Yeah.
Aaah!
Hold onto me!
Mr. Hammond!
After careful consideration,
I've decided...
not to endorse your park. So have I.