He stole the chip, he's inside.
I see him.
Kirill!
Time to work.
NSA Remote Intelligence
Facility Mt. Weather, Virginia.
At 0030 hours, the mission
deviated from the set parameters.
It wasn't part of the plan for our
agent to get shot in the back.
Identity confirmed.
McGrath was uploading some
data to us when he was killed.
Take a look at this. I'm not
sure yet exactly what it is.
- A fragment of a complex
molecule. - Gibbons.
We think it's a link to
a Soviet bio-weapon...
called Silent Night.
- James, what the hell is he
doing here? - I called him in.
We've lost three agents already.
You could use the help.
I found out your agents were
killed by this group, Anarchy 99.
They're ex-military. They can smell the
training on our agents a mile away.
Sir, I think it's time
we tried something new.
These guys aren't ours.
Who are they? CIA?
No, civilians. Convicts,
mercs, contract killers.
The best and brightest of
the bottom of the barrel.
- They're the scum of the earth. -
Programmable, expendable, effective.
I think it's our best shot.
Do we want to drop another
mouse in the snake pit?
Or send our own snake
and let him crawl in?
Sacramento, California.
Come on, Pepe. This
is unbelievable.
Hello!
Well, it's about time.
Now, listen...
Were you coming from Tijuana?
I don't mean to be rude.
Keep it out of the sun. I
don't want the paint to fade.
Do you understand English? I
pay enough for you people.
Come on, Janelle. You're
gonna love this place.
- Dick, how are you?
- This is Janelle.
- Call 911.
- Who's driving my car?
Senator Hotchkiss!
California State Senate!
Listen, somebody
just stole my car!
You, in the red Corvette!
Pull over immediately!
Yeah, yeah. These monkeys are
following me because I took this car.
Obviously the car doesn't belong
to me, it's not my style.
It belongs to Dick, Dick Hotchkiss,
a California state senator.
You remember Dick. He
tried to ban rap music...
because he feels the
lyrics promote violence.
It's music, Dick!
He also wants to pull every video game
off every shelf in the country...
because he feels that the video games
diminish the intelligence of our youth.
Come on, Dick.
It's the only education we got.
You're a bad man. You know
what we do to bad men.
We punish them.
Dick, you've just entered
the Xander zone.
I'm coming in hot
with a side of bacon!
Go, go, go!
Pull it! Pull it!
Yes!
Go get the cameras! Go! Go! Go!
Moral is, don't be a dick, Dick!
You guys got the cameras? All
right, let's go, let's go!
Peace out!
Outstanding.
Thank you.
- What's up?
- You invited these people?
Of course not.
That's my dog! What's up?
Today was off the hook!
You're psycho, bro!
Psycho? That was off
the chain, man!
Yo, yo, yo! What's up with that crazy
trick that we've been hearing about?
- My Superman seat-grab
barrel roll? - Word.
I'm still working on it.
You're a hard guy
to get ahold of.
You know, an athlete like you should
really have his own video game.
Jordan King. I can
make it happen.
- I'll hold on to this for
later. - You do that.
You know he'll never sell out.
That's why he is who he is.
So you need to relax. Who
invited you, anyway?
Shut up.
Listen, this is for real. I can get
us an advance on Internet pre-sales.
So you need to just go to
Pago Pago or something.
Get some girls, do them all. I
don't care. Go on vacation.
It's Bora Bora, J. I
got enough girls here.
Since when did you care
so much about money?
I just need you to lay low
till the heat's off, okay?
I run a secret website. I got tapes to
make and I can't do that with you in jail.
- Did you see that?
- I don't care. Listen to me.
I'm untouchable.
Let's go! Get out! Move!
Okay, I'll turn down the music.
It was only a Corvette.
Let's go, baby. Your
order is getting cold.
- Want coffee? - Can you
give me some hash browns?
- Sure. - Make them sloppy.
I like them runny.
How did I get here?
Two big guys dropped you off 10 minutes
ago. Told me to look after you.
You look like you could
use some coffee.
You all right?
Fine.
I said, you got a problem, boy?
No. No problem.
- Nobody make a move!
- Nobody move!
Just couldn't let him leave.
Keep your goddamned mouth shut!
- Keep still or you'll stop breathing.
- Empty the goddamn register!
Get back!
Get back. Get back!
- Well done, Mr. Cage.
- Who the hell are you?
The name's Gibbons.
Augustus Gibbons.
You seem upset. Is
there a problem?
- What is this place?
- Looks like a diner.
That's clever.
You almost had me going
there for a while.
I was a bit groggy before, then
I started noticing things.
Like, you got a stockbroker
over here, all dressed up...
reading the Financial Times on
Sunday when the market's closed.
Unlikely, but okay,
I can go with that.
I could even go with the stick-up
man packing a cop-issue Beretta.
But you want to know where
you blew it? With her.
My aunt was in the
restaurant business.
There's no way a career waitress
comes to work in high heels.
She'd have blisters
the size of pancakes.
And if she ain't real, then
this whole thing ain't real.
That's how I knew that this
bozo wouldn't get a shot off...
even if we waited till St.
Patrick's Day.
Because there's nothing
but blanks in these guns.
Oh, and no offense...
but their performances
were terrible.
That's good. That's very good.
It's your turn, pretty boy.
- What the hell is going on here?
- It was a test that you aced.
- He seems to have a poor
attitude. - Excuse me?
- Should we throw him back?
- Hell, no. I love his attitude.
Let's take this to the next
level. Get on the Sat-Com.
Take what to the next level?
- Yo! Take what? - I want
everybody out in 10 minutes.
I don't play this game.
- Get Mike a doctor or he'll
look like me. - I got a party.
- Shut him up.
- And pay for my windows!
Why is it always the
assholes who pass the tests?
You guys haven't been to
any diners lately, huh?
Diner finalists.
- What, no coffee?
- Oh, yeah.
- Here comes the ROTC.
- Here we go.
- Where's my peanuts?
- Nice.
Can you ask for the stewardess?
- Standing by to deploy drogue. -
Roger, deploying drogue parachute.
- This will hurt.
- What the hell?
- Release drogue now.
- Roger.
This ain't right!
I live for this shit!
Not bad!
Let's do that again!
Holy shit. This is Colombia.
Cocaine, man. These
are coke plants!
No keys.
- What the hell are you doing? -
You know what this shit's worth?
What now? Ls this another test?
- Let's go across the river. Let's
go! - Yeah, good idea! Good idea!
You monkeys are too good for me.
I failed this test.
You guys got something to drink?
Nice to see you again, fellas.
Yeah, you too.
Boy, they went all
out on this one.
You've got to be kidding.
Okay, funny guys.
I'll show you what we do when
you get in our business.
What? Hog-tie us and force us
to listen to your bad accent?
No.
We cut their Achilles tendon and watch
them flop around like a marionette.
Unless you have something to tell
me, something I need to know?
Okay. You're short.
My friend says you could use a haircut
to update your style. Get off me.
Shut up!
Two seconds ago you told us
to talk. Now it's "Shut up"?
I don't mean to nitpick, but you're
the worst at this torture thing.
You slap me again, I'm going
to throw you a beating.
I hope they're paying
you extra for this.
You know what, funny guy? Maybe
I'll cut off your nose first.
Funny guy.
What's funny is, this actually
smells like real blood.
I hope you like it, because it's the
last thing you're going to smell.
I'm hit! I'm hit! I'm hit!
Virg! Give me a hand.
This is the Colombian army!
Give up, you're surrounded!
Try to walk, T.J. Try to walk.
Virg! Get out here!
To hell with this.
Every man for himself.
I'll get us some wheels.
Hang in there.
Good luck.
The guy on the bike,
that's the drug Lord!
Let's get him!
T.J.!
X! I'm over here! X!
There he is!
We toasted his ass!
I got us a bike.
Pussies!
Look who it is. Frankenstein. Uncuff
me so I can beat the shit out of you.
Relax, X, you just graduated
at the head of your class.
What are you talking about?
You almost got us killed.
- We knew the army was moving.
- Excuse me?
It was my idea to send you as a
decoy. How do you like that?
- You're pretty fast for
an old man. - Get up.
Walk with me.
I believe under the right
circumstances, a man can change.
For instance, last night you
exhibited courage, leadership...
and willingness to protect
a man you hardly knew.
- So give me a medal.
- I'd rather give you a job.
Look at me. Do I look like
a fan of law enforcement?
This is your lucky day, Xander.
This is your chance to
pay your Uncle Sam...
for all your
wonderful freedoms.
The job's not that difficult.
I want you to meet people and
find out what you can about them.
What type of people?
Dangerous, dirty, tattooed,
uncivilized. Your kind of people.
Hold up.
My kind of people would say,
"Kiss my ass, scarface".
Usually I'd take my gun,
press it to your Temple...
and ask you very
politely to do what I want.
But you're not afraid of death.
That puts us in a quandary.
- We better call this a
day, then. - Not just yet.
You ever watch lions at the zoo?
You can tell which were captured in
the wild by the look in their eyes.
The wild cat.
She remembers running across the
plain, the thrill of the hunt.
Four hundred pounds of killing
fury locked in a box.
But after a while, their
eyes glaze over...
and you can tell
their soul has died.
The same thing happens to a man.
Leavenworth Federal
Penitentiary is no joke.
They'll take a wild man and throw
him in solitary just for fun.
No more mountains to board,
no more oceans to surf.
Just a 6-by-8 cell with no window
and only a bucket to shit in.
You can avoid that by
doing me this favor.
You don't have shit on me.
I noticed you have three X's
tattooed on the back of your neck.
I think that's rather appropriate since
you're looking at three strikes.
Grand theft, reckless endangerment,
and that bridge stunt of yours...
makes you a three-time loser.
Maybe you ought to call
yourself "Triple X".
But if you do what I want, I'll make
all your transgressions go away...
and let you get back to that
pathetic excuse of a life.
Or you think maybe I
should be like you.
Get all shot up for the
old Stars and Stripes.
I bet that flag is a real comfort
every time you look in the mirror.
A small price I paid for putting
foot to ass for my country.
So, what's it going
to be, Triple X?
You want to get on a plane...
or is "Kiss my ass,
scarface" your final answer?
Prague, Czech Republic.
Yo. What's your name, slick?
My name is Ivan.
- Ivan? What's your name,
buddy? - My name is Ivan.
You're both Ivan?
Take a seat.
Idiots! Where is the
American agent?
This is him, Sir.
We better order another bodybag.
Guys, what's up?
I told you to sit down.
I've just been on a plane for
12 hours. I think I'll stand.
My name is Milan Sova,
Czech secret police.
Here, you are under
my jurisdiction.
You take my orders,
you do what I say.
If you become any kind of an
inconvenience, I'll shoot you.
That's great. Is this
where I'm staying?
Your government is putting
pressure on mine.
This is an internal Czech affair
that you are interfering with.
I will warn you Don't
shit in my lawn.
Get whatever information your
government seeks and get out.
Let's get this straight.
You may not want me here, but I
definitely don't want to be here.
Two, I've never been under
anyone's jurisdiction.
Three, if you're going
to shoot anybody...
shoot that monkey
that sold you the suit.
Now, I'm tired. I'm
going to sleep.
Be ready in three hours.
Everybody in this club
has two things in common
- They're rich and they're criminals. -
I'll fit in, except for the rich part.
- Remember, we don't know each
other. - I wish we didn't.
Yeah, can I get a
cranberry club soda?
Throw this back there?
I'll tip you something.
Put it in the back.
How much? Do I get a ticket?
That's them. Anarchy 99.
You see the guy on the couch?
That's Yorgi. He's the leader.
He owns this club and five others like
it. All, how do you say, cash cows.
American?!
Guys, I'm American. I'm
going to see Yorgi. Yorgi!
Hey, Yorgi! I hear
you're the guy...
I heard you're the guy
to talk to about cars.
Take yourself outside.
Take myself outside? I'm just...
Okay. I'm not welcome.
Guess you'd rather have
cops in your club.
Want to talk?
Hey, you silly boy. Come with
me and show me the cop...
and don't be mistake.
See that guy there, with the
suit made out of drapes?
That's a cop.
Is there a problem? I just
had a drink, you know?
I already paid. I'm going to
give a big tip, you know?
So, what is this all about?
I've done nothing.
You've done nothing?
Who do you work for?
I work in a bank. So what?
You've got to be...
What are you doing?
Stop it! Stop it!
What's that, your bus pass?
Czech 5-0. Czech 5-0.
Leave my club.
How did you know?
When he was paying for his drinks, he
was flashing his badge to half the bar.
Cops like plague.
No matter how many you pay, there's
always another with his hand out.
I'm from the streets. I
know cops, believe me.
I appreciate you bringing this to our
attention. My question to you is why?
I figure, no one likes
cops crashing their party.
I figure, I do you a
solid, we could talk.
I just want to buy cars, man.
Is this guy going
to hump my leg?
What's your name?
Xander Cage.
I knew it.
You are amazing on snowboard,
motorbike, everything.
- You're awesome.
- Thank you, man.
My brother is crazy too, and
a great admirer of yours.
He has seen your tapes many
times. Now we can talk business.
This way, please.
Yelena.
Welcome to the Xander zone.
Now, that's funny. That's funny.
Sit down, Mr. Cage.
My friends call me X.
So, X, what exactly
are you wanting?
Ferraris, high-end pasta
rockets, 10 to start.
This car, number 10, will be very
difficult to find in Europe.
That one's for me. I put it in there
to get something out of the deal.
Well, you certainly
know your cars.
Yeah. Cars, bikes, boards.
You name it.
I like anything fast enough
to do something stupid in.
Yes.
Ten cars is hardly worth the
effort. A lousy 1.5 million, U.S.
Now, hold on a second.
The American buyers I represent,
to them, 10 cars is an appetizer.
- And it's a mil Max, sister.
- How about a million four?
I was thinking more
like a mil two.
Do you know what a
wire transfer is?
Is she for real?
Sweetheart, is there
anything you need to do?
Let us big boys have
a conversation.
"Conversation", a word
with four syllables.
Do you want some ice before
your brain overheats?
Ice. Yeah, you could chisel some off
your heart, if you could find it.
This would work a lot faster,
princess, if I had an account number.
You have 48 hours to
complete the transfer.
- Don't waste my time.
- I wouldn't dream of it.
I might throw in a couple extra
bucks and send you to charm school.
Now that business is
finished, we party.
Bitches, come!
Yeah?
Shit, I thought this
was a cell phone.
Have a nice rest?
Dial it down. I got
to sleep an hour ago.
You were given a specific list of
cars. Who told you to alter it?
The cars sucked. They
would've seen through it.
You guys should
switch travel agents.
I got that info you wanted.
Hang on a second.
You guys ready for this?
Names, birthdays, ranks
in the Red Army.
Favorite foods? How
did you get this?
Kolya, Yorgi's younger brother, happens
to be an action sports fanatic.
So naturally, he's a fan.
But when you kill a bottle of vodka
in three swigs, you'll talk.
- I got something else.
- What?
Their personal bank account
number. Where did I put that?
Stolen cars, nightclubs,
prostitution, extortion.
What's the big deal? We got
criminals like this in the U.S.
Your job isn't to ask questions.
Well, I did my job, thank you.
I'm coming home.
Not just yet.
You're a victim of your own
success. Get closer to these guys.
- They're cool, but not
that cool. - Go deeper.
I'll send a guy with a
care package to help you.
- I thought we had a deal. - You
change cars, I change the deal.
Do this for me, you
can come home.
If you send someone to save the world,
make sure they like it the way it is.
I have a really firm chest.
I bench, like, 225.
Like, bench. Weight room. Bye.
- That's him.
- Wait. You're Triple X?
- You're the care package?
- Agent Toby Lee Shavers.
Come on.
You have to rate high to get
Gibbons to send this stuff.
I kind of wish I was going with you,
mixed up in the fury of the situation.
Crazy. License to kill,
death, destruction, mayhem.
Got a gun under your pillow. Never know
when some freak villain will pop out.
- How long you been with
the agency? - Two days.
You're shitting me. No way.
That sucks.
Yeah, it sucks, but
it beats jail.
It sucks because I
spent six years...
in the basement of some windowless,
NSA, gadget freak room, man.
And I got a degree. I
got a degree from MIT.
Phi Beta Kappa, Magna cum laude.
And they probably picked you up,
what, pumping iron in San Quentin?
You ever get punched in the
face for talking too much?
Show me the stuff.
This one made my career, the
definition of perfection
My multi-purpose,
multi-function field revolver.
- Oh, I like this.
- Then you'll love these.
These are all attachment darts.
See the green ones?
Datura knockout darts.
Guy goes down for 12 hours, wakes
up, doesn't know who he is...
and his head's splitting
like a cord of firewood.
I was shot twice by those.
And the red ones are tranquilizer
and blood-splatter darts.
Looks like a kill shot without
the aftereffects. Like death.
You've got exploding and
surveillance darts...
and your standard .44-caliber
bullets, if you want to get nasty.
A little wet work. You know
what I'm talking about, right?
Knocked over a few
7-Elevens, have we?
No, I had my leg in a cast for three
months. All I did was play video games.
That's a really sad story.
Check this out, on to my baby.
Eagle Eyes. Nine
enhanced-vision modes.
Every little boy's
The penetrator mode.
Check it out.
Oh, my God.
- She's checking you out, man.
- I'll hang on to these.
Now, on to my
latest achievement.
I just put the finishing
touches on them last week.
What do you think?
- Bandages?
- No, Mr. X, watch and learn.
There's enough primer to
blow a hole in a vault...
vaporize a human, or whatever
agents like you might find a use for.
And check this out.
The detonator. How cool is that?
- You might want to back up
for this. - It's a bandage.
Just get behind the wall.
You ready?
I've always wanted to say this.
Fire in the hole.
It's loaded.
So, what do you think?
Beautiful.
You like the cars?
I love the cars, they're dope.
- You like the money? - I love
money, but I do not have it.
You look like you're doing very well.
All these employees, beautiful cars.
This is no time for being funny.
- You didn't think I wasn't good for
it? - It never crossed my mind.
A cargo ship's waiting for you
in Rijeka. Here's the address.
This place is dope.
This one's mine?
Car number 10.
Kolya found it hiding in Berlin.
It was very difficult to find.
No! Please.
Allow me. You were kind
enough to give me the money.
Now, please...
drive.
No, allow me.
- You're all right, Yorgi. -
Everything's all right with vodka.
You must come to party tonight.
Big party at one of my clubs.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
What's going on, my friend?
You tell me. You got a
sniper up there or what?
He's not with us, he
must be with you.
Bullshit! Tell your
men to get down...
or I'll give you another hole
to breathe out of. Are we clear?
All right. It's not yours.
Let's go and get him together.
Son of a bitch. That
same cop from the club.
Filthy cop.
Most people talk a lot. Few
are up for the moment.
Welcome to Anarchy 99.
- Did you enjoy that?
- Yeah.
Good, because it will
never happen again.
- After you.
- No, after you.
- No, I insist.
That's it.
Last chance to tuck me in.
Good morning.
It's none of my business, but a power
drill and some titanium bits...
will get you a lot
further than that camera.
You're not supposed
to be in here.
I was on my way to the bathroom.
What's your excuse?
I don't need an excuse.
Oh, you're good.
But not that good.
I came in here to
photograph Yorgi's safe.
I thought it might be
worth a lot to somebody.
Come on. You're cold,
intelligent and vicious.
It's your eyes that
give you away.
They gave you away
when I shot that cop.
What are you going to do now?
Now I'm going to
take you to lunch.
Oh, and that cop I
shot, isn't dead.
I have some information for you.
I can always use information. Who is
this? How did you get this number?
Yes. Important information that
you need about Xander Cage.
- So you don't like foreigners,
do you? - No, you're a pig.
Is your boyfriend a pig too?
You should recognize
one of your kind.
Now, tell me about the cop.
What if I told you I'm
not who you think I am?
That I could get you out
of the mess you're in?
Really? And what mess am I in?
The mess that makes you sneak around
the castle when everyone's asleep.
The cop?
See this? It's called a
blood-splatter dart.
The impact's real, but it's
harmless. Red paint, mostly.
Why?
I'm a secret agent.
Are you sure you don't
want to embarrass me?
- Come on.
- What's so funny about that?
I mean, look at you.
I work for the NSA.
You're funny, you know that?
Yelena, it's Kirill.
Yorgi found out that Cage
is an American agent.
Do you understand what I'm telling
you? You are in danger, my love.
The building across the street.
The statue.
Bring him outside. I
will do the rest.
What was that, your boyfriend?
Let's say you are who
you say you are.
- What can you do for me?
- What do you want?
I want immunity from prosecution,
asylum in the U.S. and citizenship.
How about a condo on South
Beach and a rich boyfriend?
Those I can get for myself.
- What do you want? - I need
to know more about Anarchy 99.
You want to know
about Anarchy 99?
You've seen the girls,
the clubs, the parties.
What you don't see is what
goes on during the day.
There's been a lot of activity in the
last year. People coming in and out.
- Russian scientists.
- Well, what are they up to?
They go in the basement
and I'm not allowed in.
Now's a good time for
you to get invited.
Yorgi knows you're an agent.
Kirill is waiting with his rifle.
- Where...?
- Don't look!
There's a back door.
They'll know you warned me.
If you go out the front, he'll
put a bullet in your eye.
- You still packing?
- Always.
Get ready to use it.
- What's your plan?
- He's still in love with you.
- He'll wait for a clear shot. -
That's your plan? Thank you. Great.
Draw!
He's on the way.
Gibbons! My favorite kidnapper.
Next time send a limo.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
You already broke me. No need
to get cruel and unusual.
A ticket? Now, that's funny.
- Where am I going to go now?
- Home.
Home?
Your cover's blown.
You're not useful.
That's it? I'm done?
No tricks. We have enough
intel to move forward.
- With what? - Sweeper
Quick, clean, effective.
Don't worry about it.
It'll all be over soon.
You mean a sweeper team to
come in and kill everybody?
Not all of them are
as bad as you think.
You had to shoot a cop. How "not
as bad as I think" could they be?
Okay, look.
We've got a complication.
There's a girl. Yelena.
There's always a girl.
She wants out and I sent her back
in to get more intel for you.
There's no time to play favorites.
The cards have been dealt.
What do you mean the
cards have been dealt?
You don't even know her, man.
Oh, by the way, that
bank number you gave us?
Your friends and Yelena have made
some large cash transfers...
to a group of Russian scientists
known to specialize and traffic...
in biological weapons.
- She had nothing to
do with it. - Go home.
- She ain't...!
- That's an order.
How's it going?
Life is shit!
Yeah, well what can you do?
Through this door, you
are with us to the end.
- Are you sure that's what
you want? - I'm sure.
This is Ahab. Think of it
as solar-powered submarine.
It can circumnavigate the
globe to reach its target.
It need only surface to gather
sunshine and to do its business.
What is it? What's its business?
Dropping off presents to all the
good little boys and girls.
My team will be
finished tomorrow.
How about you?
We're finished now.
Nikolai!
Bring the rockets.
The detonator is for you.
Yorgi! The binary
agents are mixing...
it will kill us all!
Looks like little white mouse.
Bye-bye, little mouse.
My God.
They did their job and
now they were liability.
We don't need anyone talking
about our business.
The gas gets sucked through the
extractor fans, passed into water...
and broken down to become,
once again, completely harmless.
So quiet.
I know now why they
call it Silent Night.
Let's get some food.
Find out what's going on!
What the hell was that?
That works.
Fire in the hole.
Sova. What are you
doing here, man?
First you set me up in the bar.
Then you shoot me in the back.
My boss does it to me. I did it
to you. It's a vicious circle.
- You think it's funny?
- No.
You didn't take it
personally, did you?
I did what I had to do to get
in. We're on the same side.
I'm sorry. I switched sides.
You pushed me too far. My government
doesn't pay as well as Yorgi.
My government pays
twice as much...
Think you could just walk
into the spy business...
and have all the angles figured out?
- What are you going to do, shoot me?
Where? In the head, to be quick?
Or in the chest for an open
casket, so I can see your heart?
Can I think about it?
What are you doing?!
I heard you talking. I could
tell where you were in the room.
What are you doing
with the Ivans?
What's going on?
There's something I didn't
have the time to tell you.
I'm an agent as well.
I'm an agent for FSB,
Russian Intelligence.
You know, like your CIA.
- I've been undercover for
two years. - Two years?
What was your plan, let
them die of old age?
There was no plan.
A year ago, Intelligence gets
reorganized, I stop getting orders.
They forget about me. And I did what
I must to survive. You understand?
What do I understand? I've
been an agent for a week.
But my boss needs to
know what we know now.
- Okay?
- Okay.
The submarine's purpose is to deploy
a nerve agent called Silent Night.
It's been missing since the
Soviet Union's collapse in '91.
It can kill millions.
We knew they were up to
something. You found out.
- That's excellent work, Triple X.
- There was never a sweeper team.
If I said don't jump off the
Empire State Building...
- You're right. I'd definitely
do it. - I inspired you.
I'm an authority figure, that's
what I'm supposed to do.
Look, my men are on this now.
- It's time for you to come
home. - What about Yelena?
I'm not authorized
to give her asylum.
But I promise it'll be done
by the time you get here.
Come home, Xander.
That's an order.
How soon can Yorgi
launch this thing?
You were told to go home!
Your people are handling...
How soon, Yelena?
Soon. But it's not
our problem anymore!
If they get ahead of
schedule, it's everyone's.
He's got an army, a fortress.
You don't stand a chance!
I've risked my life for stupid reasons.
This is the first one that makes sense.
This is not one of your stunts.
You'll die in this, you know that.
If you don't go back in there...
he'll know something's wrong.
You can't ask me to go
back there. You can't.
You want to know something ironic?
I volunteered for this assignment.
I wanted to make a difference.
I fought for it.
Then finish it.
Remember what I told you,
after you kissed me?
- Never again?
- I lied.
But when you break it
down, I'm a simple man.
I'd be happy with a
beautiful Czech girl...
Hey, geek! Got new orders
from Gibbons. Get in.
- I want all that in here.
- Done.
The castle's covered with
surveillance cameras.
That's why we cannot
get close enough.
Hang on. That's why I need to knock
out the communications tower...
at the base of the mountain.
Is there anyone here who
knows how to fly a plane?
I can.
Too much turbulence
around these mountains!
Just get me in line
with that tower!
I'll do the rest!
Go now!
Viktor! We got company!
Catch him fast. Kill him slow!
Nothing like fresh powder.
Yelena, my sweet dove,
did you get confused?
Your assignment was to kill
the cop after he killed X.
Not good for undercover agent
from Russian intelligence.
I knew about you all along...
and it was my pleasure to twist
you and use you how I saw fit.
And you.
Of all people, I thought
you'd understand...
what I'm trying to accomplish.
Can you imagine?
Imagine a city like
Prague vanishing...
in a cloud of poison gas.
Then Hamburg,
London, Washington.
Imagine not knowing who did it, or
why. And so they turn on each other.
These guys attack those guys.
Those guys invade these guys.
Soon, whole world implodes.
Imagine governments
disappearing.
And in the end...
imagine facing absolute,
beautiful freedom.
But neither of you will
be there to see it.
Like Viktor.
Like Kolya.
Cover me!
Get me out of this thing!
He took the hard drive.
He's going to launch Ahab!
Pick one.
Ivan, take out that nest!
You have to turn the safety off.
Hold them off as
long as you can.
See you, my friend.
Come on, baby.
Stop! He's got us pinned down.
Shit.
You got a bazooka!
Stop thinking Prague police and start
thinking PlayStation. Blow shit up!
This is not bazooka. This
is heat-seeker rocket.
Heat-seeker?
Set it.
The son of a bitch is smoking.
I told him that cigarette
would kill him.
Learn how to shoot,
piece of shit!
Quick! Help me pull him out!
It will hit the
city in 30 minutes!
Guys. I need a helicopter.
I need transportation.
I need a...
X, there you are. I gave
you everything you wanted.
This thing will
damn near fly now.
You screwed me. Gibbons
didn't authorize this.
He'll hang us both out to dry.
- Agent Shavers.
- Yeah?
I'm going to give you
a field promotion.
Take over, finish the mop-up.
You're in charge.
Yes, Sir! I'm the man for the
job! I won't let you down!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Almost forgot the Manual.
You'll need this.
Hey, X. Go kick some ass.
That thing must be going 80 mph!
How do we stop it?!
We can't! The controls
are on the bubble panel.
- You see it?
- Yeah.
The hard drive's in there!
You got the Manual. See if Shavers
put in anything we could use.
- He's got very bad
handwriting. - Come on!
Flame throwers, mini-bombs, exploding
hubcaps, rocket launchers!
This is a tank. You can't
use any of it on Ahab.
Silent Night only breaks
down in deep water.
- I'll have to get on it!
- What?
I'll have to get on it.
Our surveillance puts Ahab 22
minutes outside of Prague.
- We should evacuate the city. -
22 minutes for 1.5 million people?
Call air support. We may need
to blow it out of the water.
- If we hit that thing...
- This city will die.
And the crisis
will be contained!
One city's better than 10.
Another thing: A blue GTO is
traveling parallel to Ahab.
Shit! Does this road
go back to the river?
Come on! Check the GPS!
Yes, it does! Fifteen miles
at the town of Davle!
There's got to be something
here we could use.
Harpoon gun, parachutes built
into seats, ejectable roof.
It's all useless!
How far are we?
The river is just beyond
the next village.
I'm going through! Use
the rocket launcher!
- Twenty-two!
- Hit it!
That was a flamethrower!
Use the rockets!
It's 32! I told you! I told
you he had bad handwriting!
Hit it!
Shavers loaded this thing.
We're missing something.
There are more weapons
here on the back. Look.
- Take the wheel!
- What? You're crazy!
The brake! The brake!
The gas! The gas!
X, what are you doing?
Five minutes to target.
X, talk to me! What
are you doing?
- You said there was an
ejectable roof. - Right here!
Hit it!
Shit! It's out of range!
- There's a bridge! Cross
the bridge! - Okay.
Come on.
Come on!
- Got you!
- Yes!
- I wish I had a camera!
- What you talking about?
This is gonna be one
hell of a trick.
Three minutes to target.
One minute to target.
Move! Move! Move!
Out of the way!
Eyes!
Ten seconds to target.
Target in sight.
Call the jets off. Tell
the jets to stand down!
Welcome to the Xander zone!
Zero contamination level. I understand,
Sir. Zero contamination level.
You Yelena?
Mr. Gibbons.
I promised Xander you
could go to America.
I'm a man of my word.
It doesn't make much
difference now, does it?
He's alive! He's alive!
Come here!
Get him out of there,
double-time. Go! Move!
- Bora Bora!
- What? I can't hear you!
Bora Bora.
You're getting burnt.
Xander, you there?
I know you're there, Xander. I've got
you here on satellite magnification.
Call me. We got a whole
new thing to talk about.
Something very
important has come up.
Oh, by the way...
you passed the test.
The Gibbons test.
You gotta be kidding me.