[grunts]
[panting]
[wings flapping]
[man] Starling!
Starling.
Crawford wants to see you in his office.
[Southern accent] Thank you, sir.
[gunfire]
-[buzzer sounds]
-[gunfire continues]
[buzzer sounds]
[helicopter whirring]
[gunfire]
-Clarice.
-Hey.
Hey, I got right to the end.
[buzzer sounds]
[elevator bell dings]
[men chattering]
So there shouldn't be any problem
if you could –
-You looking for Crawford?
-Yes, sir.
He should be back in a couple minutes.
Why don't you wait in his office.
Okay.
Then I think they were over into Flushing.
Starling. Clarice M.
-Good morning.
-Good morning, Mr. Crawford.
Sorry to pull you off the course
on such short notice.
Your instructors tell me you're doing well.
Top quarter of your class.
I hope so.
They haven't posted any grades yet.
A job's come up, and I thought about you.
Not a job really.
More of an interesting errand.
-Sit down.
-Yes, sir.
-I remember you from my seminar at UVA.
-Yeah.
You grilled me pretty hard, as I recall,
on the Bureau's civil rights record
in the Hoover years.
-I gave you an "A."
-A-minus, sir.
Let's see.
Double major – psych and criminology.
Graduated magna.
Summer internships at the Reitzinger Clinic.
It says here, when you graduate,
you wanna come to work for me
in behavioral science.
Yes. Very much, sir. Very much.
We're interviewing
all the serial killers now in custody
for a psycho-behavioral profile.
Could be a real help in unsolved cases.
Most of them have been happy to talk to us.
You spook easily, Starling?
Not yet, sir.
See, the one we want most
refuses to cooperate.
I want you to go after him again today
in the asylum.
Who's the subject?
The psychiatrist, Hannibal Lecter.
"Hannibal the Cannibal."
I don't expect him to talk to you...
but I have to be able to say we tried.
So, if he won't cooperate,
I want just straight reporting –
how's he look, how's his cell look.
Is he sketching, drawing?
If he is, what's he sketching?
Here's a, uh, dossier on Lecter...
copy of our questionnaire,
and a special ID for you.
Have your memo on my desk
by 0800 Wednesday.
Okay.
Um, excuse me, sir, but why the urgency?
Lecter's been in prison
for so many years now.
Is there some connection
between him and Buffalo Bill maybe?
I wish there were.
I want your full attention, Starling.
Yes, sir.
Be very careful with Hannibal Lecter.
Dr. Chilton at the asylum will go over
all the physical procedures used with him.
Do not deviate from them
for any reason whatsoever.
And you're to tell him nothing personal,
Starling.
Believe me, you don't want
Hannibal Lecter inside your head.
Just do your job,
but never forget what he is.
And what is that?
[man] Oh, he's a monster.
Pure psychopath.
So rare to capture one alive.
From a research point of view,
Lecter is our most prized asset.
Well.
You know, we get a lot of detectives here,
but, I must say,
I can't ever remember one as attractive.
Will you be in Baltimore overnight?
Because this can be quite a fun town
if you have the right guide.
[chuckles] I'm sure this is a great town,
Dr. Chilton,
but, um, my instructions are to talk
to Dr. Lecter and report back this afternoon.
I see. Well, let's make this quick then.
We've tried to study him, of course,
but he's much too sophisticated
for the standard tests.
And, oh, my, does he hate us. [chuckling]
He thinks I'm his nemesis.
Crawford's very clever, isn't he, using you?
-What do you mean, sir?
-Pretty, young woman to turn him on.
I don't believe Lecter's
even seen a woman in eight years.
And, oh, are you ever his taste,
so to speak.
I graduated from UVA, Doctor.
It is not a charm school.
Good. Then you should be able
to remember the rules.
[man shouting]
Do not touch the glass.
Do not approach the glass.
You pass him nothing but soft paper.
No pencils or pens.
No staples or paper clips in his paper.
Use the sliding food carrier.
No exceptions.
If he attempts to pass you anything,
do not accept it.
-Do you understand me?
-Yes, I understand, sir.
I'm going to show you
why we insist on such precautions.
On the afternoon of July 8, 1981,
he complained of chest pains
and was taken to the dispensary.
His mouthpiece and restraints
were removed for an EKG.
When the nurse leaned over him,
he did this to her.
The doctors managed to reset her jaw,
more or less, save one of her eyes.
His pulse never got above 85,
even when he ate her tongue.
-I keep him in here.
-Dr. Chilton.
[buzzer sounds]
Um, if Lecter feels that you're his enemy,
then, um, well, maybe we'll have more luck
if I go in by myself.
What do you think?
[monitor beeping]
You might have suggested this
in my office and saved me the time.
Yes, sir, but then I – I would have missed
the pleasure of your company, sir.
When she's finished, bring her out.
-[radio chatter]
-[printer clattering]
Hi. I'm Barney.
He told you don't get near the glass?
-Yes, he did. Clarice Starling.
-Mm-hmm.
Nice to meet you, Clarice.
You can hang your coat up here if you like.
Oh, thank you. I will.
He's past the others – the last cell.
You keep to the right.
[slams, lock turns]
-I put out a chair for you.
-Oh, yes. That's very good. Thank you.
I'll be watching. You'll do fine.
[man] Hi.
[hissing] I can smell your cunt!
-Good morning.
-Dr. Lecter, my name is Clarice Starling.
May I speak with you?
You're one of Jack Crawford's, aren't you?
I am, yes.
May I see your credentials?
Certainly.
Closer, please.
Closer.
That expires in one week.
You're not real FBI, are you?
I'm still in training at the academy.
Jack Crawford sent a trainee to me?
Yes. I'm a student.
I'm here to learn from you.
Maybe you can decide for yourself
whether or not I'm qualified enough to do that.
Mmm.
That is rather slippery of you,
Agent Starling.
Sit. Please.
Now then, tell me,
what did Miggs say to you?
Multiple Miggs in the next cell.
He hissed at you. What did he say?
He said, "I can smell your cunt."
I see.
I myself cannot.
[inhales, sniffing]
[gasps]
You use Evyan skin cream.
And sometimes you wear L'Air du Temps.
But not today.
Did you do all these drawings, Doctor?
Ah.
That is the Duomo seen from the Belvedere.
Do you know Florence?
All that detail just from memory, sir?
Memory, Agent Starling,
is what I have instead of a view.
Well, perhaps you'd care to lend us
your view on this questionnaire, sir.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You were doing fine.
You had been courteous
and receptive to courtesy.
You had established trust
with the... embarrassing truth about Miggs.
And now this... ham-handed segue
into your questionnaire.
[clicking tongue]
It won't do.
I'm only asking you to look at this, Doctor.
Either you will or you won't.
Yeah. Jack Crawford
must be very busy indeed
if he is recruiting help
from the student body.
Busy hunting that new one, Buffalo Bill.
What a naughty boy he is.
Do you know why he's called "Buffalo Bill"?
Please tell me. The newspapers won't say.
Well, it started as a bad joke
in Kansas City Homicide.
They said, "This one likes to skin his humps."
Why do you think he removes their skins,
Agent Starling?
Thrill me with your acumen.
It excites him.
Most serial killers keep some sort
of trophies from their victims.
-I didn't.
-No.
No, you ate yours.
You send that through now.
[tray slides open, closes]
Hmm.
[affecting Southern accent]
Oh, Agent Starling.
You think you can dissect me
with this blunt little tool?
No. I – I thought that your knowledge –
You're so ambitious, aren't you?
You know what you look like to me
with your good bag and your cheap shoes?
You look like a rube –
a well-scrubbed, hustling rube
with a little taste.
Good nutrition's given you
some length of bone,
but you're not more than one generation
from poor white trash,
are you, Agent Starling?
And that accent you've tried so desperately
to shed – pure West Virginia.
What does your father do?
Is he a coal miner?
Does he stink of the lamp?
And, oh, how quickly the boys found you –
all those tedious, sticky fumblings
in the back seats of cars
while you could only dream
of getting out, getting anywhere,
getting all the way to the FBI.
You see a lot, Doctor.
But are you strong enough to point
that high-powered perception at yourself?
What about it? Why don't you –
Why don't you look at yourself
and write down what you see?
Or maybe you're afraid to.
[tray slams]
A census taker once tried to test me.
I ate his liver with some fava beans
and a nice Chianti.
[sucking teeth]
You fly back to school now, little Starling.
Fly, fly, fly.
[whispering] Fly, fly, fly.
[man moaning]
[moaning loudly]
I bit my wrist so I could die.
[laughing] Look at the blood!
-[Gasps]
-Gotcha! [laughing]
Miggs! You stupid fuck!
[laughing]
I'm gonna kill him!
Agent Starling! Come back!
Agent Starling! Agent Starling!
I would not have had that happen to you.
Discourtesy is unspeakably ugly to me.
-Then do this test for me.
-No. But I will make you happy.
I'll give you a chance
for what you love most.
-And what is that, Doc –
-Advancement, of course. Listen carefully.
Look deep within yourself, Clarice Starling.
Go seek out Miss Mofet,
an old patient of mine – M-O-F-E-T.
Go. I don't think Miggs could manage again
quite so soon, even though he is crazy.
-Go now!
-[men shouting]
[door closes]
[gasps]
-Hi, Bill.
-[car door closes]
-Hey!
-Daddy!
Hey, Clarice.
Hello, my girl.
-Did you get any bad guys today, Daddy?
-No, angel. They all got away today.
Aw, shoot.
-[dog barks]
-[Clarice sobbing]
FBI! Hands up!
-Don't move!
-Turn around.
Hands behind your back. Thumbs up.
[handcuffs clicking]
-[gun clicks]
-You're dead, Starling.
-[buzzer sounds]
-Johnson, good job.
Good entry. Good commands.
-Starling, where's your danger area?
-In the corner, sir.
-Did you check the corner?
-No, sir.
That's the reason you're dead.
3-109.
3-109. Breaking doors or windows
to enter or exit.
Uh, Rule 4-048.
[machine clicks]
Clarice. Phone. It's the guru.
-Crawford?
-Yeah.
Thanks, Ardelia.
-Starling?
-Sir.
Miggs is dead.
Dead?
How?
The orderly heard Lecter whispering to him
all afternoon and Miggs crying.
They found him at bed check.
He'd swallowed his own tongue.
Starling?
Yeah. I'm – I'm still here, sir.
I just –
I don't know how to feel about this.
You don't have to feel any way about it.
Lecter did it to amuse himself.
Look, I know it got ugly today, but –
He mentioned a name at the end – a Mofet.
Any follow-up on her?
Uh, well, Lecter altered or destroyed most
of his patients' histories prior to capture,
so there's no record of anyone named Mofet.
But, um, I thought the "yourself" reference
was, uh, too hokey for Lecter.
So I figured, he's from Baltimore,
and I looked in the phone book,
and there's a Your Self Storage facility
right outside of downtown Baltimore, sir.
[man] Unit 31 was leased for 10 years,
prepaid in full.
The contract was in the name
of a... Miss Hester Mofet.
So nobody's been in here since 1980?
Not to my knowledge.
Privacy is a great concern
to my customers.
[grunts]
Yes. I won't disturb anything. I promise.
I'll be outta here before you know it.
-[door clanking]
-Can I help you?
Yes, actually. I can't –
It's stuck.
You could return tomorrow with my son.
-What about him?
-[chuckles]
I would ask my driver to help you,
but he detests physical labor.
Right.
Well, you just stay here.
I'll be back in one minute.
[door creaking]
[grunting]
-[door creaking]
-Stuck.
-Hand me that flashlight, sir.
-[tire iron clatters]
Oh.
Um, if this door should fall down or –
[forced laugh] anything else,
uh, this is the number
for our Baltimore field office.
Now, they know that you're with me.
You call them if anything should happen.
Yes, Miss Starling.
-[fabric rips]
-Ow!
[door closes]
Clarice, I cleared the way for you.
-Watch yourself.
-Okay. Thanks.
"Hester Mofet."
It's an anagram, isn't it, Doctor?
"Hester Mofet." "The rest of me."
"Miss the Rest of Me."
Meaning that you rented that garage?
Thank you.
Your bleeding has stopped.
[TV: no audible dialogue]
How did you –
It's nothing.
It's just a scratch.
Dr. Lecter, whose head is in that bottle?
Why don't you ask me about Buffalo Bill?
Why, do you know something about him?
I might if I saw the case file.
You could get that for me.
Why don't we talk about Miss Mofet?
You wanted me to find him.
His real name is Benjamin Raspail.
A former patient of mine
whose romantic attachments ran
to, shall we say, the exotic.
I did not kill him, I assure you.
Merely tucked him away
very much as I found him
after he'd missed three appointments.
But... if you didn't kill him,
then who did, sir?
Who can say? Best thing for him really.
His therapy was going nowhere.
His dress, uh, makeup –
Raspail was a transvestite?
In life? Oh, no.
Garden-variety manic-depressive.
Tedious. Very tedious.
No, no. Just think of him
as a kind of experiment,
a fledgling killer's
first effort at transformation.
How did you feel when you saw him,
Clarice?
Scared at first, then... exhilarated.
Jack Crawford is helping your career,
isn't he?
Apparently he likes you, and you like him too.
I never thought about it.
Do you think Jack Crawford
wants you sexually?
True, he is much older,
but do you think he visualizes scenarios,
exchanges, fucking you?
[scoffs]
That doesn't interest me, Doctor.
And frankly, it's – it's the sort of thing
that Miggs would say.
Not anymore.
[clanging]
Thank you, Barney.
What happened to your drawings?
Punishment, you see. For Miggs.
Just like that gospel program.
When you leave,
they'll turn the volume way up.
Dr. Chilton does enjoy his petty torments.
What did you mean by "transformation,"
Doctor?
I've been in this room
for eight years now, Clarice...
and I know they will never, ever
let me out while I'm alive.
What I want is a view.
I want a window
where I can see a tree or even water.
I want to be in a federal institution
far away from Dr. Chilton.
What did you mean by "fledgling killer"?
Are you saying that he's killed again?
I'm offering you
a psychological profile on Buffalo Bill
based on the case evidence.
I'll help you catch him, Clarice.
You know who he is, don't you?
Tell me who decapitated your patient, Doctor.
All good things to those who wait.
I've waited, Clarice.
But how long can you
and ol' Jackie boy wait?
Our little Billy must already
be searching for that next special lady.
[radio: man singing]
♪ After all it was a great big world ♪
♪ With lots of places
To run to ♪
[singing along]
♪ Yeah, and if she had to die tryin' ♪
♪ She had that one little promise
She was gonna keep ♪
♪ Oh, yes, all right ♪
♪ Take it easy, baby ♪
♪ Make it last all night ♪
♪ She was an American girl ♪
[whirring]
[radio: song continues, faint]
[engine stops]
[cat meowing]
Hey, little cheeper.
I'll be right there.
[panting]
[grunts] Goddamn.
Fuckin' – Geez.
[chair scraping]
Can I help you with that?
-Would you?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-That's all right.
-You look kinda handicapped.
-Yeah.
I got it this far.
I just can't get it up in the truck.
I could use all the help I can get.
Just grab that.
-Up.
-[grunts] Okay.
Yeah. Just set it down. That's good.
Uh, get in the truck,
and I wanna push it all the way up.
-I really appreciate this. Thank you.
-All right. Yeah.
Thank you. Now – Push it all the way back.
Okay. Is this good?
-Yeah, that's good. That's great.
-Ah –
-That's great.
-Okay.
-Hey, say, are you about a size 14?
-Sorry?
-[screams, groaning]
-[blows landing]
[groaning]
Good.
[whimpering faintly]
Oh, good.
Good.
[engine starts]
[growls quietly]
-[blows landing]
-[man] Hold!
[man shouts]
-[whistle blows]
-[man] Starling!
Outside. Let's go.
[man 2]
Cindy! In the ring for Starling! Let's go!
[whistle blows]
[sirens wailing]
-FBI! Hold it!
-Hold it right there!
Saddle up. Pack your field gear.
You're movin' out. You're goin' with Crawford.
-Where?
-They found a girl's body down in West Virginia.
Been in the water about a week.
Looks like a Buffalo Bill-type situation.
[Crawford] Keeps 'em alive for three days.
We don't know why.
There's no evidence of rape
or physical abuse prior to death.
All the mutilation you see there
is postmortem.
Okay. Three days.
Then he shoots them, skins them,
and dumps them –
each body in a different river.
The water leaves us
no trace evidence of any kind.
That's Frederica Bimmel, the first one.
Her body was the only one
he took the trouble to weight down,
so actually she was the third girl found.
After her, he got lazy.
Okay. Let's see.
Circles where the girls were abducted.
Arrows where their bodies were found.
This new one today washed up here.
Elk River, West Virginia.
[men chattering]
Look at 'em, Starling.
Tell me what you see.
Well, he's a white male.
Uh, serial killers tend to hunt
within their own ethnic groups.
Um, he's not a drifter.
He's got his own... house somewhere,
not an apartment.
-Why?
-What he does with them takes privacy.
He's in his 30s or 40s.
He's got real physical strength,
combined with an older man's self-control.
He's-He's cautious, precise.
And he's never impulsive.
He'll never stop.
Why not?
He's got a real taste for it now,
and he's getting better at his work.
Not bad, Starling. Questions?
Yes, sir. Um, you haven't mentioned anything
about the information contained in my report
or Dr. Lecter's offer, sir.
I'm considering it.
That's why you sent me in there, isn't it?
To get his help on Buffalo Bill, sir?
Well, if that was the case, then I just –
I just wish I was in on it, that's all.
If I'd sent you in there
with an actual agenda,
Lecter would have known it instantly.
He would have toyed with you,
then turned to stone.
[bell tolling]
Excuse me, Sheriff Perkins.
These are the FBI people.
Sheriff Perkins. Jack Crawford, FBI.
Special Agent Terry, Agent Starling.
We appreciate being invited
to your jurisdiction.
I didn't call you. That was somebody
from the state attorney's office.
We'll extend you every courtesy,
but right now I –
Sheriff.
[whispering]
This type of sex crime has certain aspects
I'd just as soon discuss in private.
Know what I mean?
-[door opens]
-[organ: "Rock of Ages"]
[briefcase clatters]
-[door opens]
-[Sheriff] Oscar.
-Fetch Dr. Akin from the chapel.
-[man] Yes, sir.
Starling, we're back here.
Tell Lamar to come on
when he's finished playing his music.
-Yeah, we'll be sending in a minute.
-[chattering]
[beeping]
-I need a – I need a six-way link-up.
-[chattering loudly]
Chicago, Detroit – What? What?
Uh, excuse me.
[clears throat] Excuse me, gentlemen.
You officers and gentlemen, listen here now.
There's things we need to do for her.
I know that you all brought her this far
and that her folks would thank you
if they could
for your – for your kindness
and your sensitivity.
But now, please, go on now
and let us take care of her.
Go on now.
-Thank you.
-[police radio chatter]
Thank you.
[Crawford] Okay, good.
Yeah, that's right.
West Vir – Yeah. Elk River.
Stand by for transmission.
[machine beeps]
Ray.
[Crawford]
Doctor, Lamar, let's take a look at her.
-[whispers] Jesus.
-[sighs]
Okay, Starling.
Bill.
Star-shaped contact entrance wound
over the, uh, sternum.
Um, muzzle stamp at the top.
-[Akin] Wrongful death.
-Wrongful death.
[camera shutter clicks, whirs]
[Akin] She'll have to go
to the state pathologist at Claxton.
Well, I-I'd better get back to that service.
Lamar'll help ya.
-Lord Almighty.
-[shutter clicks, whirs]
[shutter continues clicking]
[Crawford] What else do you see, Starling?
Well, she's not local.
Her ears are pierced three times,
and there's, uh –
Uh, glitter nail polish.
It looks like town to me.
Two of her fingernails are broken off,
and there's, uh –
there's dirt or grit under them.
It looks like she's tried to claw her way
through something.
[clicks, whirs]
[Crawford] Ray, get pictures of her teeth.
We'll fax them to Missing Persons.
Right.
[Terry] Let's do another.
[clicks, whirs]
She's got something in her throat.
When a body comes out of the water,
lots of times there's, like,
leaves and things in the mouth.
[air hissing]
What is that, some kind of seed pod?
No, sir. That's a bug cocoon.
But there's no way that could get
way down in there like that.
Not unless somebody shoved it in there.
She'll be easier to print when we turn her over.
-Lamar, will you give me a hand with this?
-Yes, sir, I will.
Ooh, Jack.
-What do you make of these?
-Hmm.
Different configuration than the other victims.
Get close-ups.
[Clarice]
The victim's skin removed at this time
in two large diamond-shaped sections
above the buttocks.
Stellate exit wound level with the second
or the third thoracic vertebrae,
approximately six inches
from the right shoulder blade.
[Crawford] Starling.
When – When I told that sheriff
we shouldn't talk in front of a woman,
that really burned you, didn't it?
It was just smoke, Starling.
I had to get rid of him.
It matters, Mr. Crawford.
Cops look at you to see how to act.
-It matters.
-Point taken.
Ligature marks found around the wrists,
not around the ankles.
This would indicate that the skinning
was postmortem.
[elevator bell dings]
-[man] Time, Pilch. My move.
-[Pilch] No fair. You lured him with produce.
Tough noogies. Still my turn.
[blows]
Nice and slow, baby.
If the beetle moves one of your men,
does that still count?
Of course it counts. How do you play?
Agent Starling?
[man 1] Where the heck did this come from?
It's practically mush.
It was found behind the soft palate
of a murder victim.
The body was in the Elk River
in West Virginia.
-It's Buffalo Bill, isn't it?
-I'm afraid I can't tell you any more about that.
We heard about it on the radio.
You mean this is, like,
a clue from a real murder case?
-Cool!
-Just ignore him. He's not a PhD.
A Sphingid ceratomia maybe.
Boy, he's a big sucker.
Okay. Let's check morphology.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
What do you do when you're not detecting,
Agent Starling?
[chuckles]
Try to be a student, Dr. Pilcher.
You ever go out
for cheeseburgers and beer?
The amusing house wine?
Are you hitting on me, Doctor?
-Yes.
-Gotcha.
-What do you got, Roden?
-Agent Starling.
Meet Mr. Acherontia styx.
Weird.
Better known to his friends
as the death's-head moth.
-And where does it come from?
-That's what's strange.
-They only live in Asia.
-Asia?
In this country, they'd have to be
specially raised from imported eggs.
Uh, somebody grew this guy.
Fed him honey and nightshade.
Kept him warm.
Somebody loved him.
[rock music playing, faint]
[woman, faint] Please.
Hello?
[rock continues]
[woman] Where are you?
Let me out of here!
[singing along softly]
-Hey!
-[dog barking]
-Please help me!
-[dog continues barking]
Someone help me! Please!
Why won't you answer me? Please!
[TV: program theme]
-Good morning. I'm Donna Ferucci.
-I'm Gene Cassel with sports.
And I'm Tim Langhorn.
Our top story for this morning.
Catherine Martin, the 25-year-old
daughter of Senator Ruth Martin,
listed first as a missing person,
is now believed to have been kidnapped
by the serial killer known only as Buffalo Bill.
Memphis police sources indicate
that the missing girl's blouse –
-Thank you.
-has been identified – sliced up the back –
in what has become a kind of grim,
all-too-familiar calling card.
Young Catherine Martin, as we've said,
is the only daughter
of US Senator Ruth Martin,
the Republican junior senator from Tennessee.
And while her kidnapping is not at this point
considered to be politically motivated,
nevertheless, it has stirred the government
to its highest levels.
Reached for comment on the ski slopes
of Stowe, Vermont,
the president himself said to be,
and I quote, "intensely concerned."
-Just moments ago, Senator Martin –
-Excuse me.
taped this dramatic personal plea.
[Senator Martin] I'm speaking now
to the person who's holdin' my daughter.
Catherine is very gentle and kind.
Talk to her and you'll see.
You have the power.
You are in charge.
I know you can feel love and compassion.
You have a wonderful chance
to show the whole world
that you can be merciful as well as strong,
that you're big enough to treat Catherine
better than the world has treated you.
You have that power.
Please.
My daughter is Catherine.
-[Ardelia] Boy, that's smart.
-Release her unharmed.
-Jesus, that's really smart.
-[man] She keeps repeating the name.
If he sees Catherine as a person
and not just an object,
it's harder to tear her up.
Please, release my little girl.
[sirens wailing]
What you're doing, Miss Starling,
is coming into my hospital
to conduct an interview and refusing to
share information with me for the third time.
Sir, I told you this is just a routine
follow-up on the Raspail case.
-He is my patient. I have rights.
-I understand that, sir.
Look, I am not just some turnkey,
Miss Starling.
This is the number
for the US Attorney's office.
Please, either you discuss this with him
or you let me do my job.
Do you understand?
If your profile helps us catch Buffalo Bill
in time to save Catherine Martin...
the senator promises you a transfer
to the VA hospital at Oneida Park, New York,
with a view of the woods nearby.
Maximum security still applies, of course.
You'd have reasonable access to books.
Best of all though,
one week of the year,
you get to leave the hospital
and go here.
Plum Island.
Every day of that week,
you may walk on the beach,
you may swim in the ocean –
for up to one hour –
under SWAT team surveillance, of course.
-[exhales]
-And there you have it.
A copy of the Buffalo Bill case file.
Copy of the senator's offer.
This offer is non-negotiable and final.
Catherine Martin dies, you get nothing.
[tray clangs]
"Plum Island
Animal Disease Research Center."
Sounds charming.
That's only part of the island.
There's a very – very nice beach.
Terns nest there. There's beautiful –
Terns? Mm.
If I help you, Clarice,
it will be "turns" with us too.
Quid pro quo.
I tell you things, you tell me things.
Not about this case though.
About yourself.
Quid pro quo. Yes or no?
Yes or no, Clarice?
Poor little Catherine is waiting.
Go, Doctor.
What is your worst memory of childhood?
Death of my father.
Tell me about it. And don't lie, or I'll know.
He was the town marshal, and...
one night he
surprised two burglars coming out
of the back of a drugstore.
They shot him.
Was he killed outright?
No. He was very strong.
He lasted more than a month.
My mother died when I was very young, so –
[exhales]
My father had become the whole world to me,
and, uh, when he left me, I had nothing.
I was 10 years old.
You're very frank, Clarice.
I think it would be quite something
to know you in private life.
Quid pro quo, Doctor.
So tell me about Miss West Virginia.
Was she a large girl?
-Yes.
-Big through the hips?
-Roomy?
-They all were.
What else?
She had an object deliberately inserted
into her throat.
Now, that hasn't been made public yet.
We don't know what it means.
Was it a butterfly?
Yes. A moth.
Just like the one we found
in Benjamin Raspail's head an hour ago.
Why does he place them there, Doctor?
The significance of the moth is change.
Caterpillar into chrysalis or pupa...
and, from thence, into beauty.
Our Billy wants to change too.
There's no correlation in the literature
between transsexualism and violence.
-Transsexuals are very passive.
-Clever girl.
You're so close to the way you're
gonna catch him. Do you realize that?
No. Tell me why.
After your father's murder, you were orphaned.
What happened next?
I don't imagine the answer is
on those second-rate shoes, Clarice.
I went to live with my mother's cousin
and her husband in Montana.
They had a ranch.
Was it a cattle ranch?
Sheep and horses.
How long did you live there?
Two months.
Why so briefly?
I ran away.
Why, Clarice?
Did the rancher make you perform fellatio?
Did he sodomize you?
No. He was a very decent man.
Quid pro quo, Doctor.
Billy is not a real transsexual.
But he thinks he is. He tries to be.
He's tried to be a lot of things, I expect.
You said I was very close
to the way we would catch him.
What did you mean, Doctor?
There are three major centers
for transsexual surgery –
Johns Hopkins, the University of Minnesota,
and Columbus Medical Center.
I wouldn't be surprised
if Billy had applied for sex reassignment
at one or all of them
and been rejected.
On what basis would they reject him?
[Lecter's voice]
Look for severe childhood disturbances
associated with violence.
Our Billy wasn't born a criminal, Clarice.
He was made one
through years of systematic abuse.
Billy hates his own identity, you see,
and he thinks that makes him a transsexual.
But his pathology
is a thousand times more savage
and more terrifying.
[dog growls]
It rubs lotion on its skin.
It does this whenever it's told.
[gasping] Mister, my family will pay cash.
Whatever ransom you're askin' for,
they'll pay it.
It rubs the lotion on its skin,
or else it gets the hose again.
[barks]
Yes, it will, Precious.
It will get the hose.
[whimpering] Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Mister, if you let me go, I won't –
I won't press charges.
I promise.
See, my mom is a real important woman.
I guess you already know that.
Now it places the lotion in the basket.
[sobbing]
Please! Please! I want to go home.
I want to go home, please!
Please.
It places the lotion in the basket.
I want to see my mommy! Please –
I want to see my – I want – [sobbing]
I want – I want to see – [mouths words]
-Put the fucking lotion in the basket!
-[Precious barking]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[mock screaming]
You still think you're gonna walk
on some beach and see the birdies?
[chuckles] No, I don't think so.
I called Senator Ruth Martin.
She never heard of any deal with you.
[chuckling] They scammed you, Hannibal.
Stand outside.
And shut the door.
-Barney.
-Mm-hmm.
[door closing]
There never was a deal
with Senator Martin, but there is now.
I designed it.
Of course, I worked in a few conditions
for my own benefit as well.
Identify Buffalo Bill by name,
and if the girl is found in time,
Senator Martin will have you transferred
to Brushy Mountain State Prison
in Tennessee.
Answer me, Hannibal.
You answer me now, or by God,
you'll never leave this cell.
Who is Buffalo Bill?
His first name is Louis.
I'll tell the rest to the senator herself,
but only in Tennessee.
And I have a few conditions of my own.
Clean him up and get him ready to go.
[man over phone] Jack, Hannibal Lecter's
being transferred to Memphis.
Transferred?
Did you have a trainee make some sort of
phony offer to Lecter in the senator's name?
Yeah. I rolled the dice. I had to.
Well, she's mad as hell, Jack.
Paul Krendler's over here from Justice.
She's asking him to take over in Memphis.
[sirens wailing]
Welcome to Memphis, Dr. Lecter.
I'm Lieutenant Boyle.
This is Sergeant Patrick.
Now, we're gonna treat you
as good as you treat us.
You be a gentleman,
you're gonna get three hots and a cot.
Sir, if you'll sign right here,
we'll have us a legal transfer.
Where is it?
Here, sir. Use mine.
[exhaling]
Senator Martin, Dr. Hannibal Lecter.
Dr. Lecter.
I brought an affidavit
guaranteeing your new rights.
You'll want to read it before I sign.
I won't waste your time or Catherine's time
bargaining for petty privileges.
Clarice Starling
and that awful Jack Crawford
have wasted far too much time already.
I only pray
they haven't doomed the poor girl.
Let me help you now,
and I will trust you when it is all over.
You have my word. Paul?
Buffalo Bill's real name is Louis Friend.
I met him just once.
He was referred to me in April or May 1980
by my patient Benjamin Raspail.
They were lovers, you see.
But Raspail had become very frightened.
Apparently, Louis had murdered a transient
and done things with the skin.
We need his address
and a physical description.
Tell me, Senator,
did you nurse Catherine yourself?
-What?
-Did you breast-feed her?
-Wait a minute.
-Yes, I did.
-Toughened your nipples, didn't it?
-You son of a bitch!
[Lecter] Amputate a man's leg,
and he can still feel it tickling.
Tell me, Mom, when your little girl
is on the slab, where will it tickle you?
Take this thing back to Baltimore.
Five-foot-ten, strongly built,
about 180 pounds.
Hair blond, eyes pale blue.
He'd be about 35 now.
He said he lived in Philadelphia
but may have lied.
That's all I can remember, Mom.
But if I think of any more,
I will let you know.
Oh, and, Senator, just one more thing.
Love your suit.
[Chilton] I can tell you now
that in a meeting earlier this evening
with Senator Ruth Martin, Dr. Lecter
agreed to assist in the investigation
of trying to find the abductor
of Catherine Martin, Buffalo Bill.
-How do you fit in, sir?
-It's through my unique insight
into Lecter's mind
that this breakthrough was possible.
And Buffalo Bill's real name?
Buffalo Bill's real name is now a matter
of record with the proper authorities.
-Can you give us more information?
-My name is Dr. Frederick Chilton.
-How do you spell that?
-That's C-H –
Are you with Dr. Chilton's group?
Uh, well, I just saw him outside, sir.
Access to Lecter is strictly limited.
We've been getting death threats.
I understand, sir.
Log in and check your weapon.
[Krendler]
I can't take all the credit for myself.
Senator Martin, the Justice Department,
people at the FBI,
the folks at the Baltimore State Hospital.
And now for the hard part,
apprehending the suspect.
-Excuse me, folks. I have to catch a flight.
-[reporters clamoring]
[phone rings]
Command desk. Officer Jacobs.
-[officer] Is it true what they're saying?
-Huh?
He's some kind of vampire.
-They don't have a name for what he is.
-[elevator bell dings]
You do know the rules, ma'am?
Yes, Lieutenant Boyle.
I've questioned him before.
Go ahead.
Good evening, Clarice.
I thought you might like
your drawings back, Doctor.
Just until you get your view.
How very thoughtful.
Or did Jack Crawford
send you for one last wheedle
before you're both booted off the case?
No, I came because I wanted to.
People will say we're in love.
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk,
tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Anthrax Island.
That was an especially nice touch,
Clarice.
Yours?
Yes.
Yeah.
That was good.
Pity about poor Catherine though.
Ticktock, ticktock, ticktock, ticktock.
Your anagrams are showing, Doctor.
Louis Friend? [scoffs]
Iron sulfide, also known as fool's gold.
Oh, Clarice, your problem is
you need to get more fun out of life.
You were telling me the truth
back in Baltimore, sir.
Please continue now.
I've read the case files. Have you?
Everything you need to find him
is right there in those pages.
-Then tell me how.
-First principles, Clarice.
Simplicity.
Read Marcus Aurelius.
Of each particular thing, ask,
what is it in itself?
What is its nature?
What does he do, this man you seek?
He kills women.
No. That is incidental.
What is the first
and principal thing he does?
What needs does he serve by killing?
Anger.
Um. . . social acceptance
and, um, sexual frustration, sir.
No. He covets.
That is his nature.
And how do we begin to covet, Clarice?
Do we seek out things to covet?
Make an effort to answer now.
No. We just –
No. We begin by coveting
what we see every day.
Don't you feel eyes
moving over your body, Clarice?
And don't your eyes
seek out the things you want?
All right, yes. Now please tell me how.
No.
It is your turn to tell me, Clarice.
You don't have any more vacations to sell.
Why did you leave that ranch?
Doctor, we don't have any more time
for any of this now.
But we don't reckon time
the same way, do we, Clarice?
This is all the time you'll ever have.
Later. Now, please, listen to me.
We've only got five –
No! I will listen now.
After your father's murder, you were orphaned.
You were 10 years old.
You went to live with cousins
on a sheep and horse ranch in Montana.
And?
And one morning, I just ran away.
Not "just," Clarice. What set you off?
You started at what time?
Early. Still dark.
Then something woke you, didn't it?
Was it a dream?
What was it?
I heard a strange noise.
It was. . .
screaming.
Some kind of screaming,
like a child's voice.
What did you do?
I went downstairs, outside.
I crept up into the barn house.
I was so scared to look inside,
but I had to.
What did you see, Clarice?
What did you see?
Lambs.
They were screaming. [inhales]
They were slaughtering the spring lambs?
And they were screaming.
And you ran away?
No.
First I tried to free them. I –
I opened the gate to their pen,
but they wouldn't run.
They just stood there, confused.
They wouldn't run.
But you could, and you did, didn't you?
Yes.
I took one lamb
and I ran away as fast as I could.
Where were you going, Clarice?
I don't know. I didn't have any food,
any water, and it was very cold.
It was very cold.
I thought –
I thought if I could save just one, but. . .
he was so heavy.
He was so heavy.
[wind whistling]
I didn't get more than a few miles
when the sheriff's car picked me up.
Rancher was so angry, he sent me to live
at the Lutheran orphanage in Bozeman.
I never saw the ranch again.
What became of your lamb, Clarice?
They killed him.
You still wake up sometimes, don't you?
Wake up in the dark
and hear the screaming of the lambs.
Yes.
And you think if you saved poor Catherine,
you could make them stop, don't you?
You think, if Catherine lives,
you won't wake up in the dark ever again. . .
to that awful screaming of the lambs.
I don't know. I don't know.
Thank you, Clarice.
Thank you.
Tell me his name, Doctor.
[Lecter inhales]
[door opens]
[clicks tongue] Dr. Chilton, I presume?
I think you know each other.
[footsteps approaching]
Okay.
-[agent] We found her.
-Let's go.
It's your turn, Doctor.
-Out.
-Tell me his name.
Sorry, ma'am, I've got orders.
Have to put you on a plane.
[Boyle] Come on now.
Brave Clarice.
You will let me know when those lambs
stop screaming, won't you?
Tell me his name, Doctor.
Clarice!
Your case file.
Hey.
Good-bye, Clarice.
[Boyle, guard grunting, muttering]
[police radio chatter]
[classical piano]
[footsteps approaching]
Ready when you are, Doc.
Just another minute, please.
Son of a bitch demanded a second dinner.
Lamb chops. Extra rare.
Wonder what he wants for breakfast.
Some damn thing from the zoo?
[guard chuckles]
[classical piano continues]
Good evening, gentlemen.
Okay, Doc. Grab some floor.
-Same drill as before, please.
-Mm-hmm.
Ready when you are, Sergeant Pembry.
[Pembry] Okay.
-[Boyle] Hand me that, would you?
-Uh-huh.
Thanks.
[Lecter] Mind the drawings, please.
Thank you.
Jimmy, watch it! He's got me!
[grunting]
-[snarling]
-[screaming]
Jesus Christ!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[groans, sputters]
[Pembry] I need help.
[screaming]
[Boyle grunts]
[grunting]
[classical piano continues]
[Pembry groaning]
Ready when you are, Sergeant Pembry.
[people chattering]
[officer] What is this shit?
Did somebody go up on five?
No. Nobody went up.
-Call Pembry. Ask him to tell –
-[gunshots]
CP. Shots fired on five.
Repeat, shots fired on five.
Sergeant Tate!
[man on radio] Shots fired on five.
-[Tate] Holy shit!
-[officer] What the hell?
-[chattering]
-[Tate] Shut up!
Bobby, get the vest.
Right, Sarge.
-[Tate] Brady, Howard, cover the –
-Look!
-[elevator bell dings, faint]
-[Jacobs] It stopped.
Seal off a 10-block radius.
Get me the SWAT team
and an ambulance, double quick.
We're goin' up.
[police radio chatter]
[Tate] Pembry!
Boyle! [echoing]
[hammers cocking]
Oh, God!
Go.
-Clear.
Command post, two officers down.
-[Jacobs] Clear.
-[officer] Clear!
Lecter's gone, Sarge.
[Tate] Prisoner is missing.
-Boyle's gun is gone, Sergeant.
-Repeat, Lecter's missing and armed.
He's stripped the bed.
Might be making a rope. Check all windows.
Where the fuck is my ambulance?
-[wheezing]
-He's alive.
Sergeant Tate, he's alive!
Get ahold of him where
you can feel his hands, son. Talk to him.
What do I say?
It's Jim Pembry! Now talk to him, damn it!
[Tate] Lecter's missing and armed.
Pembry. Pembry, can you hear me?
He took Boyle's gun. Pembry got off one round.
There's a chance Lecter was hit.
Keep breathing in and out. That's it.
You're doing a good job.
Oh, you look real good there.
-Yeah, you look. . . real good.
-[sirens wailing]
[helicopters whirring]
-You ready?
-Let's go.
-Let's do it.
-Okay? Let's go.
-Got it?
-Yeah.
Lookin' good, Pembry.
You're gonna make it.
You're doin' just fine.
You're doin' all right. That's right.
-Okay, I need that IV now!
-Lactated Ringer's.
Can we get the strap?
Buzz, where's the fuckin' oxygen?
Lookin' good, buddy. That's right.
Stay with me. Stay with me here.
[grunting]
We're losin' him. Downstairs, quickly!
-And up!
-[grunting continues]
-Elevator! Out of the way!
-[Jacobs] Clear the way!
[officer] Get out of the way.
-[monitor beeping]
-[man on radio] CP to Tate.
Uh, roger, Lieutenant. Tate here.
I'm on the elevator bringin' Pembry down.
He seems to be hangin' on.
Top three floors secured.
Main stairwell secured.
We think he's on two.
[lieutenant on radio]
Tate? You still with me?
Uh, we're pretty sure
he's somewhere on two, sir.
That's all for now. Over.
[elevator bell dings]
He's on the roof of the elevator.
Okay, guys.
I see him. There's a gun by his hand.
He's not moving.
-One warning. We need him alive.
-Got it.
Lecter?
Put your hands on your head.
One in the leg.
No movement.
Johnny, hold your fire.
We're coming into the car.
We're opening the hatch.
Watch his hands.
If there's any fire, it'll come from us.
-Affirm?
-Got it.
[siren blaring]
Memphis General, this is Medical Unit 26.
We're inbound
with a 50-year-old male police officer
with severe facial lacerations.
Weapon unknown. We've got grand mal
seizure activity, but he's postictal now.
Copy.
Uh, vital signs are good.
Pressure is 130 over 90.
- Ninety?
-Yeah, that's right, 90. Pulse 84.
We've got him on
lactated Ringer's running,
and, uh – and the, uh, patient
is on 10 liters of oxygen.
Watch it!
[Ardelia] They found the ambulance
in a parking garage at Memphis Airport.
Crew was dead.
He killed a tourist too.
Got his clothes, cash.
By now he could be anywhere.
He won't come after me.
-Oh, really?
-He won't.
I can't explain it.
He – He would consider that rude.
[scoffs] It's over. She's dead.
It's not your fault it worked out like this.
Lecter said everything we need to catch him
with is right here in these pages.
Dr. Lecter said a lot of things.
He's here, Ardelia.
[sniffs]
Is this Lecter's handwriting?
"Clarice, doesn't this random scattering
of sites seem desperately random?
Like the elaboration of a bad liar.
Ta, Hannibal Lecter."
"Desperately random." What does he mean?
Not random at all maybe.
Like there's some pattern here.
Yeah, but there is no pattern,
or the computers would've nailed it.
They were even found in random order.
Random because of the one girl.
The one he weighted down.
-Oh, Frederica Bimmel.
-Right.
Yeah, from Belvedere, Ohio.
First girl taken. Third body found. Why?
Well, she didn't drift.
He weighted her down.
What did Lecter say
about the first principles?
Simplicity.
What does this guy do? He covets.
How do we first start to covet?
We covet what we see –
Every day.
-Hot damn, Clarice.
-He knew her.
-Mr. Bimmel?
-That's me.
Hello. I'm Clarice Starling.
I'm with the FBI.
[door opens, closes]
[Clarice] I sure appreciate you letting me
take a look around, Mr. Bimmel.
I don't know nothin' new to tell ya.
Police been back here
so many times already.
Frederica went into Chicago
on the bus to see about a job.
She left the interview okay.
She never come home.
Her bedroom's how she left it. Upstairs.
Door to the left.
[music plays]
[music slows]
[music continues]
[cat meowing]
[meowing continues]
[bird wings flapping]
[Clarice] He's making himself
a woman suit, Mr. Crawford,
out of real women!
And he can sew, this guy.
He-He's very skilled.
-He's a tailor or a dressmaker or –
-[Crawford] Starling –
That's why they're all big.
He has to keep them alive
so he can starve them a while,
so he can loosen their skin –
Starling, Starling, we know who he is and
where he is. We're on our way right now.
-Where?
-Calumet City, edge of Chicago.
-Be on the ground in 45 minutes with HRT.
-Oh, that's –
-That's great news, sir, but how –
-Johns Hopkins came up with some names.
We fed 'em into known offenders.
Subject's name is Jame Gumb,
aka John Grant.
Lecter's description was accurate.
He just lied about the name.
Listen to this.
Customs had some paper on him.
They stopped a carton
two years ago at LAX:
live caterpillars from Suriname.
The addressee was a Jame Gumb.
Well, Chicago's only 400 miles from here.
-I'll be there in –
- No, no, no, Starling.
There's not enough time.
We want him for murder, not kidnapping.
I need you to link him to the Bimmel girl
before he's indicted.
-See what you can dredge up in Belvedere.
-Yes, sir. You bet.
-I'll do my best.
-Starling.
We wouldn't have found him without you.
Nobody's gonna forget that.
Least of all me.
Thank you, sir.
-Thank you very much, Mr. Crawford.
-[static]
Mr. Crawford?
Thanks for the scraps, asshole.
I got a better idea.
[breathing heavily]
Yeah.
[stereo: rock]
[sighs]
Okay, Precious, time for a little treat.
[grunts]
[growling]
[stereo: man vocalizing]
Precious.
[whistles]
-Come on, girl.
-♪ He told me ♪
-Come on, Precious. Come on, Precious.
-♪ I see you rise ♪
♪ But it always falls ♪
[Catherine whistling]
Come on, Precious.
-♪ I see them come ♪
-I got a yummy, yummy snack for ya.
-♪ I see them go ♪
-Come on. Come and get it.
♪ He said ♪
♪ "All things pass into the night" ♪
Precious!
Are you out there, you little shit?
Come and get it, pretty girl.
♪ I must disagree, oh, no, sir ♪
♪ I must say – ♪
[sobs] Precious.
Please come. Come on.
♪ You told me ♪
♪ I've seen it all before ♪
[sobs] Come on, Precious. [sobs]
[weak whistle]
♪ I've seen my hopes and dreams
A-lyin' on the ground ♪
♪ I've seen – ♪
[sobs] Precious, come on.
-[growls]
-[chuckles]
Will you fuck me?
[Catherine]
Come on. Take that bone. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. [grunting]
I'd fuck me.
Come on.
-[growling]
-[grunts]
[yelps]
[gasps]
I'd fuck me hard.
I'd fuck me so hard. [chuckles]
[sobbing]
No!
♪ Good-bye, horses ♪
-♪ I'm flying over you ♪
-[humming]
-[sobbing]
-♪ Good-bye, horses ♪
-♪ I'm lyin' over you ♪
-[barks]
♪ Good-bye, horses ♪
-♪ I'm lyin', lyin', lyin' ♪
-♪ I'm lyin', lyin', lyin' over you ♪
[singer vocalizing]
[siren wailing]
Is that a good job, FBI agent?
You get to travel around and stuff?
I mean, better places than this?
[chuckles] Sometimes you do.
Freddie was so happy for me
when I got this job at the bank.
Toaster giveaways and Barry Manilow
on the speakers all day.
She thought it was such hot shit.
What did she know? Big dummy.
Stacy, did Frederica ever mention
a man named "Jamie" Gumb
or a Jame Gumb?
-How about John Grant?
-No.
Would she have had a friend
you didn't know about?
No way. If she had a guy, I'd have known.
Believe me. Sewing was her life.
-Did you two ever work together or –
-Oh, sure.
Me and Pam Malavesi used to help her
do alterations for old Mrs. Lippman.
Can you give me Mrs. Lippman's address?
I need to talk to her.
[insects clicking]
So powerful. So beautiful.
[Precious barking, whimpering]
-Precious?
-[whimpering continues]
-[Catherine] Down here, you sack of shit!
[barking]
[gasping]
-Put her in that bucket.
-No.
You get me a telephone
and lower it down here, now!
Oh, poodlie-poo, Precious.
Darling, are you all right?
She's in a lot of pain, mister.
She needs a vet.
She broke her leg on the way down.
I know it.
-She's been licking it –
-Hey, don't you hurt my dog!
Don't you make me hurt your dog!
You don't know what pain is!
Get me a live telephone
and lower it down here, and do it now!
-You fucking – Oh, fuck!
-You better be getting me that telephone!
[shouts]
I'm gonna do it, mister!
I'll cut her neck off, I swear to God!
[stereo: rock blaring]
-All right, mister, I'm doing it!
-[muttering] Motherfucking –
[ringing]
-[Catherine shouting] I'm in here! Here!
-[music blaring]
[ringing]
-Okay, I'm coming.
-[doorbell rings]
We're goin' in.
Good afternoon. Um, sorry to bother you.
I'm looking for Mrs. Lippman's family.
-FBI ! Everybody down!
-FBI ! Down, now!
The Lippmans don't live here anymore.
Excuse me, sir.
I really need to speak with you.
-Clear!
[stammers] What's the problem, Officer?
Well, I'm investigating
the death of Frederica Bimmel.
There's no one here, Jack.
Clarice.
Your name is?
-Oh, uh, Jack Gordon.
-Mr. Gordon. Good.
Um, well, Frederica used to work
for Mrs. Lippman. Did you know her?
No. Uh-uh.
Oh, wait. Was she a great big, fat person?
Yeah, she was a big girl, sir.
Yeah, I – I may have see –
No, I read about her in the newspaper.
Um, Mrs. Lippman had a son though.
Maybe he could help you.
I got his card in here someplace.
-Do you wanna come in while I look for it?
-May I?
-Yeah, sure.
-Thank you.
[Buffalo Bill] Are you close
to catching somebody, you think?
Yes. We may be.
Did you. . . take over this place
after Mrs. Lippman died? Is that right?
Yeah. I bought this house,
uh, two years ago.
Did she leave any records?
Any business records?
Tax forms? Um, list of employees?
No, nothing like that at all.
Say, has the FBI learned something?
The police around here
don't seem to have the first clue.
[insect wings flapping]
I mean, have you got like a description,
fingerprints, anything like that?
No.
Mm-hmm.
No, we don't.
Ah.
Here's that number.
Very good, Mr. Gordon.
May I use your phone, please?
[snickers]
[chuckles] Sure, you can use my phone.
Freeze!
Put your hands over your head
and turn around!
Spread your legs!
Put your hands in the back, thumbs up –
Freeze!
[panting]
[doorknob rattles, hinge creaks]
[rock song playing, faint]
[Precious barking in distance]
[Catherine] Hey!
[barking continues]
[Clarice panting]
-[gasps]
-[song continues, lyrics indistinct]
[Catherine] Hello? Are you there?
I'm down here! I'm down here!
[barking continues]
[grunts]
Catherine Martin?
Yes!
[barking continues]
FBI ! You're safe!
Safe? Shit. Get me outta here!
[grunts]
[barking continues]
[song continues, echoing]
You're all right, Catherine.
Now where is he?
How the fuck should I know?
Just get me outta here!
Catherine, you gotta be quiet.
Now shut that dog up!
Just get me outta here!
-[Precious whimpering]
-Oh, God.
Catherine,
I'm gonna get you outta there,
but right now you listen to me.
I've gotta leave this room.
I'll be right back.
No, don't you leave me here,
you fuckin' bitch! No!
Don't you leave me here!
This guy's fuckin' crazy!
[Catherine] Please!
I gotta get outta here!
Plea –
Catherine, the other officers
will be here any minute now!
[Catherine screams] Wait!
-Don't go! Wait!
-[Clarice] Shh! Quiet!
[Catherine] Come back.
[gasps] Oh, God. Oh, God.
[panting]
[grunts]
[Clarice panting]
[song continues, indistinct]
[Clarice grunts, pants]
-[clattering]
-[gasps]
[refrigerator motor chugging]
[grunts]
[song continues, muffled]
[grunts, pants]
[Clarice gasps]
[rattling, switch clicks]
[high-pitched whine]
[gasps]
[panting]
[hammer cocks]
[panting continues]
[gasps]
[panting]
[loud clack]
[gasps]
[Buffalo Bill cries out, groans]
[gurgles]
[Clarice exhales sharply]
[grunts]
[panting]
[birds twittering]
[Clarice panting]
[police radio chatter]
-[Precious whines]
-[Catherine] No.
-You okay?
-Gunpowder. It's nothing. I'm okay.
[reporter] Agent Starling, how did you
track Buffalo Bill to this address?
[applause]
Clarice M. Starling.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Ernest W. Stevens.
[applause]
[laughter, chattering]
-Special Agent Starling.
-Oh, Special Agent Mapp. [laughs]
-Phone call.
-Oh, thank you. Excuse me, gentlemen.
Starling?
Pilch. Would you take our picture?
[chuckles] Sure.
Look, I just wanted to say
congratulations.
[Clarice exhales]
And I'm not much good at this kind of thing,
so I'm gonna duck outta here.
Okay. Sure. Um –
Thank you, Mr. Crawford.
Um –
Your father would've been proud today.
Don't forget your phone call.
Starling.
[Lecter] Well, Clarice.
Have the lambs stopped screaming?
-Dr. Lecter.
- Don't bother with a trace.
I won't be on long enough.
Where are you, Dr. Lecter?
I have no plans to call on you, Clarice.
The world's more interesting
with you in it.
So you take care now
to extend me the same courtesy.
You know I can't make that promise.
I do wish we could chat longer, but. . .
I'm having an old friend for dinner.
Bye.
Dr. Lecter!
Dr. Lecter?
Very important –
Oh, excuse me. I'm sorry.
-Is the security system all set up?
-Oh, yeah, the big-shot security.
Oh, thank you. I appreciate that.
[man singing in French]
[singing in French continues]