[Jeanine] Peace.
Long ago, before
The Founders established
this great city of ours,
that word
was all but meaningless.
An ideal as elusive as a dream.
Now, 200 years later,
we are, all of us,
living proof that peace
is indeed attainable.
The reason for this is,
of course, our Faction System.
Erudite, Dauntless, Amity,
Candor, Abnegation.
In dividing people according
to personality and aptitude,
we've created a society
in which each faction
plays a critical role
in maintaining
the social order.
But this harmony we've
achieved is now under attack
from a small
but extremely dangerous group
of individuals.
[indistinct chatter]
We call them Divergents.
They are, in essence,
the worst of what
humanity used to be.
Rebellious, defiant
and uncontrollable.
Five days ago,
a rogue group of Divergents,
posing as Dauntless
brutally invaded Abnegation.
An obvious attempt
to cripple the Faction System
by attacking
its most vulnerable members.
These Divergents
despise our system
because they are incapable
of conforming to it.
These latest rumors,
for example,
that I was somehow behind
the attack on Abnegation,
nothing more
than Divergent propaganda.
I am devoting myself
to bringing these fugitives
to justice.
-I've exercised my right
as acting Council leader...
-[woman screaming]
...to declare martial law
until I'm confident
that any threat to our security
has been eliminated.
Tell Jeanine we got it.
[Jeanine] We are all
that is left of humanity.
The vast wall
that encloses this city
may protect us
from our toxic surroundings,
but it is up to us to confront
any element that could
poison us from within.
Because, when you are
civilization's last hope,
peace is not merely an ideal.
It is an obligation.
And it is up to all of us
to take a stand
against its one true enemy,
Divergents.
[Tris panting]
[birds cawing]
[panting]
Amity.
We need to make sure
it's clear.
Tris!
Help us. Please help us.
Please.
Please help us.
You have to help us.
[Johanna]
Sorry, you have to leave.
You just don't belong here.
[Christina] It's all her fault.
You killed Will.
-No.
-[people murmuring]
[all whispering]
She killed him.
She killed him. She killed him.
Mama.
-You killed us all.
-Will!
-[gunshot echoes]
-[gasps]
[panting]
[sighs in relief]
[birds cawing]
[children shouting]
And three!
[boy] Higher!
Hey.
[boy] Higher! Higher!
[Four] Wanna go higher?
[woman]
All right, everyone,
back to class. Let's go.
[Four]
Okay. Here we go. [grunts]
See ya. Bye.
[children shouting gleefully]
I just wanted to do
something different.
Yeah.
Well, it's definitely
different.
[both chuckle]
You don't like it?
No, I like it. I like it a lot.
I'm just surprised, that's all.
What's goin' on, Tris?
Nothin'. I'm fine. Just...
Still having nightmares?
No.
We're good.
You and me.
I know nothing else is,
but we are.
[woman on PA] Good morning,
and have a blessed day.
[sighs]
Time for chores.
[woman] All planters,
report to the dome.
All planters to the dome.
[Tris laughing]
[Tris] How much longer
do we have to stay here, Four?
[Four] Until we know
it's safe to leave.
[intense music playing]
[Four] Hey.
[Tris] Hi.
[Marcus] Son...
You can't ignore me forever.
I know you're thinkin'
about your next move,
but there are things
you don't know.
Marcus, please
just leave us alone.
Your mother didn't come back
to Abnegation just to save you.
She died trying to hide
something from Jeanine.
Something that was entrusted
to Abnegation a long time ago.
Marcus, stop.
Whatever you want from us,
you're not gonna get it.
I'm not the enemy here.
You found it.
It was in the home
of Natalie and Andrew Prior,
like you said.
Mind telling me what's inside?
[Jeanine]
A message from The Founders
that will ensure
the future our people deserve.
Divergents will destroy
our society.
Unless we destroy them.
And now we can.
However, only a Divergent
can open this box.
Find them.
Every last one of them.
[indistinct conversations]
[man] Go with happiness.
Go with happiness.
-Go with happiness.
-Thank you.
Go with happiness.
I really don't know
how much longer
I can do this whole peace
and love thing.
It's the Amity way, all right?
We're just trying to blend in.
[Tris scoffs]
I'm trying to blend in.
It's just not working.
[Peter]
Comin' through on your right.
Okay, here we go.
Hey, look, a rainbow.
-Oh.
-It's pretty.
[woman] Go with happiness.
Virtual pathological
friendliness
with unquestioned passivism?
I love this place.
Thank you. Go with happiness.
Oops, excuse me.
Hey, Tris, I really like
your hair, by the way.
Did you try to cut it all short
and weird like that?
Peter, why don't you take
your food and sit down, huh?
Or what?
Besides, I think we should all
stick together now that we're
-all officially fugitives.
-[Tris shushes]
Wait, what do you mean,
"officially fugitives"?
-Oh, you don't know?
-Let's go, let's go.
You didn't tell Caleb?
Yeah, so now Jeanine is saying
that the attack on Abnegation
was orchestrated by a group
of renegade Divergents
and their sympathizers.
So then they're blaming
this whole thing on us?
Yeah. Jeanine needed a reason
to petition the Council
to institute martial law.
Now she has one.
[chuckling]
Staying here at Amity is still
our best option for now.
We need to keep an ear
to the ground.
Find out where
the rest of the Dauntless are.
Then we can make a move.
We need to kill Jeanine.
I know.
But we're not ready yet.
[sighs]
Beatrice, you're not
being serious, right?
No, I am being serious.
I'm not gonna stop
until she's dead.
Tris, you can't just
go around killing people.
No, she's right.
Listen to your sister.
Tris, I think
you should go to Erudite
and kill Jeanine yourself.
I'll stay with Caleb so that
you don't get him killed, too.
What?
[Peter] Come on, you know.
Like you did your parents.
[both grunting]
[Four] Come on!
What do you think you're doing?
My office. Now.
Enjoy your meal, everyone.
Enjoy your meal.
Calm down. Just calm down.
Was I not clear that the terms
of your sanctuary here
included nonviolence?
I can guarantee you
nothing like this
will ever happen again.
Well, be that as it may,
you can no longer stay
here with us.
Your presence
is just too disruptive.
Truth is that our sanctuary
was never gonna last
very long here anyways.
Was it? With you
not standing up to Jeanine.
[scoffs]
You don't understand us at all.
[Tris] No, I do understand you.
I understand that you think
you can stay out of this.
But you can't.
One day she's gonna show up
and Jeanine is gonna take
whatever power
you think you have
away from you.
[Four] Tris, Tris...
[inhales deeply]
[Four] Look, Johanna,
we need a little more time.
I need to find
out where the rest
of the Dauntless are.
Then we can leave.
And then what? Attack Erudite?
I will not be
a party to violence.
[Four]
And no one's asking you to.
We just need a few more days.
One.
One what?
One more chance.
See, to be Amity is to forgive.
Others. And yourself.
You're hurting, Tris.
And my heart goes out to you.
I know what it's like
to stand helpless
while you lose
the ones you love.
But killing Jeanine
is not going to bring
your mother back.
I know you're angry.
But you're letting it
consume you.
[footsteps approaching]
-[Johanna] What is it?
-[vehicles approaching]
[intense music playing]
Stay here. And keep quiet.
[indistinct chatter]
[Johanna] Gentlemen,
Amity welcomes you.
To what do we owe the pleasure?
This isn't really
a social call, Johanna.
We're looking for Divergents.
I see. Well, of course,
anything we can do to help.
Gonna need you to volunteer
your faction to be tested.
-New screening technology
from Erudite.
-[electronic voice] Amity...
Now that Jeanine's
heading up the Council,
the approval process
just got a little easier.
You're exceeding
your jurisdiction.
Now, Johanna, what happened
to that Amity politeness?
The easy way or the hard way?
It's up to you.
All right.
But under protest.
Okay, we're good to go!
Move it out! Round 'em up.
[man] In the dome.
[male announcer on PA]
All Amity report to the dome
for new mandatory testing.
Please proceed to the dome
for mandatory testing.
[soldier 1] In the building.
Let's go. Get inside.
-Line up.
-[women screaming]
Let's go. Move it.
[soldier 2] This way.
[soldier 3] Line it up.
[man] Building secured.
[Eric]
You know something, lady?
You seem awfully stuck
in that doorway.
[laughs]
Eric's here.
We need to move now.
Come on.
What's up there?
-[whispering] Wait, stop.
-[Johanna] Just my office.
[horse whinnying]
[whispering] Go, go, go!
Hmm.
Hey.
There's two guards with guns.
We're going out the window?
We need to split up.
Okay, yeah. Okay.
Every man for themselves.
Good.
-Hey, they're up here! Hey!
-[Four] Go, go, go, go!
Eric, they're up here!
Come on, they're getting away!
All right, you ready?
[all grunting]
[Four] Let's go.
-Where?
-Out the window.
I got three on foot making
a break toward the dome.
-[electronic voice] Divergent.
-Got one.
[Eric on radio] I repeat,
three on foot toward the dome.
Over there!
-I demand amnesty!
-Get down! Now!
I'm the leader of Abnegation!
It is my right!
[people screaming]
Detain him!
-Whoa. Okay. All right.
-[soldier 1] Let's go.
Come on.
[vehicles approaching]
Come on, keep moving.
[intense music playing]
Come on!
Come on.
Let's go!
[panting]
[Four] Keep going. Come on.
[train whistle blowing]
-[Four] Listen!
-[Caleb] What?
[Tris] Train!
-[Four] Go, go, go!
-[gunfire]
[Four]
Go! Come on!
Caleb!
Keep moving!
Go!
Ammo!
[Four]
Come on, come on!
Go! Go! Move!
[grunting]
Move! Go, go, go!
Caleb!
Move!
[grunts]
[all panting]
[door opens]
Oh, you folks sure know
how to make an entrance.
[sighs]
[Four] Factionless.
[Edgar] Amity?
But you stand like Dauntless.
No idea what this one is.
Look, we just need to get
to the city, that's all.
Well, too bad. Train's taken.
And you damaged our cargo.
[Caleb] These are
Abnegation fabric bolts.
And you're Factionless, right?
-Caleb.
-I used to be Abnegation.
We used to use those same bolts
to make clothes for you.
You're saying that
we're stealing from you?
No. No, no, no.
I'm no longer Abnegation.
So technically you're
not stealing from me, but...
[stammers]
No, you're not stealing at all.
[stuttering]
I mean, maybe.
It's a question of semantics,
I suppose, whether it's
stealing or charity.
[stammering]
But it's all really the same.
[Tris] That's enough! Get off!
Everybody, relax.
All right, you made your point.
We'll get off your train,
all right?
Got you. Will everybody
just relax, okay?
Why don't we, uh, take a seat!
[grunts]
-[Tris] Caleb!
-[all clamoring]
-[Four] Stop!
-I'm sorry, I was
just trying to help.
Don't!
Oh, yeah,
this is gonna be fun,
isn't it?
Everybody, just calm down.
All right?
Oh.
[all grunting]
[Tris grunting]
[man screaming]
[screams]
[whimpering]
[man groans]
[screams]
[grunting]
[panting]
Caleb.
[groaning]
[Tris] No!
Get off of me! Get off!
You all right? You okay?
Yeah.
[all panting]
Tobias Eaton.
You say that again.
What? You know him?
I am him.
[laughing]
We have been looking for you.
Four, what are they
talking about?
Four.
[grunts]
Follow me.
[indistinct chatter]
[Caleb] Tris.
I'm sorry. I wanted to help...
[Tris] Four.
Four, why are they
looking for you?
How do they know your name?
[indistinct conversations]
[guns cocking]
This is Factionless?
This is insane.
Tobias.
Mother.
[whispering]
I thought she was dead.
Me too.
Someone please tell me
what's going on here.
Tobias' father
was very abusive.
I knew the only way
I could ever truly escape him
would be
to disappear completely.
Abnegation helped me
fake my death.
Anything to protect
Marcus' image.
But you just left him there
alone with Marcus?
I was very young.
I reached out to him
about a year ago.
I felt it was finally time
to reconnect.
[laughs]
I'm still your mother.
No, my mother's dead.
I went to her funeral
when I was six.
And she wasn't trying
to reconnect with me.
She was trying to use me,
like you are now.
Why?
She wants an army.
-An army?
-I want an alliance.
No, what you want is revenge.
-This isn't about me.
-[scoffs]
It's about putting an end
to a system that says
one group is more deserving
than another.
This city may be surrounded
by a wall,
but it doesn't have to be
a prison.
-I think that's a bit extreme.
-Hmm?
I mean, the Faction System
isn't perfect,
but it's hardly a prison.
Let me guess. Erudite.
I was Erudite.
You willing to kill Jeanine?
Absolutely.
When I was married to Marcus,
I knew her well.
And believe me,
there's nothing
she isn't capable of.
But I think
you already know that.
Tris, we can't trust her.
-Or maybe she knows--
-We're on the same side, Tris.
I'm Factionless
because I don't fit
into any one faction.
And you're Divergent because
you belong to too many.
But we're both
a threat to Jeanine.
My people are ready for war,
if that's what it takes.
And then what?
-We depose those in power.
-And once you've done that?
Once you've killed Jeanine,
who's in power then?
See, that's the part
that she always conveniently
leaves out.
Don't you tell me
this isn't about you.
This is only about you.
I know where the remaining
Dauntless are hiding.
Where?
They took shelter in Candor.
As far as I know,
they're still there.
Think about it.
If we were to combine forces,
Dauntless and Factionless,
we'd be unstoppable.
That's not gonna happen.
Thank you for your hospitality,
but we'll be leaving
in the morning.
Four, maybe this is...
Tobias, please, reconsider.
Don't you call me that.
My name's Four.
You wanna tuck him in,
or should I?
[door slamming]
Well, this...
This meal looks lovely.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you
about her.
[sighs]
No more secrets. Okay?
[gasps]
[whispering] I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you.
I always loved
watching him sleep.
I take it you're setting out
for Candor in the morning?
Yeah.
Listen, I only want
what's best for him.
You hardly even know him.
You'd like to think that,
wouldn't you?
But deep down,
I think you're scared
I know him all too well.
-I'm not scared.
-Of course you are.
You're scared
he'll finally see you
for what you really are.
Deadly.
You don't believe me?
Ask him.
[panting]
[Four] You okay?
Yeah.
You sure?
[intense music playing]
I'm not coming with you guys.
What?
To Candor.
I'm not coming with you guys.
What are you talking about?
What's your plan?
You guys are gonna find
the rest of Dauntless.
Then what?
You attack Erudite,
assassinate Jeanine,
start a civil war?
I'm sorry, I'm just not...
I'm not cut out for that.
I'm not like you guys.
I need to go back
to Abnegation, maybe.
Sort out what
our parents left behind.
At least I'd be useful there.
Caleb, there's nothing left
at Abnegation.
Yeah.
-You okay?
-Just need to get to Candor.
Tris.
I know you think Caleb
is your responsibility,
but he made his own choice.
You can't protect everyone.
[chuckles]
I can't protect anyone.
Nobody can.
Him leaving isn't your fault.
None of this is your fault.
[sighs]
Johanna was right.
You have to forgive yourself.
Thank you.
[woman on PA] All factions
have been instructed to
-maintain a strict curfew
until further notice.
-[Tris] we gotta move.
Repeat. All factions
have been instructed
to maintain a strict curfew
until further notice.
All factions
have been instructed
to maintain a strict curfew...
-We found them.
-Yeah.
-[Hector] Four!
-[all greeting]
-Damn, is it good
to see you guys.
-How are you, Uriah?
I'm better now.
I'm not exactly built
for laying low.
-Tris!
-Christina.
-It's so good to see you.
-[Christina] You too.
Have you heard anything
about Will?
-No.
-Nothing?
No.
Something must have happened
to him.
He would have found me
by now, you know?
-Hey.
How you holdin' up?
How many Dauntless do we have?
Hundred and seventy-five.
Total.
-Hundred and seventy-five?
That's it?
-The rest followed Max.
Not near the numbers we need.
-No.
-[man] Hold it!
Drop your guns.
-Whoa, hey. They're with us.
-We know who you are.
Last warning. Drop your guns.
[Four] All right.
Easy.
I'm Jack Kang.
I'm leadership here.
Yeah, we know who you are.
And we're not a threat
to Candor.
That might be your truth.
It's not necessarily mine.
All I know for certain
is you're both wanted
for criminal insurgency
and conspiring
in the attack on Abnegation.
Those are lies.
If you were Candor,
I would take you at your word.
Unfortunately,
given the circumstances,
I'm obliged to hand you over
to the Council.
You can make your case there.
You might as well
just kill us now.
If Jeanine finds us,
we're not gonna live
to stand trial.
I doubt that very much.
She would never supersede
the Council.
Sure about that?
Who's gonna stop her? You?
Factional law must be upheld.
All right, wait, wait, wait.
Can I ask you one question?
[grunts]
Jeanine believes that Erudite
are most fit to govern
because they are the smartest.
Do you believe that Candor
is most fit to judge because
you're so honest?
I admit I do hold that belief.
Then would you say that
a trial held here at Candor
would be inherently more fair
than a trial held by Erudite?
Hmm.
The answer is yes.
In my opinion,
a Candor trial would have
the greatest chance
of achieving true justice.
So are you asking me
to petition the Council
to grant Candor
sole judiciary power?
No. As part of Candor's
initiation,
you administer a truth serum.
Correct?
We don't typically discuss
such matters out of faction.
That's a pretty evasive answer.
Evasion is not dishonest.
It's not exactly honesty
either.
Yes. We possess such a serum.
Then use it on us.
-Four.
-If we're guilty,
we'll surrender
to the Council. All right?
If not, you've just saved
two lives.
And made some loyal allies.
[Jack] All right.
But you should know that
the serum can be quite brutal.
It was designed
for Candor applicants
who are already
predisposed to honesty.
Not everyone finds it so easy
to share their secrets.
-Don't wanna do this.
-We have to.
Neither of us have secrets
worth dying for.
[indistinct whispering]
May the truth set you free.
[instrumental music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[Jack speaking disorientedly]
Tobias Eaton,
you are accused of conspiring
with your fellow Dauntless
in the attack on Abnegation.
Is this true?
Conspiring, no.
But I did attack.
I was in a simulation
controlled by Jeanine
and the rest of the Dauntless
that she recruited.
Tris found me.
She managed to break me free
from the simulation,
and then together we...
Together we fought our way out.
So you're saying
that Jeanine orchestrated
this attack?
Yes.
One last thing.
If you suspected that Jeanine
had corrupted Dauntless,
why didn't you just leave?
Why did you stay?
[breathing heavily]
I wanted to leave.
But I fell in love
with Tris Prior.
And I couldn't leave her.
Thank you for your candor.
[all]
[Jack]
Tobias Eaton,
this trial is concluded.
And you are absolved of guilt
in the attack on Abnegation.
Miss Prior, if you would.
May the truth set you free.
Tris Prior,
Mr. Eaton said you managed
to free him from the sim.
[Tris] Yes.
[Jack] So you were never
under the simulation yourself?
No.
How is that possible?
Because I'm Divergent.
[people murmuring]
I see.
So you never harmed
any of your fellow Dauntless
or the Abnegation?
[breathing heavily]
I did.
Both.
Who?
[sniffling]
My mom.
Um...
I watched her die first.
And then my dad.
They were killed
trying to save me.
And... I... [straining]
Miss Prior,
the more you resist,
the more painful
the serum will be.
[Tris groans]
My friend...
I killed my friend.
He was trying to shoot me.
And I...
[sobbing]
I shot him first.
What was his name?
I can't.
Will.
I killed Will.
'Cause that's what happens
to people when they get
close to me.
They get hurt or they die.
I can't forgive myself.
Thank you for your candor.
[all]
[sobbing]
Tris.
I'm sorry, all right?
-I told you that
I didn't wanna do that.
-Hey...
-Christina...
-Go.
Go.
[woman groaning]
[electronic voice]
Abnegation sim complete.
Dauntless sim initiating.
[man]
Ma'am, the Divergent's
vitals are dropping.
If we don't pull her
out of the sim soon,
we'll lose her.
You'll stop when I say so.
She's gonna do it.
She's gonna pass the sim.
[electronic voice]
Dauntless sim failed.
[man]
Divergent Test Subject Six
is no longer viable.
[sighs]
All right, shut it down.
Wasting our time.
I've been assuming that
all Divergents are the same.
But some are
much stronger than others.
Assign all
non-essential personnel
to the Divergent detail.
We need to look harder.
We need to find that
very special one.
Where's your scary boyfriend?
Probably off
doing scary boyfriend things.
Mind if I join you?
I love heights.
From up here, it all just seems
so much smaller, you know?
I know it sounds crazy,
but sometimes
I think I see lights
out beyond the wall.
I know they say it's all just
wasteland out there, but...
We can't be the only ones left.
-Can we?
-[gunfire]
[glass shattering]
Let's go!
-Closest weapons?
-Ground floor.
-[gasps]
-[gunfire continues]
[women screaming]
[gunfire]
[man]
Floor's clear. Movin' down.
[gunfire in distance]
[women screaming]
-Mommy? Mommy?
-[Tris shushes]
[shushes]
They hurt my mommy?
Look, I got one, too.
See? It's okay.
It's just the thing that
made everybody go to sleep.
Okay, I need you
to do me a favor.
I need you to go to the top
of those stairs up there.
Don't come down
until your mommy comes
to get you.
-Don't come down?
-Don't come down.
Can you do that?
Be brave, okay?
Okay. Go.
[panting]
[gunfire]
[women screaming]
Hey.
Why are we the only ones awake?
Because we're Divergents.
Come on, I need your help.
We have to open this.
Uriah, I need your help.
Go.
[Eric] Hey!
Look who decided to show up.
It's really good
to see you again.
All right, folks.
Nothin' to be nervous about.
Just a little
routine inspection.
Then we can all go back
to our business.
Hello.
-[electronic voice]
Divergent, 10 percent.
-Hmm.
Shit.
You're almost normal.
That's boring.
-[gunshot]
-[gasps]
That is not
part of the mission.
[Eric] So what?
Far as I'm concerned
the rest of them
are still outlaws.
Let's just
wrap this up quickly.
The others
are gonna be awake soon.
-Hi, sweetie.
-I shouldn't...
[electronic voice]
Divergent, 40 percent.
I'm afraid
it's not you, either.
The lady said I shouldn't...
The lady said
I shouldn't come downstairs.
Guess you should've listened.
[Tris grunts]
[Max] Enough.
We still have to test her.
Eric!
[panting]
Jeanine told us
that we have to test everyone.
[groans]
[electronic voice]
Divergent, 100 percent.
I'll be damned.
-What?
-She's what
we've been looking for.
Bullshit.
[electronic voice]
Divergent, 100 percent.
Get her in a vehicle.
I'll alert Jeanine.
If you think you got lucky,
you're wrong.
You're gonna wish I killed you.
[man 1] Drop it. Don't move.
-Drop your weapon!
-[man 2] Get down.
-Let me see your hands.
-[man 3] Right there!
Hey.
Thank you.
It's lucky you got
that gun, Four.
[sighs]
Oh, we both know
you were never much
without one.
[screams]
[Four grunting]
[Eric groans]
You think she's safe now?
You're wrong.
Jeanine's never gonna stop
searching for you.
Why? What does she want
with her?
Tell me.
Look, all I know is
she's exactly what
Jeanine needs.
She's the perfect subject.
[gun cocks]
Was that supposed to scare me?
You're responsible
for the death
of hundreds of people.
You know the punishment
for that.
Listen...
I've found a way to live
with the blood on my hands.
But can you?
-[gunshot]
-[body thuds]
Why won't they come out?
All I know is it put me
in a sleeping sim,
and then I woke up
to all hell breaking loose.
Hec! Don't play with it.
[indistinct conversations]
You all know what this means.
Thank you. For helping us.
I wish I could do more.
I had no idea
Jeanine was capable
of something like this.
It's time we fight back.
We don't have the numbers.
We will.
Once we get to Factionless.
[woman on PA]
Strict curfew
until further notice.
[Four] You heard Eric.
Jeanine's never gonna stop
coming after you.
It's our only option.
[Jeanine] Tris Prior.
Of course. It had to be her.
Is she still off the grid?
Yeah. But I think
I found a solution.
It's Peter. Right?
Yeah. And, Jeanine,
can I just say that
it is truly an honor
to finally meet you in person?
[Four]
Congratulations, Mother.
You got your war.
I know you wish
there was another way.
But there isn't.
I'm the lesser of two evils.
Is that it?
You'd better be.
[Jeanine] Tell me,
why did you surrender
to Erudite?
What do you want?
I would like a position
in your regime.
Ideally, I would like
a position with some
advancement opportunities.
[chuckles]
I may be Dauntless,
but I'm not just a meathead.
No offense, Max.
[scoffs]
Prove your worth to us.
Then we can discuss
your ambitions.
Great. When do I start?
Let's talk about
your friend Tris Prior.
How do I flush her out?
[Peter] Simple. The girl's
a walking bleeding heart.
She was born Abnegation.
That's her weak spot.
You just have to know
how to press it.
[Lauren] Help! Come quick!
[man]
It's coming from up there.
[woman] Christina!
Please, help!
-[indistinct conversations]
-Somebody do something!
[boy 1] Look!
[boy 2] On the ledge!
[all] The traitor Tris Prior
must be surrendered to Erudite
or every day
more deaths will follow.
Go!
[all] Hand over Tris Prior
or every day
more deaths will follow.
Hand over Tris Prior
or every day
more deaths will follow.
[woman] Get down!
Hector! No!
[all] Hand over Tris Prior
-or every day
more deaths will follow.
-Christina!
No!
[people gasp]
[thud]
[panting]
Christina! Christina!
[struggling] Tris, help me.
Tris!
[Christina panting]
It's okay.
We removed this
from the body of the suicide.
Marlene. Her name was Marlene.
I'm sorry. Marlene.
It's a very sophisticated
sim serum injector.
It also has a radio transmitter
in its head.
How do we get them out?
I don't know.
This tech was built
to defend itself.
This tendril wraps around
the nearest major artery.
Try to remove them
and they kill the host.
[all murmuring]
-[Christina] So what do we do?
-Tori has to find a way
to neutralize the disks
before we do anything else.
[Edgar]
Or we could do
the logical thing.
And we hand her over.
Nobody knows
about this alliance.
We have to protect
that advantage.
If we hand Tris over now,
might buy us some time.
[indistinct chatter]
[Four]
I think it's a good idea.
-[woman] Get rid of her!
-Damn right.
Except you'll have to go
through me first.
-Me, too.
-[all] And all of us.
[all clamoring]
Hey! I ain't the one
with the time bomb
in my arm.
[man] Yeah!
[all shouting indistinctly]
[Tris sniffling]
I know what you're thinking.
But I'm not
gonna let you do it.
I can't let anyone else die
because of me.
No one else is gonna die
because of you.
Tori's gonna find a way
to disable the disks...
-And if she doesn't?
-Then... Then...
Then if she doesn't,
we figure it out.
Together.
You know I'm just one person.
I'm not worth it.
No, you are worth it.
You are worth it to me.
I love you.
[soft music playing]
[Jeanine]
...plays a critical role in
maintaining the social order.
But this harmony we've achieved
is now under attack.
This city may be
safely enclosed
behind a vast wall.
But make no mistake,
that wall alone
does not ensure our security.
It is up to us,
every one of us,
to remain vigilant
in identifying and isolating
any potential threat
to our stability.
There are individuals
hiding among us
who must be contained.
So permit me to address
the objections
of my fellow faction leaders.
I am aware that
there have been some concerns
about the unavoidable raid
on Candor.
-So let me be clear.
-[alarms blaring]
The harboring of Divergents
by any faction
cannot be tolerated.
Very soon,
I will be presenting
what I believe to be
no less than a mandate
from The Founders themselves.
And this will, I have no doubt,
validate the measures
I'm taking to keep the peace.
And provide the instructions
that will allow us
to eradicate
the Divergent crisis,
once and for all.
Where are you going?
Tris left. She's gone.
What? When?
-Last night.
-Wait.
[gun cocking]
Tobias!
People look to you
for leadership.
You can't just abandon them.
Tobias!
[door opens]
[Peter] Wow.
I have to admit, I'm impressed.
I mean, I knew that
you were dumb,
but I didn't think
that you were dumb enough
to actually come down here
and turn yourself in.
The killings have to stop.
Well, that just goes to show
that you can take the girl
out of Abnegation,
but you can't take
the Abnegation outta the girl.
Let's go.
Once a stiff,
always a stiff, right?
What is this?
This is the only reason
why you're alive, Tris.
Man, I love knowing stuff
that you don't.
Need you to open up
that box, Tris.
The only way to open that box
is to pass the sims
of all five factions.
But the only people that
have tried to do it so far
have died. [laughing]
Oops.
I don't think
I was supposed to
tell you that.
Oh, well.
No pressure.
[Jeanine] Remarkable.
Chances of it being you,
of all people.
Nearly defies
the laws of probability.
As remarkable
as the amount of people
you've managed to murder.
Dark times
call for extreme measures.
You may find it
hard to believe,
but I am serving
the greater good.
Step up on the disk, please.
[gun cocking]
[Peter groans]
[panting]
Ma'am?
-Hmm?
-[Peter groaning]
Oh.
Stop the suicides
or I swear I will shoot him.
That's okay.
You can kill him if you want.
We have plenty of guards.
What?
[yells]
[grunts]
[panting]
I'm guessing you need me alive
for this to work.
Right?
[shouts] Right?
[Caleb] Beatrice.
Caleb.
-I--
-Don't engage the subject.
Conditions are already
less than optimal.
Oh, my God.
If I do this,
the suicides stop?
No. The suicides will continue
until you succeed
and pass all five sims.
Should be incentive enough.
Good luck.
[machine powering up]
[yelping]
[sighing]
Let's begin.
[electronic voice]
Initializing Dauntless sim.
Mom.
[gasps]
Tris, help me!
[Tris] What? Mom!
[birds cawing]
-[Natalie] Tris?
-[Tris] Mom!
[Tris grunts]
[screams]
[groaning]
[panting]
[man] Her heart rate is rising.
Keep her in play.
[Tris grunting]
[Tris] Mom!
[birds cowing]
-[Natalie] Tris!
-[Tris] I'm coming!
[Tris yells]
[groaning]
Mom!
I'm coming.
[Tris screams]
[Natalie] Tris, help me!
-[screaming]
-Hold on.
Hold on!
Tris.
[electronic voice]
Dauntless sim complete.
[panting]
[Tris] Mom.
I miss you so much.
Mm-hmm. I know you do.
But I'm still with you.
You need to be strong now.
Tell me you're gonna be strong.
I'm trying.
You can do this.
I know you can.
You're brave.
Braver than anyone.
I'm not brave, Mom.
I pretend that I am.
And I want people
to think that I am,
but I'm not.
I'm really, really scared.
That maybe we are actually
what's wrong in this world.
Divergents.
I never wanted any of this.
You and Dad and Caleb
and then Four.
And I can't help but think
that if I was normal,
we would all still be together.
Mom, I don't wanna be
a Divergent anymore.
I just wanna feel safe again.
[Tris sobbing]
-[Tris gasping]
-[electronic voice]
Candor sim complete.
[gunfire]
[gasps]
[panting]
Four.
-You're here. Yeah?
-Yeah, I am.
You're here.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Secure the hallway.
All right.
Let's get you outta here.
-You good?
-Yeah.
-[gun cocking]
-[gasps]
[cocks rifle]
Stop. Let him go.
Wait, you're not
gonna shoot me?
Once a stiff, always a stiff.
[sighing]
[gunfire]
Go!
Four, how did you get
past security?
[Four] You know me.
Scary boyfriend skills.
[sighs]
What is it?
You weren't there.
You didn't even hear that.
Tris, we need to leave now,
all right?
I'm sorry, Four.
-What?
-I'm sorry I didn't tell you
that I was gonna go.
I wanted to say goodbye
and I just didn't know how.
I didn't know how.
What are you talking about?
So even though
I didn't get to say it
in real life
at least I get to say it now.
-Even if it is just in the sim.
-Tris, we're not in a sim.
Don't you think I'd know
if I was in a sim?
[Tris] Four,
you're not in a sim.
You are the sim.
Wait, wait.
[electronic voice]
Erudite sim complete.
[Jeanine]
There's only Amity now.
[Peter]
She hasn't passed
Abnegation yet.
Yes, she has.
When she spared your life.
This girl is extraordinary.
She's tested positive
for four factions in one day.
[chuckles]
No one's gotten that far.
[machine beeping]
[man] We've got a problem.
She's crashing.
We have to rest her.
Sure you're not letting
familial attachment
cloud your judgment?
See for yourself.
[panting]
Very well.
Detach the subject.
Good work, everyone.
We'll resume tomorrow.
[door opens]
You were never planning on
going back to Abnegation,
were you?
I had to do
what I felt was right.
Our parents
would be ashamed of you.
Well, maybe not.
I mean, I am willing
to sacrifice you,
the only family I have left,
the only person I love,
in order to preserve
what's best for everyone else.
What's more selfless than that?
What does Jeanine think
is in that box, Caleb?
It's a message
from The Founders.
But the box was to be opened
only if the Faction System
broke down,
which is why it requires
someone like you to open it.
You are living proof
that the Divergent problem
has grown beyond all control.
Do you even hear
what you're saying right now?
No one thinks it's your fault
that you were born this way.
Jeanine murdered
an entire faction, Caleb.
That faction
could no longer be trusted.
She killed our parents.
Our parents brought that
on themselves.
What are you talking about?
The box?
It was in their house.
They were the ones hiding it.
All of those lives
could have been spared.
Seems we didn't know
our parents as well
as we thought we did.
[door opens]
All right.
Family reunion's over.
It's time to go.
I got a little surprise
for you, Tris.
-[Tris] Four?
-Tris!
-Tris! Tris!
-Four! Four!
-Tris!
Stop! Four!
Four!
[screaming]
Stop, stop!
[Tris groaning]
I gather your brother
explained to you how vital
the work you're doing here
is to the future of this city?
Please, just let Four go.
If his well-being
is of such concern
then you should focus
on the task at hand.
[Jeanine sighs]
Tell me,
do you appreciate irony?
You tested positive
for Erudite,
so you must have
the intellectual capacity.
Irony?
For instance, right now
you're filled with hate.
But you need to pass
an Amity sim.
[laughing]
Then there are other ironies
at work, too.
-Such as the fact that
your cherished mother--
-Don't.
Who you so dauntlessly saved
in the sim
is the reason you're
in this mess to begin with.
You're the reason
I'm in this mess.
Then there's
the most poignant irony
of all...
-Stop.
-That Natalie Prior
not only died
trying to protect the data that
I now have in my possession.
Because you stole it from her.
You killed her for it!
Data that she
so selfishly withheld.
But her own daughter.
Her beloved Divergent Tris
-is going to be the one
to deliver it to me.
-I said stop!
Therefore, your mother's death,
just like
your boyfriend's death,
will mean absolutely nothing.
[rumbling]
Don't pull her out.
Not yet.
[Jeanine] No.
No.
Bring her back!
No!
Bring her back! Come on!
Come on.
Bring her back!
[man on PA]
Test Subject Seven
is no longer viable.
[panting]
[whispering]
I really thought
you were the one.
We'll just...
We'll just have to resume
our search.
Find solace
in your faction, Caleb.
We're your family now.
Jeanine wanted me
to show you this.
[inhales]
[gasping]
Hey, Four.
Maybe do that thing you do?
[all grunting]
[Peter] Hey, Four, come on,
that was pretty good, right?
First, I swiped a paralytic
from the infirmary.
Then I shot her up
when she was all
freakin' out about you.
I mean, I told these guys
I was pretty smart.
Guess they should've listened.
You're real.
Yeah, I'm real.
What are you doing here?
You die, I die.
Okay, guys, come on.
Let's go, seriously.
We can do that later.
-It's okay.
-Yeah.
[panting]
-Thank you, Peter.
-Yeah, whatever.
Now we're even, stiff.
All right. Come on, let's go.
Before Jeanine realizes
you're still alive.
-No, no, no.
-What?
The box.
We have to get the box.
What, are you kidding me?
Now's not the time
for a souvenir, Tris.
Four, you have to listen to me.
It's not what
Jeanine thinks it is.
I know it's not. My mother
would have destroyed it.
We have to get it.
Peter, is there
another way into the lab?
I mean, I'd have to go
into the control room
to disable all the doors.
Okay, good, then do that.
-Okay. Right now?
-Yeah.
You just chose our side,
whether you meant to or not.
If you wanna survive,
make sure we do.
Let's go.
Fuck.
[indistinct chatter on PA]
[rifle cocks]
[man]
Ma'am, our current assessment
with other possible candidates.
[Jeanine] Correct. Female.
And we have the two males
introduced to you before.
No guns. It'll draw
too much attention.
Hey.
Hold up.
[grunting]
-[electronic voice]
Access denied.
-Come on, come on.
-[electronic voice]
Access granted.
-All right, let's go.
Come on.
-Is that it?
-Yes.
All right, grab it
and let's go.
-[panting]
-[the box beeping]
[alarms blaring]
[man on PA] Security breach.
Security breach. Lockdown.
What's going on?
-What's going on? What is it?
-There's been a breach
in the sim room.
[Jeanine] Get me a remote feed.
I wanna see
who the hell is in there.
The cameras are down
in the sector, too.
I'm sending guards there now.
Let's go.
[Jeanine]
Bring up every cell. Now.
Show her.
Tori finally found a way
to get 'em out safely.
[Evelyn] How many others?
Every last one.
Let's go.
[soldier]
South corridor, 40 yards down.
Tris?
Tris, come on, we gotta move.
Tris, we have to move.
I can't. I can't.
My mom died protecting
whatever's inside of this.
I have to open it for her
and I think I know how.
Tris, if we don't leave now,
we're not gonna get outta here.
I have to do this first.
Look, I know
it doesn't make any sense,
but you have to
trust me, please.
With my life, apparently.
[man on PA] All security teams,
be advised, breach in...
Do it.
[Max] Flank right.
Don't move! [grunts]
[electronic voice]
Initializing Amity Sim.
[Jeanine] Back again, are we?
You're an even bigger fool
than your mother.
Say whatever you want to me,
Jeanine.
But I'm not gonna fight you.
-How very Amity of you.
-I mean it.
-I'm not gonna fight you.
-Of course you're not.
You're gonna fight her.
The one you really hate.
What are you?
[scoffs]
I'm you, Tris.
I'm the real you.
[panting]
I'm not gonna fight you.
I'll make you fight me.
You're not me.
I am. I'm what they see
when they look at you.
You killed Will.
And your parents.
You're deadly.
That's enough!
No one's gonna love you, Tris.
They're never even
gonna miss you.
This world will be
better off without you.
One less Divergent
ruining everything.
And no one will ever,
ever forgive you
for what you've done.
You're wrong.
[Tris sighs]
Because I will.
[scoffs]
[gunfire]
[sighs]
[electronic voice]
Amity Sim complete.
-Wait!
-No! Stop!
[electronic voice]
Initializing message.
[sparkling]
Hello.
I come from outside the wall.
Where we have all
but destroyed each other.
We designed your city
as an experiment.
We believe it is the only way
to recover the humanity
we have lost.
And we created factions
to ensure peace.
But we believe there will be
those among you
who will transcend
these factions.
These will be the Divergent.
They are the true purpose
of this experiment.
They are vital
to humanity's survival.
If you're watching this now,
then at least one of you
is proof
that our experiment
has succeeded.
The time has come for you
to emerge from your isolation
and rejoin us.
We've allowed you to believe
that you're the last of us.
But you're not.
Mankind waits for you
with hope
beyond the wall.
[sighing]
[gasping]
-You Okay?
-Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
You were wrong about us.
We were never the problem.
We're the solution.
[bitter laugh]
Bury the box.
-What?
-No one sees it.
Ever.
Kill them both.
-No!
-[gunshot]
-[man 1] Drop it! Now!
-[man 2] Stop.
[man 1] Don't move.
Down!
Put your weapons down, now!
Drop them. Drop them.
Stay!
-[man 3] Put it down!
-[Edgar] Do not move.
Hello, Jeanine.
Evelyn?
Impressive.
Think we're gonna like it here.
Do you honestly think
the other factions
will stand for this?
Because you're so popular?
[scoffs]
Get her out of here.
When that message gets out,
it'll be the end.
What message?
You'll see. I'm gonna put it
on every monitor in the city.
[woman recording]
We have separated you
from the rest of us.
And we created factions
to ensure peace.
The time has come
to emerge from your isolation
and rejoin us.
We've allowed you to believe
that you're the last of us.
But you're not.
If you're watching this now,
then at least one of you
is proof
that our experiment
has succeeded.
Mankind waits for you,
with hope,
beyond the wall.
[victorious instrumental
music playing]
These will be the Divergent.
They are the true purpose
of this experiment.
They are vital
to humanity's survival.
You did it.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
-Yeah.
Everyone's staring at me.
You changed everything.
[sighs] What now?
Only one way to find out.
You ready?
♪ Arms to the ground ♪
♪ Far from the rivers ♪
♪ Somebody heal me
From my pain ♪
♪ Hands to the sky ♪
♪ I'm a dreamer ♪
♪ Somebody free me
From my chains ♪
It's been over 200 years.
Who knows what's out there?
You'll never find out.
[gunshot]
["Blood Hands" playing]
♪ Took a lonely feeling
Just to let the meaning ♪
♪ Sink like the sun goes down ♪
♪ Never close to heaven ♪
♪ Felt my feet were burning
From the same red hot ground ♪
♪ There's blood on my hands ♪
♪ There's blood on my hands
Yeah, there's blood ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Love came and went
Faster than a penny spent
In a slot machine ♪
♪ Nowhere near the devil
Just somewhere in between ♪
♪ You and me
Sworn to secrecy ♪
♪ And I'll curse the ground
Where you kneel ♪
♪ Till I grow my hair
To my heels ♪
♪ Spike your water your wine ♪
♪ There's blood on my hands ♪
♪ There's blood on my hands
Yeah, there's blood ♪
♪ Took a lonely feeling
Just to let the meaning ♪
♪ Sink like the sun goes down ♪
♪ Never close to heaven ♪
♪ Felt my feet were burning
From the same red hot ground ♪
["Never Let You Down" playing]
♪ Will you come along cause
I'm about to leave this town ♪
♪ In my eyes a waterfall
All I can hear a siren call ♪
♪ Could you be waiting
By the shore ♪
♪ Oh, I could drown
Without you ♪
♪ Will you be holding out
The line ♪
♪ When I fall? ♪
♪ I'll never let you down ♪
♪ Never let you down ♪
♪ Baby I will find you ♪
♪ Baby I can hear you call ♪
♪ Baby I can feel your heart ♪
♪ Baby I will find you ♪
♪ Just wait a little longer ♪
♪ Baby I can hear you call ♪
♪ I won't ever let you fall ♪
["The Heart Of You" playing]
♪ There is a darkness ♪
♪ A heaviness
That is concealed ♪
♪ Inside these boundaries ♪
♪ Inside a plain
Of frozen fields ♪
♪ There are no weapons ♪
♪ No sharpened blows
To be sustained ♪
♪ No only malice
And the tapping of the rain ♪
♪ But there's a dream I keep ♪
♪ I go in when I sleep ♪
♪ There's nothing they can do ♪
♪ Nothing can keep me
From the heart of you ♪
[vocalizing]
["Sacrifice" playing]
♪ I don't wanna be touched
By the fear in your eyes ♪
♪ I don't wanna be left
For my demons to find ♪
♪ When the leaves are gone
And the beating's sung ♪
♪ Brings the world bang drums ♪
♪ When the leaves are gone
And the beating's sung ♪
♪ Brings the world bang drums ♪
♪ Tell me you will hold me
In the golden afterlife ♪
♪ Yeah, you
You don't have to die
Alone tonight ♪
♪ I will find you
In a burning sky ♪
♪ Where the ashes
Rain in your mind ♪
♪ Ohh ohh
Sacrifice ♪
♪ Sacrifice ♪
♪ If we're closer
To the other side ♪
♪ And the heavens
All start to cry ♪
♪ Ohh ohh
Sacrifice ♪
♪ Sacrifice ♪
♪ If you start running away
Then there'll be
No where to hide ♪
♪ If you starting running away
there'll be no where to hide ♪
♪ I will find you
In a burning sky ♪
♪ Where the ashes
Rain in your mind ♪
♪ Ohh ohh
Sacrifice ♪
♪ If we're closer
To the other side ♪
♪ And the heavens
Are starting to cry ♪
♪ Ohh ohh
Sacrifice ♪
♪ Sacrifice ♪
["Carry Me Home" playing]
♪ Drop your weapons ♪
♪ Carry me home ♪
♪ Leave no defense ♪
♪ Let the waves wash over me ♪
♪ Carry me home ♪
♪ On the land or the sea ♪
♪ Close your eyes
Can you feel it? ♪
♪ Can you feel
The light intertwining? ♪
♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♪ Pick up all the pieces ♪
♪ Carry them home ♪
♪ Hold on and release us ♪
♪ Carry us home ♪
♪ I give it all to find you ♪
♪ And carry you home ♪
♪ It's easy to fade on
To fade on ♪
♪ To carry me home ♪
♪ It's easy to fade on
To fade on ♪
♪ To carry me home ♪
♪ It's easy to fade on
To fade on ♪
♪ To carry me home ♪