- Hey, hey Hey-hey-hey
- Let's sweat!
- Macho, macho man
- Macho man
- Come on!
- I've got to be
- That's right! Shake it, honey!
- A macho man
Macho, macho man
- Oh, yeah! Like a pony! I'm a pony!
- I've got to be a macho
Don't you feel like
a pony when you sweat?
- Oh, yeah! Yeah! Go!
- I've got to be
- Go! Do it! Come on!
- A macho man
Macho, macho man
Here we go! One! Two!
This is my favorite exercise!
Come on! Five!
- Macho, macho man
- Whoa!
- Macho! Macho! Ohh!
- I've got to be
- I'm a pony!
- A macho man
Come on. Let's go!
Do it! Come on!
- I've got to be a macho
- I'm vogueing! You can vogue!
Can you feel it?
I've got to be
- A macho man
- Ohh!
I'm going to have an aneurysm.
Ohh! My calves are burning!
This is our science department.
The genetics wing.
I'll remind you we are
in the vanguard of research.
Get Klump in here now.
- Professor Klump.
- Good mornin'.
- Hey, Professor!
- Good mornin'!
- Morning.
- Mornin'.
- Good morning, Professor Klump.
- Morning. How are you?
Mornin'.
Aaaaaah!
Oh, my goodness.
Professor Klump, the cages-
what happened?
That is most peculiar, Jason, because I
distinctly remember locking up last night.
I locked these cages, picked up
my portfolio and turned around-
Oh. Ha-ha-ha.
I must've grazed the switch.
Ha-ha.
Shelley's the only one
that didn't get out.
Oh. Good. I'll tend to Shelley.
You students take care of this.
Excuse me.
Hello, Shelley. How are you today,
my little powder puff?
Yeah. Yeah.
Sir?
You may want to look at
the latest test results.
I'm not sure if I'm
reading them correctly.
Three ounces. She's lost three
ounces since the last feed?
Must be some kind of mistake.
No, no, Jason. Her entire molecular
structure has been realigned.
We've done it.
This new formula's working.
It's actually reconstructed
Shelley's DNA.
She lost 20 percent
of her body fat in one feeding.
What if we upped the dosage?
No, one step at a time.
We don't want to jeopardize Shelley.
- We'll keep the feedings as scheduled.
- Okay.
Schedule. Excuse me.
I'm very late.
Students, we got a lot of work to do
and don't have much time to do it in.
Tryin' to win a grant here. So, as
Arsenio used to say, let's get busy!
- Comfy?
- Quite.
Anything I can get for you?
Juice? Coffee? Rack of lamb?
No, sir, I'm fine.
You, uh, did want to see me
about something, didn't you, sir?
Well, Professor Klump,
allow me to answer that question
by posing another.
- Why are you trying to destroy my school?
- Beg your pardon, sir?
- Do you know who Louise Vindovik is?
- Oh, surely, sir.
She's a lovely woman who
so generously donates
money to help fund our science department.
Ooh! Close.
Very close. But wrong.
See, she was a lovely woman, and she
used to fund our science department.
That was before she was hospitalized
for nearly swallowing a gerbil.
Not gerbil, sir.
A hamster.
Gerbils are more streamlined and
hamsters have a tendency to be fluffier.
The male hamster's scrotum has
a tendency to be disproportionately-
Never mind.
Those National Rifle people
are right.
If I had one now- bang.
Sir, I'd like to concentrate
on the positives.
What Ms. Vindovik witnessed
was 5,000 healthy hamsters...
bred from a genetically deficient
hereditary line.
It's actually very exciting.
Do I look excited, Klump?
Uh, no, you don't
look excited at all.
But maybe you might be holding it in,
your excitement,
not wanting to...
express it.
Now listen to me carefully,
you fat tub of goo.
For years you've single-handedly
alienated every wealthy donor we've had.
Air-conditioning schools
are outdrawing us!
We've lost so much money,
red is our school color.
Inner-city schools
have better computers than we do.
Bosnia wants to give us money!
I'm going to set up a
meeting with Harlan Hartley
Klump! Are you listening?
Uh, yes, sir. Yes.
Hartley is the last rich alumnus we've got.
And he's a science fan.
And he's considering donating
a $10 million grant to this school.
And I want that money, Klump.
Your job depends upon it.
I'll let you know how to handle it,
since I'll be watching you. Now go.
But, sir, I don't know
if you should
Ah-ah-ah.
See, right back there, just before
you said, "But, sir-" Right there?
That was the end
of the meeting.
Well, I guess
I'll leave.
You have a pleasant day.
Grace, the cream
has turned again.
Of all the equations you'll learn
during the course of your studies here,
this equation shall be,
I promise you,
the most helpful throughout
the course of your studies,
because this equation
fundamentally breaks down...
what DNA is composed of...
and what components of DNA-
I seem to have messed myself.
I haven't really messed myself.
I mean, I messed my shirt up.
But, uh, make sure you read chapter four
in your textbooks on genetics.
Gon' be a pop quiz
on Wednesday.
There's a pop quiz.
Pop quiz.
Professor Klump?
- Hello.
- Oh. Hi. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
I was looking for Professor Klump.
I'm him. I'm he.
I'm Sherman Klump-
Never mind. I do that all the time.
Makes the table look more festive,
and the kids enjoy it.
The yellow and green
and purple rolling around.
The table's more colorful and...
Would another time
be better? I could always...
No, no, don't be ridiculous.
I'm between classes
and I got a m-minute to chat.
- How can I help you?
- Hi. I'm Carla Purty.
- Hello, Miss Purty.
- I'm a grad student.
I'm teaching my first chemistry
class across the hall.
Okay. Mm-hmm.
I just had to come over
and introduce myself,
because I've followed your work
for many years, and I'm a big fan.
Oh, well, thank you very much.
I'm fatter...
uh, flattered that you've been
following my work the way you have.
A chemistry teacher. Chemistry sure
is important to have... chemistry...
to have and use it.
Chemically- Chemistry. Well-
It's been a pleasure meeting you.
Oh, the pleasure was
all mine, Miss Purty.
And, um, hope to
see you around.
Well, you can't miss me.
Have a good day.
You do the same,
Miss Purty.
Mm-mmm-mmm.
Now, that's fine.
She's fine.
Oh, this is so fabulous.
Ain't nothin' like gettin' together
with family and havin' a good meal.
Cletus, take this bowl.
It's hot.
Goddamn, Sherman, it's almost
like we don't see your ass no more.
Good to see you, son.
You think you too good to spend time
with your family every now and then?
I've been real busy, Ernie.
I don't want no potatoes.
Mashed potatoes give me gas.
You know in my day, Sherman, people
used to spend time with they family
on Sundays
and special occasions.
Come around
and pay their respects.
You mess around and miss
little Ernie's golden
years, you're gonna be mad at yourself.
Oh baby's got a little gas.
Here she goes. Y'all
better cover your plates.
Mama, have some water.
Grandma, you spit on me.
What you talkin' about, coverin'
your plates? Not tonight, Cletus.
- I'll kick yo' ass.
- Sherman.
I cooked all this food.
Is that all you gonna eat?
You supposed to eat that,
not scalp it.
Daddy, all the calories in the
chicken are found in the skin.
"Where all the calories is"? You know
where that come from? Watching that damn TV.
Every time you turn it on somebody
talkin' about lose weight, get healthy.
Everybody lookin' all anorexic, talkin'
about that's healthy.
I know what healthy is.
And I don't know why everybody tryin'
to lose weight in the first place!
Ain't everybody supposed to be
the same size. We're all different.
Big, small, medium, midgets.
You supposed to have all that.
Everybody wants to be the same
size, like that Oprah Winfrey.
She gon' lose her weight.
Wasn't nothin' wrong
with her. She was fine. Oprah was a fox!
She lose all that weight,
her head look all big.
skin hanging all over.
And Luther Vandross.
Nigger used to be the black Pavarotti.
Lost all that weight,
lookin' all ashy.
Oprah and Luther need to keep their
ass one weight, 'cause I'm confused.
Yes, I hope nothin's wrong with Oprah.
She doesn't look well.
There ain't nothin' wrong with Oprah.
I seen Oprah on Hard Copy last week.
Was the picture of health. Got her a tall,
young, strong gentleman named Steadman.
So handsome.
- Amazing grace
- She's my favorite out of all of 'em-
Jenny Jones, Marilyn Kagan,
Maury Povich.
Letterman, Leno.
Montel, Ricki Lake.
- I like Geraldo.
- Mike Douglas. Ohh, Mike Douglas.
You know, Mike Douglas used to
make me moist when I'd watch his show.
I admit it. Only white man
ever did that to me was Mike Douglas.
I would like to volunteer to take
this old bird out of her misery.
Cletus! Don't you dare
say that about Mama.
No, no, hold it.
You ain't gotta protect me from Cletus.
Come on, Cletus.
Come on over here. It ain't
but a short walk. Come on over.
You gonna limp back. You'll walk over,
but you're limpin' back.
But don't let the gray hair fool ya.
I ain't no easy win, nigger.
Your problem is, you don't work out.
Look. That's all muscle.
- Ohh!
- You fat. I'm muscle.
Ohh, look at my little b-
He's a little Hercules.
Show me your muscles
again. Ohh!
Hercules, Hercules,
Hercules, Hercules!
Once you work out, your metabolism starts
to speed up, you can eat anything you want.
- He's so strong.
- Recent studies have shown...
that certain people are genetically
predisposed to gaining weight.
Someday we might even
find a cure.
Only thing you need to study
is your ass.
- I got a big ass. Your mama got a big ass.
- Cletus!
You do have a big ass.
Asses is big in our family.
You need to get used to that.
I don't care what diet you go on.
You can sew up your stomach and your asshole
- you gon' always be fat.
AII I'm tryin' to say is scientific
breakthroughs are occurring all the time.
The only thing about to break through is
your ass through the seat of your pants.
Sherman, I think I do remember hearing
something on TV about colon cleansin'.
They say everyone
should have one.
I'm thinkin' about gettin' me an appointment
and gettin' my colon cleansed thoroughly.
You want your colon cleansed?
I'm gon' clean mine.
There. Now my colon is clean.
Squeaky clean.
Every time we have a meal, you break
gas. Don't break gas and destroy our meal.
You the one that brought up
colon cleansin'!
I did not say anything
about breakin' gas!
You can talk about puttin' a tube in
somebody's ass, but I can't break wind.
I didn't say nothin' 'bout puttin'
a hose up nobody's ass.
What you think a colonic is?
You think you run your
asshole by the car wash?
You're chokin' the baby.
As long as I pay the bills,
I do what I want at this table.
Case in point.
- Who that called my name?
- Yeah, I called you if your name is-
Keep insulting me.
I'll toss this between
the crack of your ass.
I can go all night.
I hope you fart
'til your asshole falls out.
Ohh, my baby too!
Oops. Now see what you made me do?
Goddamn it,
I messed up my pants.
- Damn, Daddy. You rotten.
- You got to clean 'em yourself!
Oh, Lord, this has been a fabulous,
wonderful, fabulous evening.
Look. Them dogs done
tore up my garbage.
Cletus, the dog's ripped
open the garbage again!
Shoot the damn dog!
- I'm not shootin' no dog!
- I'm tryin' to watch Roseanne!
- Thanks for dinner, Mama.
- Sherman, what's wrong with you?
Baby, you still worried
about what your father said in there?
Oh, son, listen to me.
You are special.
When the good Lord made you,
he made you beautiful inside and out.
You can do anything, Sherman.
All you got to do is believe
in yourself and you can do anything.
You're so handsome.
Gimme some sugar.
Love you, Mama.
Love you too, baby.
Nighty-night. Ohh, my baby.
Sherman, Sherman, Sherman.
Fabulous.
Cletus, come clean
this garbage up!
- I'm watchin' TV!
- Get your lazy ass up.
- Mind your own damn business!
- You lazy mother-
Professor?
Oh. Hi, C-
Uh, Miss Purty, um-
You caught me in the middle of a little
step aerobics I was doin' out here.
Ninety-eight, ninety-nine,
one hundred.
I looked your address up in the faculty
directory. I hope you don't mind.
No, not at all. What can I do for you?
Oh, well, I was, uh...
I was, um-
I was wonderin' if-
one night if, uh-
when you weren't busy-
You get a little hungry,
you might want to, you know, uh-
If you planned on going out to get
somethin' anyway, on an occasion like that,
you don't wanna
do that alone, so-
Professor, are you
asking me out on a date?
Yes. Yes, I am.
I'd love to.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's fantastic! We can
go any place you wanna go.
Just name it.
We'll go there.
Uh, there's a place my students
go to called The Scream?
The Scream?
- I mean, if that's too-
- Oh, no, no, no. I love to scream.
Who-o-o-oa!
Screaming's good for you.
Cleans the epiglottis.
Get all the phlegm and mucus
down. That's disgusting.
- Just tell me what night.
- How's Friday?
Friday night's perfect. The best night
of the week. Friday night at 8:00.
- Friday night at 8:00.
- Great. I'll see you Friday night.
We'll go to The Scream.
It'll be a scream at The Scream.
- All right, Professor, I'll see you then.
- Good night, Miss Purty.
Good night.
Yes!
Mmm. Yeah, Friday night
at The Scream.
Gonna scream-
Friday night Friday,
Friday, Friday Friday night
Friday, Friday, Friday
I got myself a date
Friday night at 8:00
And I will not be late
She might be my mate
That would be so great
Great, great, great
And I can hardly wait
Lilo, Peabo, Lou Rawls-
Teddy Pendergrass. Teddy P.
Number six! Yeah!
Whoo!
Close the door
- Let me give you what you been waitin' for
- Whoo!
- Baby, I got so much love to give
- Don't hurt 'em, Teddy P!
And I wanna give it all to you
I waited all day long
Just to hold you in my arms
And it's exactly like
I thought it would be
Me lovin' you
and you lovin' me
Ohh, you know you got-ta, got-ta,
got-ta close the door
Shut the hell up up there, goddamn it!
Sorry about that down there, Mr.
Wilson! Teddy P turned up a little loud.
Quiet down up there!
There is a thin person inside
each and every one of us!
So give yourselves a big hug and say,
"Yes, I can!" Do that for me!
Thighmaster Plus is designed
to give you better results quicker.
I lost ten pounds in two weeks.
Thanks, Megashake.
Aaaaaah!
You're not pathetic!
People, pounds do not
lose themselves!
You have to work,
work, work!
Everybody, up!
Come on! Up!
You too at home!
Everybody up and say:
- Yes, I can!
- Say it again!
Yes, I can!
Yes, I can! Yes-
- Quiet down, goddamn it!
- Sorry!
- Klump! Shut up!
- I can!
I'm so excited
And I just can't hide it
I'm about to lose control
and I think I like it
I'm so excited
And I just can't hide it
And I know, I know
I know, I know
I know I want you
We shouldn't even think
about tomorrow
Still hungry?
Sweet memories will last
a long, long time
We'll have a good time, baby
Don't you worry
And if we're still playin' around
- Boy, that's just fine
- Help.
Let's get excited
- We just can't hide it
- Still hungry?
Oh, no
I know, I know, I know
I know, I know I want you
I want you
Oooh-hoo
Maybe you should try
Jenny Craig.
Oh, I want to love you
Feel you
Wrap myself around you
- I want to squeeze you, tease you
- One hand on you!
- I just can't get enough
- Whoo!
And if you move real slow
I'll let it go
I'm so excited
Ooh-wee, and I just can't hide it
- No, no, no, no, no
- Yeah! Yeah!
- I know, I know, I know I know, I know I want you
- Yeah!
I want you
Look what you do to me
- Yeah!
- You got me burnin' up
Ohh-ohh-ohh-ohh now
Baby, I'm so excited
This is how we do it
Come on, come on, come on.
Right there.
This is how we do it
It's Friday night
and I feel all right
The party's here
on the west side
So I reached for my 40
and I turned it up-
- Oh!
- Excuse me. Hey!
- Professor K, how's it going?
- I'm good, David.
- What are you doin' here?
- Got a date.
You have a date?
Good luck, Professor.
Yeah, see you
next week now.
The guys and I
All the gangbangers-
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Sorry about that.
Oh! Oh! Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sorry about that. Excuse me.
Sorry about that.
Excuse me. Excuse me!
- Thank you.
- Wow, these are great seats, Professor.
Oh, yeah. Listen,
don't call me "Professor. "
Call me Sherman, all right?
Sherman.
Well, I'm glad
we did this, Sherman.
With a different type
of swing, you know
- Something for the honeys
- So am I.
- So am I!
- Something for the honeys
Here's the menu.
Ooh, summertime
No funner time
for me to kick it with you
To find something
someone-
- So you altered her genes?
- Yes, yes.
And if I hadn't done it, Shelley
would be in hamster heaven right now.
Sherman, you are
absolutely amazing.
We do what
we can, you know?
Got to keep on tryin'.
Got to keep on pushin'
Something for you
and you
And for you
and for you.
Let's go. Let's go.
- Montell Jordan!
- They were wonderful.
Let's keep
this show rollin'.
- Ladies and gentlemen, you've seen him...
- He was good.
on Def Comedy Jam many times.
Y'all give it up for my man
Reggie Warrington! Give it up!
Watch me
I got it, watch me
He sure is animated.
- Yeah
- What's up?
I said, "What's up?"
- Hey!
- Women be shoppin', baby.
Women be shoppin'!
You can't stop a woman
from shoppin', baby!
That's true.
Women do shop.
It is true.
See what we got in here tonight.
Oh, my God!
She's unbe-weave-able.
Look at this.
Look like a head full
of curly fries.
Hey, look at this white dude
right here.
"What is a weave exactly?"
Huh?
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Baby, no! She got
more extensions than AT&T.
- Excuse me. I'm gonna go to the rest room.
- Oh, boy, I'm hot!
Sorry about that, ma'am.
Let me pick that up for ya.
Ooo-ooo-ooh!
It's a full moon tonight!
I think I found where
they hid Jimmy Hoffa!
Excuse me.
Yeah, that's
a good one there.
You got more crack than Harlem.
Look at that!
Boy's so fat, every time he
turns around, it's his birthday!
Got to put his belt on
with a boomerang.
Va-va-va-va! Bang!
Ah, yeah. Okay, all right, now.
That's it. You got me.
- No, I ain't got ya yet. Should I get him?
- Yeah!
- Should I get him?
Oh, look at this.
He's with a woman too.
- Oh!
- Oh, no!
Who is sucking
whose titties over here?
Last time this brother felt a breast,
it was in a bucket of K.F.C.
Extra crispy!
Every time he goes to
Sea World, they pay him!
He must be on that
new diet, Slim Slow.
He go outside with a red shirt on, and
all the kids in the neighborhood say,
"Hey! Kool-Aid!"
Yeah, man, I bet I cut his fat ass open,
it'd bleed chocolate milk.
What would you do
for a Klondike bar?
Now we know what's eating
Gilbert Grape, don't we?
Thank you for dinner tonight, Sherman.
That was very sweet.
You're welcome.
Look, that comic tonight,
he was-
Sherman, you are
a brilliant man.
You have
a pleasant evenin'.
Good night.
His fraternity was having
this thing called Pig Day.
That's the only reason
he asked me out.
To make fun of you?
Why do we do this to ourselves?
Every time we get depressed,
we eat and eat and eat.
You go to the store and buy
those little candy bars in the bag,
and before you know it,
the whole bag is empty.
Then at the end, you feel
just like that bag. Empty inside.
Don't you?
It's okay. It's all right.
Just get it all out.
- Say, "Yes, I can. " Say that.
- Yes, I can.
Yes, we can.
Can we go to commercial?
- I want him prepped and ready immediately.
- Yes, Doctor.
Call Dr. Matthews. I'm going to need
a lot of help on this one.
Let's move it.
You know the routine.
- Get that crash cart here stat!
- Blood pressure: 140 over 90 and rising.
- We need that I.V. rig in now!
- I.V. rig comin' in.
- Give me four cc's of Ambethol.
- I don't know how much more he can take.
We need the E.K.G. cart
in here now.
- What's the status?
- He's getting fatter. We can't stop it.
- Oh, my God!
- He's gonna explode!
I'm getting out of here!
Nurse!
Wait! Wait!
Aaah!
What's goin' on?
Oh, my God! Get outta here!
Get outta here!
Hey, everyone, run for
the hills! It's Fat-zilla!
He look like
King Kong with titties.
Sherman! I brought you some
nice fried chicken, Sherman.
Oh, you look fabulous!
Oh, my God!
He's gonna blow!
Way to go, son!
That's my boy!
No!
Huh?
Shelley, you've been
the guinea pig long enough.
It's time to see if
this stuff really works.
Aah!
Aaah! Aaah!
Oh! Oh! I'm thin!
I'm thin! Look at my cheekbones!
I have cheekbones!
Yes! Look at my chest.
Look at my breasts.
I don't have breasts.
I'm an "A" cup.
I don't need a bra anymore.
Oh, God! I'm thin!
I'm thin!
I'm thin! I'm thin. I'm thin.
Nothin' but air there
Nothin' but air there My ass is
gone now I'm slim, slim, slim
Well, I'll be damned!
I can see my dick!
My dick! My dick,
my dick, my dick!
Oh, I feel good
- I can do stairs. I can do stairs.
- I knew that I would now
I am the stair master!
I feel good
I knew that I would now
You lookin' for any kind
of clothes in particular?
Spandex! AII Spandex!
Where's the Spandex section?
Oh! Spandex!
Like this!
I feel nice
- Like sugar and spice
- No titties. No titties.
No titties. Not you, me.
I'm talking about me.
My titties are gone. Your titties
are lovely. What's your name?
Everybody, I'm so thin.
I am thin. You ever feel thin?
I am thin! I am thin.
Hey, man, where's the apple pie?
When I hold you in my arms
I know that
I can do no wrong
And when I hold you
in my arms
My love won't do ya
no harm
- Tootsie Roll! Get your tootsie! Whoo!
- And I feel nice
Like sugar and spice
So nice, so nice
I got you
I'm thin!
- Excuse me.
- Hey!
- Is Professor Klump here?
- Professor Klump? Sherman, Sherman Klump.
Uh, no, he had to take care
of some things, Miss Purty.
So I'm runnin'
this thing here.
- Do I know you?
- Do you know me?
Sherman didn't tell you about me?
- No.
- Oh, man!
Isn't that like Sherman
to hog all the credit?
I'm Sherman's confidante.
Have you seen him today?
I was wondering...
if he was all right after everything
that happened at the club the other night.
Oh, Miss Purty,
it tore his chunky ass up.
It's strange that a man as intelligent
as Sherman has no confidence whatsoever.
Makes me sick sometimes to think-
I'm always telling the man,
"Sherman, no matter what,
you've got to strut.
You got to suck in
your gut and strut. "
- Me, personally, I don't have that problem.
- Doesn't seem like you do.
You're just too feisty and too fine.
Me and you need to hook up.
We need to go to The Scream tonight,
have a couple of drinks...
and strut our respective stuff
together.
I don't even know your name.
Hey, buddy, what the hell
happened here?
See? Everybody
knows Buddy.
The professor must have got
a little carried away last night.
Oh! Officer Dagg,
I'm glad you came up.
He told me to tell you personally,
please thank your wife Claire...
for bringing that
upside-down cake for him.
He ate every crumb of it.
And can you have someone from
janitorial clean up this mess, please?
Thank you, Officer Dagg.
Thank you.
Buddy.
Buddy. Is that it,
or do you have a last name?
Love.
You see, Miss Purty-
There comes a time in
a man's life when he has to-
Miss Purty, people have
a tendency in life-
To always want to rush into things.
What I'm trying to say...
is, uh, there's a right time
and place for everything.
Like I said, there's a right
time and place for everything.
Tonight would be a good time.
At The Scream would be
perfect to discuss it.
I'll see you tonight at 8:00.
Don't be late! Excuse me!
Whew.
Uh-oh.
Good morning.
Good morning, class.
Morning, students. Good
morning! Morning. Good morning.
Uh, uh, you students just review
what we went over yesterday.
Professor, we weren't
here yesterday.
Well, then, um,
review the day before,
and tomorrow we'll do today.
That's it.
- Sherman!
- Oh, Carla. How are you?
I've been looking for you
all morning.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Why you lookin' for me?
I feel bad what happened
at the club the other night.
It was my idea
to go to The Scream.
I've forgotten about that. You forget
too. That's over. Go have a nice day.
There's something else. I met a friend
of yours in your lab. Buddy Love?
Buddy Love.
He's quite a character, huh?
He asked me out,
and he said it was your idea.
Oh, did he?
Well, uh, I know you're new in town.
I thought it would be nice for a new
girl to get out, meet some people.
- Did you find him attractive?
- Honestly, yes.
He's very handsome and athletic, but I don't
feel comfortable talking to you about that.
You can talk to me about anything.
I want you to.
And I think you should definitely
go out with Buddy Love.
You do?
Absolutely. I don't think
there's anything wrong...
with two young people getting together
and having a good time.
So by all means,
do just that.
- You sure you're all right with that?
- Don't worry about me.
I'm just fine. In fact, I'll put in
a good word with you for Buddy.
Oh, my goodness. I'm so late.
Excuse me. I'll talk to Buddy.
You make it hard, long
soft, short
And be strokin'
I be strokin'
I strokin' through the east
and I'm strokin' through-
Hey, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Now you be careful.
If there's a scratch in the car,
there's a scratch
in your ass.
You are too fine to be givin' me
curbside service.
- I'm not. I'm leaving.
- We just got here.
No, you just got here. I've been
waiting for you for almost an hour.
They say anticipation
helps make the appetite grow stronger.
- Anticipate a night alone.
- Hey, hey.
Let's just have a meal together.
Why you leavin'? You want me to beg?
I'll get down on my knees. I'll beg you
in front of all these people.
Think I care if these people
are watchin'?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I want
the world to know that I was late!
And I'm sorry!
My car ran outta gas.
I needed fresh drawers.
My mother's sick. The car broke down.
- Buddy, get up.
- Hear me out. I am sorry!
I don't know why
this is happenin' tonight.
Of all nights this has
got to happen to me tonight.
- Okay.
- Why? Why!
- Okay!
- Why?
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Okay. Good. Let's eat.
I am so hungry. Hey, don't let the
tears fool ya. I'm a tooth chipper.
Six T-bones, five baked potatoes
and two servings of creamed spinach.
I have never seen anyone eat so much.
You are so lucky to stay so thin.
Luck has nothin'
to do with it.
It's a matter of recombinant
ribonucleic acids
unzipped by a radioactive guanine peptide.
Then, Then what does that mean?
I don't know. I'm trying to
sound extra intelligent.
Got ya!
You gonna eat that?
Alright. Guess who's
back in the house.
From Def Comedy Jam, my man,
Reggie Warrington. Give it up!
I hate this guy. I hate this guy.
He is so obnoxious.
Give the nigger a chance.
Watch me
It's your world, dog! I'm just
a squirrel tryin' to get a nut.
I've got somethin'
that makes me wanna shout
- What's up?
- What's up, nigger?
- I said, "What's up?"
- Didn't you hear me when I say, "Hey"?
Boy, women be shoppin'.
Women be shoppin'.
You cannot stop
a woman from shoppin'.
Let's see what I got
in the house tonight.
Oh, now, look at
this white guy right here.
You cannot tell me
he ain't got a small jammie.
Man, it's so small he needs
tweezers to take a piss.
He needs tweezers
to take a piss!
Tweezers on his dick!
Reggie's hot tonight. Uh-oh.
Look at this. Look at this.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
I can't breathe!
- Excuse me, brother.
- I can't breathe!
- Okay.
- Brother, man!
You almost killed me, man!
I had to give myself
the Heimlich.
You mind waitin' for
the punch line first, brother?
I'm sorry.
You're so funny.
You're so funny the way you take a person's
personal defects and flip it around.
Like you pick somebody in the
room and say, "Look at your foot,"
and everybody look at it
and start laughin'.
That's funny shit.
You're on your way!
You goin' to the top!
You're the next Lenny Bruce!
- Why, thank you. Thank you very much.
- That's genius.
That'd even work with me
doin' it to you.
If I say, look at Reggie's gums and teeth.
His mother had an affair with Mr. Ed.
See? Everybody's laughin'.
They can visualize your mother
in a barn with Mr. Ed.
Look what I'm doin', Wilbur.
Look at me!
You snappin' on me?
Are you snappin' on Reggie?
It's your teeth, Reggie.
I don't know whether to smile at you
or kick a field goal.
Hey, Reggie! It's good!
It's all good!
And, man, what's wrong with that
breath? I can smell it over here.
Reggie, your breath is so stink,
people look forward to your farts.
Breath smell like shit.
Do you smell shit?
I smell shit.
Oh! Oh!
You done did it now, boy.
I wasn't gonna say nothin'
'cause I like black people.
But it's time to attack black.
That's right. The gloves coming off.
Don't hurt me now!
Maybe it's time for Reggie
to lay into your mama.
- Whoo!
- Oh! Oh, yeah!
Maybe it's time for Reggie to
talk about your mama a little bit.
- You're the man, Reggie!
- Your mother's so fat,
she went to Sizzler's,
and the bitch got a group discount.
Uh!
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Aah! Ha! Ha!
Uh-uh!
Okay, fat jokes!
You want to do fat jokes?
All right.
Your mother's so fat,
the bitch need a Thomas Guide
to find her asshole!
All right! Wait, wait,
wait. Your mother's so fat,
after sex I rolled over twice,
and I'm still on the bitch!
Your mother is so fat,
she fell in the Grand Canyon
and got stuck!
Reggie's mama's so fat that the bitch
gets her toenails painted at Earl Scheib!
Earl Scheib!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Hey, hey, get off the stage, man.
You ain't in show business.
Reggie's mama
is so fat,
her blood type
is Rocky Road!
Isn't that somethin'?
Reggie's mother is so fat,
her belt size is equator!
Get it? Equator?
Let's get a big round of applause
for Reggie's mama's ass...
that brought us
so much joy tonight.
Yeah!
That's a big ass.
Enough! Silence!
I can't take this shit
no more.
Now, you done talked
about me enough, boy!
I tried to be peaceful, but now it's
time for Reggie to "karatasize" your ass!
- Whoo!
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, Reggie, I heard of dreadlocks,
but "shitlocks"?
That's not your hair.
Take that pile of shit off your head.
You go too far with the comedy.
Oh, oh- I- I-
Come on! Come on!
What's that?
Oh, yeah, it's my style, boy.
You didn't know Reggie studied.
- What style is that?
- This is called "Kick-Your-Ass Style," boy.
- Oh, shit.
- Reggie done studied on
the streets. Oh! Come on!
Oh! Oh! Aaah!
Oh, you quick, but I'm quicker.
- Watch my feet.
- Come on with it!
I'm gonna come on with it.
I'm gonna... Ha! Hey! Aaah!
- Oh, damn!
- Ladies and gentlemen,
me and Reggie want to send one out to a
very special lady in the house tonight.
Lovin' you is easy
'cause you're beautiful
Do-un-do-un-doo-doo
Reggie?
Let go.
That was pretty.
Ladies and gentlemen, Reggie has left
the building. Thank you, and good night.
Oh, stop it! Stop it! Now,
thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you so
- Oh, please, please, come on now.
Hey, who pinched my ass? Cut it
out. Ha-ha-ha-ha! That's good.
All right. Thank you. Can you get the
bill for me? Thanks, man. Too much!
That was amazing.
I can't believe you did that.
Well believe it, because
"Amazing" is my middle name.
I only wish Professor Klump
was here to have seen it.
Listen.
This is our moment. I don't wanna
ruin it with talks of Sherman.
You know, your eyes,
there's something...
very familiar about them,
as if I already know you.
You know, I feel the exact same way
about you, Miss Purty.
Mmm. Miss Purty,
let me tell you.
That kiss was probably the most
wonderful kiss I've ever-
What I meant to say was that, uh-
- Your lip.
- What?
- Your lip is swollen.
- My lip?
- Yes.
- Oh, my lip! Oh.
That happens every time I-
What kind of lipstick do you have on?
Chanel.
That happens every time I
have Chanel lipstick on my lips.
An allergic reaction.
Oh. It's giving me gas too.
You have to go catch a cab.
I gotta go to the drugstore
and get some Benadryl and Kaopectate.
Excuse me. Have a
pleasant evening. Bye-bye!
Buddy! Buddy, wait!
Oh, man.
- Hey, Professor Klump is here?
- Yeah.
- Where is he?
- Uh, there he is, right there.
- That guy gave you this credit card?
- Yup.
That's not Professor Klump.
- That's not his credit card. Hey!
- What?
Hey! Hey!
Okay, fella, what are you doing
with the professor's credit card?
Where'd you get it? I'm sorry. Perhaps
you need the money more than I thought.
Aaah!
Oh, my God!
That's a bus!
You're gonna kill us, man!
What the hell is the matter-
Oh, man! This is
Freddy Krueger shit, man!
Professor?
Hello, Jason.
What's happening?
First time we had to use one of these
without an accident.
The class left
20 minutes ago.
Dean Richmond!
Oh, hello, sir.
You caught me in the middle
of an experiment I was doing.
I was trying to see how the students would
respond to a teacher-less environment.
Teacher-less environment.
New field of research for you?
- Uh, yes, sir.
- Interesting. Always thinking.
That's good, Klump. Let me know your
results. Would you mind explaining this?
Oh! Yeah, well, um,
my car's in the shop, so-
So you put a $47,000 luxury car
on your faculty account.
Initially, I- I requested a Yugo,
and this is all they had.
If it's all they had,
it's all they had.
After all, men like us
can't walk around now, can we? Hmm?
Come on.
Oh, well, well. I'm glad
you're takin' it like that, sir.
I thought you was gonna get
angry and start screamin'...
and hollerin',
and maybe even fire me.
Whoo!
Oh, Sherman, Sherman. In the end
we know so little of each other, hmm?
No, my friend, I've got
bigger fish to fry.
I spoke to Harlan Hartley.
He's offering that tiny trinket that
could save your entire research program.
- Oh, yes. Absolutely.
- I set up a meeting with him.
He wants to hear your
grant proposal personally
Friday, the Ritz, dinner, 8:00 sharp.
Well, sir, I think that's
a wonderful idea, sir. Absolutely.
And I promise you, I will not let you down.
You won't.
I know you won't.
I know you're going to be there,
and you're going to be great.
In fact, I know you're
going to be perfect.
- Do you know how I know all these things?
- How's that?
I know them, because if
you're not perfect, never
mind the yelling and the
screaming and the firing.
If anything goes wrong
for any reason,
I'm going to kill you.
I don't mean that as a euphemism.
I'm going to literally kill you.
I'm going to strangle you
and choke off your air supply...
until you pass away.
Ooh, okay.
'Til Friday, then.
It's a date.
Sir, this is incredible.
It's, it's a complete metabolic
transformation. How did it happen?
- Was it an accident?
- No, I did it to myself, Jason.
You did? Why?
If it was for the grant, the data
with Shelley was already so compelling.
Well, I have compelling
reasons of my own, Jason.
I have a case of infatuation
of sorts with Miss Purty.
Professor, if you feel this way
about Carla, why don't you tell her?
It'd be a lot simpler
than transforming into-
This guy's testosterone levels
are right off the charts.
He was mean last night.
It was so unlike you.
- You know, I did feel that.
- Sir, you can't control him.
Jason, you have no idea
what it feels like to be Buddy Love.
It's indescribable.
It's just wonderful!
The way people talk to him and
treat him, and the way she looks at him.
But he's dangerous.
He almost killed us last night.
We should be concentrating on getting
the grant proposal to Harlan Hartley.
This is nuts!
I guess you're right, Jason.
I never have behaved like this before.
But on the other hand,
I've never been in love before.
Ever.
- Afternoon, Carla.
- Hi, Sherman.
- How are you doing today?
- Pretty good.
I come over to see how things
were going with you and Buddy.
I wish I knew.
We went out last night. It was great.
We had such a wonderful time.
And then all of a sudden
he runs out of the club.
He has some allergic reaction.
- I don't even know if he's all right.
- He's fine.
He told me that his lip swelled up, he
put ice on it and the swelling came down.
- Kinda strange, huh?
- Well, did he even ask about me?
Did he say why he didn't call me
and let me know he was all right?
Carla, Buddy's kind of unreliable.
He's kind of what you call a "here
today, gone tomorrow" kind of fellow.
- Oh, I see.
- Mm-hmm.
So he had you talk to me
because he's not interested anymore.
- No, it's nothing quite like that.
- Look.
I know what it feels like
to be brushed off, and it's okay.
This is all my fault. I should've never
encouraged you to go out with Buddy.
Sherman, you have been so sweet.
I'll just have to forget about him.
I'll see you later.
Carla.
I was wonderin' if, uh,
I could talk to you
about you and I for a second.
I was-
I was wonderin' what
you were doin' later, 'cause...
the family gonna get together.
She made a meal and...
we gonna be eatin', so I figured if you
not doin' anything for dinner,
we'd love to have you,
if you want to come over for dinner.
We'd love to have you
over for dinner.
I'd love to.
- Would you, now?
- Yes, I would.
Should we call and make sure there's
going to be enough food?
I don't think that's
going to be a problem.
There's nothing
like being with family!
I am hungry. Come on now.
- Carla, where are you from?
- Chicago.
- Oh, Chicago! We have family there.
- Windy City, huh?
I was workin' on a skyscraper in Chicago
once and my lunch blew off the 27th floor.
Yeah, I figure your fat ass would remember
somebody's sandwich flyin' off a building.
Oh, baby, eat some bread.
Miss Purty, are you and Sherman
havin' relations?
- That's a good question.
- Uh, no, Grandma.
It's not like- like that.
We're colleagues.
- Oh.
- We just work together.
That's how it start out- colleagues.
Me and your grandfather
was colleagues.
Next thing you know he's on top of me
in the shed, pumpin' and a-sweatin'.
- It's not like that.
- Will you hush up?
You never brought a girl home. The
least you can do is let us talk to her.
Yeah, I'd like to get to know her
a little better myself.
Ain't nothing wrong with havin'
relations. Don't be ashamed of that.
Relations is beautiful. When I was young
I used to always have relations.
Every night, if a nice gentleman
bring me flowers and candy,
take me to a movie,
show me a lovely evenin',
then I would take him home
and give him hot, lovely relations.
Relations is a beautiful thing.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Especially two young people.
- That blowhole.
- Cletus!
Sometimes when I'm
alone, I relate to myself.
I can relate.
Oh, Mama.
I don't wanna hear this
shit while I'm eatin'.
- Cletus!
- I'm gonna kill you later.
- Carla, do you like children?
- Yes. Oh, that's wonderful.
I can't wait for Sherman
to bring me home some grandbabies.
I know you're gonna enjoy making them
babies. Got those childbearing hips.
Baby'll pop right out.
Your family got any money?
I ain't payin' for no big-ass wedding.
I know a wonderful minister.
What religious background are you?
I still got my wedding dress.
If you want it, I'll take it in.
You'd look so lovely in it.
It's white, though.
Can you wear a white wedding dress,
young lady?
Now, Sherman,
you can wear a white tuxedo.
'Cause you know Sherman- Sherman
has never had relations.
Mama, you gonna
embarrass my baby.
- I hope you got a strong back.
- Oh, look at my baby blushin'.
When you get all that man, and release
all that that's been built up...
for 35 years-
Just wantin' and wantin'
and wantin'!
Whoo! Might make
your head blow off.
Pop goes the weasel!
I got my own self hot
tellin' that story.
Pop goes the weasel,
'cause the weasel say "pop"!
You gonna get married
here or in Chicago?
Do you cook? 'Cause somebody's
got to feed my Sherman.
Yeah, I know a wonderful church
down there on Main Street,
but they won't marry you
if you're a lesbian.
Not that I have anything
against lesbians. I love lesbians.
- Lesbians is cool.
- There's nothing wrong with a little bingo.
A little cunnilingus
ain't never hurt nobody.
- Why is it the woman always gets the choice where they're gonna be married?
- Tradition.
Tradition, my ass! I ain't gonna pay
for everybody flyin' to no Chicago!
- You know how much plane tickets cost?
- You cheap bastard.
We're gonna have to
drive down there.
I'm not driving over to Chicago.
Sherman gonna have relations
My baby's not gettin' married
There you go again, poppin' off gas
in front of this lovely young lady.
We're trying to have a meal.
Put that brake on this gas.
I hope your ass
turn into a frog.
Don't nobody want to hear
your flatulence, Cletus Klump.
You're such a disgrace!
- I stopped holding my gas a long time ago.
- You spoiled the dinner!
Say one more word
Listen, Carla,
I want to apologize
about my family back there.
I think they got the wrong
idea about things.
Oh, no no. I should be
the one to apologize.
I'm so sorry if I seemed
distant tonight,
but I still have Buddy on my mind.
- You really care for Buddy, huh?
- I don't know.
I mean, on the outside,
he seems so cocky and brash.
But when I look in his eyes,
I see kindness, I see warmth.
And that's the side of Buddy
I wanted to get to know.
I just got way
ahead of myself.
And here I am, talking your ear off
once again about Buddy.
No, it's quite all right, really.
Listen, Carla,
don't you worry about Buddy.
I'll find him for you.
Thank you, Sherman.
Thank you for being
such a good friend to me.
A good friend.
Good night.
Professor?
Is that you?
I just finished
the grant proposal.
What's the matter with you? Never seen
a brother wearing a circus tent before?
- Black man can't go campin'?
- Now, wait a minute. You. You can't be you.
We agreed that
you wouldn't do this.
Someone has to tend
to chunky butt's sex life.
Chunky butt is extremely horny.
Excuse me.
But Professor Klump has a meeting
tonight with Harlan Hartley at the Ritz.
I'm gonna be at the Ritz tonight, but it
will not be in the interest of science.
No! I can't let you go.
Professor!
If you're in there
and you can hear me, come out!
Professor, listen to me. The
testosterone levels are way too high.
You can't control him.
- Oh! Jason!
- What?
It's me, Sherman. I'm talking to you
from deep down inside Buddy Love.
Listen to me closely. Go in
the back room while I'm holding him,
and get the coagulant serum
off the back shelf!
In the storage closet?
- Yes, Jason! Hurry, Jason!
- I got it!
- We don't have much time. Let's move!
Professor!
I have an appointment with love!
Good night, hamster boy!
No, Professor!
"Sorry I haven't phoned,
but I haven't been myself lately.
"Join me for dinner. Buddy Love.
P.S. I've enclosed a wallet-sized photo
for your enjoyment. "
Buddy, how can I stay mad at you?
This is gorgeous!
You're gorgeous and I'm gorgeous, so we
should be in gorgeous surroundings.
- Let me get the room key.
- Wait. Hold it.
I didn't say anything
about going to any room with you.
You said you were
taking me to dinner.
What are you talking about?
Oh, you think that- Oh!
Oh, my- Hey, hey, hey.
Slow down.
I just want to spend
some time with you, by ourselves.
I don't want to share you with these
people. I want to eat, alone, quiet.
I would never disrespect you.
I'm a puppy dog.
Please, can I go
get this room?
- Yes?
- Yes.
I'd throw him in the river with a Buick tied
to his neck. He'd probably drag the car down.
- Miss Purty. Purty!
- Dean Richmond.
Have you seen Professor Klump?
He's 40 minutes late.
If Harlan Hartley walks out that door,
$10 million goes with him.
Oh, Lord. I'm gonna have to lay down
in front of his car.
- Let's go.
- Buddy, you know Sherman's research.
He's late for a meeting.
Fill in for him.
No, it's a nice thought, but he'd
have to know Sherman's research.
You know Sherman's research?
Who are you?
You might say I'm a visiting professor
who might be staying for a while.
I do know Sherman's work.
In fact, I am Sherman's work.
Buddy!
Do you think you can do Klump's job
and crowbar that dough out of Hartley?
Hey man, there's not a job on this planet
I can't do twice as good as Sherman.
Good. Follow me.
I'll go do this just 'cause
you asked me, not 'cause of him.
You just stay put.
I've got to go be brilliant.
Look at your fine self.
I bet you have on
a thong made of licorice, don't you?
Excuse me.
All righty!
Well, this had better be
Professor Klump.
Klump? That fraud,
that hack, that no-talent.
No, sir, this is the man
behind Klump's work, the real genius.
I give you
Professor Buddy Love.
All right, Professor Love. You have
one minute to show me your research.
No, you got it backwards, Rockefeller.
You have one minute to listen.
May I borrow this?
You haven't used it, have you?
Don't want to get your boogers
on my fingers. Okay. Here we go.
25N times C.
You have to excuse my handwriting.
I'm in a bit of a rush.
- You have a pleasant evening. Good night.
- Uh, Professor Love,
don't you think Mr. Hartley would like
to know what that means in lay terms?
Oh, you mean rich-dummy terms?
I'll break it down for the rich dummies
in the room. Listen up.
If you eat nasty stuff
like this-
I know it looks good,
and some of y'all like pork chops,
but this greasy, nasty pork chop-
there's a gene in your D.N.A...
that routes this straight to your fat
cells, and it causes unsightly conditions.
The arm is taking on a gelatin
sort of vibe. It's quite nasty.
To my left, this gentleman
has turkey neck.
To my immediate left, this woman is
suffering from what we like to call...
"saddlebag syndrome. "
To my extreme left, this young lady is
suffering from what I
like to call "tank ass".
Tank ass?
Please, sit down. Not tonight. I'm
your brother! I'm your brother.
Like I was saying, everybody,
where there's a will, there's a way.
and there is a way we can
turn these genes off.
I'm not talking about
using exercise or diet.
I'm talking about
by taking a simple solution...
that helps reconstruct
your metabolic cellular strands,
thus giving you the appearance
of, in medical terms, gluteus minimus.
Or, in layman's terms,
an extremely tight, wonderful ass.
Let's give a big round of applause
for the woman with the nice ass.
Her ass is so nice, don't you agree?
She's worked so hard.
Have a seat.
Oh, are these girls with you?
Everyone has a nice ass
at this table.
Is this the nice-ass section?
- Where'd you find this man?
- Harlan, it's an outrage.
I assure you he has no affiliation
with this school.
- He's brilliant.
- Exactly my point.
It's an outrage that his brilliance
has no affiliation with this school.
That's why I found him
and brought him to your money.
Attention.
Brought him to your attention.
My goodness, it is time
to take my medication.
- Professor!
Hartley loved you. He's going to be
at the Alumni Ball tomorrow night.
If you can prove the formula works,
the ten million is ours!
What makes you so sure that the money
is ours, instead of just being mine?
You're good, Love. Very good.
How'd you like to fill in for Professor
Klump on a more permanent basis?
That's what I had in mind.
- He talked to me first.
- Hey, I'm the one with the gluteus minimus.
Will you guys just chill?
He said he could handle all three of us.
With a name like Buddy Love,
I bet he can.
Carla, are you ready to go upstairs?
I guess not.
Hey, wha- Where ya goin'?
What's your problem?
They're my problem, and you can handle
all three of them, huh?
Oh, well, I thought after dinner you
might want to have a little group activity.
After all, Buddy does have
a lot of love to give.
Oh, you are one sick,
twisted freak!
Oh, come on, Carla.
What's the- Hey!
Go on, leave!
There's more titties over here anyway!
Think I want them two titties.
I have six titties.
I had two titties.
Now I have six. That's multiplication.
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
- Boys will be boys
- Whoo! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Whoo!
Oh, yeah! This is what I call
burnin' calories!
Come on! Help me
burn this stuff up!
Yeah! Hey, this is goin'
down to Mr. Wilson downstairs!
The roof, the roof,
the roof is on fire!
Sherman?
Sherman, is that you?
Are you all right?
Oh, hi, Carla. Hi.
- Did you have a party last night?
- Oh, no.
My cleanin' lady's, uh Cleanin' lady's sick,
so I got to clean up myself.
I see.
You sure she didn't die?
Oh. Look, I'm a little embarrassed
about the way how my place is lookin'.
Why don't I clean up and
get back at you later?
No, no, no.
Sherman. Sherman, I need
to talk to you now.
- It's about Buddy.
- He hasn't been misbehavin', has he?
He's an egotistical pig,
and I wish I never met him.
But, Sherman, I owe you
a very big apology.
- You owe me an apology?
- Yes. Last night I was only trying to help-
I insisted that Buddy Love
speak to Harlan Hartley.
He took all the credit
for your research.
- Now Dean Richmond-
- Where's Buddy?
- Oh-
- Buddy came here?
- No!
- So what's this?
- Are you guys. You guys share girls?
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
- I guess I was next on the list.
- No, you don't understand.
I cannot believe
I came over here feelin' sorry for you.
Carla, will you please
just listen to me?
I assure you it is nowhat it appears to be!
You're no better than he is!
You are just as sick as Buddy,
and I don't wanna see you or him again!
Ca-Carla, please
just listen. Carla!
"Eviction notice"?
"Violation of noise ordinance"?
Professor?
- We have to get to the lab right away.
- Whatever it is...
is gonna have to wait until later.
No, that's the thing.
There's isn't gonna be a "later".
Professor, what did you do last night?
Jason, I have
such a bad hangover,
I honestly
do not remember.
Well, the good news is
I'm not going to kill you,
not physically, anyway.
I am, however,
going to kill you professionally.
You're not only fired
from this institution,
but I'm going to make sure you never get
hired by any other college in the state,
the country, the world,
maybe even the universe.
Unless, of course, they're looking
for teachers on Planet Fat.
Oh, by the way,
Buddy Love is going to be using
your invitation to the alumni ball,
so show a little school spirit
and see that he gets it.
We're in the money Put that
food down! They ate yesterday!
...really tight and say,
"Yes, I can. "
- Say it again.
- Yes, I can!
Hey, chunky drawers!
Hey, tank ass!
What are you eatin'? Muffin? Strudel?
Put it down. Let me talk to you.
If you're receivin' this message, that
means you went and plumped back up...
to your usual, fat, sorry,
stuff-my-face 'til-I'm-almost-dead self.
Is that what you did?
Shame on you, Sherman!
Do you know what you did last night?
You had the time of your life.
Do you know you can get arrested in 50
states for the shit you did just last night?
- Oh, my goodness!
- You know what you need to do?
You need to go down to the laboratory and
mix up another batch of this blue stuff.
Come on back to the party, Sherman,
because Carla doesn't want you.
She wants me.
Me, not you.
So come join me,
because you can't beat me.
You can't beat me.
You can't beat me!
Yes, I can!
Yes, I can.
Professor, I got your message.
What's up?
I'm goin' to that alumni ball tonight,
and I'm gonna reclaim my life.
Yes! I'm so glad
to hear you say that.
Get things straight
with Miss Purty,
and I'm gonna get that
grant from Harlan Hartley.
Excellent.
Jason, we have seen the last
of Buddy Love.
Horace, good to see you.
The jitterbug contest just started.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Your table's upstairs.
That's another joke.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
When did you marry
Sharon Stone?
Keep those legs crossed.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Hartley! Damn it!
And where the hell
is Buddy Love?
- No sign of him yet, sir.
- Here's an idea.
- Find him!
- Yes, sir!
Harlan.
Well, Richmond. Where's your
Professor Buddy Love?
Oh, with you it's always business.
Let's get to know each other man-to-man.
Now, if our files are correct, you and
your fabulous wife have a terrific daughter.
I'm divorced,
and my daughter is in rehab.
So you're saying
our files are not correct.
Listen, you pompous butt-kisser.
I have a check in my pocket
for $10 million.
Your Buddy Love has 'til midnight
to prove that formula works.
He'll be here, the formula works,
and you have the check.
Really? On you now?
Because on behalf of- Which pocket?
No, don't tell me.
Let me smell it. Punch?
Oh, come on now.
Look at this.
I can't eat this.
This stuff is too tiny.
I can't get full
off this mess!
I think it's wonderful,
all the precious little finger foods.
Finger food?
I got a finger for 'em.
I ain't paid no hundred-dollar ticket
for no finger food.
I could go down to Subway,
get me a sandwich for three dollars.
I gotta pay a hundred-dollar ticket
for finger food?
You must be crazy to think
I'm gonna eat this-
- You're getting on my damn nerves! Shut up!
- I'm hungry!
There's Carla. I wonder
if she's seen Sherman. Carla!
Carla. Oh.
Oh, oh!
- Oh, you look fabulous.
- Thank you, Mrs. Klump.
- Have you seen Sherman?
- Yeah, where's Sherman at?
I ain't come to pay no hundred-dollar
ticket to suffer this alone.
- Cletus, shut up, please!
- Hey! That's strike two.
I don't think Sherman
will be coming tonight.
Yes, he is. Sherman called me
and told me make sure we was here.
He got a big announcement
to make or something.
Something about gettin'
it all off his chest.
Have you noticed that Sherman's
been acting kind of strange lately?
Sherman has definitely
been acting strange lately.
I knew it!
See, Cletus? I told you.
You really think I be listenin' to you.
I ain't listenin' to you!
Well, Mrs. Klump, I hope you have
a wonderful evening.
Oh, you do the same.
Thank you so much.
So precious. Look at your little
purple dress. They gonna think we twins.
Mr. Klump.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Fabulous.
You know, Cletus, I think something's
goin' on between her and Sherman.
You don't go get up in Sherman's
business. That's Sherman's business.
Sherman's business?
That's my business. Sherman is my baby.
Sherman's 35 years old!
What you talkin' about he's your baby?
I don't wanna hear it.
Shut up, please! Carla!
That's strike three, damn it!
Don't you walk away from me,
goddamn it!
- Hey, this is the last of it, Professor.
- I'll tell you this, Jason.
If I'm gonna change my life, it's not
gonna come from some magic drink.
Gotta come from a lot of hard work
and exercise and plenty of these.
Good-bye, Buddy Love.
Hello, Megashake.
Professor?
Oh!
I lost 300 pounds
in 30 seconds!
- Thanks, Megashake!
- You tricked him!
You damn right, hamster boy.
I knew Sherman was gonna go soft on me.
That can wreak havoc
on a man's sex life.
See, I've done
some calculations of my own.
If I drink 500 milliliters
of formula,
I'll have enough cellular stability
to be rid of Sherman's ass forever!
You drink that much formula at one time
and it will kill you!
If I drink it all at once, yes. If I
drink half now and half later, that's safe.
At midnight, I don't have to worry
about turning into no Klumpkin.
If you don't mind, I have a
date at the alumni ball,
and you have a date with linoleum.
Who?
No, no, no, child.
Not a wild party. Not Sherman.
He's too shy for something like that.
He hates parties.
In fact, we tried to have a party
for Sherman when he was 18 years old...
and he's so shy,
he didn't even show up.
Well, I must admit,
it didn't seem like the Sherman I knew.
Oh, no, not my baby. Maybe he
loaned his house out to somebody...
or one of his buddies was
throwin' a party there.
Is that a test tube in my pocket?
Or am I just happy to see you?
- Oh! How dare you?
- Oh, you know you loved it.
I felt you percolatin'. Whoo!
Hey, thanks a lot, man.
Thank you so much.
Oh! What you servin' here?
This stuff is na- Y'all got to get
some collard greens and yams!
- Some red beans and rice!
- Some "Buddy" is right.
- This ain't no party! This ain't no ball!
- Dr. Love!
Y'all gotta get y'all
some peach cobbler up in here!
Dr. Love!
Where the hell have you been?
I've been nursemaiding Hartley for three
hours, and if I didn't need that money-
Shut up! Who you think
you're talkin' to, Sherman Klump?
Man, if you ever talk to me
like that again, I'll kill ya!
I don't mean that as a euphemism.
I mean I'm gonna literally kill ya.
I'm gonna strangle you and cut off
your air supply until you pass away!
Now find the rich dummy a seat.
It's show time.
It's show time, everybody!
Show time!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
That's enough out of you! That's it.
You're the reason everybody fallin' asleep.
Take a break, Nigger-ace. Take the
Everly Brothers with you. Get outta here!
Look at everybody sleepin'
because of y'all! It's show time!
Whoo! Now why are y'all lookin'
at me like y'all don't know me?
- Y'all know me!
- I don't know that fool.
How 'bout now?
You recognize me?
- I don't know that fool.
- Maybe it's because...
this morning
I weighed 400 pounds!
You should've seen me.
Look at me now.
You know how I did it?
One sip.
I know why he like that,
'cause he drunk.
- Be quiet!
- Don't tell me to be quiet! He drunk!
I like to call it
"Buddy's Wonder Tonic. "
I know what
wonder tonic you had.
Right on schedule.
Cellular destabilization
due to arrive in exactly three,
two, one
Ain't that a bitch!
- What the hell?
- My goodness!
Hey, moneybags, you want a demonstration?
Well, then feast your eyes on this.
That's a hell of a trick.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for my final demonstration-
Look out, David Copperfield.
I'm about to make a 400-pound fat man...
disappear forever!
No! Wait!
I cannot let you do this anymore!
This has got to stop!
This man is trying to kill
Professor Sherman Klump!
- That's it. I'm glad I brought my knife.
- Mm-hmm. And I got my razor.
- Hand over the vial now!
- Oh, sure thing, hamster boy.
But first,
a short musical interlude.
Buddy!
What has gotten into you,
and where is Sherman?
Sherman is gone!
- Disappeared!
- What the hell-
And that's a pretty good trick for a man
with an ass as big as his.
Oh! I'm late for an appointment.
Ladies and gentlemen,
say good-bye to Sherman Klump!
I hate being called hamster boy.
Ahhh!
You just don't know
when to quit, do you?
It's too late, fat boy.
It's over!
Let go! Let go!
- My goodness!
- Damn!
Give it up, fat boy! It's over!
It ain't over 'til
the fat professor sings!
Let go of my hand, you fat mother-
Say one more word, Buddy,
I'll tear your arm off!
It's time... we take...
Nestea... plunge!
Whoo!
Gonna get the hell outta here
in a second. It's okay.
Ah!
- Ahhh!
- Sweet Jesus!
- Sherman!
- Sherman, don't do this! You need me!
No, I don't!
You fat ass!
Tinkerbell!
- Blubber butt!
- Featherweight!
Somebody better call
an exorcist!
Sherman! Sherman!
You can't beat me!
This is some scary shit!
Yes, I can!
Ooh!
- Sherman, come back here! Sherman!
- What's happening to me?
Everything's getting real dark!
Oh! I feel real jiggly!
I'm blubbifying! Sherman!
You need me! I taught you to be
confident! You needed me, Sherman!
Sherman!
No matter what-
No matter what,
ya got to strut.
I ain't gonna be pickin' up your big ass
all night, Anna. Shit.
- Oh, my God.
- Well, I'll be damned.
If you give me a moment,
I believe I can try to explain.
My research is, uh-
Well, uh, when
I started out I wa-
I wanted to help people.
But I became desperate
and selfish.
What I did was wrong.
Buddy's who I thought
the whole world wanted me to be.
He's who I thought
I wanted to be.
And sometimes when you
want something so, so bad,
you do just about anything
to get it.
But I learned one thing
from Buddy.
I learned that life
is not about...
bein' happy about how much you weigh,
but just bein' happy with yourself.
I'm terribly sorry about all this. I
hope I haven't ruined everybody's evenin'.
Please excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Sherman!
Sherman, wait a minute.
Sherman, why did you lie to me?
Why didn't you
say anything?
I didn't think you'd have me. I mean,
the fact of the matter is I'm a big man.
Now, I will lose weight, but I'm
always gonna be big no matter what I do.
So, anybody I wind up with is just goin'
to have to accept me for who I am.
And more important, I'm just going
to have to accept myself for who I am.
Sherman,
I don't have a date tonight.
Would you like to
dance with me?
Professor.
I thought you might need this.
Yeah, I guess
I tore this one up, huh?
You know one thing I
couldn't stand about that Buddy?
What's that?
He was too damn scrawny.
Okay, Professor!
Lookin' good!
Have I mentioned we also
have a terrific English Department?
- I'm giving him the grant.
- What?
I hate to admit it, but
you're absolutely right.
He's a brilliant scientist and
a gentleman as well.
Well, I told ya!
- Will you shut up!
- I'm fine with that.
Ooh! Sherman, Sherman, Sherman,
Sherman, Sherman, Sherman, Sherman!
Light as a feather tonight.
Come on. Bump me.
Whoo, yeah!
Oh, oh, my goodness!
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
- You didn't hurt yourself, did you?
- I'm fine.
- Yeah!
- Fabulous!