1
00:01:05,315 --> 00:01:07,066
Master Li is here!

2
00:01:07,443 --> 00:01:10,194
-Master Li is here!
<i>-Master Li is here!</i>

3
00:01:22,958 --> 00:01:26,169
Shu Lien!

4
00:01:28,839 --> 00:01:31,466
Shu Lien! Li Mu Bai is here!

5
00:01:37,014 --> 00:01:38,765
-Master Li.
-Hello.

6
00:01:39,183 --> 00:01:42,059
-How's everything?
-Fine. Please come in.

7
00:01:53,530 --> 00:01:56,616
-Li Mu Bai. lt's been a long time.
-lt has.

8
00:01:57,576 --> 00:02:00,578
-How's business?
-Not bad. And how are you?

9
00:02:01,038 --> 00:02:02,205
Fine.

10
00:02:06,502 --> 00:02:09,045
Monk Zheng came by
from the Wudang Mountain.

11
00:02:09,129 --> 00:02:11,756
He said you were practising
deep meditation.

12
00:02:14,009 --> 00:02:17,595
The mountain must be so peaceful.
l envy you.

13
00:02:17,679 --> 00:02:20,848
My work keeps me so busy
l hardly get a minute's rest.

14
00:02:23,018 --> 00:02:25,937
l broke it off.
l couldn't complete the training.

15
00:02:27,231 --> 00:02:30,733
Why? You're a Wudang fighter.
Training is everything.

16
00:02:31,819 --> 00:02:37,573
During my meditation training,
l came to a place of deep silence.

17
00:02:38,617 --> 00:02:40,743
l was surrounded by light.

18
00:02:41,453 --> 00:02:44,413
Time and space disappeared.

19
00:02:45,791 --> 00:02:49,877
l felt l had come to a place
my master had never told me about.

20
00:02:52,339 --> 00:02:55,508
-You were enlightened.
-Far from it.

21
00:02:56,051 --> 00:02:59,470
l didn't feel the bliss
one should feel when enlightened.

22
00:02:59,555 --> 00:03:03,933
lnstead, l was surrounded
by an endless sorrow.

23
00:03:05,394 --> 00:03:08,104
lt was more than l could take.

24
00:03:08,897 --> 00:03:12,024
l couldn't go on. l failed.

25
00:03:13,360 --> 00:03:16,821
There was something pulling me
back into the world.

26
00:03:18,448 --> 00:03:19,907
What was it?

27
00:03:23,078 --> 00:03:25,329
Something l can't seem to let go of.

28
00:03:29,376 --> 00:03:31,544
l see you're preparing to leave.

29
00:03:32,129 --> 00:03:36,090
We're making a delivery to Beijing.

30
00:03:36,800 --> 00:03:40,803
Perhaps l could ask you
to deliver something to Sir Te for me.

31
00:03:46,143 --> 00:03:49,270
The Green Destiny Sword?
You're giving it to Sir Te?

32
00:03:49,354 --> 00:03:52,899
l am. He has always been
our greatest protector.

33
00:03:52,983 --> 00:03:55,943
l don't understand.
How can you part with it?

34
00:03:56,028 --> 00:03:58,404
lt's been with you a long time.

35
00:03:59,573 --> 00:04:02,158
Too many men have died at its edge.

36
00:04:06,580 --> 00:04:08,372
lt may look pure

37
00:04:08,540 --> 00:04:11,250
but only because blood
washes easily from its blade.

38
00:04:11,335 --> 00:04:15,212
You use it for good cause,
making you worthy of it.

39
00:04:17,716 --> 00:04:20,009
lt's time for me to leave it behind.

40
00:04:21,053 --> 00:04:23,512
So what will you do then?

41
00:04:26,600 --> 00:04:28,601
Come with me to Beijing.

42
00:04:28,977 --> 00:04:31,938
You can give the sword to Sir Te in person.

43
00:04:32,064 --> 00:04:34,690
lt'll be just like old times.

44
00:04:36,318 --> 00:04:39,737
l need to visit my master's grave.

45
00:04:40,572 --> 00:04:44,241
lt's been many years since
he was murdered by Jade Fox.

46
00:04:44,326 --> 00:04:49,080
l have yet to avenge his death,
and yet l'm thinking of quitting.

47
00:04:49,706 --> 00:04:52,124
l must pray for his forgiveness.

48
00:04:52,793 --> 00:04:57,088
Catch up with me when you have finished.

49
00:04:57,422 --> 00:04:59,757
l will wait for you if you come.

50
00:05:00,884 --> 00:05:02,176
Maybe.

51
00:05:09,810 --> 00:05:12,436
-Okay, you may pass.
-Thanks.

52
00:05:12,521 --> 00:05:14,397
Let's go into the city. We can rest
after we unload the shipment.

53
00:05:25,617 --> 00:05:28,244
Thank God everything is safe.
Much obliged, Miss Yu.

54
00:05:28,328 --> 00:05:31,622
Just doing my job.

55
00:05:31,915 --> 00:05:35,626
Sun Security has been the best
since your father started it.

56
00:05:36,336 --> 00:05:40,589
You're a credit to your father's memory.

57
00:05:40,841 --> 00:05:44,093
-Thank you.
-lt's the truth.

58
00:06:19,546 --> 00:06:22,256
This is Li's personal sword.

59
00:06:23,300 --> 00:06:26,927
A great hero is worthy of a great weapon.

60
00:06:27,262 --> 00:06:31,640
He is the only one in the world
worthy of it.

61
00:06:32,142 --> 00:06:35,061
lt's too fine a gift. l cannot accept it.

62
00:06:35,479 --> 00:06:39,148
The sword has brought Li Mu Bai
as much trouble as glory.

63
00:06:39,483 --> 00:06:42,109
Li wants to leave these troubles behind.

64
00:06:42,235 --> 00:06:45,362
Take the sword and help him
leave his old way of life.

65
00:06:45,906 --> 00:06:48,949
l see. All right.
l'll act as the sword's custodian.

66
00:06:52,037 --> 00:06:54,038
Ninth Level Counsel, Chief Yu has arrived.

67
00:06:54,122 --> 00:06:55,706
l must change.

68
00:06:56,333 --> 00:07:01,295
Thank you. You've always been
a great friend to Li and me.

69
00:07:01,379 --> 00:07:03,964
No hurry to leave. Please feel at home.

70
00:07:04,382 --> 00:07:06,926
You'll stay the night as my guest.

71
00:07:07,844 --> 00:07:10,221
Now, Shu Lien,

72
00:07:10,305 --> 00:07:14,225
tell me something,
and forgive me for prying.

73
00:07:14,976 --> 00:07:17,770
But your father was like a brother to me

74
00:07:17,854 --> 00:07:21,023
and l think of you as my own daughter.

75
00:07:21,274 --> 00:07:23,484
Please, Sir Te, what is it?

76
00:07:23,819 --> 00:07:28,781
Li Mu Bai giving up his sword
and his warrior days,

77
00:07:29,574 --> 00:07:32,368
maybe he's hinting something to you.

78
00:07:33,245 --> 00:07:35,871
-l don't know.
-Don't be coy.

79
00:07:36,206 --> 00:07:39,083
l've known all along about
your feelings for each other.

80
00:07:39,167 --> 00:07:41,585
Neither of you have been brave enough

81
00:07:41,670 --> 00:07:45,339
to reveal your feelings to each other.

82
00:07:46,967 --> 00:07:49,677
So many years went wasted.

83
00:07:50,762 --> 00:07:52,888
Li Mu Bai and l aren't cowards.

84
00:07:52,973 --> 00:07:55,432
Maybe it isn't what you've thought.

85
00:07:57,435 --> 00:08:03,232
When it comes to emotions,
even great heroes can be idiots.

86
00:08:04,442 --> 00:08:08,612
lf Li Mu Bai doesn't talk straight
next time you see him,

87
00:08:09,739 --> 00:08:12,575
let me know, and l'll give him an earful!

88
00:08:21,418 --> 00:08:23,377
You will stay in this room.

89
00:08:29,342 --> 00:08:30,384
You?

90
00:08:35,724 --> 00:08:39,143
l am your guest here today.

91
00:08:41,062 --> 00:08:43,981
This is Sir Te's study. You are here to...

92
00:08:44,357 --> 00:08:48,277
lt's so crowded out there.
l was looking for a quiet place.

93
00:08:49,070 --> 00:08:53,240
l'm Sir Te's head servant, De Lu.
This is another of our guests.

94
00:09:05,921 --> 00:09:08,881
lt's heavy for such a thin piece of metal.

95
00:09:09,132 --> 00:09:12,885
lt's the handle that's heavy.
And that blade is no ordinary metal.

96
00:09:13,053 --> 00:09:16,305
Still, the sword is the lightest
of all weapons.

97
00:09:16,389 --> 00:09:19,225
You find it heavy because
you're not used to handling them.

98
00:09:19,309 --> 00:09:21,727
No, l've had a lot
of experience with weapons.

99
00:09:21,811 --> 00:09:24,063
My father has security guards
living with us.

100
00:09:24,147 --> 00:09:26,398
They let me play with their weapons.

101
00:09:27,609 --> 00:09:29,944
This scabbard is so beautiful.

102
00:09:31,446 --> 00:09:33,322
Beautiful and yet dangerous.

103
00:09:33,406 --> 00:09:37,159
Once you've seen it tainted with blood,
you'll think otherwise.

104
00:09:38,119 --> 00:09:40,621
lt's 400 years old.

105
00:09:41,248 --> 00:09:42,915
lt's exquisite.

106
00:09:43,875 --> 00:09:46,377
You said this sword belongs to...

107
00:09:46,628 --> 00:09:48,963
My friend Li Mu Bai.

108
00:09:49,506 --> 00:09:51,423
He's given it to Sir Te as a gift.

109
00:09:51,508 --> 00:09:54,009
Li Mu Bai! The famous warrior?

110
00:09:54,094 --> 00:09:58,222
l've heard so much about him.
Why would he give his sword to Sir Te?

111
00:09:59,266 --> 00:10:01,058
lt's a long story.

112
00:10:02,894 --> 00:10:07,147
-You must be a sword fighter, too.
-Yes, but l prefer the machete.

113
00:10:07,274 --> 00:10:11,318
This sword fits Li Mu Bai perfectly.

114
00:10:13,196 --> 00:10:14,571
Really.

115
00:10:16,700 --> 00:10:19,743
lt must be exciting to be a fighter.

116
00:10:20,161 --> 00:10:23,747
Fighters have rules, too.
Friendship, trust, integrity.

117
00:10:24,207 --> 00:10:25,958
Always keep your promise.

118
00:10:26,084 --> 00:10:28,836
Without rules, we wouldn't survive long.

119
00:10:29,838 --> 00:10:31,964
l've read all about people like you.

120
00:10:32,048 --> 00:10:34,967
Roaming wild,
beating up anyone who gets in your way!

121
00:10:35,051 --> 00:10:38,012
Writers have to write like that
to sell books.

122
00:10:38,179 --> 00:10:40,931
You're just like the characters
in the stories.

123
00:10:41,057 --> 00:10:44,893
Sure, no place to bathe for days,
sleeping on flea-infested beds.

124
00:10:45,562 --> 00:10:47,771
They tell you all about that in those books?

125
00:10:47,856 --> 00:10:49,773
You know what l mean.

126
00:10:50,191 --> 00:10:54,194
l'm getting married soon,
but l haven't lived the life l want.

127
00:10:55,488 --> 00:10:58,574
l've heard of your engagement.
Congratulations.

128
00:11:02,245 --> 00:11:05,998
lt's the most important step
in a woman's life, isn't it?

129
00:11:07,584 --> 00:11:11,003
-You are not married, are you?
-What do you think?

130
00:11:11,421 --> 00:11:14,715
No. You couldn't roam around
freely if you were.

131
00:11:15,300 --> 00:11:17,676
l admit you're probably right.

132
00:11:50,043 --> 00:11:51,877
Chief Yu, take a look.

133
00:12:03,348 --> 00:12:08,018
2 feet 9 inches long, 1 .1 inch wide.

134
00:12:08,186 --> 00:12:11,480
The handle is 1 inch long, 2.6 inches wide,

135
00:12:11,815 --> 00:12:15,567
0.7 inch thick, each side is 1 .5 inches.

136
00:12:15,652 --> 00:12:18,195
With seven rubies missing from the hilt.

137
00:12:18,530 --> 00:12:22,908
You can tell from the design that
it was made during the Qin Wu era.

138
00:12:22,992 --> 00:12:26,120
Engraved with a technique lost
during the Han Dynasty.

139
00:12:26,204 --> 00:12:29,331
Your knowledge is remarkable.

140
00:12:31,042 --> 00:12:33,252
A sword by itself rules nothing.

141
00:12:33,461 --> 00:12:36,463
lt comes alive only through
skilful manipulation.

142
00:12:37,090 --> 00:12:40,050
l see your point. Please continue, Sir Te.

143
00:12:40,218 --> 00:12:43,011
The inner city in Beijing is not a problem.

144
00:12:43,596 --> 00:12:47,224
With royalty and officials everywhere

145
00:12:47,809 --> 00:12:52,020
the Royal Guard keep security tight.

146
00:12:52,439 --> 00:12:54,773
But the outer city is hard to govern.

147
00:12:54,858 --> 00:12:58,110
lt's full of complex characters.

148
00:12:59,154 --> 00:13:02,197
Proceed with caution
in your quest for law and order.

149
00:13:02,282 --> 00:13:04,658
Don't depend only on the court.

150
00:13:04,742 --> 00:13:07,703
Keep some contacts
in the Jiang Hu underworld.

151
00:13:08,496 --> 00:13:10,581
lt can ensure your position.

152
00:13:15,211 --> 00:13:18,672
Be strong yet supple.
This is the way to rule.

153
00:13:47,994 --> 00:13:49,369
Governess.

154
00:13:50,914 --> 00:13:52,164
Let me do it.

155
00:13:55,919 --> 00:13:59,338
-Please sit.
-l've made a pair of silk pyjamas.

156
00:13:59,422 --> 00:14:02,299
-Want to change into them?
-Leave them there.

157
00:14:08,097 --> 00:14:10,724
l heard you met Yu Shu Lien today.

158
00:14:11,601 --> 00:14:13,143
You know her?

159
00:14:14,354 --> 00:14:18,190
Your mother would not want you
consorting with her kind.

160
00:14:21,110 --> 00:14:23,570
l'll socialise with whomever l please.

161
00:14:23,780 --> 00:14:26,573
Don't invite danger
into your father's house.

162
00:14:29,744 --> 00:14:32,829
-l'm tired now!
-Go to bed then.

163
00:14:37,210 --> 00:14:39,920
You've grown up
and will get married soon.

164
00:14:41,589 --> 00:14:44,216
God knows what the future will bring.

165
00:14:45,176 --> 00:14:47,010
lt'll be just the same.

166
00:14:47,845 --> 00:14:49,596
Enough, l'm tired.

167
00:14:54,352 --> 00:14:57,604
lt's autumn now.
l'll shut the windows for you.

168
00:15:24,716 --> 00:15:26,383
Chilly, eh?

169
00:16:02,879 --> 00:16:04,671
Thief!

170
00:16:27,362 --> 00:16:30,322
Someone help! Catch the thief!

171
00:16:30,406 --> 00:16:32,240
He's on the rooftop!

172
00:16:34,619 --> 00:16:37,663
The sword's been stolen! Someone help!

173
00:16:38,706 --> 00:16:40,957
He's on the roof! Stop, thief!

174
00:17:05,608 --> 00:17:08,527
Catch him!

175
00:17:09,904 --> 00:17:11,697
Avenge my mother!

176
00:17:14,075 --> 00:17:17,035
What are you standing here for?
Go get him!

177
00:17:19,497 --> 00:17:22,249
Return the sword, and l'll let you go.

178
00:17:27,714 --> 00:17:30,048
You've been trained at Wudang?

179
00:17:33,970 --> 00:17:36,722
We are street performers. You're wrong.

180
00:17:36,848 --> 00:17:39,516
-We're just practising the stunts.
-Let's go.

181
00:17:40,101 --> 00:17:43,186
Practising? Who are you trying to fool?

182
00:17:43,771 --> 00:17:45,522
Where did they go?

183
00:17:56,951 --> 00:17:58,744
Chief Yu's house.

184
00:19:40,763 --> 00:19:42,347
Get down here!

185
00:19:58,531 --> 00:19:59,990
Give me the sword.

186
00:21:14,023 --> 00:21:16,358
Sir Te awaits you in the great hall.

187
00:21:17,985 --> 00:21:19,444
l didn't get the sword back.

188
00:21:19,528 --> 00:21:23,281
But l'm sure the thief's connected
to the Yus.

189
00:21:23,366 --> 00:21:25,075
-How dare you!
-But l saw...

190
00:21:25,159 --> 00:21:26,952
Enough! Get out!

191
00:21:38,631 --> 00:21:40,882
Has Chief Yu ever seen the sword?

192
00:21:41,300 --> 00:21:44,970
Yes, though l doubt he's involved in this.

193
00:21:45,554 --> 00:21:48,556
But the sword is somewhere
in his compound.

194
00:21:52,228 --> 00:21:56,356
Then someone's out to frame him.

195
00:21:56,899 --> 00:21:59,901
We should get word
to Li Mu Bai about this.

196
00:22:04,824 --> 00:22:06,533
Watch your step.

197
00:22:09,328 --> 00:22:12,038
-What is it?
-Someone's put fliers up.

198
00:22:18,087 --> 00:22:19,546
Let me see.

199
00:22:26,178 --> 00:22:30,265
Someone's after Jade Fox.
Preposterous, looking for her here!

200
00:22:46,699 --> 00:22:50,785
-Best spear fighting in the world!
-The Yang School of Spear Fighting!

201
00:23:07,053 --> 00:23:09,929
-Where did they go?
-l really don't know.

202
00:23:10,890 --> 00:23:14,309
l saw them couple of days ago.
Probably gone by now.

203
00:24:05,694 --> 00:24:08,446
Miss, there's a Miss Yu here
asking to see you.

204
00:24:08,614 --> 00:24:11,449
-Our Lady is busy right now.
-l will tell her then.

205
00:24:11,534 --> 00:24:13,034
Show her in.

206
00:24:14,662 --> 00:24:15,829
Yes.

207
00:24:20,543 --> 00:24:23,211
This spells trouble.

208
00:24:25,214 --> 00:24:26,798
l have a guest now.

209
00:24:34,014 --> 00:24:36,182
This way please, Miss Yu.

210
00:24:42,231 --> 00:24:44,482
-l've missed you!
-Missed me? How so?

211
00:24:44,567 --> 00:24:46,151
l have nothing to do.

212
00:24:53,033 --> 00:24:55,160
You're practising calligraphy.

213
00:24:56,245 --> 00:24:59,414
l'll write your name. Just for fun.

214
00:25:25,941 --> 00:25:28,985
l never noticed that my name
looks like the word for sword.

215
00:25:29,069 --> 00:25:32,864
You write gracefully.
Calligraphy is so similar to fencing.

216
00:25:33,699 --> 00:25:35,950
Maybe it is. l wouldn't know.

217
00:25:37,953 --> 00:25:39,245
Please.

218
00:25:43,417 --> 00:25:46,628
Thank you for seeing me.
l hear your wedding day is near.

219
00:25:46,921 --> 00:25:49,130
You must be overwhelmed
with the preparations.

220
00:25:49,215 --> 00:25:52,717
l'm hardly doing a thing.
The less l think of it, the better.

221
00:25:53,135 --> 00:25:57,931
My parents are arranging everything,
including the groom.

222
00:25:58,307 --> 00:26:02,310
Mother says the Gous
are a very powerful family.

223
00:26:02,728 --> 00:26:06,481
My marrying into this family
will give my dad's career a big boost.

224
00:26:06,899 --> 00:26:10,235
lt's a great fortune to marry
into such a noble family.

225
00:26:11,111 --> 00:26:15,281
ls it? Actually,
l like the great heroes in the books

226
00:26:15,658 --> 00:26:17,951
just like you and Li Mu Bai.

227
00:26:18,827 --> 00:26:20,495
Marriage is a good thing.

228
00:26:20,663 --> 00:26:23,081
lf only l could be free to live my own life,

229
00:26:23,165 --> 00:26:26,834
to choose who l love
and love him in my own way.

230
00:26:28,170 --> 00:26:30,088
That's real happiness.

231
00:26:31,632 --> 00:26:35,468
-Think so? Let me tell you a story.
-About you and Li Mu Bai?

232
00:26:35,761 --> 00:26:39,597
Yes. l was once engaged
to be married when l was young.

233
00:26:41,016 --> 00:26:43,810
-Really?
-His name was Meng Si Zhao.

234
00:26:44,311 --> 00:26:47,021
He was a brother-by-oath to Li Mu Bai.

235
00:26:47,481 --> 00:26:49,691
One day,
while defending Li Mu Bai in battle

236
00:26:49,775 --> 00:26:53,027
he was killed by another man's sword.

237
00:26:53,946 --> 00:26:57,532
After Meng's sacrifice,
Li and l went through a lot together.

238
00:26:57,616 --> 00:26:59,659
Our feelings for each other grew stronger.

239
00:26:59,743 --> 00:27:03,913
But we decided to honour
my engagement to Meng.

240
00:27:04,123 --> 00:27:06,958
The freedom you talk about,
l too desire it,

241
00:27:07,293 --> 00:27:09,210
but l've never tasted it.

242
00:27:09,545 --> 00:27:12,046
lt's not your fault, or Li Mu Bai's.

243
00:27:12,214 --> 00:27:15,550
Too bad for Meng,
but that's just the way things turn out.

244
00:27:17,553 --> 00:27:20,555
As a woman,
l still must abide by tradition

245
00:27:20,973 --> 00:27:25,518
even if l'm not an aristocrat like you.

246
00:27:26,145 --> 00:27:32,025
Don't distance us.
From now on, let's be sisters.

247
00:27:33,694 --> 00:27:38,364
All right. As a sister,
l hope you find real happiness.

248
00:28:14,693 --> 00:28:17,278
Miles and miles of nothing.

249
00:28:18,280 --> 00:28:22,075
Can't your father get an appointment
closer to civilisation?

250
00:28:22,534 --> 00:28:23,951
This place!

251
00:28:25,079 --> 00:28:28,623
Jen, are you listening to me?

252
00:28:57,486 --> 00:28:58,820
Let's go!

253
00:29:22,886 --> 00:29:24,971
-Who are you?
-Dad!

254
00:29:25,055 --> 00:29:27,557
Hold it! l'm a friend!

255
00:29:31,353 --> 00:29:34,230
l don't care about your sword.

256
00:29:34,314 --> 00:29:38,693
-Why are you spying on the Yus?
-l'm looking for someone. Jade Fox.

257
00:29:39,528 --> 00:29:43,781
l'm a police inspector
from the Shaan Xi, Gen Su district.

258
00:29:43,866 --> 00:29:47,827
This Jade Fox is a master criminal.
l hear she infiltrated the Yus.

259
00:29:48,036 --> 00:29:51,581
She must have come with them
when he transferred here.

260
00:29:52,040 --> 00:29:54,667
But l cannot just go in and catch her there.

261
00:29:54,751 --> 00:29:56,711
l have to lure her out.

262
00:29:56,795 --> 00:29:58,838
-This Jade Fox is a woman?
-You bet.

263
00:29:58,922 --> 00:30:01,132
Then leave her to me. Don't worry.

264
00:30:01,425 --> 00:30:04,051
Thank you, but l doubt you can handle her.

265
00:30:04,595 --> 00:30:08,639
My wife used to be quite a martial artist.
Jade Fox killed her.

266
00:30:08,724 --> 00:30:13,394
lt's both an official and a personal matter
to me.

267
00:30:14,897 --> 00:30:18,191
-Meatballs are ready!
-l'm more than ready for them.

268
00:30:18,942 --> 00:30:21,277
Wait, dad gets first dip!

269
00:30:23,906 --> 00:30:25,072
Hey!

270
00:30:26,074 --> 00:30:27,617
They are gone.

271
00:30:29,286 --> 00:30:30,661
What does it say?

272
00:30:30,746 --> 00:30:33,956
We'll settle this at midnight tonight
on Cemetery Hill.

273
00:30:34,082 --> 00:30:36,584
Good! The Fox is out of her hole.

274
00:30:38,504 --> 00:30:39,629
Please.

275
00:30:41,548 --> 00:30:43,799
Shu Lien, look who's here.

276
00:30:49,681 --> 00:30:53,267
Sir Te thinks it's not appropriate
to cast doubt on Chief Yu.

277
00:30:53,352 --> 00:30:56,979
But there is something up
in the Yu household. l'm investigating.

278
00:30:57,064 --> 00:30:58,606
What have you found?

279
00:31:11,203 --> 00:31:13,621
Jade Fox? lmpossible!

280
00:31:13,956 --> 00:31:16,916
You'd always suspected
she'd fled out west.

281
00:31:17,000 --> 00:31:19,293
She has the nerve to come to Beijing.

282
00:31:19,378 --> 00:31:23,047
ls there any place safer than
under the nose of Chief Yu?

283
00:31:25,133 --> 00:31:28,386
l shall avenge my master's death after all.

284
00:31:29,846 --> 00:31:32,265
But be careful, Li Mu Bai.

285
00:31:32,766 --> 00:31:34,934
Sir Te requires discretion.

286
00:31:35,102 --> 00:31:37,687
Official business is already
difficult to resolve,

287
00:31:37,771 --> 00:31:41,357
it'd be a bigger mess
with your personal matters involved.

288
00:31:41,984 --> 00:31:44,860
And l don't know,
this flyer may not be reliable.

289
00:31:44,945 --> 00:31:46,946
lt could be some sort of trap.

290
00:31:49,658 --> 00:31:52,034
-Did you see who posted it?
-No.

291
00:31:52,411 --> 00:31:54,537
lt says Fox is hiding at Yu's.

292
00:31:54,955 --> 00:31:58,833
Sir Te says the night of the theft
there was a brawl in front of Yu's.

293
00:31:58,917 --> 00:32:00,918
Were you involved?

294
00:32:01,003 --> 00:32:04,171
No, that was Bo, Sir Te's man.

295
00:32:04,256 --> 00:32:06,007
Bo followed the thief to the Yus.

296
00:32:06,091 --> 00:32:10,094
-Have you cross-examined him yet?
-Bo? No, not yet...

297
00:32:10,178 --> 00:32:13,097
But you've had your men
stake out Yu's compound?

298
00:32:13,849 --> 00:32:16,267
No, l'd already sent them back.

299
00:32:18,186 --> 00:32:20,563
You can blame me for losing the sword

300
00:32:20,647 --> 00:32:24,191
but trust me, l'll get it back soon
using my own methods.

301
00:32:25,861 --> 00:32:27,653
That's not what l meant.

302
00:32:27,738 --> 00:32:29,947
l don't care about the sword.

303
00:32:30,157 --> 00:32:33,618
How can you say that?
Didn't you come back here for it?

304
00:32:34,286 --> 00:32:37,413
l didn't know it was stolen until l got here.

305
00:32:38,915 --> 00:32:40,666
Then, why did you come?

306
00:32:42,878 --> 00:32:45,379
Well, we had talked...

307
00:32:48,925 --> 00:32:52,386
Pardon my intrusion.
Master Li, your room is ready.

308
00:32:54,806 --> 00:32:56,223
Thank you.

309
00:32:57,017 --> 00:32:58,893
Please, lead the way.

310
00:33:09,780 --> 00:33:12,281
This Fox doesn't care much for punctuality.

311
00:33:12,366 --> 00:33:14,367
There's no sign of her.

312
00:33:22,250 --> 00:33:24,251
Enough! Don't pretend any more.

313
00:33:28,590 --> 00:33:30,883
Tsai! You old scoundrel!

314
00:33:31,468 --> 00:33:33,886
You won't leave me alone. Payback time!

315
00:33:33,970 --> 00:33:36,555
Yeah, old lady? Watch your mouth!

316
00:33:36,765 --> 00:33:39,934
lf you surrender now, you'll suffer less.

317
00:33:40,227 --> 00:33:43,104
lf you resist, you're dead today.

318
00:33:43,271 --> 00:33:46,190
Dad! Let me avenge my mother's death.

319
00:33:46,274 --> 00:33:48,526
You'll end up like her, you little whore!

320
00:33:48,610 --> 00:33:51,278
You old fox!

321
00:34:26,481 --> 00:34:27,648
Dad!

322
00:34:57,012 --> 00:35:00,514
You old fox, you ruined my life.
You won't get away with it.

323
00:35:14,863 --> 00:35:17,239
Watch out for her acupressure!

324
00:35:23,205 --> 00:35:24,830
Sue!

325
00:35:33,298 --> 00:35:35,299
Tsai, you dog!

326
00:35:37,719 --> 00:35:39,720
You even have hidden hands!

327
00:35:43,934 --> 00:35:46,101
-Dad, are you okay?
-l'm fine.

328
00:35:46,728 --> 00:35:49,563
Wudang should have gotten rid of you
long ago.

329
00:35:50,065 --> 00:35:52,191
lt's been a long time, Jade Fox!

330
00:35:53,276 --> 00:35:55,611
You probably don't remember me.

331
00:35:55,779 --> 00:35:58,572
But you remember my master.

332
00:35:59,449 --> 00:36:03,702
You infiltrated my clan while l was away.

333
00:36:03,787 --> 00:36:06,455
You poisoned my master
and stole the secret manual.

334
00:36:06,540 --> 00:36:09,583
Now it's time for you to pay!

335
00:36:09,960 --> 00:36:12,545
Your master underestimated us women.

336
00:36:12,629 --> 00:36:15,673
He wouldn't teach me even after
he'd slept with me.

337
00:36:15,757 --> 00:36:19,343
He deserved to die by a woman's hands!

338
00:36:59,634 --> 00:37:02,595
You stole the top secrets
of Wudang's martial arts.

339
00:37:02,679 --> 00:37:05,764
But you've mastered only
the basic moves in the past ten years.

340
00:37:05,849 --> 00:37:08,475
For you to die under Wudang's
sword today

341
00:37:10,353 --> 00:37:11,353
is no disgrace!

342
00:37:17,652 --> 00:37:20,821
My disciple! Fight with me!
We'll kill them all!

343
00:37:21,156 --> 00:37:23,073
-Fox has a disciple!
-l've got to get rid of Tsai!

344
00:37:31,499 --> 00:37:33,000
Who are you?

345
00:37:34,961 --> 00:37:38,297
Why is the Green Destiny Sword
in your possession?

346
00:37:38,882 --> 00:37:41,967
-lt's none of your business.
-My name is Li Mu Bai.

347
00:37:42,135 --> 00:37:44,511
The Green Destiny Sword is mine.

348
00:37:54,898 --> 00:37:57,232
Jade Fox can't be your master.

349
00:37:57,359 --> 00:37:59,360
Where did you learn this "Xuan Piu" move?

350
00:37:59,444 --> 00:38:01,362
Piece of cake.

351
00:38:06,910 --> 00:38:08,619
Who is your master?

352
00:38:30,392 --> 00:38:33,060
-Let's go.
-l'll kill them once and for all.

353
00:38:37,732 --> 00:38:39,400
Let's go!

354
00:38:41,653 --> 00:38:52,788
Dad!

355
00:39:04,968 --> 00:39:06,510
This is Tsai?

356
00:39:08,471 --> 00:39:12,057
My father. Police lnspector from Shaan.

357
00:39:13,768 --> 00:39:17,771
Homicide must be reported to Chief Yu.

358
00:39:18,606 --> 00:39:20,607
ln addition, the victim is an officer.

359
00:39:20,692 --> 00:39:24,236
You believe the killer is hiding out
in this compound?

360
00:39:25,655 --> 00:39:27,948
l'd put my life on it, sir.

361
00:39:32,162 --> 00:39:33,704
Come with me.

362
00:39:35,498 --> 00:39:38,292
This needs to be resolved, and quickly.

363
00:39:39,169 --> 00:39:42,129
l'll get into the Yu household and get her.

364
00:39:42,505 --> 00:39:45,424
l'll ferret out this Fox
and her gang in no time.

365
00:39:45,508 --> 00:39:50,137
Too dangerous. Yu is a court official
and in charge of security.

366
00:39:50,555 --> 00:39:53,057
This could ruin his reputation and career.

367
00:39:53,141 --> 00:39:55,476
lt might also get Sir Te in trouble.

368
00:39:57,479 --> 00:39:59,438
This calls for the utmost delicacy.

369
00:39:59,522 --> 00:40:05,110
Sir Te, can you find some excuse
to invite Mrs and Miss Yu over?

370
00:40:06,696 --> 00:40:08,489
What do you have in mind?

371
00:40:09,824 --> 00:40:13,077
The best way to trap a fox
is through her cubs.

372
00:40:16,206 --> 00:40:21,585
Oh, my! Mrs Te is spoiling us
with all these gifts.

373
00:40:21,920 --> 00:40:24,922
She is being so considerate
to our daughter.

374
00:40:25,048 --> 00:40:28,342
l'm sorry she's not feeling well enough
to entertain you today.

375
00:40:28,426 --> 00:40:31,136
l heard Sir Te has lost something.

376
00:40:31,346 --> 00:40:34,223
And now Mrs Te is not feeling well.

377
00:40:34,724 --> 00:40:37,351
We know who stole the missing item.

378
00:40:40,355 --> 00:40:43,524
lf the thief returns it

379
00:40:43,858 --> 00:40:47,194
l'm sure Sir Te will pursue
the matter no further.

380
00:40:47,403 --> 00:40:48,904
That's good.

381
00:40:49,197 --> 00:40:53,367
lt's a real annoyance to have
servants who steal.

382
00:40:54,035 --> 00:40:57,788
Sir Te knows that even well-meaning
people sometimes make mistakes.

383
00:40:57,872 --> 00:41:00,165
Some mistakes can ruin
not only themselves

384
00:41:00,250 --> 00:41:02,584
but their entire family as well.

385
00:41:03,795 --> 00:41:05,712
But don't be too lenient.

386
00:41:05,922 --> 00:41:08,966
Sure. For example,
no mercy will be shown to the murderer

387
00:41:09,050 --> 00:41:11,301
who just turned up in Beijing.

388
00:41:11,553 --> 00:41:14,680
-A murderer?
-Yes,

389
00:41:14,848 --> 00:41:18,559
the very killer of Li Mu Bai's own master.

390
00:41:18,935 --> 00:41:22,855
Last night she killed a policeman
who had tracked her for many years.

391
00:41:22,939 --> 00:41:25,566
A female criminal! Now that's news!

392
00:41:25,900 --> 00:41:28,902
You say she killed a policeman?

393
00:41:29,404 --> 00:41:30,821
Yes, from the west.

394
00:41:30,905 --> 00:41:34,575
He went undercover as a street performer,
and followed her here.

395
00:41:34,659 --> 00:41:38,996
l'm no detective, but maybe
the murderer and thief are the same.

396
00:41:39,289 --> 00:41:40,831
l doubt that.

397
00:41:41,416 --> 00:41:45,419
This particular thief is very unusual.

398
00:41:45,628 --> 00:41:48,589
And most likely smarter than a mere killer.

399
00:42:00,602 --> 00:42:04,938
-Greetings, Sir Te.
-Hello, Mrs Yu.

400
00:42:05,273 --> 00:42:08,650
Let me introduce Li Mu Bai,
the renowned swordsman.

401
00:42:09,194 --> 00:42:11,987
lt's a pleasure to meet you,
Mrs Yu, Ms Yu.

402
00:42:12,113 --> 00:42:14,615
Ms Yu is getting married soon.

403
00:42:17,285 --> 00:42:18,952
Congratulations.

404
00:42:32,884 --> 00:42:34,885
Why don't you come in?

405
00:42:35,136 --> 00:42:39,473
-l'm standing guard.
-Come in. lt's cold.

406
00:42:45,647 --> 00:42:49,149
Come in. We don't have to fear
Jade Fox if we're together.

407
00:43:13,841 --> 00:43:16,343
lsn't it a little late to be out?

408
00:43:19,180 --> 00:43:21,139
You can give the sword to me.

409
00:43:21,808 --> 00:43:23,684
l'll do as l please.

410
00:43:26,980 --> 00:43:30,023
-Where's your master?
-None of your business!

411
00:43:56,551 --> 00:43:58,051
Had enough flying?

412
00:44:01,889 --> 00:44:03,265
You've got potential.

413
00:44:03,349 --> 00:44:07,227
But you've misunderstood
Wudang's secret manual quite a bit.

414
00:44:10,231 --> 00:44:12,733
You need a real master.

415
00:44:13,109 --> 00:44:15,694
A master like you? lt's a meaningless title.

416
00:44:15,778 --> 00:44:17,404
You're right, it's all meaningless.

417
00:44:17,488 --> 00:44:20,490
School is meaningless,
the secret manual is meaningless

418
00:44:20,575 --> 00:44:23,577
even this sword.
lt is just a state of mind.

419
00:44:24,620 --> 00:44:27,998
Don't talk like a monk
just because you're in a temple. Just fight!

420
00:44:28,082 --> 00:44:31,418
-Then tell me where Jade Fox is!
-Move!

421
00:44:45,475 --> 00:44:48,393
True strength is light as a feather.

422
00:45:05,620 --> 00:45:07,788
No assistance, no growth.

423
00:45:08,790 --> 00:45:11,124
No reaction, no explanation.

424
00:45:12,001 --> 00:45:13,794
No control, no desire.

425
00:45:14,087 --> 00:45:16,797
Give yourself up and find yourself again.

426
00:45:17,965 --> 00:45:20,342
Here's a lesson for you on life.

427
00:45:25,473 --> 00:45:26,848
Go ahead.

428
00:45:28,684 --> 00:45:30,894
Why should l? You need practise.

429
00:45:30,978 --> 00:45:33,647
Learn to defeat movement with stillness.

430
00:45:33,981 --> 00:45:36,775
That way you'll be worthy
of the Green Destiny.

431
00:45:39,320 --> 00:45:41,321
Why do you want to teach me?

432
00:45:42,865 --> 00:45:47,744
l've always wanted a disciple
worthy of the Wudang secrets.

433
00:45:49,872 --> 00:45:52,749
Aren't you afraid that l'd kill you
once l mastered it?

434
00:45:52,834 --> 00:45:56,086
That's a risk l'm willing to take
as your teacher.

435
00:45:56,170 --> 00:46:00,090
Deep down you're good. Even Jade Fox
hasn't been able to corrupt you.

436
00:46:01,968 --> 00:46:05,512
Wudang is a whorehouse!
Keep your lessons to yourself!

437
00:46:24,574 --> 00:46:27,492
You're home late, or should l say early?

438
00:46:30,371 --> 00:46:34,458
Why are you still here?
You've killed a policeman!

439
00:46:35,209 --> 00:46:37,919
You'll bring ruin on my whole family.

440
00:46:38,212 --> 00:46:42,090
They wouldn't have tracked me here
if you hadn't stolen the sword.

441
00:46:42,508 --> 00:46:46,052
You're not a little girl any more.
You thought this would be fun?

442
00:46:46,387 --> 00:46:48,388
l'm in this, and you're in too.

443
00:46:48,514 --> 00:46:50,557
Come with me, Jen.

444
00:46:50,683 --> 00:46:53,101
You don't want to waste your life

445
00:46:53,561 --> 00:46:57,314
as the wife of some pompous bureaucrat.

446
00:46:57,857 --> 00:47:01,610
-As master and disciple, we will rule.
-l'll never live as a thief.

447
00:47:01,736 --> 00:47:03,695
You're already the most wanted thief!

448
00:47:03,779 --> 00:47:05,197
That was just for fun.
Why would l leave, and where?

449
00:47:08,242 --> 00:47:11,828
Wherever we want.
We'd get rid of anyone in our way.

450
00:47:11,913 --> 00:47:14,039
-Even your father.
-Shut up!

451
00:47:14,123 --> 00:47:17,626
That's the underworld fighter lifestyle.
Kill or be killed.

452
00:47:18,252 --> 00:47:20,921
Exciting, isn't it?

453
00:47:25,051 --> 00:47:29,596
-l've fulfilled my obligations to you.
-No, l have.

454
00:47:31,349 --> 00:47:35,101
To have you as my disciple
is the thing in my life l'm most proud of.

455
00:47:42,151 --> 00:47:46,446
You think you've been teaching me
all these years from the manual?

456
00:47:46,948 --> 00:47:49,241
Thank goodness you're illiterate.

457
00:47:51,244 --> 00:47:53,870
l studied the illustrations,
and you studied the words.

458
00:47:53,955 --> 00:47:56,039
You hid the details from me?

459
00:47:56,123 --> 00:48:00,210
You wouldn't have understood it
even if you knew how to read.

460
00:48:00,336 --> 00:48:04,047
You know you've gone
as far as you will go.

461
00:48:05,049 --> 00:48:07,842
l hid my skills from you because
l was afraid you might get hurt.

462
00:48:10,346 --> 00:48:13,348
lf it weren't for seeing you fight
with Li Mu Bai,

463
00:48:14,392 --> 00:48:17,811
l'd still be ignorant
of all you've hidden from me.

464
00:48:20,690 --> 00:48:21,898
Governess.

465
00:48:23,609 --> 00:48:26,945
l started learning from you
in secret when l was 1 0.

466
00:48:27,363 --> 00:48:30,574
You enchanted me with the dream
of the Jiang Hu underworld.

467
00:48:30,658 --> 00:48:33,952
But once l realised l could exceed you,

468
00:48:34,704 --> 00:48:37,289
you can't imagine how frightened l was!

469
00:48:37,873 --> 00:48:41,585
l had no one to guide me,
no one to follow,

470
00:48:43,421 --> 00:48:45,297
no one to learn from.

471
00:48:47,383 --> 00:48:51,261
There will be more
frightening things ahead.

472
00:50:03,959 --> 00:50:07,045
Are you happy now that the sword is back?

473
00:50:08,506 --> 00:50:12,092
l admit, getting it back made me realise
how much l missed it.

474
00:50:13,969 --> 00:50:16,304
But it's not your sword any more, is it?

475
00:50:16,389 --> 00:50:18,264
You gave it to Sir Te.

476
00:50:20,184 --> 00:50:24,688
True. But l must borrow it for one last job.

477
00:50:25,564 --> 00:50:27,941
Jade Fox will die on its edge.

478
00:50:31,529 --> 00:50:36,074
Did you know what you were hiding
when you covered for that girl?

479
00:50:36,826 --> 00:50:40,286
My job was to recover the sword
without embarrassing anyone.

480
00:50:40,913 --> 00:50:45,667
l wasn't about to ruin her life,
or her father.

481
00:50:46,127 --> 00:50:47,627
You did yourjob well.

482
00:50:47,712 --> 00:50:51,214
The sword is back. But...this girl.

483
00:50:52,800 --> 00:50:54,676
l saw her last night.

484
00:50:56,637 --> 00:50:58,847
l knew you'd be suspicious.

485
00:50:59,140 --> 00:51:00,974
She needs controlling.

486
00:51:01,183 --> 00:51:03,810
She needs real direction and training.

487
00:51:04,520 --> 00:51:07,689
She's an aristocrat's daughter,
she's not one of us.

488
00:51:07,815 --> 00:51:13,319
lt will all be over soon.
You'll kill Fox and she'll marry.

489
00:51:15,573 --> 00:51:19,534
That's not her.
She should become a Wudang disciple.

490
00:51:20,995 --> 00:51:23,037
But Wudang doesn't accept women.

491
00:51:23,372 --> 00:51:25,999
For her, perhaps they could make
an exception.

492
00:51:26,083 --> 00:51:30,003
lf not, left to her own, l'm afraid
she'll become a poisonous dragon.

493
00:51:30,629 --> 00:51:33,173
lt's not our affair.

494
00:51:33,507 --> 00:51:37,635
Even if Wudang accepts her,
her husband might object.

495
00:51:41,682 --> 00:51:46,186
l thought by giving away the sword,
l could escape the Jiang Hu world.

496
00:51:46,520 --> 00:51:49,814
But the cycle of bloodshed continues.

497
00:51:51,692 --> 00:51:53,526
l had hoped so, too.

498
00:51:54,069 --> 00:51:57,197
l wish there were something
l could do to help you.

499
00:52:02,369 --> 00:52:05,038
Just be patient with me, Shu Lien.

500
00:52:21,889 --> 00:52:23,097
Freeze!

501
00:52:26,685 --> 00:52:29,020
-Lo!
-Jen!

502
00:52:42,284 --> 00:52:44,410
You shouldn't have come.

503
00:52:46,413 --> 00:52:49,541
With all the traffic
on your rooftop these days

504
00:52:50,125 --> 00:52:54,087
it took me a while to get in here.
l can't wait any longer, Jen.

505
00:52:54,213 --> 00:52:56,047
l was wrong to let you go.

506
00:52:57,383 --> 00:53:00,635
Come with me, back to the desert.
You'll be happy there.

507
00:53:01,095 --> 00:53:03,096
You can do whatever you want.

508
00:53:05,599 --> 00:53:08,726
<i>You have been looking for me all this time?</i>

509
00:53:31,333 --> 00:53:33,459
Jen, stop playing with it.

510
00:53:34,795 --> 00:53:36,546
l won't break it.

511
00:53:58,777 --> 00:53:59,986
Charge!

512
00:54:02,823 --> 00:54:03,990
Stop!

513
00:54:04,992 --> 00:54:06,576
lt's Dark Cloud!

514
00:54:06,660 --> 00:54:08,578
Dark Cloud is coming!

515
00:54:24,303 --> 00:54:27,013
Lower the shade, don't be seen!

516
00:54:27,097 --> 00:54:29,098
Don't be afraid, Miss.

517
00:54:44,865 --> 00:54:47,200
Don't touch the women!

518
00:55:33,914 --> 00:55:36,040
Come!

519
00:56:24,757 --> 00:56:25,798
Hey!

520
00:56:27,176 --> 00:56:29,844
Your mother is fine.
Hurry back to your mother.

521
00:57:29,363 --> 00:57:30,655
Hey!

522
00:57:31,657 --> 00:57:34,450
She's mine! Leave her to me!

523
00:57:44,878 --> 00:57:47,839
-Let's take a break.
-Give me back my comb!

524
00:57:50,050 --> 00:57:52,385
Take a break.

525
00:57:53,887 --> 00:57:56,180
You're tired. You need rest.

526
00:58:02,229 --> 00:58:05,523
Your horse needs water.
There's a spring up here.

527
00:58:13,073 --> 00:58:15,741
Well, there was when l last visited.

528
00:58:22,708 --> 00:58:23,875
Your name?

529
00:58:25,169 --> 00:58:28,421
My name is Lo.
The Hans call me Dark Cloud.

530
00:58:29,214 --> 00:58:32,550
l'm not that tall or that big,
but l'm quick as lightning.

531
00:58:33,010 --> 00:58:34,177
Here.

532
00:58:45,898 --> 00:58:47,398
Give me my comb.

533
01:00:23,161 --> 01:00:25,913
lf you like that, l can make you a bow.

534
01:00:26,373 --> 01:00:28,499
Great for hunting pheasants.

535
01:00:28,709 --> 01:00:30,376
They're delicious.

536
01:00:35,882 --> 01:00:38,592
You need to eat something. Understand?

537
01:00:39,636 --> 01:00:42,638
That way, you'll have the strength to fight.

538
01:00:44,599 --> 01:00:46,017
Understand?

539
01:00:55,277 --> 01:00:58,446
You'll slowly regain your strength.
Don't rush.

540
01:03:04,573 --> 01:03:07,867
You have a bad temper.
lt's much better this way.

541
01:03:14,416 --> 01:03:15,875
You coward!

542
01:03:19,212 --> 01:03:22,631
Still in a bad mood? But you're speaking.

543
01:03:23,550 --> 01:03:25,176
What's your name?

544
01:03:26,761 --> 01:03:29,763
l didn't think the Hans had names like that.

545
01:04:09,387 --> 01:04:13,641
Relax. lf l wanted to do what you think
l want to do, l'd have done it already.

546
01:04:14,976 --> 01:04:17,102
You must be dying for a bath.

547
01:04:17,187 --> 01:04:20,481
The water source is far,
and difficult to get to.

548
01:04:21,316 --> 01:04:23,734
l managed to bring back some fresh water.

549
01:04:23,818 --> 01:04:26,362
You can wear my clothes
when you are done.

550
01:04:26,780 --> 01:04:28,322
They're clean.

551
01:04:44,464 --> 01:04:45,923
Don't worry.

552
01:04:48,301 --> 01:04:51,303
l'll sing a song, so you'll know where l am.

553
01:04:52,889 --> 01:04:55,891
After the bath, you will calm down a little.

554
01:04:57,143 --> 01:05:00,062
But promise me,
no more rocks on the head.

555
01:06:12,010 --> 01:06:16,221
-All this trouble, just for a comb?
-lt's mine.

556
01:06:17,766 --> 01:06:21,894
And it's worth a lot to me.
But to a barbarian like you, it's nothing.

557
01:06:22,520 --> 01:06:25,981
Not true. l can use it
to pick fleas from my horse.

558
01:06:26,941 --> 01:06:29,568
By the way, l'm a real Manchurian.

559
01:06:32,155 --> 01:06:34,406
l'm sorry, l guessed wrong.

560
01:06:35,075 --> 01:06:37,159
l thought you were a Han.

561
01:06:39,287 --> 01:06:40,913
Give me back my comb.

562
01:06:45,168 --> 01:06:47,670
l don't take orders from anyone.

563
01:06:54,260 --> 01:06:55,803
Give it to me.

564
01:08:13,923 --> 01:08:16,842
<i>One night, when l was a boy</i>

565
01:08:16,926 --> 01:08:19,887
<i>l saw a thousand stars fall out of the sky.</i>

566
01:08:21,181 --> 01:08:24,141
<i>l remember thinking,</i>
<i>where did they all go?</i>

567
01:08:24,642 --> 01:08:27,770
<i>l'm an orphan.</i>
<i>l used to look for stars alone.</i>

568
01:08:29,773 --> 01:08:33,525
Maybe if l rode to the other end
of the desert, l'd find them.

569
01:08:35,653 --> 01:08:38,572
l've been riding in the desert ever since.

570
01:08:40,116 --> 01:08:42,701
And that little boy became
a fearsome bandit.

571
01:08:42,786 --> 01:08:46,121
Couldn't find the stars,
so now he steals my comb.

572
01:08:47,207 --> 01:08:50,209
Out there,
you're always fighting for survival.

573
01:08:51,252 --> 01:08:54,213
You have to gang up
just to stand a chance.

574
01:08:54,964 --> 01:08:57,883
Slowly, your gang becomes your family.

575
01:08:59,010 --> 01:09:02,221
All that Dark Cloud stuff
is just propaganda

576
01:09:02,305 --> 01:09:04,306
but it does make my life easier.

577
01:09:05,433 --> 01:09:08,101
So you are still the little boy at heart

578
01:09:08,186 --> 01:09:10,103
looking for fallen stars.

579
01:09:11,898 --> 01:09:17,611
l am a man. And l've found
the brightest star of them all.

580
01:09:40,635 --> 01:09:43,345
Your father's men are looking for you.

581
01:10:13,543 --> 01:10:16,420
They're still out there, circling closer.

582
01:10:18,131 --> 01:10:19,715
Let them look.

583
01:10:21,009 --> 01:10:23,969
They'll keep looking. lt's trouble for me.

584
01:10:26,139 --> 01:10:28,724
Don't even think of sending me back.

585
01:10:30,810 --> 01:10:32,269
lt's up to you.

586
01:10:32,604 --> 01:10:35,606
You might get tired of this

587
01:10:37,483 --> 01:10:39,818
and start missing your family.

588
01:10:40,987 --> 01:10:43,989
lf we had a daughter,
we'd look for her, too.

589
01:10:44,157 --> 01:10:45,908
She'd miss us, too.

590
01:10:51,748 --> 01:10:55,375
Jen, l want you to be mine forever.

591
01:10:57,378 --> 01:11:01,506
What if l make my mark on the world,
earn your parents' respect?

592
01:11:02,800 --> 01:11:06,762
We have a legend. Anyone who dares
to jump from the mountain,

593
01:11:07,055 --> 01:11:09,222
God will fulfil a wish of his.

594
01:11:09,974 --> 01:11:13,518
A long time ago, a man's parents were ill,
so he jumped.

595
01:11:14,938 --> 01:11:17,689
He didn't die, wasn't even wounded.

596
01:11:19,025 --> 01:11:22,194
He just floated away, far away,
never to return.

597
01:11:23,780 --> 01:11:25,822
He knew his wish had come true.

598
01:11:27,200 --> 01:11:29,534
lf you believe in it, it will happen.

599
01:11:30,370 --> 01:11:32,454
l've asked Han people, they say,

600
01:11:32,914 --> 01:11:35,791
"A sincere heart will make
your dreams come true."

601
01:11:46,427 --> 01:11:48,053
Keep it safe.

602
01:11:49,305 --> 01:11:52,057
And return it to me
when we are together again.

603
01:11:54,602 --> 01:11:55,894
l will.

604
01:12:03,444 --> 01:12:07,239
lf you don't return it to me,
l will have to chase you down.

605
01:12:07,991 --> 01:12:10,701
And next time, l won't go easy on you.

606
01:12:22,463 --> 01:12:25,924
Wherever l went,
they always recognised me.

607
01:12:26,718 --> 01:12:28,301
l really tried.

608
01:12:31,597 --> 01:12:35,434
l heard you came to Beijing.
l was afraid l'd never see you again.

609
01:12:36,436 --> 01:12:38,061
So l came.

610
01:12:39,147 --> 01:12:41,857
l can't let you get married like that.

611
01:12:45,111 --> 01:12:46,194
Go back.

612
01:12:47,196 --> 01:12:48,405
Jen.

613
01:12:51,200 --> 01:12:54,202
-Don't ever come back.
-This is it?

614
01:12:56,456 --> 01:12:57,622
Yes.

615
01:13:13,347 --> 01:13:15,599
We heard noises. ls everything all right?

616
01:13:15,683 --> 01:13:17,768
Fine. lt was just a cat.

617
01:13:34,869 --> 01:13:37,329
You think Jade Fox will show up?

618
01:13:37,580 --> 01:13:39,331
She must be nearby.

619
01:13:39,916 --> 01:13:42,334
But l doubt she'll show herself.

620
01:13:42,835 --> 01:13:48,256
We'll keep our eyes open.
She'll come for the girl sooner or later.

621
01:14:07,902 --> 01:14:09,736
Jen!

622
01:14:17,411 --> 01:14:20,122
Go back to Xin Jiang with me.

623
01:14:25,086 --> 01:14:29,506
Let go of me.

624
01:14:34,137 --> 01:14:35,387
You're mine.

625
01:14:35,888 --> 01:14:37,889
Go back to Xin Jiang with me.

626
01:14:50,736 --> 01:14:53,446
Jen, come back to Xin Jiang with me.

627
01:14:59,328 --> 01:15:03,039
-Tell me. Where is Jade Fox?
-Come with me. Hurry.

628
01:15:06,961 --> 01:15:10,755
You really thought she'd give it all up
and go back west with you?

629
01:15:12,300 --> 01:15:15,135
-She's mine.
-Whether she's yours or not

630
01:15:15,428 --> 01:15:19,097
you will be no good to her dead.
With Gou and Yu hunting you,

631
01:15:19,182 --> 01:15:21,933
it won't be long until
you're in their hands.

632
01:15:22,310 --> 01:15:24,269
l don't care any more.

633
01:15:26,105 --> 01:15:29,274
lf you truly loved her,
you wouldn't say that.

634
01:15:31,444 --> 01:15:33,945
Don't you want to see her again?

635
01:15:36,449 --> 01:15:40,035
l'll write an introduction for you.
Take it to Wudang Mountain.

636
01:15:40,203 --> 01:15:42,454
Wait there for news from me.

637
01:15:44,707 --> 01:15:45,957
Okay.

638
01:15:54,342 --> 01:15:56,885
When will this end?

639
01:15:57,136 --> 01:15:59,971
They take it, put it back, and take it again.

640
01:16:00,139 --> 01:16:03,308
My place is no better than a warehouse.

641
01:16:04,310 --> 01:16:05,560
Come in.

642
01:16:07,355 --> 01:16:09,814
-Speak.
-Jen Yu's run away.

643
01:16:10,149 --> 01:16:12,400
The groom found her missing.

644
01:16:12,485 --> 01:16:15,028
Chief Yu requests your assistance

645
01:16:15,488 --> 01:16:18,114
since you know
the Jiang Hu underworld so well.

646
01:16:18,199 --> 01:16:21,201
He wants to find her
and keep her from harm.

647
01:16:22,245 --> 01:16:25,497
Sir Te, leave this to us. Don't worry.

648
01:16:44,392 --> 01:16:46,351
What can l serve you?

649
01:16:48,187 --> 01:16:50,021
This cup is dirty.

650
01:17:04,537 --> 01:17:09,541
Hi there. May l ask your name?

651
01:17:10,626 --> 01:17:11,876
Long.

652
01:17:13,629 --> 01:17:16,548
lt's young master Long. My apologies!

653
01:17:17,049 --> 01:17:19,384
l'm lron Eagle Sung.

654
01:17:20,052 --> 01:17:23,471
This is my fellow brother,
Flying Cougar Li Yun.

655
01:17:23,639 --> 01:17:27,475
What brings you to Huai An
and where are you headed, Master Long?

656
01:17:28,936 --> 01:17:31,062
Anywhere there's action.

657
01:17:31,230 --> 01:17:34,899
ln that case,
perhaps we could be of assistance.

658
01:17:36,277 --> 01:17:37,819
Don't bother.

659
01:17:39,447 --> 01:17:41,906
You don't seem to be getting our drift.

660
01:17:43,909 --> 01:17:45,744
So what if l don't?

661
01:17:47,079 --> 01:17:50,623
We have ways of dealing with people
who don't get it.

662
01:17:59,175 --> 01:18:01,760
Are you related to Li Mu Bai?

663
01:18:04,430 --> 01:18:06,598
He's my defeated foe.

664
01:18:25,159 --> 01:18:26,534
Some tea.

665
01:18:56,065 --> 01:18:57,357
Shu Lien.

666
01:18:57,900 --> 01:19:00,735
There's no eternity
to the things we can touch.

667
01:19:03,072 --> 01:19:04,864
My master used to say,

668
01:19:04,990 --> 01:19:07,826
"There's nothing we can hold onto
in this world.

669
01:19:09,578 --> 01:19:12,872
"Only by letting go can we
finally possess what is real."

670
01:19:13,999 --> 01:19:18,002
Even to an old Taoist like you,
not everything is an illusion.

671
01:19:18,212 --> 01:19:21,798
When you were holding my hand just now,
wasn't that real?

672
01:19:24,385 --> 01:19:28,763
Your hand is cold and callused
from practising machetes.

673
01:19:29,223 --> 01:19:33,935
All these years,
and l've never had the courage to touch it.

674
01:19:35,771 --> 01:19:38,440
Crouching tigers and hidden dragons
are in the underworld

675
01:19:38,524 --> 01:19:40,692
but so are human feelings.

676
01:19:40,901 --> 01:19:44,904
Swords and knives harbour unknown
perils, but so do human relationships.

677
01:19:46,198 --> 01:19:48,867
l gave away the Green Destiny
with sincerity.

678
01:19:49,034 --> 01:19:51,411
But it brought us more troubles.

679
01:19:51,537 --> 01:19:54,581
Repressing your feelings
will only make them stronger.

680
01:19:54,707 --> 01:19:56,416
l can't repress my desire.

681
01:19:57,710 --> 01:19:59,878
l want to be with you.

682
01:20:02,548 --> 01:20:04,257
Just sitting like this

683
01:20:05,968 --> 01:20:08,178
gives me a sense of peace.

684
01:20:26,739 --> 01:20:28,448
Please follow me.

685
01:20:30,284 --> 01:20:33,578
-l want a clean room.
-There are plenty of rooms.

686
01:20:35,623 --> 01:20:38,666
-What would you like to eat?
-Some steamed cod, fried ribs,

687
01:20:38,751 --> 01:20:41,211
meatballs, not too big, with little starch!

688
01:20:41,295 --> 01:20:44,672
And cabbage soup with shark fins,
plus a bottle of warm rose wine.

689
01:20:44,757 --> 01:20:47,467
l have to order them from
a bigger restaurant.

690
01:20:47,593 --> 01:20:49,594
-Hurry then.
-Yes.

691
01:21:32,304 --> 01:21:33,680
lt's him.

692
01:21:42,523 --> 01:21:44,691
l am lron Arm Mi.

693
01:21:44,984 --> 01:21:48,570
l heard a true master has arrived.

694
01:21:48,654 --> 01:21:50,947
l have come to seek a lesson.

695
01:22:03,502 --> 01:22:05,003
You asked for it!

696
01:22:25,357 --> 01:22:27,317
What kind of lron Arm are you?

697
01:22:42,583 --> 01:22:46,669
That's amazing technique!
l am Flying Machete.

698
01:22:46,754 --> 01:22:49,380
Are you related to Southern Crane?

699
01:22:49,882 --> 01:22:52,842
Southern Duck?
l don't eat anything with two feet.

700
01:22:53,093 --> 01:22:55,428
Who could remember such lengthy names?

701
01:22:55,679 --> 01:22:56,721
You!

702
01:22:56,847 --> 01:23:01,684
lf Li Mu Bai is your defeated foe,
why don't you know his master?

703
01:23:03,020 --> 01:23:04,270
Who are you?

704
01:23:05,397 --> 01:23:09,776
l'm Phoenix Mountain Gou.

705
01:23:10,694 --> 01:23:14,113
Gou? l hate that name.

706
01:23:14,281 --> 01:23:16,699
l feel like throwing up
when l hear that name.

707
01:23:16,784 --> 01:23:21,245
Too bad you're named Gou!
You'll be the first to taste my sword today.

708
01:23:43,602 --> 01:23:47,605
Hold it! Don't you know Monk Jing?

709
01:23:48,399 --> 01:23:51,025
A monk eating meat and not reading
scriptures? You need a lesson, too.

710
01:23:51,110 --> 01:23:55,279
-Who the hell are you?
-l am...

711
01:23:55,489 --> 01:23:56,739
l am...

712
01:23:56,824 --> 01:23:58,950
Be careful of her sword!

713
01:24:01,787 --> 01:24:04,622
...the invincible Sword Goddess

714
01:24:05,999 --> 01:24:10,586
with the Green Destiny
that has no equal

715
01:24:15,467 --> 01:24:17,969
be it Li or Southern Eagle.

716
01:24:19,596 --> 01:24:22,265
Lower your head and ask for mercy!

717
01:24:29,481 --> 01:24:31,816
l'm the dragon from the desert

718
01:24:40,951 --> 01:24:43,828
with no trace to be discovered
in my wake.

719
01:24:54,173 --> 01:24:57,508
Today l fly over Eh-Mei Mountain,

720
01:24:59,678 --> 01:25:03,347
tomorrow, l'll uproot
the last dregs of Wudang!

721
01:25:18,822 --> 01:25:22,867
We politely asked for a friendly match,
but she showed no respect

722
01:25:23,076 --> 01:25:24,368
and started to reproach and attack us.

723
01:25:24,453 --> 01:25:28,122
My friends offered to come by
and teach her a lesson.

724
01:25:28,207 --> 01:25:30,374
Her sword is just too powerful.

725
01:25:30,542 --> 01:25:34,086
l've travelled far and wide,
but l've never met anyone that uncivilised.

726
01:25:34,171 --> 01:25:38,090
She kept accusing me of being
the brother of Gou Jun Pei.

727
01:25:38,509 --> 01:25:41,219
Who is this guy Gou, anyway?

728
01:25:43,055 --> 01:25:44,555
Her husband.

729
01:25:56,735 --> 01:26:00,613
Sun Security is nearby. Why don't you
go home and see how things are going?

730
01:26:00,697 --> 01:26:04,200
-What about you?
-l'll look around and catch up later.

731
01:26:04,576 --> 01:26:07,703
Not a bad idea.
Let's stay at Sun Security tonight.

732
01:26:07,788 --> 01:26:09,914
-Get a good night's sleep.
-Yes.

733
01:26:35,607 --> 01:26:37,275
-You are back.
-Yes.

734
01:26:41,947 --> 01:26:43,823
You're back, Master!

735
01:26:45,450 --> 01:26:47,869
-Hello guys. How's home?
-Things are fine.

736
01:26:47,953 --> 01:26:51,414
-You've been gone a while.
-Something came up. l leave tomorrow.

737
01:26:51,498 --> 01:26:53,541
-Wei, your wife was due?
-Yes, a baby girl.

738
01:26:53,625 --> 01:26:56,711
-A girl? Good.
-l'd be happy if she grows up like you.

739
01:26:58,005 --> 01:27:00,923
-Mrs Wu.
-You're back!

740
01:27:01,341 --> 01:27:04,218
-How's the arm? Still sore?
-Much better.

741
01:27:04,720 --> 01:27:06,637
l've been worried about you.

742
01:27:07,890 --> 01:27:10,641
Mrs Wu,
Li Mu Bai is coming to stay the night.

743
01:27:12,144 --> 01:27:15,062
Really? l'll go and tidy up the room then.

744
01:27:44,259 --> 01:27:45,718
Sister Yu!

745
01:27:52,351 --> 01:27:55,519
You came to find me.
Let's find you some proper clothes.

746
01:27:55,604 --> 01:27:59,148
l'm just borrowing them.
l'm not moving in.

747
01:28:00,692 --> 01:28:04,195
You get around pretty well.
l don't think you need my clothes.

748
01:28:05,572 --> 01:28:09,200
l just happened to be around.
l wanted to see how you're doing.

749
01:28:10,702 --> 01:28:12,203
Sister...

750
01:28:15,040 --> 01:28:17,875
Now, now.
With all the trouble you've caused,

751
01:28:17,960 --> 01:28:20,711
now you know what Jiang Hu life
is really like.

752
01:28:20,796 --> 01:28:23,965
You came here,
that means you think of me as your sister.

753
01:28:24,049 --> 01:28:27,009
lf so, let me give you some sisterly advice.

754
01:28:27,511 --> 01:28:31,097
You don't have to marry,
you can't just leave your parents.

755
01:28:31,640 --> 01:28:34,475
But they're the ones
who forced me to get married.

756
01:28:34,559 --> 01:28:38,521
Go back to your parents first.
Then you can decide about Lo.

757
01:28:40,565 --> 01:28:42,358
You know about Lo?

758
01:28:50,409 --> 01:28:53,327
He really loves you.

759
01:28:54,246 --> 01:28:58,207
Come back to Beijing with me.
We'll figure a way out for you.

760
01:29:02,546 --> 01:29:05,965
-Where is he now?
-Li Mu Bai has made arrangements.

761
01:29:07,551 --> 01:29:11,262
-Li Mu Bai?
-He sent him to Wudang Mountain.

762
01:29:12,848 --> 01:29:15,766
So, you're all working together
to set me up.

763
01:29:15,934 --> 01:29:18,102
Shut up! How dare you accuse us!

764
01:29:18,270 --> 01:29:20,771
From the beginning,
l knew you stole the Green Destiny!

765
01:29:20,856 --> 01:29:23,274
l've done nothing but protect you
and your family.

766
01:29:23,442 --> 01:29:25,943
And you've repaid me
with nothing but contempt.

767
01:29:26,028 --> 01:29:28,904
Li Mu Bai spared you,
and all you do is insult him.

768
01:29:28,989 --> 01:29:32,408
All we hoped for was a little peace,
and you've ruined it for us!

769
01:29:32,492 --> 01:29:34,577
You're no sister of mine!

770
01:29:36,830 --> 01:29:38,706
l don't give a damn.

771
01:29:39,207 --> 01:29:41,792
Friendship is not real anyway.

772
01:29:41,877 --> 01:29:45,546
But l wonder,
how long could you last as my enemy?

773
01:29:48,300 --> 01:29:50,134
Put the sword down.

774
01:30:00,687 --> 01:30:01,979
Jen!

775
01:30:05,150 --> 01:30:07,443
Everyone out. Shut the doors.

776
01:30:18,538 --> 01:30:20,623
Fine. No more friendship.

777
01:33:36,569 --> 01:33:38,654
That's Li Mu Bai's sword.

778
01:33:39,948 --> 01:33:42,199
Come and get it if you can.

779
01:33:42,742 --> 01:33:45,911
You just rely on the Green Destiny
to do your fighting.

780
01:33:46,496 --> 01:33:49,623
Don't blame the weapon
if you can't fight me.

781
01:33:53,128 --> 01:33:55,212
Go ahead. Take your pick.

782
01:33:56,047 --> 01:33:57,172
l'll wait.

783
01:33:59,551 --> 01:34:00,592
Go ahead.

784
01:34:55,815 --> 01:34:57,566
Give me the sword.

785
01:34:59,527 --> 01:35:00,611
Take it!

786
01:35:05,492 --> 01:35:06,658
Stop!

787
01:35:09,954 --> 01:35:11,622
You are not worthy of this sword.

788
01:35:11,873 --> 01:35:14,208
Not another lecture! On guard!

789
01:35:16,628 --> 01:35:20,422
-Stop yourself before l do.
-Now the sword will settle it.

790
01:35:56,042 --> 01:36:00,671
l didn't force you at the monastery
because l wanted to see the real you.

791
01:36:06,261 --> 01:36:09,263
What do you know about seeing
a true heart?

792
01:37:51,115 --> 01:37:54,201
-Why can't you leave me alone?
-l'll say it again,

793
01:37:54,285 --> 01:37:55,994
let me teach you.

794
01:38:28,611 --> 01:38:31,989
Okay, if you can take back the sword
in three moves

795
01:38:32,991 --> 01:38:35,033
l will go with you.

796
01:38:39,122 --> 01:38:41,123
-Give it back.
-Greet your master.

797
01:38:41,207 --> 01:38:43,458
-You wish.
-Then the sword is useless.

798
01:39:58,951 --> 01:40:02,579
lt's only a matter of time before
those guys get their revenge.

799
01:40:02,830 --> 01:40:06,625
Your parents value their reputation.
They'll never take you back.

800
01:40:09,629 --> 01:40:14,216
What good's a home? You've gone so far.
Now we can go all the way together.

801
01:40:14,926 --> 01:40:17,010
You'll always be my Lady.

802
01:40:20,014 --> 01:40:23,934
After all, happiness is the most
important thing in life, isn't it?

803
01:40:24,143 --> 01:40:26,645
We'll be our own masters at last.

804
01:40:27,271 --> 01:40:30,399
All we have left is each other, isn't that so?

805
01:40:35,113 --> 01:40:37,030
Now lie down and rest.

806
01:40:59,887 --> 01:41:02,764
Crazy girl like that,
you should have killed her.

807
01:41:02,849 --> 01:41:04,975
l didn't have the heart to do it.

808
01:41:05,101 --> 01:41:07,269
Maybe Li Mu Bai can do it.

809
01:42:18,132 --> 01:42:20,509
ls it me or the sword you want?

810
01:42:40,863 --> 01:42:42,739
You've been drugged.

811
01:43:00,633 --> 01:43:02,342
Where's Jade Fox?

812
01:43:44,844 --> 01:43:46,553
What's going on?

813
01:43:47,638 --> 01:43:49,514
Jade Fox drugged her.

814
01:43:50,057 --> 01:43:51,933
How did you get here?

815
01:43:54,103 --> 01:43:55,979
We followed Jade Fox.

816
01:43:58,900 --> 01:44:00,400
Watch out!

817
01:44:10,494 --> 01:44:11,912
Governess!

818
01:44:26,177 --> 01:44:28,136
This is the end of the road.

819
01:44:30,389 --> 01:44:32,140
For you too.

820
01:44:40,483 --> 01:44:42,275
A poisoned needle!

821
01:44:45,988 --> 01:44:47,822
You deserve to die

822
01:44:49,575 --> 01:44:51,409
but l was really

823
01:44:51,869 --> 01:44:54,287
aiming at Jen.

824
01:44:56,165 --> 01:44:58,166
Ten years l sacrificed

825
01:44:58,542 --> 01:45:00,585
but you deceived me.

826
01:45:01,671 --> 01:45:05,256
You hid the book's true meaning.
l never improved

827
01:45:06,676 --> 01:45:10,345
but your progress was limitless.

828
01:45:12,556 --> 01:45:14,557
You know what poison is?

829
01:45:15,309 --> 01:45:18,144
An eight-year-old girl who's full of deceit!

830
01:45:18,646 --> 01:45:20,355
That's poison!

831
01:45:24,360 --> 01:45:25,485
Jen!

832
01:45:27,321 --> 01:45:28,822
My only love,

833
01:45:30,241 --> 01:45:31,741
my only enemy!

834
01:45:41,252 --> 01:45:44,546
You can't die! Tell us,
what poison did you use?

835
01:45:44,755 --> 01:45:46,381
What poison?

836
01:45:46,882 --> 01:45:49,426
You can't die, tell us the antidote!

837
01:45:49,719 --> 01:45:52,429
You can't let him die! Li Mu Bai can't die!

838
01:45:52,555 --> 01:45:54,889
-lt's the Purple Yin Poison.
-What?

839
01:45:55,766 --> 01:45:59,102
Purple Yin Poison.
lt goes straight to the heart.

840
01:46:02,023 --> 01:46:05,567
My blood will stop flowing
within two hours.

841
01:46:07,278 --> 01:46:10,280
lt's the same poison that killed my master.

842
01:46:11,949 --> 01:46:15,201
-There's no antidote.
-There must be an antidote!

843
01:46:15,786 --> 01:46:19,456
Every living thing has its antithesis.
And not this?

844
01:46:20,791 --> 01:46:23,543
There is. Fox taught it to me.

845
01:46:24,045 --> 01:46:28,465
The recipe isn't complicated, but the
ingredients are hard to find. lt takes time.

846
01:46:35,473 --> 01:46:37,140
Please, trust me.

847
01:46:37,641 --> 01:46:40,810
As you have helped me, let me help him.

848
01:46:43,481 --> 01:46:45,440
All right. Hurry up.

849
01:46:45,983 --> 01:46:48,234
Maybe l can hold on for two hours.

850
01:46:48,319 --> 01:46:50,904
Ride my horse to headquarters.
They have the ingredients.

851
01:46:50,988 --> 01:46:53,490
Give this to Mrs Wu.
She'll help you. Hurry!

852
01:46:53,949 --> 01:46:57,327
Save your breath.
Guard your energy. l'll be back.

853
01:47:22,937 --> 01:47:24,604
Who is this?

854
01:47:26,899 --> 01:47:29,275
Mrs Wu! Where's Mrs Wu?

855
01:47:29,485 --> 01:47:30,819
Stop it!

856
01:47:32,196 --> 01:47:34,989
Yu gave me this
and told me to come to you.

857
01:47:36,117 --> 01:47:37,826
Let her come in!

858
01:47:51,715 --> 01:47:54,050
Mu Bai, hold on.

859
01:47:58,556 --> 01:48:00,348
Give me some hope.

860
01:48:25,249 --> 01:48:26,708
Shu Lien.

861
01:48:28,252 --> 01:48:30,336
Don't waste your breath.

862
01:48:32,256 --> 01:48:34,215
My life is departing.

863
01:48:36,010 --> 01:48:38,094
l've only one breath left.

864
01:48:40,598 --> 01:48:43,266
Use your last bit of strength to meditate.

865
01:48:43,767 --> 01:48:48,271
Free yourself from this world
as you've been taught.

866
01:48:49,899 --> 01:48:54,068
Let your soul rise to eternity
with your last breath.

867
01:48:56,238 --> 01:48:59,407
Don't waste it on me.

868
01:49:02,870 --> 01:49:05,455
l've already wasted my whole life.

869
01:49:06,790 --> 01:49:09,626
l want to tell you
with my remaining strength

870
01:49:11,462 --> 01:49:13,796
that l love you. l always have.

871
01:49:49,583 --> 01:49:53,503
l'll drift next to you everyday as a ghost

872
01:49:54,922 --> 01:49:56,756
just to be with you.

873
01:49:59,510 --> 01:50:02,762
Even if l was banished
to the darkest place,

874
01:50:05,307 --> 01:50:06,516
my love

875
01:50:10,104 --> 01:50:13,982
will keep me from being a lonely spirit.

876
01:51:10,122 --> 01:51:11,581
He's gone?

877
01:51:40,903 --> 01:51:42,445
Bo,

878
01:51:43,113 --> 01:51:45,740
please take this sword back to Sir Te's.

879
01:51:52,956 --> 01:51:57,210
You may go to Wudang Mountain.
Lo awaits you there.

880
01:51:58,670 --> 01:52:02,924
Promise me whatever path
you decide to take in this life,

881
01:52:04,093 --> 01:52:05,927
be true to yourself.

882
01:52:53,684 --> 01:52:54,851
Jen!

883
01:53:55,704 --> 01:53:56,787
Jen.

884
01:54:00,459 --> 01:54:03,127
Remember the story
you told me in the desert?

885
01:54:05,422 --> 01:54:08,424
Have faith, then the dreams will come true.

886
01:54:14,640 --> 01:54:16,390
Make a wish, Lo.

887
01:54:18,936 --> 01:54:22,438
l wish that we'll be in the desert,
together again.

