Cold this morning, Captain.
Cold.
And hard.
lt's time, captain.
lt's time.
Time indeed.
Time to open the orders, sir.
The Political Officer is in your cabin.
Very well.
You have the conn.
What are you doing?
l must oversee
the stability of the crew, Captain.
By invading my privacy?
Privacy is not a major concern
in the Soviet Union, comrade.
It's often contrary to the collective good.
"Behold, I am coming as a thief. . .
"And they gathered them together
"In a place called. . .
"Armageddon."
He's turning green.
You speak Russian.
A little.
It's wise to study
the ways of one's adversary.
Don't you think?
The Captain is fighting them.
The Captain is fighting the Americans.
Captain scared 'em out of the water!
FORCED subtitles by LL