Subtitles by explosiveskull
Sync by GoldenBeard
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
OMAR: Hey, look! Over there!
Wow!
LIAN:
Their ship is so big.
OMAR: Wish ours
was that fancy.
I'd be so happy
if ours was that fancy.
- 'Cause then...
- MARINER: Why is that?
Because it looks better?
This boat has seen us
through many a storm.
It may not look like much,
but it has something
theirs never will.
What? Wood rot and rats?
(OMAR AND LIAN GIGGLE)
WOMAN: Are the children
learning something, dear?
It is unclear.
All right,
(CLAPS HANDS)
sit, children.
I think it's time
that I told you the story...
of Aladdin, the princess,
and the lamp.
What's so special
about a lamp?
Oh,
this is a magic lamp.
Maybe if you sing.
It's better
when you sing.
No, no. No singing.
It's been a long day.
♪ Oh, imagine a land
It's a faraway place
♪ Where the caravan
Camels roam
♪ Where you wander among
Ev'ry culture and tongue
♪ It's chaotic
But hey, it's home
♪ When the wind's
From the east
♪ And the sun's
From the west
♪ And the sand
In the glass is right
♪ Come on down, stop on by
Hop a carpet and fly
♪ To another Arabian night
(MARINER CHUCKLES)
(MIDDLE EASTERN MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MAN: Hey! Psh!
MARINER: ♪ As you wind
Through the streets
♪ And the fabled bazaars
♪ With the cardamom-cluttered
Stalls
♪ You can smell e'vry spice
While you haggle the price
♪ Of the silks
And the satin shawls
♪ Oh, the music that plays
As you move through a maze
♪ In the haze
Of your pure delight
♪ You are caught in a dance
You are lost in the trance
♪ Of another Arabian night
♪ Arabian nights
♪ Like Arabian days
♪ More often than not
Are hotter than hot
♪ In a lot of good ways
♪ Arabian nights
♪ Like Arabian dreams
♪ This mystical land
Of magic and sand
♪ Is more than it seems
♪ There's a road
♪ That may lead you
♪ To good or to greed
♪ Through the power
Your wishing commands
♪ Let the darkness unfold
Or find fortunes untold
♪ Well, your destiny
Lies in your hands
LION'S HEAD:
Only one may enter here.
One whose worth
lies far within.
The diamond in the rough.
MARINER:
♪ Arabian nights
♪ Like Arabian days
♪ They seem to excite
Take off and take flight
♪ To shock and amaze
LION'S HEAD: Seek thee out
the diamond in the rough.
MARINER:
♪ Arabian nights
♪ 'Neath Arabian moons
♪ A fool off his guard
♪ Could fall and fall hard
♪ Out there on the dunes ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What's your monkey's name?
- Abu.
- (ABU CHITTERING)
He's a lovely monkey.
Hmm.
That's a lovely necklace.
So, where does Abu come from?
He, uh...
Oh!
I think this belongs to me.
Good day, ladies.
Okay.
Abu.
(MAN SHOUTING)
(CHITTERING)
(GRUNTS)
How'd we do, Abu?
- Good monkey.
- (CHITTERS)
Stop right there, Aladdin.
Whatever it is you stole
today, I don't want it.
Whoa, whoa.
I didn't steal anything.
It's a family heirloom
that's worth a lot.
I'll give you a bag of dates
for it, nothing more.
Zulla, we both know it's
worth at least three bags.
Take the bag of dates
and get out!
- (ZULLA SHOUTS IN ARABIC)
- MAN: Go!
Please.
MAN: Move it,
you street rat.
Here you go, Abu.
Shh.
VENDOR 1: Come here!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
FISHMONGER: Fresh fish!
We catch them, you buy them!
VENDOR 2: Try this,
please. Please.
VENDOR 3:
Sugar dates and pistachios!
Hello.
Oh.
Are you hungry?
Here, take some bread.
- (CHILDREN CHATTERING)
- (WOMAN CHUCKLES)
Hey! Hey!
You steal from my brother.
- Stealing? No, I...
- You pay, or I take bracelet.
Sir, I don't have any money.
Let go of me!
- JAMAL: No.
- Whoa! Take it easy, Jamal.
Kalil walks away
from the stall...
and this one,
she steals the bread.
Those children
were hungry!
- I...
- Okay, give me a minute.
You keep your little street
rat nose out of it! Huh?
Do you have any money?
No.
Okay, trust me.
- Here you go.
- Wait!
This is what you wanted,
right?
Yeah. Thank you.
Okay, and an apple.
For your troubles.
- Nice!
- That was my...
I'm not leaving
without my bracelet!
You mean this bracelet?
Come on.
(VOCALIZING MELODY)
(VOCALIZES HALTINGLY)
JAMAL: Aladdin!
Thief with Aladdin!
- Are we in trouble?
- Only if you get caught.
- JAMAL: Aladdin!
- Down that alley.
Monkey knows the way.
- JAMAL: Guards! Guards!
- Abu.
- (GASPS)
- (ABU CHITTERS)
- Uh...
- You'll be fine.
JAMAL: They stole from me!
- Over there! Aladdin!
- GUARD: Hey, you!
You looking for this,
Jamal?
JAMAL: Aladdin,
you street rat!
(GUARDS GRUNTING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
♪ Gotta keep one jump
Ahead of the bread line
♪ One swing
Ahead of the sword
♪ I steal
Only what I can't afford
♪ And that's ev'rything
♪ One jump
Ahead of the lawmen
♪ That's all
And that's no joke
♪ These guys
Don't appreciate I'm broke
♪ Riffraff!
Street rat!
- ♪ Scoundrel!
- ♪ Take that!
♪ Try a dif'rent tack, guys
- ♪ Rip him open!
- ♪ 'Round the back, guys
♪ I can take a hint
Gotta face the facts
♪ Could really use
A friend or two!
♪ Oh, it's sad
Aladdin's hit the bottom
Ooh, ladies!
♪ He's become
A one-man rise in crime
Well...
♪ I'd blame parents
'Cept he hasn't got 'em
♪ Gotta eat to live
Gotta steal to eat
♪ Tell you all about it
When I got the time
GUARD: Huh?
(YELLS)
- (ALADDIN GRUNTING)
- (WOMAN YELPS)
- There are stairs, you know.
- (GUARDS SHOUTING)
Where's the fun in that?
♪ One jump
Ahead of the slowpokes
♪ One skip ahead of my doom
♪ Next time
Gonna use a nom de plume
(GASPS)
♪ One jump
Ahead of the hit men
♪ One hit ahead of the flock
♪ I think I'll take a stroll
Around the block
(WOMEN GASP)
- MAN: ♪ Stop, thief!
- ♪ Vandal!
ALADDIN: Abu!
♪ Scandal!
♪ Let's not be too hasty
♪ Still, I think
He's rather tasty
♪ Gotta eat to live
Gotta steal to eat
- ♪ Otherwise we'd get along ♪
- ♪ Wrong! ♪
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
GUARD: No, no, no!
(BOTH SCREAM)
- Together on three!
- Together on three?
- We jump.
- We jump?
Why are you repeating
everything I say?
The pole.
- GUARD 1: Move, move!
- GUARD 2: This way!
One, two, three!
GUARD 3: Thief! Stop!
On the roof!
I'm sorry!
I can't do this.
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
Stop him!
Look at me. Look at me.
You can do this.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay.
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(SCREAMING)
- (YELPS)
- Oh!
- Oh.
- Nicely done.
Thank you.
♪ One jump
Ahead of the hoof beats
♪ One hop ahead of the hump
♪ One trick
Ahead of disaster
♪ They're quick
But I'm much faster
♪ Here goes!
♪ Better throw my hand in
Wish me happy landin'
♪ All I gotta do is jump! ♪
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
GUARD: Move back!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ABU CHITTERING)
- (BELL TOLLING IN DISTANCE)
- Oh, dear.
(GASPS, SIGHS)
- (CHITTERING EXCITEDLY)
- (GRUNTS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Come on. I know
somewhere we'll be safe.
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
Here comes the master.
(SNIFFING)
You bring me the rough
but never a diamond.
Take them away.
- GUARD: Move!
- IAGO: Take them away.
- PRISONER: Please!
- HENCHMAN: My vizier...
perhaps this diamond in
the rough does not exist?
He is out there.
But we've searched
for months!
I do not understand what could
possibly be in that cave...
that could help a man
as great as you.
You are already second
only to the sultan!
Second! Uh-oh!
Who's in trouble now?
And you think
second is enough?
Of course.
You were not born
to be sultan.
IAGO: Not smart.
Do you know what I had to do
to get the power that I have?
The sacrifices that I've made,
the bodies that I've buried?
The five years
spent in a Shirabad jail?
People need to understand
that they will pay
for underestimating me.
Second is not enough!
And it will never be enough!
That's why I need the lamp,
and why I no longer need you!
(GASPS, SCREAMS)
(IAGO CACKLES)
This way.
WOMAN: Oh.
Where are we, exactly?
You'll see.
Oh, my.
Is this...
Is this where you live?
ALADDIN: Yep.
Just me and Abu.
Come and go as we please.
Welcome to my humble...
You'll see.
(CREAKING)
You are
quite the magician.
ALADDIN: Thank you.
(WHISPERS) Abu, no, help!
(PEOPLE ON STREET CHATTERING)
(EXHALES)
I can't believe...
What?
I can't believe we did that.
That I did that.
(SCOFFS)
That we're alive!
With the chase.
Abu, tea?
- (CHITTERING)
- WOMAN: Jumping buildings.
- That was incredible.
- Tea?
Thank you. And thank you
for getting me out of there.
Aladdin, isn't it?
Uh, you're welcome...
I'm... I'm Dalia.
Dalia.
From the palace.
How could you tell?
Well, only someone
from the palace
could afford a bracelet
like that.
And that silk lining
is imported, too.
It comes
from the merchant boats,
straight to the palace.
But not to servants.
At least, not most servants,
which means you are
a handmaid to the princess.
Impressive.
You think that's impressive,
you should see the city
from up there.
WOMAN: Oh.
Agrabah. It's so beautiful.
I should get out more.
You should tell the
princess to get out more.
The people haven't
seen her in years.
They won't let her.
Ever since my...
The queen was killed,
the sultan's been afraid.
So she's kept locked away.
Seems everyone's
been afraid since then.
But the people of Agrabah
had nothing to do with that.
The people loved her.
- They did, didn't they?
- (CLATTERS)
(CHITTERS)
- (ALADDIN CLEARS THROAT)
- Is this yours?
It's kind of borrowed.
(STRUMMING CHORD)
My mother taught me
that song.
Mine too.
It's all I remember of her.
And what about your father?
I lost them both
when I was young.
Been on my own ever since.
It's all right, it's just...
What?
It's a little sad.
Having a monkey
as the only parental
authority in your life.
(CHUCKLES)
- (FLY BUZZING)
- (CHITTERS)
We get by.
Every day I just think
things will be different...
but it never
seems to change.
It's just sometimes,
I feel like I'm...
Trapped.
Like you can't escape
what you were born into?
Yes.
Hmm.
(SHIP HORN BLOWS)
MAN 1: Welcome Prince Anders!
I have to get back
to the palace.
Uh... Now?
(BELL TOLLING)
MAN 1: Make way
for Prince Anders!
Make way for Prince Anders!
It's just another prince
coming to court the princess.
Yes, and I have
to get her ready.
Oh! Do you have my bracelet?
Sure.
MAN 1: Make way
for Prince Anders.
I'm sure I put it in here.
- Somewhere.
- (CHITTERS)
Abu, did you take it?
That was
my mother's bracelet.
Yes. It's beautiful.
You are a thief.
- No, no. Yes, but...
- I'm so naive.
- ALADDIN: Abu.
- WOMAN: Excuse me.
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, it's not like that!
GUARD: Clear the way!
MAN 2: No! Watch it!
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
Street rat,
get out of the way!
Who do you think
you're calling a street rat?
Are you talking back to me?
You were born worthless
and you will die worthless.
And only your fleas
will mourn you.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
- Come on, Abu.
- (CHITTERS)
Let's go home.
(SIGHS)
♪ Riffraff, street rat
♪ I don't buy that
♪ If only they'd look closer
♪ Would they see a poor boy?
♪ No, siree
♪ They'd find out
♪ There's so much more to me ♪
(CHITTERING)
(SIGHS)
Abu.
There's a time
that we do steal,
and a time we don't.
This was definitely a don't.
(CHITTERS DEJECTEDLY)
SULTAN:
Welcome, Prince Anders!
We trust you had
an enjoyable journey.
(THICKLY ACCENTED)
Oh, wow.
Prince Anders, my daughter,
Princess Jasmine.
So, why did no one tell me
of your beauty?
No one mentioned yours,
either.
Oh! Thank you. (CHUCKLES)
They say that in Skanland.
Yeah. Right?
(ALL LAUGHING)
- It's very, very amusing.
- (IAGO LAUGHING)
- Is it?
- Yeah.
We have the same title,
yet are never
described the same way.
SULTAN: (CLEARS THROAT)
Jasmine.
Yeah.
Oh.
- (GROWLS)
- What is that?
Don't tell me. (CHUCKLES)
It's a cat with stripes!
He likes you.
I know.
'Cause in Skanland,
cats love me.
Here, puss, puss.
Hey, puss, puss.
- (GROWLING)
- Hey, puss, puss, puss...
- (ROARS)
- (ANDERS SCREAMS)
(LAUGHTER)
My sultan, our enemies
grow stronger every day...
yet you allow your daughter
to dismiss Prince Anders...
and a possible
military alliance.
Which enemies?
Shirabad continues to amass.
- Shirabad is our ally.
- Was our ally!
You would drag us into a war
with our oldest...
And you would allow
your kingdom
to sink into ruin
for mere sentiment!
Jafar!
Remember your place.
I apologize.
Forgive me, my sultan.
I went too far.
- But...
- (WHOOSHES)
if you would
only reconsider...
I think you will see...
(ECHOING AND DISTORTING)
that invading Shirabad
is the right thing to do.
(MONOTONE)
Invading Shirabad is...
JASMINE: Invade Shirabad?
What?
Why would we invade
Mother's kingdom?
We would never
invade Shirabad.
But an ally in Skanland
would improve our situation.
Yes, if you consider giving
Prince Anders a chance.
To rule? Baba,
Rajah would make a better ruler.
My dear, I'm not
getting any younger.
We must find you a husband,
and we are running
out of kingdoms. (CHUCKLES)
What foreign prince could care
for our people as I do?
I could lead if only...
My dear,
you cannot be a sultan...
because it has
never been done
in the 1,000-year history
of our kingdom.
I have been preparing for this
my whole life. I have read...
Books? But you cannot
read experience.
Inexperience
is dangerous.
People left unchecked
will revolt.
Walls and borders unguarded
will be attacked.
SULTAN: Jafar is right.
One day...
you will understand.
- You may leave now.
- (HUFFS)
(RAJAH GROWLS)
(SIGHS)
Life will be kinder to you,
Princess,
once you accept
these traditions...
and understand
it's better for you
to be seen and not heard.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(RAJAH GROWLING)
(SIGHS)
(SOFT GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Here comes a wave
Meant to wash me away
♪ A tide
That is taking me under
♪ Broken again
Left with nothing to say
♪ My voice drowned out
In the thunder
♪ But I can't cry
♪ And I can't
Start to crumble
♪ Whenever they try
♪ To shut me or cut me down
♪ I can't stay silent
♪ Though they wanna
Keep me quiet
♪ And I tremble
When they try it
♪ All I know is I won't
♪ Go speechless ♪
GUARD: Open the gate!
(CROWD EXCLAIMS)
WOMAN: Splendid!
You know what to do, Abu.
- (CROWD EXCLAIMING)
- (ABU CHITTERS)
Get off me!
Get off me, you dirty monkey!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
GUARD: Close the gate!
Dirty monkey!
Street thief. Street thief.
- (SQUAWKS)
- "Remember your place, Jafar."
Remember your place!
If I hear that
one more time...
Sorry, master!
Another petty insult
from that small-minded fool.
(IAGO LAUGHING)
He sees a city
where I see an empire.
IAGO: Such vision.
Once that lamp
sits in my hand...
then I shall sit
on his throne.
Thief.
Thief in the palace.
"Thief in the palace"?
That's what I said. Thief!
What have you seen, Iago?
Diamond in the rough.
(GUARD SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: I told you,
now, come on!
Bigger circles.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Who's a clever boy?
(SQUAWKS)
But, Dalia,
there has to be something I can do.
A handsome prince
wants to marry you.
Oh, when will
life get easier?
It's not that I don't want to
marry, it's just...
You want to be sultan.
But why?
You remember
my mother used to say...
we would only ever be as happy
as our least happy subject?
If she saw what I saw today,
she would be heartbroken.
She would also
want you to be safe.
And clean.
I'll draw the bath.
Jafar's guards
on every corner.
Soon, he'd have them
invading our neighbors,
risking lives, for what?
I can help.
I know I can.
I was born to do more than
marry some useless prince.
If you had to marry
a useless prince,
you could certainly
do worse than this one.
He's tall and handsome.
And yes, he's a little dim,
but you're just
getting married.
It's not like
you have to talk to him.
But you'd prefer that boy
from the market.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
JASMINE: Can I help you?
Tea?
You? You!
- What are you doing here?
- (MEN CHATTERING)
Get in here, now!
I came back to return
your bracelet.
My bracelet?
Where is it?
On your wrist.
JASMINE: What?
ALADDIN: Not bad.
I like what she's done
with the place.
How did you
get past the guards?
That was challenging,
but I have my ways.
While the princess is out,
would you like to go
for a stroll?
Have a little chat?
You are unbelievable.
You cannot just
break into a palace
and walk around
like you own the place.
If you don't have anything,
you have to act like
you own everything.
So, what do you say?
I did find your bracelet.
You did not find it,
you stole it!
Correction,
the monkey stole it.
He's your monkey.
- He's still just a monkey.
- (CHUCKLES)
Who ordered the tea?
Uh...
I did.
For you, Princess Jasmine.
- Your Majesty!
- (MOUTHING)
Why are you being weird?
Oh, I'm the princess.
Yes.
Mmm-hmm.
And it is good to be me...
with all my palaces...
and wagons of gold things...
and dresses
for every hour of the day.
Now it is time
for my cat to be cleaned.
She doesn't get out much.
Mmm-hmm.
Clearly.
- (RAJAH GROWLS)
- (GASPS)
JASMINE: Oh.
Aren't you supposed to be
in the bath?
(SNIFFING)
DALIA: Oh, servant girl,
this cat isn't
going to clean itself!
But don't cats
clean themselves?
You have to go now.
Oh, okay. But I'm coming back
tomorrow night.
What? No, you can't...
Meet me in the courtyard
beside the fountain
when the moon
is above the minaret.
To return this.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
I promise.
(CHUCKLES)
(ABU CHITTERS)
Can you believe it, Abu?
The most heavily guarded
place in all of Agrabah...
Evening.
(HIGH-PITCHED) Evening.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(NORMAL VOICE) Evening.
Guards are behind me.
Hello, boys.
- (PANTING)
- (GUARDS CHATTERING)
Where am I?
In a world
of trouble, boy.
That bracelet,
is that what this is about?
Because I didn't steal it.
The handmaid...
What was a handmaid doing
wearing the queen's bracelet?
The queen? No, no.
She said that
it belonged to her...
Mother.
(SCOFFS)
Well, at least she told
the truth about one thing.
Are you saying
that was the princess?
I was talking to the...
She was toying with you.
It amuses her
to meet commoners.
Did you actually think
she liked you? (CHUCKLES)
What do they call you?
Aladdin.
Aladdin. People like us
must be realistic if...
Us?
You see,
I was once like you.
A common thief.
Only I thought bigger.
Steal an apple
and you're a thief,
steal a kingdom
and you're a statesman.
Only weak men stop there.
You're either the most
powerful man in the room,
or you're nothing.
You, you stumbled upon
an opportunity.
I can make you rich.
Rich enough
to impress a princess.
But nothing comes for free.
What would I have to do?
JAFAR: There's a cave nearby,
and in it, a simple oil lamp.
Retrieve it for me
and I will make you
wealthy enough
to impress a princess.
You're nothing to her,
but you could be.
Your life begins now, Aladdin.
Still waiting?
No. No, I came out to...
(INHALES)
(SIGHS)
He promised.
I'll be upstairs
if you need me.
Good night, Dalia.
(SIGHS)
JAFAR: The Cave of Wonders.
When you enter,
you will see more riches
than you ever dreamed of...
gold, diamonds,
and the lamp.
Bring it to me and I will
make you rich and free.
(IAGO WHISTLES)
But take no other treasure,
no matter how sorely
you are tempted.
And you will be tempted.
(LION'S HEAD GROWLING)
LION'S HEAD:
Only one may enter here.
One whose worth
lies far within.
The diamond in the rough.
JAFAR: Remember...
take nothing but the lamp.
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
(ALADDIN SCREAMING)
(RUMBLING)
(GRUNTING)
- (CHITTERING)
- (GRUNTS)
ALADDIN: Abu, don't touch.
Remember?
- (CHITTERS)
- (GASPS)
(CHITTERING)
- (CLATTERING)
- (SCREECHES)
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
Whoa.
Abu.
This is a magic carpet.
These really do exist.
Hello, Carpet.
(CHUCKLES)
(SCREECHES)
Let's see what we can do
about your situation here.
(STRAINING)
(CLINKING)
Oh, hey.
Don't mention it.
(CHITTERS, SCREECHES)
Abu, keep your little
monkey hands to yourself.
(WHINES)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREECHES)
(CLINKING)
(WARBLES)
(DIAMOND CLINKING)
(EXHALES)
(CHITTERING SOFTLY)
- (LION'S HEAD GROWLING)
- (RUMBLING)
Abu, no!
LION'S HEAD: You have touched
the forbidden treasure.
Now you will never again...
see the light of day!
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
Carpet!
- (SCREECHING)
- Abu, jump!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Could you give me a hand?
First, the lamp.
No, first your hand.
We don't have much time.
- Give me the lamp.
- (SQUAWKING)
Your hand!
Second no more, master.
Now your hand.
How about my foot?
- (IAGO CACKLING)
- ALADDIN: No! No!
(SCREAMING)
(YELPS)
- JAFAR: Get off me, monkey!
- (ABU SCREECHING)
- (RUMBLING)
- (JAFAR COUGHING)
- Stop.
- (IAGO SQUAWKS)
IAGO: Dirty monkey!
Second, second!
(IAGO SQUAWKS AND CACKLES)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
Whoa.
We're alive.
I think.
Thank you, Carpet.
(CHITTERS)
(WHISTLES)
Abu.
How did you...?
You cunning little monkey.
Now, all we need's a way out.
(GRUNTS)
Hey, Carpet, do you know
a way out of here?
The lamp?
What is that?
(DEEP VOICE)
Oh, great one who summons me,
terrible one
who commands me...
I stand by my oath,
loyalty to wishes three.
(WHIMPERS SOFTLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
I said, "Oh, great..."
(NORMAL VOICE) Excuse me,
boy, where's your boss?
Help me out here.
Where's your boss?
If I was gonna
talk to myself,
I could've just
stayed in the lamp.
Uh... Uh...
Hello?
I'm... (GULPS)
Use your big boy voice.
I'm talking
to a smoking blue giant?
No! (WARBLES)
I am not a giant,
I am a genie.
There is a difference.
Giants are not real.
- Where's your boss?
- Uh, my boss?
Look, kid, I've been doing
this a long time, all right?
There's always a guy,
you know...
he's cheated somebody
or buried somebody...
I mean, you get my point.
Where's that guy?
I know that guy.
He's outside.
So, it's just you and me
down here?
- (ABU CHITTERING)
- And a monkey?
That's your
personal business...
but we gonna need to talk
about that monkey later.
It's a pretty
little monkey.
So, you rubbed the lamp?
Uh-huh.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, do you mind...
if I could just stretch it out over
here, do you mind?
Uh... Are you asking me?
Yes. You're my master.
(EXHALES)
I'm your master?
Downward dog. (GRUNTS)
No, no. You look like
you should be my master.
Right, but that's not quite
how it works, though.
How long have you been
trapped in here?
(SIGHS)
'Bout thousand years.
A thousand years?
(IMITATES ALADDIN)
"A thousand years."
Kid, is it me or does, like,
everything surprise you?
So, you really don't know
who I am?
Genie, wishes, lamp,
none of that ringing a bell?
Wow! Well, that's a first.
- Monkey!
- (SCREECHES)
(PIPE SQUEAKS)
Oh, you don't need to worry
about him. He's fine.
(PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
(CHORUS) ♪ Well,
Ali Baba He had them 40 thieves
♪ Scheherazade
Had a thousand tales
♪ But, master, you're in luck
Because up your sleeve
♪ You got a genie
That never fails ♪
(PIPE SQUEAKS)
Whoo!
I'm the best.
- Yeah.
- Heh.
(CHUCKLES)
- Not enough, huh?
- Uh...
I'm kidding.
Watch this.
- (PLAYING UPBEAT JAZZY MUSIC)
- Here I go!
Uh! Ooh! Whoo!
Back up.
Uh-oh! Watch out!
You done wound me up.
'Bout to show you
what I'm working with. Uh!
♪ Well, Ali Baba
He had them 40 thieves
♪ Scheherazade
Had a thousand tales
♪ But, master, you're in luck
Because up your sleeves
♪ You got a brand of magic
Never fails
♪ You got some power
In your corner now
♪ Heavy ammunition
In your camp
♪ You got some punch, pizzazz
Yahoo, and how
♪ All you gotta do
Is rub that lamp
♪ And then I'll say
♪ Mister, man
What's your name?
♪ Whatever
What will Your pleasure be?
♪ Let me take your order
I'll jot it down
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me
♪ Life is your restaurant
And I'm your maitre d'
♪ Come whisper to me
Whatever it is you want
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me
♪ We pride ourselves
On service
♪ You the boss
The king, the shah
♪ Say what you wish
It's yours, true dish
♪ How about
A little more baklava?
♪ Have some of column A
Try all of column B
♪ I'm in the mood
To help you, dude
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Oh! Uh!
This the big part!
Watch out!
This the big part! Oh!
♪ Can your friends do this?
♪ Can your friends do that?
♪ Can your friends pull this
♪ Outta they little hat?
♪ Can your friends go
(BEATBOXING)
♪ I'm the genie of the lamp
♪ I can sing, rap, dance
If you give me a chance
♪ Don't sit there buggy-eyed
♪ I'm here to answer
All your midday prayers
(GENIES VOCALIZING)
♪ You got me bona fide
Certified
♪ Got a genie
For your charge d'affaires
♪ I got a powerful urge
To help you out
♪ So what you wish?
I really wanna know
♪ You got a list that's
Three miles long, no doubt
♪ All you gotta do
Is rub like so
♪ Mister...
- Aladdin.
- Yes!
♪ One wish or two or three
♪ Well, I'm on the job
♪ You big nabob
♪ You ain't never had a friend
Never had a friend
♪ You ain't never had
A friend
♪ Like me
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me ♪
You can clap now.
(MIMICS MIC DROP)
(MIMICS CHEERING)
No, no, no. Please, please.
You can thank me outside.
In the sun.
When you wish us out.
So, how does it work?
You're kidding, right?
The whole song
was the instructions!
Obviously, you can't dance
and listen at the same time.
So, here's the basics.
Step one, rub the lamp.
Step two, say what you want.
Step three...
there is no step three.
See, it's that easy.
You get three wishes...
they must begin
with rubbing the lamp
and saying,
"I wish." Got it?
- I think so.
- Couple other rules.
You can't wish for more
wishes. Three is enough.
Now, I can't make
anybody love anybody or
(EVIL VOICE) bring anybody
back from the dead.
(NORMAL VOICE)
Feel free to interrupt me
anytime you don't understand.
I'm kidding, don't ever
interrupt me, no matter what.
Now, I usually don't have to
go through all of this...
because by the time
the guy gets to me,
he pretty much knows
what he wants...
and it generally
has to do with
(EVIL VOICE)
tons of money and power!
(LAUGHING EVILLY)
(NORMAL VOICE) Do me a favor,
do not drink from that cup.
I promise you there is
not enough money
and power on earth
for you to be satisfied.
Good? So,
what's your first wish?
Mmm... Well,
I have to think about it.
I mean,
if there are only three...
Why are there
only three anyway?
I don't know, who cares?
You don't know?
I thought
you were all-knowing.
That's 'cause
you don't listen.
I never said
I was all-knowing.
I said I was all-powerful.
The most powerful being
in the universe.
- (ABU CHITTERS)
- Look, whatever I don't know,
- I know I can learn it.
- (WHISTLES)
Outside in the sun.
Why are you playing
hard to wish?
I know you can't tell,
but I am very pale.
This is sky blue.
My natural pigmentation is navy.
Give us some sun.
Okay, Genie. I wish for you
to get us out of this cave.
Boom! Booyah!
He has made his first wish!
Thank you for choosing
Carpets, Camels and Caravans.
Please don't forget to tip
your genie on the way out.
GENIES: Hey.
GENIE: Hold yourself, kid!
(GENIE WHOOPING)
(CONTINUES WHOOPING)
Whoa.
Man, look at this world.
It's so big!
Inside the lamp,
everything is, like,
brass, brass, brass!
You're like,
"Oh! Is that some copper?"
Nope, brass! Sorta the
problem with the genie life...
phenomenal cosmic powers,
but itty-bitty living space.
So, is this magic,
or are you magic?
Eh, kind of a package deal.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
(EXCLAIMS)
Can you warn me
before you do that?
Oh, you'll get used to it.
Right.
So, do I have to make
all my wishes here?
I mean, if I take you back
to Agrabah, won't people...?
No, no, no!
I can look totally normal.
Boo!
Right, totally normal.
(EXCLAIMS)
Still blue.
Do we need the top knot?
That's my little
cherry on top!
Okay, okay.
So, what are you gonna wish?
Oh, I haven't
thought about that.
Mmm. You really
are not that guy.
Okay.
So, what would
you wish for?
Mmm.
No one's ever
asked me that before.
It's an easy one, though.
I'd wish to be free.
- (CLANGING)
- To not have to say,
"Poof! Can I help you?"
"Poof! What would you like?"
"Poof! Welcome to the lamp.
"May I take your order,
please?"
Freedom.
I wish to be...
to be human.
Why don't you just
set yourself free?
(LAUGHING)
Carpet! Did you hear
what this boy said?
Why don't I set myself free?
Only way a genie
gets to be free...
is if the owner of the lamp
uses one of his wishes
to set him free...
and the last time
that happened was, like,
the fourth of Never-ary.
I'll do it.
I've got three, right?
Actually, you have two left.
You used one to get out
of the cave. Remember?
Did I? Or did you?
I thought I had to be
rubbing the lamp.
Okay, little street boy.
Let's rewind the tape.
(MIMICS TAPE REWINDING)
- Okay, Genie. I wish...
- (AUDIENCE EXCLAIM)
Ooh! Little monkey
with the lamp trick!
Never seen that one before.
- I'll keep my eye on you.
- ABU: Uh-oh.
At least now, I can use
my third wish to set you free.
Here's the thing
about wishes...
the more you have,
the more you want.
That's not me.
Mmm.
We'll see about that.
- But there is something.
- GENIE: Uh-oh.
Seen that face before.
Who is she?
Who's the girl?
She's a princess.
Aw, aren't they all?
"Treat your woman like
a queen," I always say.
No,
she's an actual princess.
Well, I already told you,
I can't make anyone
love anyone, so...
No, no.
We had a connection.
Did they?
Okay.
She is smart, and kind,
and so beautiful.
But she has to marry a...
Hey! Can you make me
a prince?
There's a lot of gray area
in "make me a prince."
I could just
make you a prince.
Oh, no.
Right. You'd be snuggled up
with that dude
for the rest of your life.
PRINCE:
Yo, y'all seen my palace?
Be specific with your words.
- The deal is in the detail.
- Got it.
Which I don't
really understand
because if she
already likes you...
why change?
I told you,
she has to marry a prince.
PRINCE: I just
wanna go home, man!
Okay, I can do that.
An official wish this time,
for those of us
who are counting...
which now, I am one.
Genie, (CLEARS THROAT)
I wish...
Lamp.
Oh, sorry.
All right. Genie...
Don't hurt him, Genie!
I wish to become a prince.
Back up, boy.
I need some room to work.
I'm about to fabulize you.
- (GENIE WHOOPING)
- ALADDIN: Genie?
(GENIE SHOUTING)
Little head-spinney.
Better though, right?
(BREATHLESSLY) I think
I'm getting used to it.
Okay, a prince, a prince.
Obviously, the ghetto-chic
is not gonna work.
I'm feeling a periwinkle.
What's periwinkle?
No! Chartreuse.
(GASPS) Cerise!
Ah! (GROANS)
- The lines are all wrong.
- What is this?
The color clashes
with your skin tone,
the silhouette is confused.
This is a big hat!
No, that is not a big hat.
Come on, Genie!
Gotta kick the door down!
We gotta go bold and gold!
(GENIE YELLS)
(EXCLAIMS) No!
- We've gone too far.
- Genie, you're slippin'!
It's gotta be neutral
for the desert.
Ivory, beige, bone, Albion.
It's a little heavy.
(GASPS DEEPLY)
GENIE: White.
- Oh! And the crowd goes wild!
- (CROWD CHEERING)
Oh!
The genie!
The genie's on fire!
The genie's on fire, folks!
Don't hurt him, Genie!
Don't scald him!
Somebody cool me down!
Somebody put me out!
I'm too much!
Ow! I'm back!
- So, what do you think?
- I like it.
Of course you like it, boy!
I made it!
I think that's me.
Strictly speaking,
it is me.
I mean,
I did most of the work.
You was just
standing there.
But I hear you.
But won't people
recognize me?
Nobody'll recognize you.
That's how
genie magic works.
People see
what they're told to see.
Right. Who am I?
Who...? (SCOFFS)
Prince Ali?
- From?
- Duh!
From Ababwa.
A-bub-wha?
(SIGHS) You're not listenin'.
Ababwa.
- Is that a real place?
- Yeah!
Like,
everybody knows about it.
It has a brochure.
Little hot in the summer,
temperate in the fall.
But no, I'll let you
read it en route.
How are we gonna
get there?
GENIE: I guess
you can't ride a chimp.
Don't you just love
a moonwalking monkey?
- Uh-uh. Hold it there, Abu.
- (SCREECHING)
- (BRAYING)
- Donkey. Too small.
- (GENIE GROANS)
- ALADDIN: No.
GENIE: Too obvious.
We need somethin' robust!
(TRUMPETS)
(TRUMPETING)
GENIE: Relax, Abu.
It's just for a minute.
- Whoa.
- (LAUGHING)
Prince Ali of Ababwa.
And now,
for your entourage!
- What?
- (RUMBLING)
What's happening?
- Genie?
- (ABU TRUMPETS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DISTANT THUDDING)
(ALARMED CHATTER)
GUARD: Clear the way!
Clear the way!
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(DRUMS POUNDING)
(PLAYING FANFARE)
♪ Make way for Prince Ali
♪ Say hey, it's Prince Ali
♪ Hey, clear the way
In the old bazaar
♪ Hey, you, let us through
It's a brand new star
♪ Oh, come
Be the first
♪ On your block
To meet his eye
♪ Make way, here he comes
Ring bells, bang the drums
♪ You're gonna love this guy
♪ Prince Ali, fabulous he
Ali Ababwa
♪ Show some respect
Boy, genuflect
♪ Down on one knee
♪ Now, try your best
To stay calm
♪ Brush up
Your Friday salaam
♪ Then come and meet
His spectacular coterie
♪ Prince Ali, mighty is he
Ali Ababwa
♪ Strong as ten regular men
Definitely
(GENIE LAUGHS)
♪ He's faced
The galloping hordes
♪ A hundred bad guys
With swords
♪ Who sent those goons
To their lords?
♪ Why, Prince Ali
♪ Fellas, he's got
- ♪ 75 golden camels
- Whoo!
♪ Now the ladies
What he got?
♪ Purple peacocks
He's got 53
♪ When it comes
To exotic-type mammals
♪ Everybody, help me out!
♪ He's got a zoo
I'm telling you
♪ It's a world-class
Menagerie!
♪ Prince Ali, handsome is he
Ali Ababwa
♪ That physique
How can I speak?
♪ Weak in my knees
♪ So yummy boy!
♪ So get on out
In that square
♪ Adjust your veil
And prepare
♪ To gawk and grovel and stare
At Prince Ali!
- Oops.
- (WOMEN GASP)
♪ He's got
95 white Persian monkeys
♪ He's got some monkeys
A bunch of monkeys!
♪ And to view them
He charges no fee
♪ He's generous, so generous
♪ He's got 10,000 servants
And flunkies
♪ Proud to work for him
♪ Bow to his whim
Love serving him
♪ They're just lousy
With loyalty
♪ To Ali
♪ Prince Ali
♪ Prince A...
We waitin' for you!
We're not goin' till you go!
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
GENIE: You can do it!
There it is!
♪ Prince Ali
♪ Amorous he
♪ Ali Ababwa
♪ Heard your princess was hot
Where is she?
♪ And that
Good people, is why
♪ He got all cute
And dropped by
♪ With
♪ With 60 elephants
Llamas galore
- ♪ For real?
- ♪ With his bears and lions
♪ A brass band and more
- ♪ What?
- ♪ With his 40 fakirs
♪ His cooks, his bakers
His birds that warble on key
♪ Make way
♪ For Prince Ali ♪
- (MUSIC ENDS)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
(CRACKERS BURSTING)
(TRUMPETING)
- ALADDIN: Where are they?
- GENIE: Relax.
- Shh.
- What is taking so long?
(DOOR OPENS)
- GENIE: Here comes the man.
- Oh.
(UNDERBREATH)
What are you doing?
Put your arms down.
I'm presenting it.
Put your arms down!
It's a pleasure to welcome you to
Agrabah, Prince Ali.
Oh.
How did you break that?
ALADDIN: I don't know,
it fell off.
It's a pleasure
to meet him, probably.
Uh...
It's just as much a pleasure
for me, Your Highness, sir.
You look very serene.
That's a curtsy,
not a bow. Stand up.
I'm afraid I'm unfamiliar
with Ababwa.
- Well, it's north.
- It's south.
Uh, we have
a north and a south.
What?
It's near,
if you were to go, it's...
Around there, you can find it,
if you just look.
Don't help me.
The world is
changing quickly, Jafar.
It seems as if there is a new
country every day. (CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING)
(UNDERBREATH)
Don't touch me.
Well, yes,
you are very wise.
Uh, tell him
that we have gifts, please.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, right! We have things.
Gifts!
- Did you organize this?
- Yeah!
- (EXCLAIMS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Yes, here we are.
Gifts coming right up!
We have spices, golden camels,
and spoons, tiny spoons!
Spoons!
ALADDIN: How do they
make them that tiny?
We have jams!
- Jams?
Yes, jams!
Yam jams, fig jams.
- Yam jams!
- ALADDIN: And date jams.
Seedless, delicious,
exotic jams.
Move away from the jams.
- What?
- We have jewels.
(CLEARS THROAT) Jewels!
We have them! And, uh, that!
Over there,
- hidden for suspense.
- Hmm?
Whew!
ALADDIN: Ta-da!
- Uh...
- It's a wheel?
It's, uh, very expensive.
And what do you hope to buy
with this expensive?
You!
- (PEOPLE GASP)
- (IAGO SQUAWKS)
(WHISPERS) Wow!
No! No, no, no.
A moment with you,
a moment. That's not...
(MIMICS EXPLOSION)
Are you suggesting
I am for sale?
Of course...
not! No, of course not!
No!
It's cold and it's dark
in that lamp.
But I prefer it to this.
JASMINE: Please excuse me.
I need to go
and find some bread.
For the jams.
No! That's not
what I meant. I...
You did great.
That's not what I meant.
Just leave her alone.
You didn't do great.
You will get the chance
to speak again.
We hope you can
join us tonight, Prince Ali,
when we celebrate
our harvest.
Of course, your serene self.
- (SULTAN SIGHS)
- ALADDIN: We will join you.
IAGO: Smooth.
In 10,000 years...
I've never been
that embarrassed.
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING
AND CHEERING)
Don't worry. You are not
out of the game yet.
Just do whatever
you'd normally do at a party.
I've never been to a party.
- What?
Oh, you're gonna need to
go back to the room, then.
You're not messing up
my night.
JAFAR: Prince Ali.
(FIREWORKS CONTINUE)
May I have a word?
Privately.
This doesn't concern
your servant.
Well, be over there
minding my business.
(ALADDIN CLEARS THROAT)
I know who you are.
You do?
Yes.
You're a man of
great ambition like myself.
I, uh, don't believe we've
been properly introduced.
Jafar,
vizier to the sultan.
I could be a valuable ally to
help you get what you want.
I, uh...
I will think on that.
I don't wanna
keep the princess waiting.
Perhaps I'm not
making myself clear.
This offer will not be on
the table for long, you see.
(WHOOSHING)
(ECHOING) Prince Ali.
Excuse me. Prince Ali,
your presence is requested.
So, I guess
that's the guy.
Mmm-hmm.
That's the guy.
- (FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
GENIE: Okay, there she is.
This is your chance.
You know what?
There are a lot of people.
I don't think I can do this.
- GENIE: You'll be fine.
- ALADDIN: Okay.
This one's gonna be easy.
Ooh! And look
at her handmaid.
And she's going
to get some punch.
Feelin' a little
thirsty myself.
No! No, no!
You can't leave me.
They'll see
right through me.
No, they won't.
All you have to do is walk over there.
And speak.
I also have to speak.
GENIE: Okay, listen to me.
- I live in a lamp.
- Mmm-hmm.
This is a party.
Do not mess this up
for me. Okay?
I like to party.
Go get her! (PATS BACK)
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
(ANDERS EXCLAIMS)
Princess Jasmine! (LAUGHS)
You? You're still here?
Yes.
(ANDERS LAUGHING)
- GENIE: What are you doing?
- Hmm?
What are you doing?
I'm just making sure the
water is a good temperature.
Why are you not over there?
How am I supposed to
compete with that?
Look at him.
He's so princely.
You have got to be
more confident
about what you have to offer.
What do I have to offer?
Knowledge of
how to steal food?
How to jump
between buildings?
Now, Prince Ali,
he has jewels.
No, stop, stop, stop!
I made you look like a prince
on the outside.
But I didn't change anything
on the inside.
Prince Ali got you
to the door...
but Aladdin has to open it.
Oh.
See, the sultan
does like me!
Okay, well, maybe
he'll let you be his wife.
Look at that, another prince
more interested in Baba.
I don't know,
I think this one might be different.
And he comes with an
incredibly attractive friend.
Please make it work.
And what about Prince Ali?
DALIA: Oh, look at him.
He's trying so hard.
And that's the problem.
- Showtime.
- No.
I'm waiting
for the right moment.
No. No waiting.
We're done waiting.
No, I'm in charge. Okay?
I say when
it's the right moment.
- (BLOWING)
- (SHOES SQUEAKING)
Really? Really?
He's here.
Say something, act natural.
(FORCING LAUGH) Hi!
I'm sorry for the jams,
and the jewels...
(STAMMERS)
and the buying you.
That wasn't me. It was me,
I don't...
It was me, I don't have a
twin or anything, but I...
- Um...
- (APPLAUSE)
Dance? I'd love to.
Yes.
(MOUTHS) Dance?
(WHISPERS) Just dance.
(SLOW FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SIGHS)
- (WHISPERS) Go. Go.
(MOUTHING)
Relax.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (MUSIC PICKS UP TEMPO)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMS)
(MOUTHING)
(CROWD EXCLAIMS)
(PEOPLE GASP)
(CROWD CLAPPING RHYTHMICALLY)
(ALL GASP)
(CHEERING)
MAN: Bravo! Well done!
Something very strange
about him.
Keep a close eye
on Prince Ali.
She just walked out.
Maybe I went a tad far
with the back flip...
but that dance
may be the best thing
you ever do in your life!
I was pretty good.
But nothing seems
to impress her.
Yeah, it's crazy.
Not gems or jams or jewels.
If I can't impress her,
I wonder who can.
What's that
supposed to mean?
I'm just sayin'
try being yourself.
But she has to
marry a prince.
(SIGHS) If I just had
a few more minutes with her,
I know I could...
You need to get me
over there.
Is that an official wish?
No. It's a favor.
For a friend.
Oh, yeah, see, genies don't
really have friends.
I thought you said you never
had a friend like me.
No, I said you never had
a friend like me!
When you're a genie,
somebody always wants
something from ya.
It's awkward.
You're right,
you're right.
Besides,
it would've involved
distracting
a certain handmaiden...
Ooh! Ha!
I see what you're doing!
You hooked me.
See you there?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Good evening.
How did you get past
the guards?
Oh, uh, I snuck past.
All 48 of them?
Even the ones that eat fire?
Impressive.
Yes, well, that's what people
say about me! (CHUCKLES)
Well, that didn't come out
the right way.
No one says that.
I don't know why I said that.
Uh...
(GASPS) They're beautiful!
She will hate them.
Tell Prince Ali the way to
her heart is through her mind.
Oh, actually, these are
from me to you.
Could you excuse me
one moment?
Wait, no, just...
(BOTH MOUTHING)
"That's what people say
about me." Come on, Genie!
My favorites. I accept.
Please continue.
I was noticing
how pleasant the evening is.
At the party,
I noticed you noticing...
how pleasant I am.
Right. How's this going?
It's clumsy,
but in a charming sort of a way.
A stroll.
Would you like to take
an evening stroll?
Just the two of us?
On purpose?
Yes, as people.
Just one more second.
Okay.
Why would I say
"as people"?
That kid is contagious!
Go.
I've never done this before.
How does it work?
- Do you like sheep cheese?
- Uh...
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Come in.
Actually,
I'm already in.
Don't move.
(GROWLING)
I just came back
because you left so...
How did you get there?
Magic carpet?
(SCOFFS)
Actually, I'm glad
you are here.
You are?
I've been trying
to find Ababwa,
but it doesn't seem to be
on any of my maps.
Care to show me?
I'd love to.
(GROWLS)
JASMINE: Rajah,
let's not eat the prince today.
He needs his legs
for dancing.
Did I go too far
with the back flip?
A little.
- Ababwa?
- Yes.
(QUIETLY) Genie,
I need to find Ababwa.
DALIA: My other brother...
the short one,
not the one
who gifted me a goat,
he's married...
ALADDIN: She has maps, lots of maps.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Ababwa, of course.
Ababwa.
Yak napkins
are not easy to find...
(GENIE CHUCKLES)
(MOUTHING)
Have you lost your country?
My country?
No, no. (CHUCKLES)
Uh...
There it is.
(SCOFFS) I don't think so.
I've been...
There it is.
How did I not see that?
ALADDIN: Who needs maps
anyway?
They're old and useless,
and add no practical value.
Maps are how I see the world.
I thought a princess
could go anywhere.
Not this princess.
Well, (STAMMERS)
- would you wanna...?
- (CLATTERING)
- Oh. Uh... (SIGHS)
- (CHUCKLES)
Sorry, sorry.
Rajah!
- (GROWLS)
- Oh.
- Thanks for that.
- (PURRS)
I was saying you should
see these places.
I mean, there's a whole world
outside of books and maps.
Do you want to?
How? Every door is guarded.
Who said anything
about a door?
What are you doing?
Sometimes, Princess...
sometimes, you just
have to take a risk.
(GASPS)
What just happened?
What?
Is this...?
A magic carpet?
Do you trust me?
What did you say?
Yes.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(RAJAH WHINES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING
IN DISTANCE)
♪ I can show you the world
♪ Shining, shimmering
Splendid
♪ Tell me, Princess
♪ Now when did you last
Let your heart decide?
♪ I can open your eyes
♪ Take you wonder by wonder
♪ Over, sideways and under
♪ On a magic carpet ride
♪ A whole new world
♪ A new fantastic
Point of view
♪ No one to tell us no
♪ Or where to go
♪ Or say we're only dreaming
♪ A whole new world
♪ A dazzling place
I never knew
♪ But when I'm way up here
♪ It's crystal clear
♪ That now I'm in
♪ A whole new world
With you
ALADDIN: ♪ Now I'm in A
whole new world with you
♪ Unbelievable sights
- ♪ Indescribable feeling
- ♪ Feeling
JASMINE: ♪ Soaring,
tumbling Freewheeling
♪ Through an endless
Diamond sky
♪ A whole new world
♪ Don't you dare
Close your eyes
♪ A hundred thousand
Things to see
♪ Hold your breath
It gets better
JASMINE:
♪ I'm like a shooting star
♪ I've come so far
♪ I can't go back
To where I used to be
♪ A whole new world
♪ Ev'ry turn a surprise
ALADDIN: ♪ With new
horizons To pursue
♪ Ev'ry moment red-letter
♪ I'll chase them anywhere
♪ There's time to spare
♪ Let me share
This whole new world
♪ With you
ALADDIN:
♪ A whole new world
♪ That's where we'll be
♪ A thrilling chase
♪ A wondrous place
♪ For you and me ♪
- (DRUMS BEATING)
- (RHYTHMIC CLAPPING)
(EXCITED CHATTER)
(JASMINE CHUCKLES)
JASMINE: Of all the places
you've shown me,
this is by far
the most beautiful.
Sometimes,
you just have to see it
from a different
perspective.
It's them, the people.
They make it beautiful.
And they deserve a leader
who knows that.
I don't know why
I think it could be me.
Because it should be you.
You think so?
Does it matter
what I think?
Oh, look at that adorable
monkey down there.
Is that Abu?
No, no,
it couldn't be Abu, he's...
(SIGHS)
So, how many names
do you have, Prince Aladdin?
No, no, I...
So who is Prince Ali?
I am Prince Ali.
But how would you
know the city so well?
I came to Agrabah early...
because to know a people,
you have to see them
for yourself.
But you already
know that.
When we first met,
you were disguised in your own city.
You saw us arrive
with dancers, an elephant,
and a magic carpet.
How could a street thief
have all that?
But how could I not
recognize you?
People don't see the real you
when you're royalty.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
I mean, you've seen
more of Agrabah in days
than I have
in an entire lifetime.
We should...
probably head back.
Already?
Until tomorrow, Princess.
Good night.
Yes!
(WHOOPING)
Fascinating.
Ooh.
I like that face.
Good date?
The best.
But it was better
than the best.
She figured out I was Aladdin.
You said that wouldn't happen.
Wow! I mean, genie magic
is really just a facade.
At some point,
real character's always
gonna shine through.
But that's a good thing,
right? Now, she knows.
Well...
Well, what?
He told me he was only
pretending to be a thief
to see the city...
but he's actually
a prince.
I convinced her that
I really was a prince.
And you believed him?
And she believed you?
I think so.
Eventually, you are going to
have to tell her the truth.
Eventually,
I will tell her.
Anyway,
I sort of am a prince now.
Oh!
So, you're gonna drink
from that cup.
You don't think maybe
you want to believe him...
because you have to
marry a prince,
but you can't marry a thief?
No, I believe him. I do.
(IAGO SQUAWKING)
When the time is right,
I will tell her.
(CHITTERING)
Morning.
HAKIM: Morning.
(SIGHS)
Not again.
Please, please.
Gentlemen, I think there's
been some sort of confusion.
I don't think you know
who I am.
JAFAR: Oh, no, no.
I know who you are.
- Aladdin.
- (SQUAWKS)
Aladdin?
IAGO: Aladdin.
I don't know who that is.
I'm Prince Ali...
- Street rat!
- ...of Ababwa.
JAFAR: Prince from a kingdom
that doesn't exist...
who now possesses
a magic carpet
from the Cave of Wonders.
Seems to me, the only way
that's possible...
Where's your monkey?
JAFAR: ...is if you found
a certain treasure.
My treasure.
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
Where's the lamp?
(SCREECHING)
There's clearly been some
sort of misunderstanding.
I'm Prince Ali.
If I throw you
off of that balcony,
and you are
who you say you are...
you will die
a watery death.
(GRUNTS)
If you survive,
it can only be because of the lamp.
In which case,
I will have my answer.
For the last time...
where is the lamp?
Listen to me. I don't know
who you think I am.
Goodbye, Aladdin.
No! No!
(SCREAMING)
Hmm.
(CHITTERING)
Boy, what in the...?
Whoa. Hey, kid, okay.
I can't get you out of this
unless you make a wish!
You have to make a wish!
Come on, wake up!
Okay, try and form the words
"I wish."
Kid, come on, wake up!
Wake up.
You need to think.
Think, think.
Think.
Okay, okay!
A little gray area here,
but it's worth a try.
(CLEARS THROAT)
"I, Aladdin,
being of sound body and mind...
"declare that my second wish
"is to be saved
from certain doom."
I took the liberty
to backdate that a day.
I hope you don't mind.
Yes! Here we go! Come on!
(GENIE YELLING)
(CONTINUES YELLING)
Come on, kid! Come on!
Kid? Kid? Kid, please.
Come on! Wake up!
Wake up, wake up!
Kid, wake up.
Please.
- (COUGHING)
- Ew.
Probably could've done that
the other direction, but...
(GASPING)
How you doing?
(SIGHS) Thanks, Genie.
Hey, no problem, you know.
I was in the neighborhood.
I thought you said no favors.
(STAMMERS)
I thought you said no friends.
Right. Um... It actually
cost you a wish.
(PANTING)
Whatever it cost,
you saved my life.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, strictly speaking
though, it was a team effort.
(CHITTERING)
Thank you.
We have to stop Jafar.
That's not gonna be easy.
The sultan trusts him
completely.
He has everybody fooled.
Maybe not everyone.
(DOOR OPENS)
JAFAR: I overheard Prince Ali
talking to his advisor...
about returning with an army
to conquer Agrabah.
SULTAN: What?
JAFAR: Now it appears
he's fled in the night.
SULTAN: Jasmine.
You heard him
say this, Jafar,
and you saw him leave?
IAGO: Uh-oh.
Yes, with my own ears
and my own eyes.
So, what's the problem
now, Princess?
This is the problem, Jafar.
If what you say is true,
then why is Prince Ali
still here?
Your Majesty.
Prince Ali.
This is a surprise.
Your Highness,
your advisor's not who he says he is.
Oh.
I'm not who I say I am?
Baba, he tried
to kill Prince Ali.
Jafar, can you explain
this to me?
Yes.
(WHOOSHES)
JAFAR: (DISTORTED)
My sultan...
you know my loyalty
belongs to you.
Your loyalty...
Yes.
Prince Ali, you invited
yourself into our city...
and we welcomed you
as our guest.
But I believe
your intentions are...
(WHOOSHES)
...deceitful.
You're a grave danger
to Agrabah
and you shall be
dealt with as such.
- Baba, what are you saying?
- Enough, Jasmine!
Jafar told me
of Prince Ali's ambition.
(QUIETLY) His staff.
SULTAN: He's here
for my throne.
Hakim!
(YELLING)
(WHOOSHES)
Baba?
(GASPING) What happened?
He had you under a spell.
He's not to be trusted,
Your Majesty.
He wants your throne.
Jafar! You were
my most trusted advisor.
Hakim! Put him
in the dungeon!
(CHUCKLES)
(SQUAWKING)
You should think
about how quickly
the sands of power shift
in a storm, Hakim.
I am loyal to my sultan,
as you should have been.
The law is the law.
Prince Ali,
I must apologize.
Well, Your Highness,
there's something I'd like to explain.
Your honor and integrity
will never again be
questioned here in Agrabah.
I...
SULTAN: A more noble
and sincere young man
has never graced
the chambers of this palace.
Well, uh...
- Wow.
- I...
I would be honored
to call you my son...
Ooh!
...if that were something
anyone wanted.
GENIE: So, you got the girl.
I mean, trust me,
I had my doubts
after your whole jam debacle.
But you pulled yourself
back together a little bit.
I did, didn't I?
I think I finally got the
hang of being a prince.
Oh, well, that's not
exactly what I meant.
You were right! People see
what they wanna see.
Aladdin is gone.
I'm Prince Ali now.
Wow. Got it all figured out
now, huh, kid?
And, you know, I was thinking
about my last wish...
and I just can't do this
without you.
I know I told you
I'd use it to set you free,
but you heard the sultan.
I can't let everything
we worked for fall apart.
So, you just
never tell her the truth?
You're gonna
keep living the lie?
It's not a lie.
People can change.
(SCOFFS) Oh,
they can change all right.
And that's a bad thing?
Everything is better now.
No one got hurt.
You'd rather me be
back on the streets
stealing to survive?
I thought you'd be
happy for me.
But all you cared about
was that
I use my last wish
to set you free.
Well, kid, I don't care
nothin' about that wish.
This is about you,
what's happening to you.
You'd rather lie
to somebody you love
than give all of this up.
You don't get it, Genie.
People like me
don't get anything
except by pretending.
I think maybe
you don't get it.
The more you gain
by pretending,
the less you're actually
gonna have.
In 10,000 years,
I have never once, ever...
called a master a friend.
I broke the rules for you,
I saved your life.
And for what?
You are breaking
my heart here, kid.
You're breaking my heart.
Genie, no!
Hey, come on!
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(ABU CHITTERS)
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
IAGO: Lamp. Lamp.
Master. Lamp.
Who does he think he is?
He's supposed to serve me.
I'm the same as I always was
on the inside. Right, Abu?
(ABU SCREECHES)
Hey!
Aah! Are you kidding?
Now, why would you
rub the thing under the...
archway?
(LAUGHING)
ALADDIN:
♪ Riffraff
♪ Street rat
♪ Would they think that
♪ If they look much closer?
♪ Still, I can't
Play a prince here
♪ No, siree
♪ Gotta tell the truth
I can't pretend
♪ Even if it means
This dream will end
♪ Even if she walks away
♪ From me ♪
(PEOPLE CHATTERING
IN DISTANCE)
Jafar.
You should have left Agrabah
while you had the chance.
Why leave when the city
belongs to me now?
- It's over, Jafar.
- IAGO: Oh, good for you.
I've endured
your spineless incompetence
- for long enough now.
- (IAGO CACKLES)
- Hakim.
- IAGO: Old fool.
JAFAR: Genie!
For my first wish,
I wish to be
sultan of Agrabah!
What?
As you wish, Master.
No!
(CRACKLING)
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
(YELLING)
(YELLING CONTINUES)
(PANTING)
(RAJAH GROWLS)
Hakim.
JAFAR: Hakim!
You obey the sultan,
so you obey me now.
You know the law, Hakim!
No.
My sultan!
GUARDS: My sultan!
(SPEARS THUMPING)
Hakim.
Marshal an army
to invade Shirabad.
- Shirabad!
- You cannot...
I think we've heard enough
from you, Princess.
It's time you start doing
what you should have done
all along.
Stay silent.
- Guards, remove her!
- (RAJAH GROWLS)
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(SNARLING)
Control that cat if you know
what's good for you.
Rajah.
Rajah!
- (SNARLS)
- Rajah! It's all right.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(CHUCKLES)
- Don't touch her!
- Baba.
SULTAN: Jasmine.
(RAJAH WHINES)
JAFAR: And understand
it's better for you
to be seen and not heard.
I think we've heard enough
from you, Princess.
Stay silent.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
♪ Written in stone
Ev'ry rule, ev'ry word
♪ Centuries old
And unbending
♪ "Stay in your place
Better seen and not heard"
♪ Well, now that story
Is ending
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
♪ 'Cause I
♪ I cannot start to crumble
♪ So come on and try
♪ Try to shut me
And cut me down
SULTAN: Jasmine!
♪ I won't be silenced
♪ You can't keep me quiet
♪ Won't tremble
When you try it
♪ All I know is
I won't go speechless
♪ Speechless
♪ Let the storm in
♪ I cannot be broken
♪ No, I won't live unspoken
♪ 'Cause I know
That I won't go speechless
♪ Try to lock me
In this cage
♪ I won't just lay me down
And die
♪ I will take
These broken wings
♪ And watch me
Burn across the sky
♪ Hear the echo saying
♪ I won't be silenced
♪ Though you wanna see me
Tremble when you try it
♪ All I know is
I won't go speechless
♪ Speechless
♪ 'Cause I'll breathe
♪ When they try
To suffocate me
♪ Don't you underestimate me
♪ 'Cause I know that
I won't go speechless
♪ All I know is
♪ Speechless ♪
(PANTING)
JASMINE: Hakim!
Hakim!
Take her away!
Tell them, Hakim.
You were just a boy
when your father
came to work the grounds.
But you have risen up
to become
our most trusted soldier.
As a man, I know you to be
both loyal and just.
But now you have to choose.
Duty isn't always honor.
Our greatest challenge
isn't speaking up
against our enemies...
but defying those whose
approval we seek the most.
Jafar is not worthy of your
admiration nor your sacrifice.
I wish nothing but glory
for the kingdom of Agrabah.
No. You seek glory
for yourself.
And you would win it
off the backs of my people!
Hakim, these men,
they will follow
where you lead...
but it's up to you.
Will you stand silent
while Jafar destroys
our beloved kingdom...
or will you do
what is right...
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
and stand with the people
of Agrabah?
My princess.
Forgive me, my sultan.
Hakim.
Guards, arrest the vizier!
- (IAGO SQUAWKS)
- (RAJAH ROARS)
IAGO: Lamp! Rub the lamp.
So, this is how it will be.
Not even the title of sultan
will wake the herd
from their sleep.
I should've known.
If you won't bow
before a sultan,
you will cower
before a sorcerer.
Genie! I wish to become
the most powerful sorcerer
there is!
As you wish, Master.
(CRACKLING)
(SQUAWKING)
(HISSING)
(SQUAWKS) This could be fun.
(RAJAH GROWLS)
Hakim, I had
such big plans for you.
But now...
you are no longer
of any use to me.
Perhaps your men would like to
follow you to the dungeon.
- (STAFF THUDS)
- (GUARDS SCREAMING)
- JAFAR: You too.
- (ROARING)
- Prince Ali!
- (STAFF THUDS)
If it isn't our Prince Ali.
- Ali!
- Or should I say...
- (GROANS)
- (GASPS)
Aladdin.
He's been pretending
the entire time.
An impostor.
There is no Prince Ali.
There never was.
He's nothing
but a lying thief.
I'm sorry.
JAFAR: You're insignificant.
An irritation I no longer
need to tolerate...
once I ensure
your agonizing death
by banishing you
to the ends of the earth.
JASMINE: No!
(SCREAMING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(SHIVERING)
No.
No!
Abu.
Abu!
I could simply kill you all.
But that would be
inadequate repayment
for years of humiliation
and neglect.
(BLOWS)
"Remember your place, Jafar."
"You forget yourself, Jafar."
Jafar.
No, what you need, Baba,
is to suffer.
- Like I have suffered.
- (GASPS) Baba?
Would watching me rule
your kingdom be enough?
Stop!
Or watching my armies
devour your toothless ally?
Please, make it stop.
No, the most
suitable punishment
would be to make you watch...
while I take
what you love most.
No. No, please.
Baba.
And marry your daughter.
- No!
- (STAFF THUDS)
- (GASPS)
- No.
(STRAINING)
She will never marry you.
(WHOOSHING)
Baba.
I will do as you wish!
Make it stop.
(CHOKING)
- (STAFF THUDS)
- (DALIA GROANS)
JASMINE: Baba!
Baba, are you all right?
SULTAN: (WEAKLY) Jasmine.
ALADDIN: Abu!
Abu!
(WEAK WHISTLING)
(GRUNTING)
- Abu.
- (WHIMPERING)
Are you okay?
Let's get out of here.
- (ICE CRACKING)
- No.
(SCREAMING)
- (ABU WHIMPERING)
- (BREATHING WEAKLY)
(GASPING)
IMAM: Your Highness, Sultan,
in honesty and sincerity...
do you accept
Princess Jasmine...?
JAFAR: Yes.
Yes, I accept.
Princess.
IMAM: Princess Jasmine,
do you accept the sultan
to be your husband?
Come on, woman.
IAGO: Accept.
I...
Yes?
do not!
IAGO: (SQUAWKS)
The lamp! The lamp!
JAFAR: (GASPS) Stop her!
No, Jasmine! No!
- (JASMINE SCREAMS)
- JAFAR: No! No!
(CHUCKLES)
The lamp! Iago!
- ALADDIN: Are you okay?
- JASMINE: Yes.
(SQUAWKING)
(ROARS)
Hold on!
(PEOPLE YELPING)
The lamp!
ALADDIN: Abu!
(ROARS)
(JASMINE YELPING)
IAGO: The lamp!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Carpet, get me up there!
Abu!
- (ALADDIN GRUNTS)
- (IAGO SCREECHES)
Jump!
(JASMINE YELPS)
(SCREAMING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
JAFAR: No!
(SQUAWKS)
(SCREECHES)
- (ALADDIN GRUNTS)
- (CHITTERS)
You're nothing
without your staff!
Nothing!
- (ROARS)
- (THUNDER CRASHING)
(YELLING)
(PANICKED CHATTER)
(BOTH YELLING AND SCREAMING)
JASMINE: The lamp!
(JASMINE SCREAMING)
ALADDIN: Carpet!
(CONTINUES YELLING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Jasmine.
(SQUAWKS)
Punish them. Punish them.
Genie should witness.
(CHITTERING)
JAFAR: As the old man said...
you should've left Agrabah
when you had the chance.
I told you before
to think bigger.
You could've been the most
powerful man in the room.
But now I hold the lamp.
I hold the power.
(RUMBLING)
You can't find
what you're looking for
in that lamp, Jafar.
I tried and failed,
and so will you.
You think so,
but I am sultan!
I am the greatest sorcerer
the world has ever seen.
I will create an empire
that history cannot ignore.
I can destroy cities.
I can destroy kingdoms.
(GRUNTS)
And I can destroy you.
ALADDIN: True.
But who made you a sultan?
Who made you a sorcerer?
There will
always be something,
some man, some being...
- more powerful than you.
- What are you doing?
ALADDIN:
Genie gave you your power,
and he can take it away.
- He serves me!
- ALADDIN: For now.
But you'll never have
more power than the genie.
- (WHOOSHING)
- (GROANING)
(SCREECHES)
You said it yourself.
You're either most powerful
in the room...
or you're nothing.
You'll always be second.
Second! Second!
(IAGO LAUGHS DERISIVELY)
Second?
- (GASPING)
- Only second?
He serves me!
I will make sure no one will
ever say these words again.
Genie!
For my final wish,
I wish to become
the most powerful being
in the universe.
More powerful than you!
A lot of gray area
in that wish, but, uh...
most powerful being
in the universe
coming right up!
- (WHOOSHING)
- (LAUGHING)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(SQUAWKS)
(GROWLING)
(LAUGHING)
The most powerful
in the universe, at last...
second to no one.
And I thought
I had power before!
First, I'll lay waste
to those fools in Shirabad.
- (YELLING)
- (CRACKLING)
(GRUNTS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (CUFFS CLANG)
What have you done to me?
I haven't done anything
to you, Jafar.
What have you done to me?
This was your wish, not mine.
(GRUNTS)
A genie might have
phenomenal cosmic powers...
But an itty-bitty
living space.
You see,
a genie without a master
goes back in their lamp.
JAFAR: (GASPS)
No! Not the lamp!
(GRUNTING)
I will not forget you, boy!
Mark my words,
I will not forget
what you have done to me!
IAGO: Goodbye, Jafar!
Parrot! You're coming with me!
- (SQUAWKS)
- (SCREAMS) No!
(SCREAMING)
Baba.
- Baba.
- ALADDIN: Come on.
Couple thousand years
in the Cave of Wonders
ought to cool you off.
(LAMP WHISTLING)
(DISTANT BOOM)
(CHITTERING)
(PANTING) Wait. Wait.
How can I ever thank you?
Oh, no. No,
you don't need to thank me.
But I hope
you accept my apology.
I'm sorry to the both of you.
Especially you.
You deserve so much.
We all make mistakes.
Aladdin?
I hope you find
what you're looking for.
Ooh, that's a bit
of a mess there, Abu.
Let me take care
of that for you.
(CHITTERING EXCITEDLY)
(GRUNTS, CHITTERS)
Beautiful.
Uh-uh-uh.
No, no long faces, all right?
I got an idea.
All right?
This is your last wish.
Royalty was
the right idea, okay?
We should just
riff on that a little bit.
All right,
here's what I'm thinking.
(DEEP VOICE)
Aladdin, warrior prince,
a noble heart in a land
where thieves run feral!
Jasmine!
(NORMAL VOICE)
You like it?
No? Okay, all right.
I hear you loud and clear.
All right.
But this is what you need.
The governing laws of Agrabah
by royal decree.
Okay? And here it is.
"Must marry a prince."
Right.
But you say the words...
and this law just,
kinda like, goes away.
And you and the princess
are in it together forever.
You can just make
the law disappear?
Pfft! Please.
Like it never existed.
All right.
Last wish, let's get it.
Okay. (SIGHS) Last wish.
Genie?
I'm ready, hold on.
Here we go.
I wish...
Third and final wish.
I wish
to set you free.
What?
Whoa. What? Oh!
(GASPS) Wait.
Wait, am I...?
Wait, wait, wait.
Um...
Tell me to do something.
Um... Get me some jams.
(HESITANTLY)
Get it yourself?
(CHUCKLES) Get your own jams!
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you.
No. Thank you, Genie.
I owe you everything.
What are you gonna do now?
GENIE: Um...
Actually,
there is this handmaiden...
that I would love
to travel the world with.
If she'll have me.
When do we leave?
Also, I want children.
Yes. Two of them.
DALIA: Lian and Omar,
three years apart.
They will worship us both
and ask lots of questions...
and you will entertain them
with stories and songs.
...and he's handsome like me.
GENIE: We'll have a boat.
DALIA: A large one
with multiple levels
and magnificent sails.
I was thinking
more of a smaller one.
Perfect.
Perfect. (CHUCKLES)
Sit with me, my child.
I'm sorry.
- Baba, why are you...?
- Please, let me finish.
I feared losing you.
Like I lost your mother.
All I saw was my little girl,
not the woman you have become.
You have shown me
courage and strength.
You are the future of Agrabah.
(GASPS)
You shall be the next sultan.
(SULTAN EXHALES)
Thank you, Baba.
And as sultan,
you may change the law.
He is a good man.
Where'd he go?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
- (SIGHS)
- (ABU CHITTERS)
JASMINE: Stop, thief.
Your sultan commands it.
(CROWD MURMURS)
Sultan?
Does that mean I'm in trouble?
Only because you got caught.
(ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (UPBEAT JAZZY MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
(CROWD SHOUTING IN UNISON)
♪ Can your friends do this?
(PLAYING FLUTE)
(JASMINE BEATBOXING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(CROWD CHEERS)
(CROWD SHOUTING IN UNISON)
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me ♪
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
- ♪ Yeah
- ♪ Another one
♪ You know it's Will Smith
And DJ Khaled!
♪ Whoo!
♪ Too late
Y'all done wound me up
♪ Hurry up!
♪ Too late
Y'all done wound me up
♪ Hurry up!
♪ 'Bout to show you
What I'm workin' with
♪ Show me
What you're workin' with
♪ It's the Ali Baba
It's the big papa
♪ It's the blue pants
Jasmine, like the flower
♪ It's the grant you wishes
That don't even cost a dollar
♪ You ride in on a carpet
♪ When you ride in
Wanna holler like
♪ Ay
Tell me where you wanna go
♪ Hold up!
Don't tell me, I already know
♪ Watch out
It's the genie with a attitude
♪ Three wishes
What I need to make true?
- ♪ Mister
- ♪ Tell me whatever you need
- ♪ What you need?
♪ Anything rearranged
Even climate can change
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me
♪ Never!
♪ Just a lamp and a rub away
From whatever you want
♪ Habibi, let me show you
The dream
♪ Habibi!
♪ Just whisper
If you don't wanna
♪ Shout out what you need
♪ But I promise you ain't
Never had a friend like me
♪ Tell the angels and gods
Pass the baklava
♪ Make 'em travel from close
Or make 'em travel from far
♪ Well, this is your chance,
man Wish from the soul
♪ When I'm out of the lamp,
man I'm out of control
♪ I got gold on my shoes
Temple with jewels
♪ A room for wise men
And plenty for fools
♪ I don't want you to lose
Tryin' to help ya, dude
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me
♪ Never!
- ♪ Go big time!
- ♪ Big time!
- ♪ Wish big time!
- ♪ Go big time!
- ♪ Big time!
- ♪ Wish big time!
♪ Go big time!
- ♪ Let me see you flex on her
- ♪ Flex on her
- ♪ Shine on her
- ♪ Style on her
- ♪ Slide on her
♪ Too fly, too fly on her
♪ Just glide on her
♪ Cool as a fan
♪ I'm the coolest
Bluest one of 'em all
♪ You can wish to be rich
You can wish to be tall
♪ You can wish away the haters
You just give me a call
♪ You can wish for
What you want
♪ 'Cause I'm grantin' 'em all
- ♪ Mister
- ♪ Tell me whatever you need
- ♪ What you need?
♪ Anything rearranged
Even climate can change
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me
♪ Never!
♪ Just a lamp and a rub away
From whatever you want
♪ Habibi, let me show you
The dream
♪ Habibi!
♪ Just whisper
If you don't wanna
♪ Shout out what you need
♪ But I promise you ain't
Never had a friend like me
♪ Please don't get me started
♪ Fly like magic carpet
♪ You ain't never had a friend
- ♪ Never had a friend
- ♪ Never!
♪ You ain't never had a friend
- ♪ Never had a friend
- ♪ Never!
- ♪ You ain't never
- ♪ Never
- ♪ Had a
- ♪ Friend
- ♪ Like
♪ Me!
♪ You ain't never had
A friend like me
♪ Never! ♪
♪ I can show you the world
♪ Shining, shimmering splendid
♪ Tell me, Princess
♪ Now when did you last
Let your heart decide?
♪ I can open your eyes
♪ Take you wonder by wonder
♪ Over sideways and under
♪ On a magic carpet ride
♪ A whole new world
♪ A new fantastic
Point of view
♪ No one to tell us no
♪ Or where to go
♪ Or say we're only dreaming
♪ A whole new world
♪ A dazzling place
I never knew
♪ But when I'm way up here
♪ It's crystal clear
♪ That now I'm in
A whole new world with you
♪ Now I'm in a whole new world
With you
♪ Unbelievable sights
♪ Indescribable feeling
♪ Soaring, tumbling
Freewheeling
♪ Through an endless
Diamond sky
♪ A whole new world
♪ Don't you dare
Close your eyes
♪ A hundred thousand things
To see
♪ Hold your breath
It gets better
♪ I'm like a shooting star
I've come so far
♪ I can't go back
To where I used to be
♪ A whole new world
♪ With new horizons to pursue
♪ I'll chase them anywhere
♪ There's time to spare
♪ Let me share
This whole new world with you
- ♪ A whole new world
♪ A new fantastic
Point of view
♪ No one to tell us no
♪ Or where to go
♪ Or say we're only dreaming
- ♪ A whole new world
- ♪ Every turn, a surprise
- ♪ With new horizons to pursue
- ♪ Every moment, red-letter
♪ I'll chase them anywhere
There's time to spare
- ♪ Anywhere, ooh
- ♪ There's time to spare
♪ Let me share
This whole new world with you
- ♪ A whole new world
- ♪ That's where we'll be
- ♪ A thrilling chase
- ♪ A wondrous place
♪ For you and me ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Sync by GoldenBeard