ln 1973, Egypt and Syria launched
a surprise attack against lsrael.
By Day Two, lsraeli ground forces
appeared on the verge of defeat.
ln the event that their ground forces
were overrun,
an lsraeli A-4 jet
took off on patrol. . .
. . .with one nuclear bomb.
- Why not negotiate?
- The interview is over.
Only criminals and their friends
in the West wish it to be separate.
But, Mr. President,
if you will kindly come back...
we do have a few more questions
we would like to ask you.
So what is it?
Are you blind?
It's a bomb.
Where's the fuse?
It's warm.
So am I. Come on.
I don't have all night.
It's a dud.
Let's get it on the truck.
But how can we sell it now?
There's always someone
who'll buy this crap.
I cannot stand all these questions
about my health.
I am to be described as
"robust" and "healthy".
Zdrastuyte, William Cabot.
Where you received
highest honors in English.
For ten years now,
we have contended--
Finally...
every nation has a right
to defend itself.
This terrorism must end.
The bombing of Chechnya
was my decision.
Who did it?
General Pildysh, General Mitkin.
Unhappy old Communists.
Bastards.
- Relieve them of command.
- I will shoot them myself.
Just disappear them.
Their execution would tell the world
I didn't have control.
These days, better to appear guilty
than impotent.
Your scarf, Monsieur.
I expected this.
Really?
What will you do?
Nothing.
We will do nothing.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Mrs Spassky.
At the end of the corridor.
I haven't seen Sasha since university.
And you were his teaching assistant?
Strange, I don't remember you.
When he heard I was in Arzamas,
he asked me to look in on you.
- He says he'll take me to the West.
- That would require a lot of money.
Just because the imbeciles here pay
him nothing doesn't mean others won't.
He has a secret job.
For the government?
For imbeciles with money.
Same nonsense, do this, don't do that.
They even told him
not to call his mother.
The pigs.
I could die any day
and he can't phone his mother.
But my Sasha, he called.
Just last night.
Ah, the warmth of plutonium decay.
It's completely corroded.
At least you're wearing gloves.
Anyone want to light up
an American cigarette?
You're crazy.
I'm going out.
Attention.
You've heard of the bomb in the USA.
What you haven't heard
is that 15 minutes ago
an American ICBM hit Moscow.
We are to retaliate against an American
aircraft carrier in the North Sea.
Man your aircraft.
But rest assured those responsible
will be dealt with most severely.
He's fishing.
Send our reply.
...but we will protect ourselves
from further aggression.
He thinks we did this.
We must demonstrate
the strength of our weapons.
They have to understand that
attacking Russia would be suicide.
Increase the alert status.
I ordered no such attack.
You must not respond to this action...
You dropped the bomb on Hiroshima.
You dropped the bomb on Nagasaki.
What?
Spinnaker.
To make no response
is to invite a greater attack.
American submarines from Norfolk
and Kings Bay are putting to sea.
They carry Trident D3 missiles.
A first strike weapon.
Fowler is not so insane
as to launch a first strike.
Perhaps he doesn't think
it's the first strike.
Once their Stealth bombers go up,
we will have no choice.
That will be the sign.
How do we convince him
not to launch his bombers?
- Maybe we should...
- Bring our missiles to highest alert.
They'd be crazy to attack then.
A nuclear strike on Colorado Springs
would take out NORAD.
It would limit their ability
to launch a counter-attack.
How many people live
in Colorado Springs?
Three or four hundred thousand.
Mr President, to use nuclear weapons
against the Americans...
...would be to cross a threshold.
They think we already have. Should
we now wait for them to annihilate us?
I cannot stop what I did not start.
Mr President.
Their Stealth bombers
have left Aviano.
That is the sign.
Shoot them down.
God protect us.
How close are the bombers?
They're slipping in and out of radar
over Poland.
Activate the missile regiments.
Type exactly what I say.
This is madness. He is CIA.
We cannot hang our fate
on the word of their spy.
What is the harm of listening
a bit more?
You see? He is wasting time.
We must launch now.
We have only moments.
They cut him off.
They are going to strike.
Prepare the launch orders now.