Oh, oh, oh
Woke up today
Feeling the way I always do
Oh, oh, oh
Hungry for something that I can't eat
Then I hear that beat
That rhythm of town
Starts calling me down
It's like a message from high above
Oh, oh, oh
Pulling me out to the smiles
And the streets that I love
- Good morning, Baltimore!
- Good morning, Baltimore
Every day's like an open door
Every night is a fantasy
Every sound's like a symphony
Good morning, Baltimore
And someday when I take to the floor
The world's gonna wake up and see
Baltimore and me
Oh, oh, oh
Look at my hair
What 'do can compare with mine today?
Oh, oh, oh
I've got my hairspray and radio
I'm ready to go
The rats on the street
All dance around my feet
They seem to say,
"Tracy, it's up to you"
So, oh, oh, don't hold me back
'Cause today all my dreams
Will come true
Good morning, Baltimore
There's the flasher
Who lives next door
There's the bum on his barroom stool
They wish me luck on my way to school
Good morning, Baltimore
And someday when I take to the floor
The world's gonna wake up and see
Baltimore and me
I know every step
I know every song
I know there's a place where I belong
I see all those party lights
Shining ahead
So someone invite me
before I drop dead
Before she drops dead
So, oh, oh, give me a chance
'Cause when I start to dance
I'm a movie star
Oh, oh, oh
Something inside of me makes me move
When I hear that groove
My ma tells me "no"
But my feet tell me "go"
It's like a drummer inside my heart
So, oh, oh, don't make me wait
One more moment for my life to start
I love you, Baltimore
Every day's like an open door
Every night is a fantasy
Every sound's like a symphony
And I promise, Baltimore
That someday when I take to the floor
The world's gonna wake up and see
Gonna wake up and see
- Baltimore and me
- Yes, more or less, we all agree
- Someday the world is gonna see
Baltimore and me
Mount Everest is the most famous
but not the highest
geographical point on this Earth.
Now, who can tell me what that is?
Um, excuse me, Miss Whimsy?
I can't see the board again.
Tracy Turnblad.
If I have to write you up
for inappropriate hair height
one more time,
you will be removed to detention.
Miss Wimsey,
what am I supposed to do?
Hair can't just hang there
like a dead thing on your cheeks.
I mean, Well,
You know what I mean. I,
As I said, it is not Mount Everest.
Now, next week, we will be talking
about earthquakes and volcanoes.
And as exciting as that might sound,
we have to look back
approximately 60 million years.
Now, if you turn your pages,
we are going to start
with the Ring of Fire.
I want you to contemplate what causes
the separation of the two components.
Penny, come on, hurry!
Outta my way!
Push! We're late.
- One minute to air.
- Okay.
Don't change that channel.
Coming up next,
The Corny Collins Show.
Thirty seconds.
- Hiya, Dad!
- Goodbye!
Hi.
It's my daughter.
10 seconds. Places, everyone.
Hurry up, Penny, we're missing it!
My mom says I'm not allowed
to perspire!
Hey there, teenage Baltimore!
Don't change that channel
'cause it's time
for The Corny Collins Show!
Brought to you
by Ultra Clutch hairspray.
Oh, every afternoon
When the clock strikes four
Bop-bee-ba, ba-ba-ba-ba, bee-ba
Well, a crazy bunch of kids
Crash through that door, yeah
Bop-bee-ba, ba-ba-ba-ba, bee-ba
Well, they throw off their coats
And leave the squares behind
And then they shake it,
Shake it, shake it
Like they're losing their mind
You'll never see them frown
'Cause they're the nicest kids
In town
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Oh, every afternoon
You turn your TV on, huh
Na, na, na
Yeah, we know you turn the sound up
When your parents are gone, yeah
Na, na, na
Then you twist and shout
For your favourite star
And when you've practiced every step
That's in your repertoire
You better come on down
And meet the nicest kids in town
Nice white kids
Who like to lead the way
And once a month
We have our Negro Day
And I'm the man
Who keeps it spinning round
Mr Corny Collins
With the latest, greatest
Baltimore sound
So, every afternoon, drop everything
Bop-bee-ba, ba-ba-ba-ba, bee-ba
Who needs to read and write
When you can dance and sing, yeah!
Bop-bee-ba, ba-ba-ba-ba, bee-ba
Forget about your algebra
And calculus
You can always do your homework
On the morning bus
Can't tell a verb from a noun
They're the nicest kids in town
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Roll call!
I'm Amber.
Brad.
- Tammy.
- Fender.
- Brenda.
- Sketch.
- Shelley.
- IQ.
Lou Ann.
- Joey. Mikey.
- Vicki. Becky.
- Bix.
- Jesse.
- Darla.
- Paulie.
- Noreen.
- Doreen.
And I'm... Link.
So, if every night you're shaking
As you lie in bed
- Mony, mony
- Shake it, baby
And the bass and drums
Are pounding in your head
Mony, mony, ooh, mony, mony
Who cares about sleep
When you can snooze in school
You'll never get to college
But you'll sure look cool
Don't need a cap or a gown
When you're the nicest kids in town
They must think my ears
are garbage cans.
Would you turn that racket down?
I'm trying to iron here.
Nicest kids in...
Kids in town
- Whoo!
Ma, it's not racket.
It's The Corny Collins Show.
Well, it's turning your brains
into mud.
Mrs Turnblad, it's a new dance!
The Stricken Chicken.
Well, I can't hear myself think.
How am I supposed
to negotiate pleats?
- Edna?
- I'm in here, Prudy.
What's that racket?
Oh, Tracy.
Edna, is my laundry ready?
Yep.
That'll be three dollars, hon.
That's pretty pricey
for a pair of petty pants.
Well, I'm sorry, Prudy,
but some of your personal stains
required pounding with a rock.
I'm sure I don't know what you mean.
You're letting her listen
to that race music again?
My daughter spends every afternoon
at the Stamp and Coin Club.
Oh, really?
Well, your daughter hap...
Oh, what is that? The Waving Raven?
It's a little twitchy.
Oh, you wanna play Charades now.
All right.
Okay, go ahead.
You.
Penny.
No.
Tracy Turnblad.
Are you trying to tell me
that Penny didn't get permission
from her mother to be here?
What?
Penny.
You are banned from this house!
You will never watch that show again!
Without that show, I have nothing!
Having nothing builds character!
Toodle-oo, Edna!
Give them a hand, folks.
All right, all right.
And, once again,
that's the Stricken Chicken.
We will be right back
for some more
of that hot Detroit sound.
And we're off!
Corny.
"Detroit sound"?
What's that,
the cries of people being mugged?
Aw, Velma.
The kids dig the rhythm and blues.
Yeah, they're kids, Corny.
That's why we have to steer them
in the white direction.
Right direction?
Didn't I say that?
I'll do it.
You try that again
and there'll be stumps
where your feet should be.
You got that? You little who...
- Amber.
- Holy moly.
Baby.
Good job dancing today.
It's time.
- Link.
- Amber.
Amber. Amber, Amber, Amber.
Save your personal life
for the cameras, sweetie.
Shiny.
Tammy, Lou Ann, you're gonna die.
Speaking of cameras,
did you have a nice nap?
If you'd do your job,
my daughter wouldn't have to fight
to be visible.
I gotta show some of the
other kids once in a while.
You know, this is a small city.
There aren't that many stations.
This time next year,
you could be wearing
an ill-fitting tux,
snapping bar mitzvah photos.
I don't know.
Show Link.
This is nuts. She can't even dance.
Plastic little spastic.
Oh, Link.
I can dance so much better than her.
- Why don't you notice me at school?
- Mm-hmm.
Ooh
Hey.
That was our very own Link Larkin
singing It Takes Two.
And I'm Motormouth Maybelle
reminding,
the last Tuesday of this month's
your rhythm and blues day.
That's right!
Negro Day will be coming your way.
So don't... Uh...
Over here.
Thank you.
So, catch all the crooning
when you're all set and tune in.
Thank you, Motormouth. And now...
Owner's coming.
He'll call my mother again. Let's go!
- ...very own fun-loving...
- Hey!
Come on up here, Brenda.
Brenda will be taking...
What?
...a leave of absence from the show.
How long you gonna be gone, Brenda?
Just nine months.
Seems like we'll have an opening
here on the show for a girl
just as fun-loving,
but maybe not quite as freewheeling.
Wanna be one
of the nicest kids in town?
Cut school tomorrow and come down
to station WYZT to audition.
- No.
- But, Ma.
Don't test me, Tracy Turnblad.
My diet pill's wearing off.
But come on!
No one is auditioning for anything
in this household.
But why not? Why not?
Because dancing is not your future.
One day, you're gonna own
Edna's Occidental Laundry.
I don't wanna be a laundress.
I wanna be famous!
Look, if you wanna be famous,
learn how to take blood
outta car upholstery.
That's a skill you can take
right to the bank.
- Hey. What's all the ruckus in here?
- Not a word.
Daddy, tomorrow I'm auditioning
to dance on a TV show.
- No, she is not!
- You are?
First the hair, now this?
But all the kids
are batting up their hair now, hon.
- You're no help.
- It's "ratting," Daddy.
And our first lady,
Jacqueline Kennedy, does it.
I don't believe that.
What do you mean
you don't believe that?
- I don't.
- How else would it look that way?
I believe that it is naturally stiff.
She doesn't understand anything.
- Dancing on that show is my dream.
- I know.
Just because
she wouldn't know a dream
if it bit her on the nose!
Well, I have information
for you, missy.
I once had a dream that I owned
a coin-operated laundromat,
and I came down from that cloud
real quickly, I'll tell you that.
No!
- Oh, Wilbur.
- Fine! I'm going to my room!
She thinks I'm being mean,
but I'm not.
Those TV people,
they don't pick people like Tracy
or... girls like us.
They're gonna hurt her, Wilbur.
I'll talk to her.
Okay. Talk to her.
I'll talk to her. Don't you worry.
Okay.
What?
Tracy, this TV thing.
You really want it?
With all my heart.
Then you go for it!
This is America, babe.
You gotta think big to be big.
Big ain't the problem
in this family, Wilbur.
You follow your dream.
Mine came true,
and now, I have
the most precious thing in the world.
The Taj Mahal of joke shops.
Back step, cha-cha-cha.
Side step, front step.
Back and turn.
Front step, cha-cha-cha.
Tammy, sharper.
Side step, front step.
Back, again. Front step.
Oh, my god, Penny.
There's Link. Link!
Penny, pinch me!
You told me to.
I can't believe
I'm really here auditioning.
- Side step, front step.
- I can't believe I'm really here
watching you audition.
Front step, cha-cha-cha.
Back step, cha-cha-cha.
Side step, front step, back and...
Oh, Amber, look at this motley crew.
This town sure has gone downhill
since I was crowned
Miss Baltimore Crabs.
Oh, my god, how times have changed
These girls must be blind
Or completely deranged
But time seemed to halt
When I was Miss Baltimore Crabs
Amber, that move is far too dirty.
Mother, wake up
from that dream of yours.
This isn't 1930.
You can laugh but life's a test
Don't do this, don't do that
Remember, Mother knows best
For the crown's in the vault
From when I won Miss Baltimore Crabs
These steps are perfect ammunition
Let me show you how your mommy dear
Took out the competition
Girls, go get them.
Boys, let's rumba.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
Those poor runner-ups
Might still hold some grudges
They padded their cups
But I screwed the judges
Those broads thought they'd win
If a plate
They would spin in their dance
Not a chance
Boys, put me down
Good morning, ladies.
Let's see what you got.
Twist, twist, twist, twist
Mashed potato, mambo
Ready, begin
On my show you'll never find
A thrusting hip or bump and grind
What's that
A dance for fleas and ticks?
Oh, you should have seen
My bag of tricks
Oh, I hit the stage batons ablaze
While belting Aida
And preparing soufflés
But that triple somersault
Is how I clinched
Miss Baltimore Crabs
Proceed.
Are you scared we're on live?
No, I'm sure I can cope
Well, this show isn't broadcast in...
- Cinemascope
I never drank one chocolate malt
No desserts for Miss Baltimore Crabs
This one will never get a date
In those hand-me-down clothes
Ha! Kid, she'll never get a date
Till Daddy buys her a new nose
I would say, "Oy gevalt"
If I wasn't Miss Baltimore Crabs
Do you dance like you dress?
Amber, there's no need to be cruel
Would you swim in an integrated pool?
I sure would.
I'm all for integration.
It's the new frontier!
Not in Baltimore, it isn't.
And may I be frank?
First impressions can be tough
And when I saw you, I knew it
If your size weren't enough
Your last answer just blew it
And so, my dear, so short and stout
You'll never be in
- So we're kicking you out
With your form and your face
Aw, well, it isn't your fault
You're just down with a case
Of Miss Baltimore Crabs
You may go.
Um, thank you?
I think they secretly liked you.
Cutting my class, Tracy Turnblad?
I trust it was something
really important.
It should've been.
There's a party grooving
Let's get down
- What you looking at?
- Nothing. Not you.
Can I help you?
That move's swift.
You got that right.
The man can dine me
on a diet of detention,
so long as he don't starve me
of my tunes, baby.
- Does that dance have a name?
- Oh, this?
Call it
the "Peyton Place After Midnight."
I use it to attract, uh,
the opposite sex.
Wow.
That is so groovy.
You're really good.
Why, thank you.
So, would it be kinda like this?
You can't do that dance.
Hello, now.
Not bad for a white chick.
Hey, I know
where I've seen you before.
- Where?
- On Corny's show on Negro Day.
Negro Day's the best.
I wish every day were Negro Day.
At our house, it is.
Hey.
Show me another one?
You wanna see another one.
Well, here's a little
something signified to say,
"Hello, my name is Seaweed...
J,
Stubbs."
What's yours, baby?
I'm Tracy Turnblad!
You're gonna get it, white girl!
Well, Tracy,
you got it going on, girl.
You one of us.
You're joining this program
already in progress!
Well, let's go.
No, I get who Caesar is.
But what's the "Ideas of March"?
I mean, how can a month have an idea?
Hold on.
Come on.
How you liking detention now?
I'm a bad, bad girl
who needs to be punished.
Hey.
You know,
Corny's hosting the hop tomorrow.
If he saw you dancing like that,
he'd put you on the show.
See you.
Sorry, little darling.
Hope I didn't dent your 'do.
- Hey!
- See you all later.
Hey, Trace. I was looking for you.
What?
I can hear the bells
What? What are you talking about?
Well, don't you hear them chime?
"Chime" is not exactly
how I'd put it.
Can't you feel my heartbeat
Keeping perfect time?
And all because he touched me
He looked at me and stared
Yes, he bumped me
My heart was unprepared
When he tapped me
And knocked me off my feet
One little touch
Now my life's complete
- 'Cause when he nudged me
- Oh!
Love put me in a fix
Yes, it hit me
Just like a ton of bricks
Yes, my heart burst
Now I know what life's about
One little touch
And love's knocked me out
And I can hear the bells
My head is spinning
I can hear the bells
Something's beginning
Everybody says
That a girl who looks like me
Can't win his love
Well, just wait and see
'Cause I can hear the bells
Just hear them chiming
I can hear the bells
My temperature's climbing
I can't contain my joy
'Cause I finally found the boy
I've been missing
Listen, I can hear the bells
Round one
He'll ask me on a date, and then
Round two
I'll primp but won't be late because
Round three
Is when we kiss inside his car
Won't go all the way
but I'll go pretty far
Round four
He'll ask me for my hand and then
Round five
We'll book the wedding band so by
Round six
Amber, much to your surprise
This heavyweight champion
Takes the prize
And I can hear the bells
My ears are ringing
I can hear the bells
The bridesmaids are singing
Everybody says
That a guy who's such a gem
Won't look my way
Well, the laugh's on them
'Cause I can hear the bells
My father will smile
I can hear the bells
As he walks me down the aisle
My mother starts to cry
But I can't see 'cause Link and I
Are French kissing
Listen, I can hear the bells
Yeah.
I can hear the bells
My head is reeling
I can't stop the pealing
Everybody warns
That he won't like what he'll see
But I know that he'll look
Inside of me
Yeah, I can hear the bells
Today's just the start 'cause
I can hear the bells
Until death do us part and
Even when we die
We'll look down from up above
Remembering the night
That we two fell in love
We both will shed a tear
And he'll whisper
As we're reminiscing
- Listen, I can hear the bells
- She can hear the bells
- I can hear the bells
- Bum, bum, bum
Hey, little girl
With the cash to burn
Well, I'm selling something
You won't return
Hey, little girl
Take me off the shelf
'Cause it's hard having fun
Playing with yourself
Once you bounce
Through the whole selection
Shake those hips in my direction
Prettier package you never did see
Take me home and then unwrap me
Shop around but, little darling
I've got to be
The ladies' choice
Ladies' choice
Go on. Get out there and show them.
It's packed pretty tight.
Okay, I'll go in front of you
and I'll push.
Test drive this American male
Wait.
It's gonna take cash to fill my tank
So let's crack open your piggy bank
Hey, Seaweed!
Wanna do Peyton Place for Corny?
Are you crazy?
You gotta dance with your crowd,
- I gotta dance with mine.
- Why?
It's just the way it is, Tracy.
But it's your dance.
Well, how 'bout you go
borrow it for a second.
- Really?
- Go get it, girl.
I'm the ladies' choice
Ladies' choice
What is she doing?
All right! Yeah!
Hey, little girl on a spending spree
I don't come cheap
But the kisses come free
On closer inspection
I'm sure that you'll agree
Oh, hey, little girl,
Listen to my plea
I come with a lifetime guarantee
One day maybe we'll find
That baby makes three
- It's the ladies' choice
- Link!
I'm the ladies' choice
The ladies' choice
Choice, choice
I'm the ladies' choice
Mr And Mrs Turnblad!
Hey, look out!
Mrs Turnblad!
Mr Turnblad, come quick!
- Me?
- Come on!
Mrs Turnblad! Come quick!
You gotta see this!
Oh, I read all about it.
- It's a big fake Hollywood set.
- No, Mrs...
You think I'm gonna think
that he's really up there?
It's not John Glenn, Mrs Turnblad!
- Well, why are we watching this?
- Just watch.
- Lou Ann!
- Joey!
- Mikey! Vicki!
- Becky! Bix!
- Jesse!
- Darla!
- Paulie!
- Noreen!
- Doreen!
- Link!
And I'm Tracy!
- Oh! Oh, my!
- She...
Oh, yeah!
And the bass and drums
Are pounding in your head
Go, Tracy!
- Go, go, Tracy!
Who cares about sleep
When you can snooze in school
You'll never get to college
But you sure look cool
Don't need a cap and a gown
When you're the nicest kids in town
Kids in town
- Whoo!
Yeah! That was the dance of the week.
I don't know what happened,
Mr Spritzer.
Corny had some sort of aneurysm
or something, and...
picked her.
...brand-new Council Member,
Miss Tracy Turnblad.
So, Trace,
come on, cosy up to old Corny
and tell us about yourself.
Well, I watch The Corny Collins Show,
and I do absolutely nothing else!
Oh, Wilbur, to think that
I almost stopped her,
from reaching for the stars.
And now,
here she is on local daytime TV.
She's gonna be a regular!
Imagine, my little girl,
regular at last.
I also hope
to be the first woman president
or a Rockette!
And if you were president, Tracy,
what would your first
official act be?
I'd make every day Negro Day.
I read you
like tomorrow's headlines, Tracy.
What do you think, kids?
You think we might have
a hot new candidate
for Miss Teenage Hairspray?
That's only the dream of my life.
But Miss Hairspray is mine.
Uh, we're on the air.
And your dream
will be coming to you, sweetheart,
Saturday, June 2nd,
right here on WYZT.
You have to vote for a person, Corny,
not one of the Himalayas.
Hi, Penny.
Always the charmer, Amber.
I want that chubby communist girl
off the show!
Well, let me be the first
to toss the harpoon.
She's a corrupting influence!
I agree. We don't want our dancers
thrusting like savages!
Hey, speak for yourself.
Don't get flip with me.
I'm not.
Look, now I got some new ideas
for the show.
First, we get rid of Negro Day.
Finally, some sense outta you.
And we mix those kids in
with the rest of the Council.
Mix those kids?
That's right, I said it.
This is not a black-and-tan cocktail!
Well, why couldn't it be?
Velma, isn't this where
it's all heading anyway?
Now, you can fight it
or you can rock out to it.
Maybe it is time
for some fresh ideas,
like, like a nice, fresh new host!
Gee, Velma,
how do you fire Corny Collins,
from The Corny Collins Show?
They do it all the time on Lassie!
Velma, you've let this go too far!
- Me?
- Fix it!
- What?
Hey, look out for that moving van
Driving down our streets
You better lock up your man
Before he meets the new girl in town
Who just came on the scene,
TracyFace whoopee cushion.
Good choice.
We got your Tracy souvenirs for days.
Here, your signed photos.
Tracy wigs.
Whoa, whoa, whoa
We don't know what to do
'Bout the new girl in town
The new girl in town
Seems to dance on air
She's got the coolest hair
You better tell the homecoming queen
To hold onto her crown
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa
Or she's gonna lose it to
The new girl in town
That big little girl
is sending my sales through the roof.
More people are breathing aerosol
than oxygen!
Do you think you could show us
some of those new dance moves?
- Yeah, sure.
- Ooh, pretty flowers.
Tracy, wait up!
She's hip
So cool
I'm gonna get her after school
And yet we'd like to be like her
'Cause she's the kitten
That the cats prefer
The new girl in town
Has my guy on a string
- The new girl in town
- Hey, look, she's wearing his ring
I can't stop crying
And so in my own tears
I'm gonna drown
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
'Cause he wants to rendezvous
With the new girl
We're kinda sad and blue
Yes, it's true, girl
We'd like to say
To the new girl in town
The new girl in town
Hi, I'm here to see Tracy Turnblad.
Where's her write-up?
She doesn't need a detention slip.
She's with me.
Penny, this is Seaweed.
Seaweed, this is Penny.
Whoa, whoa, whoa
To the new girl in town
The new girl in town
Whoa, whoa, whoa
From out of the blue, girl
This town's in a stew, girl
What a hullabaloo, girl
She ain't just passing through, girl
She's sticking like glue, girl
To the man I thought I knew, girl
Whoa, whoa, whoa
Hey, look out for that moving van
Look out, look out, look out
She was the new girl in
Town
And that's the way you do it.
And I'm your fabled
Miss Motormouth Maybelle,
your DJ du jour,
pitching rhythm your way.
So, hey, better stay
and shimmy and sway.
We'll be right back
with more Negro Day.
"Brought to you by...
Nap-a-Way, for stubborn hair.
Every kink will be gone in a blink."
We're off.
Girls, that was great.
How dare you pick the same song?
They wrote it.
You watch yourself.
You are one inch
from being cancelled.
You know what your demographic is?
Cleaning ladies and lawn jockeys.
A foot in the door, that's all it is.
One toe at a time.
Hello?
Is this the Turnblad residence?
- Yes.
- Mr Pinky speaking.
Mr Pinky from... from the dress shop?
Uh-huh.
I'd like Tracy for our spokesgirl.
You want Tracy to do what?
- Be our spokesgirl.
- Be a spokesgirl?
I think she'd be perfect.
I'd like to meet her
and discuss the details.
As soon as possible.
Okay, um...
Well, we'll have
to send someone down to meet you.
- Tonight, if you can.
- So, um...
- Oh, okay. Bye-bye, Mr Pinky.
- Bye-bye.
The Mr Pinky?
From Mr Pinky's hefty hideaway!
A spokesgirl?
Oh, tell me I get a free caftan.
Tell me!
Oh, Tracy!
I think perks like caftans
have to be negotiated.
Maybe we should get you an agent.
Okay. You be my agent!
What? Tracy Turnblad!
Has fame gone to your head
and made you wacky?
Well, why not?
Who's going to look out for me
better than my mom?
Me, an agent?
You see me hobnobbing
and drinking rum and cokes
with all those hoi pollois?
And out-negotiating them.
Oh, you're crazy!
Oh, Tracy,
I haven't left this house in years.
Then isn't it time you did?
Oh, no, Tracy.
We'll have your father meet with him.
I don't wanna be seen like this.
Why not?
I'll do it after my next diet.
That's when I'll do it.
You see,
the neighbours haven't seen me
since I was a size 10.
Don't make me do it, Tracy.
Ma, it's changing out there.
You'll like it.
People who are different...
Their time is coming.
Hey, Mama, hey, Mama, look around
Everybody's grooving
To a brand-new sound
Hey, Mama, hey, Mama follow me
I know something's in you
That you wanna set free
So let go, go, go of the past now
Say hello to the love in your heart
Yes, I know
That the world's spinning fast now
You gotta get yourself
A brand-new start
Hey, Mama, welcome to the '60s
Oh, oh, oh
Oh, Mama, welcome to the '60s
Go, Mama, go, go, go
Welcome to the '60s
Oh, oh, oh
Hey, Mama
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey, Mama, hey, Mama, have some fun
I haven't left this house since 1951
Hey, Mama, hey, Mama, take a chance
Oh, Tracy, it's been years
Since someone asked me to dance
So let go, go, go of the past now
Say hello to the light in your eyes
Yes, I know
That the world's spinning fast now
But you gotta run the race
To win the prize
Hey, Mama, welcome to the '60s
Oh, oh, oh
Oh, Mama, welcome to the '60s
Go, Mama, go, go, go
Welcome to the '60s
Ma, you did it!
Oh, Tracy, I'm a little lightheaded.
There's so much air out here!
Can't we go someplace that's stuffy?
No, Ma, you're on your way.
Hey, Mama, welcome to the '60s
Oh, oh, oh
Oh, Mama, welcome to the '60s
Go, Mama, go, go, go
They're so glamorous.
Wow.
- It kicked!
- Swell.
Let's toast to that. To your boy!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Welcome to the rhythm
Of a brand-new day
Take your old-fashioned fears
And just throw them away
You should add some colour
And a fresh new 'do
'Cause it's time for a star
Who looks just like you
I thought we marked these down.
What?
Thank you, Nadine.
There's my shining star!
Fantastic to meet you!
I'm Mr Pinky.
It's so nice to meet you.
Tracy, is this your older sister?
Oh, my.
Perhaps she'd like
some complimentary couture.
Couture?
Now, if you'll just sign here.
Flattery will not distract
Miss Turnblad's agent
from reading the fine print.
Her agent?
Tracy, eat your donuts.
Let's talk.
All right, let's see here.
All right. Now...
No!
I want a non-exclusive contract.
Extensions by mutual option.
And I want you to absorb
my 15 percent commission.
Not a dime over ten!
Throw in a bustier?
Fifty-four double D?
Triple E.
I hit the mother lode!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Care for a Baby Ruth?
I got one right here.
Oh, oh, oh
Oh, Mama, welcome to the '60s
Go, Mama, go, go, go
Don't-cha let nobody try
To steal your fun
'Cause a little touch of lipstick
Never hurt no one
The future's got a million roads
For you to choose
But you'll walk a little taller
In some high-heeled shoes
And once you find the style
That makes you feel like you
Something fresh, something new
Step on out, hear us shout
Mama, that's your cue
Ba da ba da ba da
Step on out, hear us shout
Mama, that's your cue
Hey, Tracy, hey, baby, look at me
I'm the cutest chickie
That you ever did see
Hey, Tracy, hey, baby, look at us
Where is there a team
That's half as fabulous
I let go, go, go of the past now
Said hello to this red-carpet ride
Yes, I know
That the world's spinning fast now
Tell Lollobrigida to step aside
Your Mama's welcoming the '60s
Oh, oh, oh
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-baby
Go, Mama, go, go, go
Welcome to the '60s
Open the door to the girl
Who has more
She's a star, Tracy, go, go, go
Hey, Mama, welcome to the '60s
- Your mama's hip, your mama's in
- Hey, Mama
Your mama's looking at herself
And wondering, "Where you been?"
Where you been?
- Your mama's lit
- Lit
- She's all aglow
- Go, Mama
Your mama once was holding back
But Mama's gotta let go, go, go
Welcome to the "six," to the "O"
To the apostrophe "S"
Hey-yay, baby, yeah
Oh, oh, oh
Oh, yeah
Go, Mama, go, go, go
Oh, oh, oh
Wait until Dad sees you.
Sees me?
He never notices what I wear.
In 20 years,
he's never even said to me,
"Nice muumuu" or nothing.
Now he will.
Well, maybe if he leaves that shop
for five minutes.
I swear,
I don't know what goes on down there.
Well.
Mrs Turnblad.
I'd know
whose mother you were anywhere.
Really?
Hello, Amber.
Hello, Tracy.
Ma, this is Amber and Mrs Von Tussle.
Mrs Von Tussle
is the station's manager.
Oh, the station manager.
Oh, it was so nice of you
let her on that show.
Well, Tracy certainly has...
redefined our standards.
That's for sure.
Let me guess...
brand-new dress?
Oh, yes.
Well, you'll stop traffic.
It was nice meeting you. Tracy.
Bye, Tracy.
Ma, don't listen to a word she says!
I'm taking this back.
- Don't you dare.
- I am.
Don't you dare!
Don't you know why she hates us?
She's afraid I'll beat Amber
for Miss Teenage Hairspray.
Really?
They can't put Tracy in special ed.
I won't have it.
I mean,
even if I have to tutor her myself,
they cannot hold my friend back.
You're a saint.
Oh, and it's totally not true
about her
and the entire football team.
I mean, please.
Anybody can get grass stains
all over their back.
Amber, stop it.
I'm sick of you doing that.
Just because she's a good dancer.
I'm sorry,
you think that she can dance?
Well, maybe you'd rather have her
as your partner.
You could get sponsored by Goodyear.
Excuse me.
What is going on back there?
Tracy, that's horrible.
Mr Flak does not have breasts.
What? No!
I would... I would never.
Oh, and Mr Larkin,
perhaps you'd like to share
with the rest of the class
Patrick Henry's immortal last words.
"Kiss my ass"?
You didn't have to do that, Link.
Hey, no prob.
Besides, it looks like
a cool scene down here.
Right.
Hey, cool.
Hey, Tracy!
Not quite, huh?
Aw, damn. Just when I was getting it.
Listen, man,
you ain't gotta stop now.
My mom's having
a platter party tonight.
- Y'all wanna come check it out?
- Now?
Would you mind if I, too,
checked it out?
I've never been
to North Avenue before.
Uh, well, would it be safe?
You know, for us?
Calm down, cracker boy!
It's cool.
Wow, being invited places
by coloured people!
It feels so hip!
I'm glad y'all feel that way
'cause, uh, not many people do.
- Y'all know what I'm saying?
- Yeah, that's right.
Hey!
I can't see why people look at me
And only see the colour of my face
Ah, yeah
Then there's those that try to help
God knows
But always have to put me in my place
But I won't ask you
To be colour-blind
'Cause if you pick the fruit
Then, girl, you're sure to find
The blacker the berry
The sweeter the juice
I could say it ain't so
But, darling, what's the use?
The darker the chocolate,
the richer the taste
And that's where it's at
Now, baby, run and tell that
- Now run and tell that
- Aw, sugar
- Run and tell that
Hey, yeah!
I can't see why people disagree
Each time I tell them
What I know is true, oh, no
- And if you come
- And see the world I'm from
I bet your heart
Is gonna feel it, too, yeah
I could lie but, baby, let's be bold
Vanilla can be nice
But if the truth be told
Blacker the berry,
the sweeter the juice
I could say it ain't so
But, darling, what's the use?
The darker the chocolate,
the richer the taste
And that's where it's at
Oh, baby, baby, run and tell that
- Run and tell that
- Aw, sugar
Go run and tell that
- Run and tell that
- Go on and run and tell that
- Hey, run and tell
Go tell
Keep moving, people
Run and tell that
Link!
Link Larkin!
Hey, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey! Whoo!
Whoo!
Come here, girl.
This is my sister, Little Inez.
Oh, I know Tracy Turnblad.
Good for you, girl!
You got on the show.
- Well, you better be next.
- You got that right.
Oh, you know she is.
You better show them, girl.
Go, girl!
I'm tired of covering up all my pride
So give me five
On the black hand side
I got a new way of moving
And I got my own voice
So how can I help
But to shout and rejoice
Oh, the people 'round here
Can barely pay their rent
They try to make a dollar
Outta fifteen cent
But we got a spirit
Money just can't buy
It's deep as a river
And soars to the sky
- To the sky!
- Hey!
I can't see the reason it can't be
The kinda world
Where we all get our chance
- Oh, yeah
- The time is now
So we can show them how
Just turn the music up
And let's all dance, yeah, yeah
'Cause all things are equal
When it comes to love
Well, that ain't quite true
'Cause when push comes to shove
The blacker the berry
The sweeter the juice
They say it ain't so
But, darling, what's the use?
The darker the chocolate
The richer the taste
And that's where it's at
Now, baby, baby, baby
Run and tell that
- Run and tell that
- Oh, baby
Go run and tell that
Go home and run and tell that
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoo!
- Go, baby!
- Yeah!
It was horrible.
Mom, he just danced on that bus
with that great white whale
and those negroes.
No, honey.
Reeling him back in
is the easiest thing in the world.
Remember, I control his career.
Now, don't worry.
Mommy will take care of everything.
Are you all hungry for some good fun?
Yeah
Bring on that pecan pie
Pour some sugar on it
Sugar, don't be shy
Scoop me up a mess
Of that chocolate swirl
Don't be stingy, I'm a growing girl
I offer big love with no apology
How can I deny the world
The most of me?
I am not afraid
To throw my weight around
Pound by pound by pound
Because I'm big, blonde
And beautiful
Face the fact
It's simply irrefutable
No one wants a meal
That only offers the least
When, girl, we're serving up
The whole damn feast
Well, looks like y'all
took a step outta bounds.
Now who we got here?
Mom, I want you to meet
my new friends.
This here is Link. Tracy Turnblad.
This is just so Afro-tastic!
And this young lady right here...
is Penny Pingleton.
I'm very pleased
and scared to be here.
Oh, now, honey.
We got more reason to be scared
on your street.
Latoya, put that record down.
You gonna scratch it.
Can't you keep your little girl...
Shall we dance? Come on.
My name is Mike.
Mike?
Yes, Mike.
- Mike who?
- It's Mike!
Anyway...
I'm calling
because I have some information
about your daughter's whereabouts.
- What?
- Right now, as we speak,
your daughter has entered
a hotbed of moral...
turpentine.
Baby don't sleep
Baby don't eat
Baby just like another boink-boink
Link, aren't you gonna get
in awful trouble for this?
I'm not planning on telling my dad.
No, I mean in trouble
with someone else.
Maybe.
Maybe it's worth it.
I think knowing you's the start
of a pretty big adventure.
Tracy Edna Turnblad!
Oh, we get any more
white people in here.
This gonna be a suburb.
Do you know what I had to pay a cab
just to consider coming down here?
Oh, uh, Mom...
No call! You just disappear.
And all mashed up against a crooner?
Um, Edna Turnblad, this is Link.
Come on, we're going.
And, Penny, go home
before your mother shoots you.
Miss Edna, is it?
Hi, I mean,
you don't have to rush off, you know.
Well, I do. I left my iron on.
Oh, your iron.
Well, before you go,
you sure you wouldn't like to have
a little something to eat?
Is that braised?
Whoa, oh, oh
Slice me off a piece
Of that hogshead cheese
And take a look inside
My book of recipes
Now, don't you sniff around
For something fluffy and light
We need a man
Who brings a man-size appetite
We'll use a pinch of sugar
And a dash of spice
I'll let you lick the spoon
Because it tastes so nice
We keep it in the oven
Till it's good and hot
Keep on stirring
Till it hits the spot
Because I'm big, blonde
And beautiful
There is nothing 'bout us
That's unsuitable
Why sit in the bleachers
Timid and afraid
When, Edna,
You look like the whole parade?
They say that white
Has might and thin is in
Well, that's just bull
'Cause, ladies, big is back
And as for black, it's beautiful
All shapes and sizes follow me
Who wants a twig
When you can climb a whole tree
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Groovy, baby. Groovy!
Hello?
Oh, my god!
Oh, you got me.
Welcome... to the Hardy-Har Hut.
If we can't put a smile on your face,
your skin's too tight.
- Oh!
- Bop, bop.
- Oh.
- I got something for you. Yeah.
It's just in.
You're gonna love it.
Cigarette?
Tempting but, uh...
No, thanks!
Well, eh, okay.
What can I do you for?
Something for the mister?
Sadly, there is no mister
at the moment.
Beautiful woman like yourself?
My husband...
accidentally suffocated.
- You need a fella.
- I do.
I do need a fella.
And the way to a man's heart
is through his funny bone.
Now here's an icebreaker for you.
Oh, Miss Maybelle,
you do throw a lovely party.
But what are you celebrating?
Well, it's kind of an ending.
But it deserved
to go out with a bang.
What ended?
- Negro Day.
- What?
All right. Time y'all knew.
Velma Von Tussle just told me
we have had our last show.
- No.
- What?
Yeah, it seems our little show
was a nice little placeholder,
but it was time to get some ratings.
I didn't wanna tell y'all up front.
I just wanted
to have a little fun tonight.
But I practiced so hard.
Now I'll never get a chance
to be on the show.
Oh, you will be seen, baby.
I promise.
You can't have your own show?
Fine, you'll come dance with us.
Honey, you been dozing off
during history?
Yes, always.
Trace, black and whites
ain't never danced on TV together.
Well, if we can't dance...
maybe we should just march.
Ooh, that'd get some big ol' ratings.
Better time slot, too.
Like on the 11:00 news.
What y'all say?
Should we give this fine woman
all the ratings she deserves?
- Yeah!
Hey, hey!
Well, it is a school night...
and I think
we ought to call it a night.
Tell you what.
We meet up at the church
Friday, 4:00,
and we will march on WYZT.
- Yeah!
Yeah!
Tracy, you can't protest, hon.
I mean, these are lovely people,
but if you protest,
you'll be on lists.
You'll be on files.
J. Edgar Hoover'll
be still wiretapping
your cold, dead body in the grave.
Oh, Mother.
Link, we're going with them, right?
Walk with me.
You want your Belgian chocolate
animal droppings.
Dot, dot. This store's for you.
- Oh! What a treasure trove.
- Huh?
Come here, baby.
Don't be sad.
We gonna make it happen, okay?
- Can I go?
- Now, come on, now.
I can't be worried about you
out there.
Trace...
I been smiling and dancing
on this show for 3 years.
Mrs Von Tussle just promised
I could sing
at the Miss Hairspray pageant.
She's... she invited agents.
That's my shot, Trace.
I can't jeopardize that.
But it's what's right.
I'm sorry, Trace.
I just think this adventure's...
a little...
too big for me.
Oh, God. No, no, no.
That's not what I...
I get it, Link. It's your shot.
No, Trace, that's not what I...
It's fine.
Oh, hon.
I should go.
Give him time.
He'll figure out
he's crazy 'bout you.
You have to say that.
You're my mother.
Well, I know
a little something about men.
And, my personal favourite,
X-ray specs.
You can see through anything.
Skin, clothes, you name it.
Now, take your father.
And he's always downstairs
in that shop working late.
Do I take it personal? No.
Men always put their career first.
- Remember that.
- Okay.
I'm really tired.
I'm gonna go to bed.
All right, hon. Night.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
I think I'm gonna go to bed, too.
Oh, I'm so tired.
You don't need those...
to see what's under these clothes.
There's a product that really works
'cause these are phony
as a three-dollar bill.
Incredible!
I could do a fan dance
with a lettuce leaf
and you would remain
completely obtuse!
Obtuse.
Yes, obtuse!
I flunked geometry.
Yeah, well...
And biology too, no doubt!
Yeah.
Wait! How about this?
Okay.
Those lips, those eyes
That food
Well, there ain't nothing
Like a spread
To get you in the mood
Wilbur, can't you feel
The burning flame of hot desire
You're gonna need
More than some seltzer
To put out this fire
I'm wailing, "Look out, old Balti...
"...More!" I'm selling something
You can't purchase
At a ten-cent store
Oh, Wilbur, I feel like a princess
Come on and take me to the ball
I bet you're tired of heavy lifting
Get your hands on something small
Because I'm a-big...
...blonde...
- ...and beautiful
It's time to face the facts
It's irrefutable
Why waste one more minute
Now I feel brand spanking new
Hey, Wilbur, take a look
It's all for
You
You?
- Edna.
- Your wife!
You said she was out! Wait a minute!
Hi, hon.
Ma, you don't really believe
that he would do that.
You are never setting foot
on that show again.
You hear me?
I heard you the first 400 times, Ma.
Hey.
Daddy!
It wasn't me.
I had to improvise
a bed out of something.
Whoopee cushions?
That will play heck with my sciatica.
That one was me.
Daddy, are you okay?
Tracy, you know...
These peepers have never looked
at another woman.
This heart only beats for size 60.
Daddy, you know what Velma wanted.
She wanted me off the show.
And I knew that,
but how could she go that far?
Come here. Come here, little girl.
Little girl.
And then,
to just cancel Negro Day like that.
Just to make sure
that nobody who's different,
or who's black, or Chinese,
or maybe who needs to lose
a few pounds.
What are you talking? Stop it.
What are you talking?
I think I've been in a bubble
or something.
Thinking that fairness
was just going to happen.
It's not.
I think people like me
are gonna have to get up
off their father's laps
and go out there and fight for it.
Your mother and I,
we don't see too far past
our front door.
But you...
see all the way to Schenectady.
So, if there's something
you need to stand up for,
don't you listen to old dogs like us.
We need to learn some new tricks...
from you.
You don't need new tricks, Dad.
You need Mom.
She changed the locks.
Good night, Daddy.
Aw, love.
Come on, baby.
Honey, took me five years
to figure out you were flirting.
How could I ever?
Well, she is very glamorous.
Edna.
She just makes me feel old.
Nonsense.
Doll!
You're spry as a Slinky.
I'm not talking to you.
Styles keep a-changing
The world's rearranging
But, Edna, you're timeless to me
Hemlines are shorter
A beer costs a quarter
But time cannot take what comes free
You're like a stinky old cheese, babe
Just getting riper with age
- You're like a fatal disease, babe
- What?
But there's no cure
So let this fever rage
Some folks can't stand it
Say time is a bandit
But I take the opposite view
'Cause when I need a lift
Time brings a gift
Another day with you
A twist or a waltz
It's all the same schmaltz
With just a change in the scenery
You'll never be old hat
That's that
You're timeless to me
Fads keep a-fading
Castro's invading
But, Wilbur, you're timeless to me
Hairdos are higher
Mine feels like barbed wire
But you say I'm chic as can be
- You're like a rare vintage ripple
- Thank you.
A vintage they'll never forget
- So pour me a teeny-weeny triple
- Any time!
And we can toast the fact
We ain't dead yet
- What?
- I can't stop eating
- Your hairline's receding
- Hey!
And soon, you'll have nothing at all
Never.
So you'll wear a wig
While I roast a pig
Hey! Pass that Geritol
I love pig.
Glenn Miller had brass
That Chubby Checker's a gas
But they all pass eventually
You'll never be passé, hip-hooray
You're timeless to me
You're like a broken-down Chevy
All I need is a fresh coat of paint
And, Edna
You got me going hot and heavy
You're fat and old
- What?
- But, baby, boring you ain't
Some folks don't get it
But we never fret it
'Cause we know
That time is our friend
Yeah, it's plain to see
That you're stuck with me
Until the bitter end
And we got a kid
Who's blowing the lid
Off the Turnblad family tree
You'll always hit the spot
Big shot
You're timeless to me
You'll always be du jour, mon amour
You'll always be first string
Ring-a-ding-ding
- You're timeless to me
You're timeless to me
- You're timeless
- To me
Oh, Wilbur.
Tracy.
Wake up, hon.
Wake up. Everything's good again.
Wilbur?
Wilbur!
Seaweed, help pass those signs out.
Give her one.
Hey, Jackie, we're over here.
Aw, you looking good, Gertrude.
Come on, y'all. Here we go now.
Tracy!
You're gonna pay a heavy price.
I know.
You'll never dance on TV again.
If I can't dance
with Seaweed and Little Inez,
then I don't wanna dance
on TV at all.
I just want tomorrow to be better.
There's a light
In the darkness
Though the night is black as my skin
There's a light burning bright
Showing me the way
But I know where I've been
There's a cry
In the distance
It's a voice that comes
From deep within
Hey, yeah
There's a cry asking why
I pray the answer's up ahead
'Cause I know where I've been
There's a road we been traveling
Lost so many on the way
But the riches will be plenty
Worth the price
The price we had to pay
There's a dream
In the future
There's a struggle
That we have yet to win
And there's pride in my heart
'Cause I know where I'm going
Yes, I do
And I know where I've been
Yeah
- There's a road
- We must travel
- There's a promise
- We must make
- That we must make
- But the riches
- Oh, but the riches
- Will be plenty
- The riches will be plenty, yeah
- Worth the risk
- And the chances that we take
- And the chances we take
There's a dream
Yeah, yeah, yeah, in the future
- There's a struggle
- Struggle
- That we have yet to win
- We have yet to win
- Use that pride
- Pride
- In our hearts
- To lift us up
- Lift us up
Until tomorrow
'Cause just to sit still
Would be a sin
I know it, I know it
I know where I'm going
Lord knows I know
- Where I've been
- Oh, when we win
Yeah, I'll give thanks to my God
'Cause I know where I've been, yeah
Oh, yeah, amen!
- Amen, amen!
- That's right.
Tracy, hon,
you don't know what you're doing.
Yes, I do, Ma.
Hello, Miss Maybelle.
Well, good evening, Miss Edna.
Nice of you to join us.
She's got a lovely turnout.
Now, I really think
they don't need you anymore.
You come home with me.
No, we are not sending a camera crew.
They're protesting
our own station, dimwit.
Why is Channel Five there?
Well, of course they're all Negroes.
And why would...
I know who would.
I know exactly who would.
- Two, four, six, eight!
- TV's got to integrate!
Two, four, six, eight!
TV's got to integrate!
- Two, four, six, eight!
- Oh, my god, no!
- TV's got to integrate!
- No!
- Ma, come on.
The sound's not working.
You knew there'd be police.
But I didn't know there'd be cameras.
So?
Oh, I cannot be seen on television
at this present weight.
Two, four, six, eight!
TV's got to integrate!
Excuse me.
Is there some reason
we can't pass by peacefully?
I strongly suggest you
and your little friends
head back to where you come from.
Hey, you don't have to be so rude.
Tracy!
It's all right, Tracy.
I can handle this.
- Excuse me. She was talking to you.
- Tracy!
Tracy, no.
You just assaulted
a police officer, miss.
- No!
- I what?
Assaulted?
Enough! Hey!
All right, boys.
Let's take the whole lot in.
- No!
- Run, Tracy! Run!
Two, four, six, eight!
TV's got to integrate!
And our cameras
also caught Tracy Turnblad,
the teenage TV personality
and rabble-rouser.
Miss Turnblad brutally attacked
a sergeant
- with a blunt instrument...
- You see?
You see?
If I let you leave the house
right now,
you'd be in prison
fighting whores for cigarettes.
That Tracy Turnblad always was
a bad influence.
Well, you are never, ever gonna see
that beehived harlot again.
Okay, Mother. Excuse me.
Penny?
Pray for her.
She's gonna need it.
- Wait! Wait!
- Tracy! Tracy!
She's not here, I told you.
Hon, she knows...
If the cops are looking for her,
this is the first place they'll come.
What this
must have put you through, Wilbur.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm not.
- You're not?
I'm proud of you.
You are?
Baby, somebody had to do something.
'Course, we may be eating beans
for the next ten years.
Bail for 20's kind of pricey.
You bailed all those people out?
You upset with me?
I'm sorry.
Hon, it just seemed
like the right thing.
Oh, Wilbur, it was the right thing.
Knights in armour
don't come any shinier than you.
But where's our little girl?
Are you okay, Trace?
Oh, you have no idea.
- Come on.
- Thank you so much.
You're such a great friend.
Thanks.
Penny, the cops are looking
for me everywhere.
You could go to jail for helping me.
Tracy, I'm already in jail. Come on.
- Oh, no.
- What?
Your hair deflated.
Oh, let it.
It was just a symbol
of my conformity to the man.
You are so tough.
So, what do you think?
Maybe you could live down here.
I don't even know why we
have this room down here,
but there's food,
water, first aid kit,
gas mask, Russian-language books.
It's very well-insulated.
It won't be where you're going.
The police are on their way.
Mom, please don't send my best friend
to the big house.
Penny, hush.
You haven't heard the last
of me, Mrs Pingleton.
Things need to change
and I won't stop trying
to change them.
I don't care how long it takes.
Good, you'll be waiting 20 to life.
Get the jump rope, Penny.
- Mom, not the jump rope!
- Don't you touch my canned tuna.
You wait till your father
gets out of prison.
You'll see
more than a jump rope, missy!
A massive manhunt is underway
for Miss Turnblad...
who bludgeoned sergeant
and decorated Korean war veteran,
Mike Morris, with a crowbar,
- shattering his jaw...
- That is a lie!
They're talking
about our baby, Wilbur.
They're telling lies.
Sergeant Morris
is in critical condition.
This is such a Midol moment.
Wilbur, that... Oh!
Maybe that's her. Oh, that's her.
Is that you, Tracy?
Oh, Link. I thought you'd be Tracy.
Uh, no. I was just at home, uh,
practicing my new twist on the twist
and I overheard it on the news.
I can't believe Tracy
savagely bludgeoned an Eagle Scout.
- That's just not like her.
- Well, it's not true. I was there.
He didn't even bleed.
I should have been there...
beside her.
I can't sleep, I can't eat.
You can't eat?
Well, come on in and worry with us.
I'll make you some pork.
Penny Lou Pingleton,
you are absolutely, positively,
permanently punished.
You will live on a diet
of saltines and Tang,
and you will never leave
this room again.
Devil child! Devil child!
Seaweed. Don't let her hear you.
Penny, what happened to you?
She's punishing me
for harbouring a fugitive
without her permission.
What are you doing?
I'm here to rescue
the fair maiden, baby.
Oh, Seaweed, you do care.
I was afraid the colours of our skin
would keep us apart.
No.
These knots might.
Was your mom in the navy?
Once I was a selfish fool
Who never understood
Never looked inside myself
Though on the outside, I looked good
Then we met and you made me
The man I am today
Tracy, I'm in love with you
No matter what you weigh
- 'Cause without love
- Without love
Life is like the seasons
with no summer
- Without love
Life is rock 'n' roll
Without a drummer
Tracy, I'll be yours forever
'Cause I never wanna be
- Without love
Tracy, never set me free
- No, I ain't lying
- I ain't lying
- Never set me free
Tracy, no, no, no
Living in the ghetto
Black is everywhere you go
Who'd have thought I'd love a girl
Whose skin was white as winter snow?
In my ivory tower
Life was just a hostess snack
But now I've tasted chocolate
And I'm never going back
'Cause without love
Life is like a beat
That you can't follow
Without love
Life is Doris Day at the Apollo
Darling, I'll be yours forever
'Cause I never wanna be
Without love
So, darling, never set me free, no
- I'm yours forever
- Never set me free
No, no, no
If I'm left without my baby doll
I don't know what I'll do
Link, I've got to break out
So that I can get my hands on you
Girl, if I can't touch you
Then I'm gonna lose control
Seaweed, you're my black white knight
I've found my blue-eyed soul
Sweet freedom is our goal
Trace, I wanna kiss you!
Let me out at the next toll!
Without love
Life is like a prom
That won't invite us
Without love
It's like getting my big break
And laryngitis
Without love
Life's a 45 when you can't buy it
Life is like my mother on a diet
Like a week that's only Mondays
Only ice cream, never sundaes
Like a circle with no centre
Like a door marked "Do Not Enter"
Darling, I'll be yours forever
'Cause I never wanna be
Without love
- Yes, now you've captured me
- Now you've captured me
Without love
I surrender happily
Oh, Seaweed, never set me free
No, no, no
I ain't lying
Never set me free
No, no, no
No, I don't wanna live without
Love, love, love
Pretty Penny little
Darling, you had best believe me
Never leave me without love
Link, your pork is ready.
- Uh, Mama, I...
- You trying to hide her here?
Why you ain't think of that before?
Everything she done for us.
Where your manners at, boy?
Well, I don't know.
And what about this one?
Seaweed's got a girlfriend.
Inez, shut up.
- You.
- Oh.
So this is love.
Well, love is a gift.
Lotta people don't remember that.
So you two better brace yourselves
for a whole lotta ugly coming at you
from a never-ending parade of stupid.
So you met my mom?
Hello?
- Mom? Yes, I'm safe.
- Tracy, are you okay?
- Oh, my god.
- Mom, listen.
- Where are you? What?
- I need your help.
Tomorrow's the Miss Teenage
Hairspray pageant.
I need you to come down
to the station.
- Well, Tracy...
- Dress nice.
- What?
- Penny will meet you out front.
- Tracy...
- Now let me talk to Dad.
Turn your face this way.
The other way. Go.
Everybody, please take your seats.
The Miss Teenage Hairspray Pageant
is about to begin.
Oh, you've come
on a very exciting day.
It's our... first live show.
Oh! Bye-bye, Birdie.
My Amber is perfect for that.
She's the pretty little blonde.
And we're live
in five, four, three...
And now, broadcast live
in front of a live studio audience
for the first time from the certified
up-to-code WYZT studio,
it's the Corny Collins
Miss Hairspray Spectacular.
- He's Corny.
Brought to you
by Ultra Clutch hairspray.
What gives a girl power and punch
Is it charm, is it poise
No, it's hairspray
What gets a gal asked out to lunch
Is it brains, is it dough
No, it's hairspray
If you take a ride
With no can at your side...
"And preserve our family
through our father."
"Let us make our father drink wine,
and let us lie with him."
You can take off in a rocket
And in outer space
Each hair will be in place
Link, the agents are here. Look.
...When you get up and dance?
If you twist, I insist
You use hairspray
And tell your mother
Maybe they'll sign us together.
...She should smother
With Ultra Clutch faithfully
Well?
There's no sign of her.
We're on every door.
She's not inside.
Doesn't mean she won't try.
Velma, I seriously doubt
this girl's gonna risk incarceration
to win a pageant.
That's me!
I risked communicable diseases.
She'll certainly risk jail.
Better than hairspray
That's me
What makes a man reach out and
touch?
Ultra Clutch
So if you're a redhead
A blonde, or brunette
Just take my advice
And you might just get
The only thing better than hairspray
That's me
- Ah!
- He's Corny Collins
The only thing better than hairspray
- Hairspray
- Wow!
That's me
Hey, baby, you look like
you could use a stiff one.
And we are out.
Link, you sprayed it
right in my face!
What'd I tell you about that?
Stop! You guys.
Uh, powder.
And we're back. Five, four...
- Here?
- Three.
And now for the talent portion
of our competition,
our Councilettes
in their Miss Teenage Hairspray
official dance-off.
First off, we have the sunny pride
of Highlandtown, Darla.
Hello, Darla.
Miss Teenage Hairspray.
Your vote is for?
This little girl could power
all of greater downtown Baltimore
with her energy.
Lou Ann.
Who are you voting for? Lou Ann?
Very good, thank you.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the almost too happy Tammy.
And thank you, Tammy.
- Confirmed sighting.
- What?
You three. Outside, now.
- We can't go out...
- No, no. No buts. Out, out!
Whatever you say, Mrs Von Tussle.
Aw, she's too cute, isn't she?
Hold it right there, Tracy.
Looking for someone?
All right, ladies and gentlemen...
- A what?
- It was a diversion.
Oh, please, these people
are not capable of a diversion.
It's beyond their mental capacity.
I wouldn't be so sure, Velma.
Oh, my god.
What if she's already
in the building?
What if she's been here for hours
and you've locked yourselves out?
What?
Check the doors!
- Let's go!
It's locked!
It's all locked!
And now a fast girl
who loves to slow dance,
our own smooth-as-silk Shelley.
Keep going. Keep going. That's it.
- Come on.
- Put your backs into it, men.
Put your backs into it this time.
Come on, one more time.
One more time.
Come on, come on, come on.
Here's our little dynamic duo
from Conkling Street.
Double your fun
with Noreen and Doreen.
What is with you people?
I mean, how hard is it
to beat down a door?
That hairspray battering ram
was heavy.
Heavy?
How could they be heavy? They're...
hollow.
Move it.
Let's get them. Let's go.
And of course, our three-time
Miss Hairspray champion,
the ever-charming, Amber.
Oh, my god.
You carried her in!
Go!
- It's locked.
- Open it!
Let's give a final round of applause
to our Miss Teenage
Hairspray contestants.
Hey.
All right, all right.
We are so close to announcing
the new Miss Teenage Hairspray.
Look at that board.
What a nail-biter
this one is turning into.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the final tally.
It is my...
obligation...
to announce that Amber Von Tussle...
Is about to get out-danced.
Tracy Turnblad!
What?
You can't stop an avalanche
As it races down the hill
You can try to stop the seasons, girl
But you know you never will
And you can try to stop
My dancing feet
But I just cannot stand still
'Cause the world keeps spinning
Round and round
And my heart's keeping time
To the speed of sound
I was lost till I heard the drums
- Then I found my way
- No.
- 'Cause you can't stop the beat
- Link!
Ever since this old world began
A woman found out if she shook it
She could shake up a man
This throne is mine!
The best that I can today
- 'Cause you can't stop
- Let me down!
The motion of the ocean
Or the sun in the sky
You can wonder if you wanna
But I never ask why
And if you try to hold me down
I'm gonna spit in your eye and say
That you can't stop the beat
They love you, Link.
Yeah? Not for long.
Inez, come on!
Let's dance.
Little Miss Inez Stubbs,
ladies and gentlemen.
Look at my baby go.
- Inez.
- Inez?
Come on.
Oh, there you go!
Give her a hand, folks!
Little Miss Inez Stubbs,
ladies and gentlemen.
You can't stop a river
As it rushes to the sea
You can try to stop the hands of time
But you know it just can't be
And if they try to stop us, Seaweed
- We'll call the N-double A-C-P
'Cause the world keeps spinning
Round and round
And my heart's keeping time
To the speed of sound
I was lost till I heard the drums
Then I found my way
'Cause you can't stop the beat
Ever since we first saw the light
A man and woman liked to shake it
On a Saturday night
And so I'm gonna shake and shimmy it
- With all of my might
- Mother!
Today
'Cause you can't stop
The motion of the ocean
Or the rain from above
- They can try to stop the paradise
- Hello?
We're dreaming of
But you cannot stop the rhythm
Of two hearts in love
To stay
'Cause you can't stop the beat
Amen.
I am now a checkerboard chick.
Penny! No!
Live television.
There's nothing like it.
Penny!
- And now, it's the moment...
- Wait, wait, wait!
We have to wait
till they go to commercial.
As you know, we've kept
the lines open up to the last minute.
And those lines
have been burning up our switchboard.
Never in the history of this pageant
has there been such a surge
of late voting.
Baltimore, you've picked a winner.
And the new Miss Hairspray is...
- Inez Stubbs!
- What?
Inez, you done it! You did it!
How about that?
Yes!
Come on over here, Little Inez.
Go, babe!
Oh! Inez! Oh, my god!
That's my baby! That's my baby girl!
But... she's...
She's not even a candidate.
She just got
a tidal wave of calls, Velma.
But this is invalid.
This is impossible.
Well, anyone who dances for it
is eligible.
Rule 30, paragraph five, asterisk,
down at the bottom. Okay.
Well, this also makes you
the lead dancer
on The Corny Collins Show.
Ladies and gentlemen,
The Corny Collins Show
is now and forever
officially integrated!
All right. Yeah.
Interracial dancing has broken out
at the WYZT stage.
Just look at the crowd's reaction.
Back to you, Steve.
...Heard the drums
Then I found my way
'Cause you can't stop the beat
Amber, stop it!
I lost, Mom. Let's just deal with it.
No, you did not lose.
You cannot have lost
because I switched the damn tallies.
Smile, Miss Crabmeat.
You're on Candid Camera.
That was a good shot,
don't you think?
Not bad.
What are you doing?
Get that away from me!
Go to commercial!
Go!
Velma!
Pack your desk.
You've tainted the name
of Ultra Clutch.
How can you taint
a cancerous can of chemicals?
You're fired!
I can't be fired.
Oh, yeah?
Last chance to join the dance, folks.
Everyone is welcome!
Wilbur...
Do it now or forever wish you had.
Really?
Show them, baby.
Nobody can dance like you.
You can't stop my happiness
'Cause I like the way I am
And you just can't stop
My knife and fork
When I see a Christmas ham
So if you don't like the way I look
Well, I just don't give a damn
'Cause the world keeps spinning
Round and round
And my heart's keeping time
To the speed of sound
I was lost till I heard the drums
Then I found my way
'Cause you can't stop the beat
Ever since this old world began
A woman found out if she shook it
She could shake up a man
And so I'm gonna shake and shimmy it
The best that I can today
'Cause you can't stop
The motion of the ocean
Or the sun in the sky
You can wonder if you wanna
But I'll never ask why
And if you try to hold me down
I'm gonna spit in your eye and say
That you can't stop the beat
I love you!
You did great!
Corny, do something!
The show is turning to gumbo!
Not a chance, Velma.
This is the future.
Maybelle, let's go.
This is your time.
Yeah.
All right, Miss buttercup.
It's time to wrap this mutha up.
Oh, oh, oh
- You can't stop today
- No!
As it comes speeding down the tracks
- Ooh, child, yes
- Child, yesterday is history
- Be gone!
- And it's never coming back
- Look ahead!
- 'Cause tomorrow is a brand-new day
- And it don't know white from black
- Yeah!
'Cause the world keeps spinning
Round and round
And my heart's keeping time
To the speed of sound
I was lost till I heard the drums
Then I found my way
'Cause you can't stop the beat
Ever since we first saw the light
A man and woman liked to shake it
On a Saturday night
And so I'm gonna shake and shimmy it
With all of my might today
'Cause you can't stop
The motion of the ocean
Or the rain from above
They can try to stop the paradise
We're dreaming of
But you cannot stop the rhythm
Of two hearts in love to stay
'Cause you can't stop the beat
Ever since we first saw the sun
A man and woman liked to shake it
When the day is done
And so we're gonna shake
And shimmy it
And have some fun today
'Cause you can't stop
The motion of the ocean
Or the rain from above
They can try to stop the paradise
We're dreaming of
But you'll never stop the rhythm
Of two hearts in love to stay
- 'Cause you can't stop the beat
- You can't stop the beat
You can't stop the beat
Hey, old friend, let's look back
On the crazy clothes we wore
Ain't it fun to look back
And to see it's all been done before
All those nights together
Are a special memory
And I can't wait for tomorrow
Just as long as you're dancing
Next to me
'Cause it's so clear, every year
- We get stronger
- Stronger
'Cause what's gone is gone
The past is the past
Turn the radio up
And then hit the gas 'cause
I know we've come so far
But we've got so far to go
I know the road seems long
But it won't be long
Till it's time to go
So, most days, we'll take it fast
And some nights, we'll take it slow
I know we've come so far
But, baby, baby
We've got so far to go
Oh, yeah, baby
Hey, old friend, together
Side by side and year by year
The road was filled
With twists and turns
Oh, but that's the road
That got us here
Let's move past the bad times
But before those memories fade
Let's forgive but not forget
And learn
From all the mistakes we made
'Cause it's so clear, every year
- We get stronger
- Stronger
So don't give up and don't say when
And just get back on the road again
'Cause I know we've come so far
But we've got so far to go
I know the road seems long
But it won't be long
Till it's time to go
So, most days, we'll take it fast
And some nights, we'll take it slow
I know we've come so far
But, baby, baby
We've got so far to go
Oh, yeah, baby
Oh, oh, oh
Hey, old friend
Come along for the ride
There's plenty of room so jump inside
The highway's bumpy
Every now and then
But it's so much better
Than where I've been
Just keep moving at your own speed
Your heart is all the compass
You'll ever need
Let's keep cruising the road we're on
'Cause the rear-view mirror
Only shows what's
Gone, gone, gone
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Got so far to go
Yeah
It's so clear
- Every year we get stronger
- Stronger
So shine that light
Take my hand
Let's dance into the promised land
'Cause I know we've come so far
But we've got so far to go
I know the road seems long
But it won't be long
Till it's time to go
So, most days, we'll take it fast
But some nights, we'll take it slow
I know we've come so far
But, baby, baby
We've got so far to go
Oh, oh, oh
- Yeah, yeah
- Welcome to the '60s
- Stop!
- Stop telling me what to do
- Don't!
- Don't treat me like a child of two
- No!
- I know that you want what's best
- Please!
- But, Mother, please
Give it a rest!
Stop! Don't! No! Please!
Mama, I'm a big girl now
Once upon a time
When I was just a kid
You never let me do
Just what the older kids did
But lose that laundry list
Of what you won't allow
'Cause, Mama, I'm a big girl now
Once upon a time
I played with childhood toys
But now I'd rather play around
With older boys
So, if I get a hickey
Please don't have a cow
'Cause, Mama, I'm a big girl now
Ma, I gotta tell you
That without a doubt
I get my best dancing lessons
From you
You're the one who taught me
How to twist and shout
Because you shout non-stop
And you're so twisted, too!
Whoa-oh-oh
Once I used to fidget
'Cause I just sat home
But now I'm just like Gidget
And I gotta get to Rome!
- So say, "Arrivederci!"
- "Toodle-oo!"
And, "Ciao!"
'Cause, Mama, I'm a big girl now
Oh, stop! Don't! No! Please!
Stop! Don't! No! Please!
Mama, I'm a big girl now
Hey, Mama, say, Mama
Once upon a time
I was a shy young thing
Could barely walk and talk
So much as dance and sing
But let me hit that stage
I wanna take my bow
'Cause, Mama, I'm a big girl now
Whoa-oh-oh
Once upon a time
I used to dress up Ken
But now that I'm a woman
I like bigger men
And I don't need a Barbie doll
To show me how
'Cause, Mama, I'm a big girl now
Ooh, ooh, ah
Ma, you always taught me
What was right from wrong
And now I just wanna give it a try
Mama, I've been in the nest
For far too long
So please give a push
And, Mama, watch me fly
- Watch me fly
- Show off
Someday I will meet
A man you won't condemn
And we will have some kids
And you can torture them
But let me be a star
Before I take that vow
'Cause, Mama, I'm a big girl now
Whoa-oh-oh
Mama, I'm a big girl now
Hey, hey, hey
Mama, I'm a big girl
Oh, such a big, big girl!
I'm a big girl now
Whoa-oh-oh
Please, Mama, I'm a big girl now
They came from way far out
In outer space
She's hard to miss
And so they landed on her face
She's got cooties
They've found a place to nest
- She's got cooties
- Cooties
If I were her, I'd be depressed
Long tailed, sharp nailed
Fuzzy legs, laying eggs
Oh, no, get them
In science class
She's like a walking show-and-tell
Her pet skunk ran away
'Cause it couldn't take the smell
- She's got cooties
- Cooties
Nobody wants to sit by her
No, don't need a coat
'Cause she's got fur
Circle, circle, dot, dot, dot
Glad I got my cootie shot
Come on, boys, let's stamp them out
Cootie, cootie
Come on, boys
- Whoa, no, no, no
- She's got cooties
- She's just as friendly as can be
- She shows them cootie hospitality
- She's got cooties
- She's like a living Twilight Zone
Can you get Rod Sterling
on the phone?
Black, white, red, green
Every colour in between
Dresses like a circus clown
ought to
Grew up in a cootie zoo
I bet her two-ton Mama's
Got them, too!
She... she... she's coming!
- She's got cooties
- Somebody ought to hose her down
- Oh, yeah
- She's got cooties
- Somebody ought to hose her down
- Yeah, yeah
- She's got cooties
- She's just as friendly as can be
- She shows them cootie hospitality
She's got cooties
- This girl is sure to catch your eye
- She's got cooties
She surely likes
To let her freak flag fly
Come on, boys
- Let's jam
- She's got cooties
Let's stamp them out
Come on, boys
- Let's jam
- She's got cooties
Let's stamp them out
Come on, boys
- Let's jam
- She's got cooties
Let's stamp them out
Come on, boys
- Let's jam
- She's got cooties
Let's stamp them out
Black, white, red, green
Every colour in between
Dresses like a circus clown
Somebody ought to hose her down
Grew up in a cootie zoo
I bet her two-ton Mama's
Got them, too!