1
00:00:39,439 --> 00:00:44,025
False alarm. Hold it!
It's OK, I'm here. it's all right.

2
00:00:44,694 --> 00:00:49,156
- Set it down nice and easy.
- At the impound. Next time, read the sign.

3
00:00:49,240 --> 00:00:53,118
You don't understand. I'm here to meet
my wife's plane. Let me have this car.

4
00:00:53,202 --> 00:00:56,204
Sure. Tomorrow, 8.00 to 4.00.
Pay $40, we give it back.

5
00:00:56,330 --> 00:00:58,415
Don't write it up!

6
00:00:58,499 --> 00:01:00,417
This is my mother-in-law's car.

7
00:01:00,501 --> 00:01:02,878
She's already mad at me
cos I'm not a dentist.

8
00:01:02,962 --> 00:01:07,924
- Look, I'm a cop. LAPD.
- I was in LA once. Hated it.

9
00:01:08,009 --> 00:01:10,469
I can understand. I don't like it much...

10
00:01:10,553 --> 00:01:13,346
That's a plastic fender up there.
Take it easy!

11
00:01:13,431 --> 00:01:16,558
Cut me some slack, will you?
I was a cop in New York City.

12
00:01:16,642 --> 00:01:20,979
I only moved to LA cos my wife
took a job there. What do you say?

13
00:01:21,063 --> 00:01:26,067
Here we are, Washington, DC, the heart
of democracy. One hand washes the other.

14
00:01:26,194 --> 00:01:27,569
Come on, man. it's Christmas.

15
00:01:27,653 --> 00:01:30,322
So ask Santa Claus to give you
another car.

16
00:01:30,406 --> 00:01:32,240
Merry Christmas, pal.

17
00:01:33,951 --> 00:01:35,952
It's all yours, Murray.

18
00:01:39,415 --> 00:01:41,041
Son of a bitch.

19
00:02:22,917 --> 00:02:25,043
- Hi. Where are the telephones?
- Over there.

20
00:02:25,127 --> 00:02:27,003
Thank you very much.

21
00:02:27,088 --> 00:02:30,882
Leonard Adkins has a story
that grows hotter by the minute.

22
00:02:30,967 --> 00:02:34,886
Security was tight today
at Escalan airport in Valverde,

23
00:02:34,971 --> 00:02:38,932
where it is reported that deposed general,
Ramón Esperanza,

24
00:02:39,016 --> 00:02:42,352
will be delivered for extradition
to the United States.

25
00:02:42,436 --> 00:02:45,605
Two years ago,
the general led his country's army

26
00:02:45,690 --> 00:02:48,066
against communist insurgents

27
00:02:48,150 --> 00:02:51,236
in a campaign fought with
American money and advisers.

28
00:02:51,320 --> 00:02:53,780
Esperanza's fall from power caused ripples

29
00:02:53,864 --> 00:02:58,076
in his country's recent election,
and closer to home as well,

30
00:02:58,160 --> 00:03:01,830
when Pentagon officials were charged
with supplying him with weapons,

31
00:03:01,914 --> 00:03:03,915
despite the Congressional ban.

32
00:03:04,000 --> 00:03:08,670
Evidence that Esperanza's forces violated
the neutrality of neighbouring countries

33
00:03:08,754 --> 00:03:10,755
made Congress withhold funds.

34
00:03:10,840 --> 00:03:16,428
Funds which Esperanza is accused of
replacing by going into cocaine smuggling.

35
00:03:16,512 --> 00:03:20,432
Although Esperanza was removed
as commander in chief this year,

36
00:03:20,516 --> 00:03:23,935
the agreement to extradite him
was only reached yesterday.

37
00:03:24,020 --> 00:03:29,232
Washington insiders say a phone call
made it happen, a phone call from a...

38
00:03:34,280 --> 00:03:35,739
All right!

39
00:03:39,493 --> 00:03:42,579
If I could find a phone,
I'd call you, whoever you are.

40
00:04:15,196 --> 00:04:17,030
Excuse me. Thank you.

41
00:04:25,915 --> 00:04:28,500
This is Lieutenant McClane.
Somebody beep me?

42
00:04:28,584 --> 00:04:33,171
- I'd like to think I'm somebody.
- Honey! Where are you? Did you land yet?

43
00:04:34,048 --> 00:04:36,007
It's the nineties, remember?

44
00:04:36,092 --> 00:04:39,427
Microchips, microwaves, faxes, air phones.

45
00:04:40,846 --> 00:04:44,849
As far as I'm concerned,
progress peaked with frozen pizza.

46
00:04:44,934 --> 00:04:48,186
Listen, we're gonna be
about half an hour late landing.

47
00:04:48,270 --> 00:04:51,398
I just wanted to let you know.
The kids OK?

48
00:04:51,774 --> 00:04:56,069
They're about to lose their minds from all
the sugar your parents are giving them.

49
00:04:56,153 --> 00:04:58,947
Did Mom give you a hard
time about borrowing her car?

50
00:04:59,031 --> 00:05:01,157
No. Not yet.

51
00:05:01,784 --> 00:05:05,995
Listen, honey, when you land,
can we just rent a car,

52
00:05:06,080 --> 00:05:09,207
check into a hotel,
leave the kids with your parents?

53
00:05:09,291 --> 00:05:13,586
Order some room service, a bottle
of champagne? What do you say?

54
00:05:14,547 --> 00:05:16,464
You're on, Lieutenant.

55
00:05:16,590 --> 00:05:19,968
I'll see you in half an hour, honey.
I love you. Bye.

56
00:05:24,890 --> 00:05:27,225
Isn't technology wonderful?

57
00:05:28,644 --> 00:05:31,479
- My husband doesn't think so.
- I do.

58
00:05:32,648 --> 00:05:35,734
I used to carry around
those awful Mace things.

59
00:05:35,818 --> 00:05:37,068
Now...

60
00:05:39,321 --> 00:05:42,615
I zap any bastard that screws with me.

61
00:05:45,161 --> 00:05:47,328
I tried it on my little dog.

62
00:05:48,581 --> 00:05:51,082
Poor thing limped for a week.

63
00:05:58,507 --> 00:05:59,924
Excuse me.

64
00:06:01,635 --> 00:06:03,678
You look really familiar to me.

65
00:06:03,804 --> 00:06:06,097
I get that a lot. I've been on TV.

66
00:06:06,182 --> 00:06:08,016
Yeah. Me too.

67
00:06:33,000 --> 00:06:35,210
- Grab the tools.
- You got it.

68
00:06:35,711 --> 00:06:39,130
This is Amy Nichole,
live from Escalan airport,

69
00:06:39,215 --> 00:06:43,593
where deposed general, Ramón Esperanza,
has just arrived under heavy guard.

70
00:06:43,677 --> 00:06:46,888
The deposed dictator's mood
seems jubilant.

71
00:06:46,972 --> 00:06:51,726
He is smiling and waving to the crowd,
like a man running for political office.

72
00:06:52,812 --> 00:06:57,148
...thousands of political prisoners,
including the new president.

73
00:06:57,233 --> 00:07:02,654
There's no doubt he still has some
ardent supporters, both here and abroad.

74
00:07:02,738 --> 00:07:05,448
Rumours abound on Capitol Hill
that there were...

75
00:07:08,828 --> 00:07:11,287
- Yeah?
- Sir, we're checking our equipment.

76
00:07:11,372 --> 00:07:15,500
- Any problems with the conduit line?
- I don't know anything about that.

77
00:07:15,584 --> 00:07:18,878
- Would you mind if we take a look?
- Help yourself.

78
00:07:30,516 --> 00:07:33,768
It don't seem right somehow,
closing down this church.

79
00:07:33,853 --> 00:07:38,022
The parish is gonna keep on using it,
but it won't be the same.

80
00:07:38,107 --> 00:07:41,359
Been here a lot of years,
and I've been right here with it.

81
00:07:41,443 --> 00:07:45,697
Yeah, I kind of feel like
a piece of me is dying with this church.

82
00:07:45,781 --> 00:07:47,907
You're right about that.

83
00:07:53,539 --> 00:07:57,375
...cocaine smuggling
and bribing government officials.

84
00:07:57,459 --> 00:08:01,796
He certainly doesn't show it,
but no matter how high his spirits,

85
00:08:01,881 --> 00:08:07,468
they can't hide the fact that the US war
on drugs has taken its first prisoner.

86
00:08:10,097 --> 00:08:13,057
This is Buckwheat. The clubhouse is open.

87
00:08:15,978 --> 00:08:18,813
Here at Dulles,
the men from the Justice Department

88
00:08:18,898 --> 00:08:21,149
wait to handcuff the man who symbolises

89
00:08:21,233 --> 00:08:23,693
the enemy in America's fight
against cocaine.

90
00:08:23,777 --> 00:08:27,196
That battle may be almost won,
but the war is still in doubt.

91
00:08:27,281 --> 00:08:30,491
Samantha Coleman, WNTW,
for Night-Time News.

92
00:08:30,576 --> 00:08:32,660
Roger that, Colonel. Out.

93
00:08:48,344 --> 00:08:50,178
That was the Colonel.

94
00:08:50,846 --> 00:08:53,890
Everyone's in position. How's the weather?

95
00:08:53,974 --> 00:08:56,768
We got flurries all along the Virginia coast.

96
00:08:56,852 --> 00:08:59,854
New storm front coming in
from the northeast.

97
00:09:00,940 --> 00:09:03,483
- God loves the infantry.
- Amen.

98
00:09:05,152 --> 00:09:07,236
Carry out your assignments.

99
00:09:10,199 --> 00:09:12,992
- 15.51 . Mark.
- Check.

100
00:09:14,328 --> 00:09:15,578
Later.

101
00:09:38,644 --> 00:09:42,563
It's cold out there, man!
I stomped my feet for five minutes.

102
00:09:52,324 --> 00:09:54,659
Two cappuccinos. Make it fast.

103
00:10:15,848 --> 00:10:20,893
Excuse me, officers. This may sound like
a wild-goose chase, but I think I saw...

104
00:10:22,604 --> 00:10:24,188
Saw what?

105
00:10:25,274 --> 00:10:27,900
Elvis. Elvis Presley.

106
00:10:30,863 --> 00:10:33,156
Fucking tourists. Ought to be a law.

107
00:10:34,074 --> 00:10:36,034
There's a lot of you from
the Justice Department here.

108
00:10:36,118 --> 00:10:39,871
- Is there any particular reason for that?
- Just routine.

109
00:10:40,289 --> 00:10:42,707
- Any comment, sir?
- Not now.

110
00:10:43,792 --> 00:10:45,585
Thank you, sir.

111
00:10:50,632 --> 00:10:53,051
That's Colonel Stuart over there.

112
00:10:53,469 --> 00:10:57,305
Got a little problem with personnel.
Last-minute replacement.

113
00:10:57,639 --> 00:11:01,309
- How's the security here?
- Like we figured... a joke.

114
00:11:01,977 --> 00:11:04,062
Colonel Stuart,
could we have a few words?

115
00:11:04,146 --> 00:11:06,314
You can have two: "fuck" and "you".

116
00:11:06,398 --> 00:11:08,733
No pictures, you pinko bitch.

117
00:11:10,944 --> 00:11:12,361
Old news.

118
00:11:52,111 --> 00:11:53,528
Hey, man.

119
00:11:56,031 --> 00:11:58,366
- What is it?
- You got a key for this door?

120
00:11:58,450 --> 00:12:00,201
Yeah. Why?

121
00:12:00,327 --> 00:12:03,246
Because I want you to open it up,
that's why.

122
00:12:05,791 --> 00:12:09,210
- Is there a cop on duty around here?
- The airport police.

123
00:12:09,294 --> 00:12:10,711
Go get 'em.

124
00:12:49,084 --> 00:12:53,546
All right. Perfect. Good to go.

125
00:12:57,009 --> 00:13:00,011
It's a restricted area. What's the matter?

126
00:13:00,095 --> 00:13:03,055
- Couldn't wait for a skycap?
- We work here.

127
00:13:03,432 --> 00:13:05,433
Let's see some lD.

128
00:13:05,517 --> 00:13:07,602
Sure. No problem.

129
00:13:48,810 --> 00:13:50,978
Jeez. Fuck!

130
00:14:38,193 --> 00:14:40,152
This is a tag team?

131
00:15:13,395 --> 00:15:15,104
He came in here and flashed a badge?

132
00:15:15,188 --> 00:15:18,107
Yeah. He said to bring you guys back here.

133
00:15:45,427 --> 00:15:46,927
Christ.

134
00:16:04,071 --> 00:16:05,321
Fucker!

135
00:16:06,615 --> 00:16:07,948
Freeze!

136
00:16:09,201 --> 00:16:12,828
Nice guess, asshole.
I'm a cop. That was the bad guy.

137
00:16:13,538 --> 00:16:15,206
Where's your lD?

138
00:16:19,544 --> 00:16:21,587
On its way to Cleveland?

139
00:16:27,469 --> 00:16:32,056
You did not explain anything. You just
shoved me back here into this cattle car.

140
00:16:32,140 --> 00:16:36,143
- Sir, you were told we were overbooked.
- Fine. I accept that.

141
00:16:36,269 --> 00:16:39,563
But why can't I get the first-class
meal my network paid for?

142
00:16:39,648 --> 00:16:42,650
- Do you know who I am?
- Yes. We've seen your programme.

143
00:16:42,734 --> 00:16:47,071
Your episode "Flying Junkyards" was
an objective look at air-traffic safety.

144
00:16:47,155 --> 00:16:51,242
It wasn't nearly as edifying as
"Bimbos of the Sky", was it, Connie?

145
00:16:51,326 --> 00:16:54,203
You think you're funny.

146
00:16:54,663 --> 00:16:57,665
Fine. I've got your number.

147
00:16:57,749 --> 00:17:00,835
And I've got yours. So park it, sir.

148
00:17:03,171 --> 00:17:04,380
Fine.

149
00:17:14,433 --> 00:17:16,934
- Stewardess.
- Mr Thornberg.

150
00:17:17,018 --> 00:17:19,145
You cannot monopolise my time.

151
00:17:19,229 --> 00:17:22,606
- You cannot put me near that woman.
- Excuse me?

152
00:17:23,984 --> 00:17:27,361
He means he's filed
a restraining order against me.

153
00:17:27,863 --> 00:17:30,448
I'm not allowed within 50 feet of him.

154
00:17:30,532 --> 00:17:35,536
50 yards. So by keeping me in this
section, you are violating a court order.

155
00:17:36,204 --> 00:17:38,581
I can sue you and this airline.

156
00:17:39,541 --> 00:17:43,169
That woman assaulted me,
and she humiliated me in public.

157
00:17:51,219 --> 00:17:52,887
What did you do?

158
00:17:54,639 --> 00:17:56,974
Knocked out two of his teeth.

159
00:17:57,642 --> 00:17:59,643
Would you like some champagne?

160
00:18:03,565 --> 00:18:06,025
Sorry, Officer McClane. I had to check.

161
00:18:06,109 --> 00:18:08,611
Here's your piece and shield back.

162
00:18:09,529 --> 00:18:10,863
Thanks.

163
00:18:18,330 --> 00:18:20,831
Jesus! Christ!

164
00:18:21,750 --> 00:18:24,502
What the fuck are you people...
What are you doing?

165
00:18:24,586 --> 00:18:27,505
This is a crime scene.
You gotta seal this area off.

166
00:18:27,589 --> 00:18:28,672
That's up to the captain.

167
00:18:28,757 --> 00:18:31,967
Maybe you better take me up
to the captain.

168
00:18:43,104 --> 00:18:45,856
- Where's Cochrane?
- He didn't make it.

169
00:18:54,950 --> 00:18:59,620
- You're late.
- We ran into trouble, Colonel.

170
00:19:00,080 --> 00:19:05,042
Some cop killed Cochrane.
I barely got away, sir.

171
00:19:05,126 --> 00:19:07,545
Did you accomplish your mission?

172
00:19:08,380 --> 00:19:10,631
Yes, sir, but... Cochrane, sir.

173
00:19:10,715 --> 00:19:14,301
Then the damage is minimal.
The penalty could be severe.

174
00:19:23,270 --> 00:19:26,564
You fail me again,
and the chamber won't be empty.

175
00:19:27,732 --> 00:19:29,191
Dismissed.

176
00:19:46,001 --> 00:19:48,168
Who is it? Come in.

177
00:19:49,170 --> 00:19:51,422
- Captain Lorenzo?
- Yeah.

178
00:19:51,506 --> 00:19:54,216
- I'm John McClane...
- I know who you are.

179
00:19:54,301 --> 00:19:56,802
You're the asshole
that just broke seven FAA

180
00:19:56,886 --> 00:19:59,054
and five District of Columbia regulations

181
00:19:59,139 --> 00:20:02,516
running around my airport
with a gun, shooting at people.

182
00:20:02,642 --> 00:20:05,894
- What do you call that shit?
- Self-defence.

183
00:20:06,605 --> 00:20:11,609
You think that LA badge is gonna get you
a free lunch or something around here?

184
00:20:11,693 --> 00:20:14,903
No. Maybe a little professional courtesy.

185
00:20:14,988 --> 00:20:18,282
In an airport on Christmas week?
You gotta be kidding.

186
00:20:18,366 --> 00:20:21,201
OK, fuck courtesy.
How about being professional?

187
00:20:21,328 --> 00:20:24,288
Your boys just walked away
from a crime scene.

188
00:20:24,372 --> 00:20:26,457
You can't wrap this up in ten minutes.

189
00:20:26,541 --> 00:20:28,834
You got to seal the area off,
dust for prints...

190
00:20:28,918 --> 00:20:30,794
Don't lecture me, hotshot.

191
00:20:30,879 --> 00:20:34,048
I know what I'm doing.
We're gonna dust it down.

192
00:20:34,132 --> 00:20:37,092
We'll take all the pictures.
We'll sweep for fibres.

193
00:20:37,177 --> 00:20:40,054
After 400 people go through there?

194
00:20:40,138 --> 00:20:42,097
You'd be lucky to get a print
from one of your people.

195
00:20:42,182 --> 00:20:45,225
- Just shut down that area...
- Shut the area down?

196
00:20:45,352 --> 00:20:48,562
It's that simple? Just shut the area down?

197
00:20:48,647 --> 00:20:51,273
I got everybody
from the Shriners' convention

198
00:20:51,358 --> 00:20:54,068
to the goddamn Boy Scouts in here.

199
00:20:54,152 --> 00:20:57,655
I got lost kids, lost dogs...
Not now. Later!

200
00:20:57,739 --> 00:20:59,823
I got international diplomats.

201
00:20:59,908 --> 00:21:04,078
I got a fuckin' reindeer flying in here
from the fuckin' petting zoo.

202
00:21:04,204 --> 00:21:07,414
But John McClane,
he's got a little problem.

203
00:21:07,499 --> 00:21:09,833
Let's shut down the whole fuckin' airport.

204
00:21:09,918 --> 00:21:14,213
- What do you think they'll say upstairs?
- Phone and find out.

205
00:21:14,297 --> 00:21:19,635
I don't need fuckin' forensics to tell me
this was some punk stealing luggage!

206
00:21:19,719 --> 00:21:22,096
Luggage?
That punk pulled a Glock 7 on me.

207
00:21:22,180 --> 00:21:24,848
That's a porcelain gun made in Germany.

208
00:21:24,933 --> 00:21:26,850
It doesn't show up on X-ray machines

209
00:21:26,935 --> 00:21:28,936
and it costs more than you make
in a month.

210
00:21:29,020 --> 00:21:31,689
You'd be surprised
what I make in a month.

211
00:21:31,773 --> 00:21:33,107
If it's more than $1 .98...

212
00:21:33,191 --> 00:21:36,652
Hey, McClane, don't start
believing your own press.

213
00:21:36,736 --> 00:21:40,364
Yeah, I know all about you
and that Nakatomi thing in LA.

214
00:21:40,448 --> 00:21:44,201
But just cos the TV thinks
you're hot shit, that don't make it so.

215
00:21:44,285 --> 00:21:47,162
Look, you are in my little pond now,

216
00:21:47,247 --> 00:21:49,790
and I am the big fish that runs it.

217
00:21:50,917 --> 00:21:53,627
So you capped some lowlife. Fine.

218
00:21:53,712 --> 00:21:57,965
I'll send your fuckin' captain in LA
a fuckin' commendation.

219
00:21:58,049 --> 00:22:00,342
Now, get the hell out of my office

220
00:22:00,427 --> 00:22:03,762
before I have you thrown out
of my goddamn airport.

221
00:22:13,982 --> 00:22:16,316
Carmine, let me ask you something.

222
00:22:16,401 --> 00:22:18,902
What sets off the metal detectors first?

223
00:22:18,987 --> 00:22:21,739
The lead in your ass
or the shit in your brains?

224
00:22:21,823 --> 00:22:23,323
Fat fuck.

225
00:22:32,917 --> 00:22:36,503
- Any lD on this guy?
- That's somebody else's problem.

226
00:22:39,090 --> 00:22:41,675
Okay, your car is ready.
You could just sign right here.

227
00:22:41,760 --> 00:22:45,387
I need to borrow this and this.
I'll bring it right back.

228
00:22:48,141 --> 00:22:49,516
Hold up!

229
00:22:53,772 --> 00:22:56,106
Hold up, boys. We gotta check something.

230
00:22:56,191 --> 00:22:59,568
- What are you doing?
- Pretty gruesome fuckin' job.

231
00:22:59,652 --> 00:23:04,281
All the confusion in there,
forgot to get this clown's prints.

232
00:23:07,952 --> 00:23:09,161
Christ.

233
00:23:09,245 --> 00:23:10,788
You're supposed to do that at the morgue.

234
00:23:10,872 --> 00:23:14,458
Not any more. Got a new SOP
for DOAs from the FAA.

235
00:23:18,797 --> 00:23:22,174
I don't think this one's gonna make it.
Thanks a lot.

236
00:25:15,663 --> 00:25:19,082
- Powell here.
- Take that Twinkie out of your mouth.

237
00:25:20,418 --> 00:25:23,045
- John, how ya doing?
- Holly stood me up a day

238
00:25:23,129 --> 00:25:26,423
and I'm here alone in DC with my in-laws.

239
00:25:27,425 --> 00:25:32,012
The old in-laws? Man, they do love
their policemen son-in-laws.

240
00:25:32,096 --> 00:25:36,600
Listen, Al, what is the fax machine
telephone number there at the station?

241
00:25:40,813 --> 00:25:42,689
5553212.

242
00:25:42,774 --> 00:25:47,444
3212. Hold on a second, all right?
I wanna send you something.

243
00:25:47,528 --> 00:25:48,737
Excuse me.

244
00:25:48,821 --> 00:25:51,782
You and faxes? This is a first.

245
00:25:51,866 --> 00:25:55,285
Holly told me I should wake up
and smell the nineties.

246
00:25:55,370 --> 00:25:57,496
- This way?
- No. That way.

247
00:25:57,956 --> 00:26:00,290
- It's upside down.
- It doesn't matter.

248
00:26:00,375 --> 00:26:02,084
Here it comes.

249
00:26:04,671 --> 00:26:08,507
- I'm sending you something now.
- Hold on a second, cowboy.

250
00:26:24,065 --> 00:26:26,817
- Fingerprints?
- We've got an unidentified stiff.

251
00:26:26,901 --> 00:26:30,153
I've circled the whorls
in case the transmission's fuzzy.

252
00:26:30,238 --> 00:26:33,198
Run it through State and Federal,
and maybe lnterpol.

253
00:26:33,282 --> 00:26:37,077
- Will do. What's this about?
- Just a feeling I have.

254
00:26:37,745 --> 00:26:41,832
Ouch. When you get those feelings,
insurance companies start to go bankrupt.

255
00:26:41,916 --> 00:26:43,959
The fax number is...

256
00:26:44,043 --> 00:26:49,256
On the top of the transmission
you just got.

257
00:26:52,218 --> 00:26:56,430
An airport? You're not
pissing in somebody's pool?

258
00:26:57,765 --> 00:27:00,350
Yeah, and I'm fresh out of chlorine.

259
00:27:00,935 --> 00:27:03,353
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.

260
00:27:06,566 --> 00:27:08,650
Just as this storm starts breaking,

261
00:27:08,735 --> 00:27:12,195
the satellite-feed up
and drops the other shoe on us.

262
00:27:12,280 --> 00:27:13,697
Look at this new front moving in.

263
00:27:13,781 --> 00:27:16,867
Makes its baby brother
look like chickenshit.

264
00:27:18,286 --> 00:27:22,205
I can sand down the runways
and run the ploughs between landings

265
00:27:22,290 --> 00:27:24,958
but you gotta downshift them,
give me time to work.

266
00:27:25,043 --> 00:27:26,460
You got it.

267
00:27:27,587 --> 00:27:31,548
All right, everyone.
Let's slow down our birds

268
00:27:31,632 --> 00:27:33,800
before we get a parking lot over our heads.

269
00:27:33,885 --> 00:27:38,305
The line starts at the Mississippi,
and they better start taking numbers.

270
00:27:48,149 --> 00:27:50,067
Can I get you another?

271
00:27:53,154 --> 00:27:57,449
No, thank you. I only have to look
at his face for another 20 minutes.

272
00:27:59,077 --> 00:28:03,830
This is the captain speaking. I've just
been informed by Dulles traffic control

273
00:28:03,956 --> 00:28:06,917
that there's a weather front ahead of us.

274
00:28:07,001 --> 00:28:09,920
We may be up here a little while longer.

275
00:28:10,004 --> 00:28:12,756
- Thank you.
- On second thought...

276
00:28:21,432 --> 00:28:26,186
I'm right here, partner.
Your stiff's dossier is coming through now.

277
00:28:28,689 --> 00:28:31,108
- What can you tell me about him?
- He's dead.

278
00:28:31,192 --> 00:28:32,859
You needed a computer to figure that out?

279
00:28:32,944 --> 00:28:35,070
No, you don't follow me.

280
00:28:35,655 --> 00:28:39,449
According to the Department of Defense,
he's been dead for two years.

281
00:28:39,534 --> 00:28:43,578
- What?
- That's right. Sergeant Oswald Cochrane.

282
00:28:43,663 --> 00:28:45,997
American adviser in Honduras.

283
00:28:46,541 --> 00:28:49,126
Killed in a helicopter accident, 5-11 -88.

284
00:28:49,210 --> 00:28:50,544
Officer.

285
00:28:51,796 --> 00:28:55,382
Read between the lines
and it looks like a lot of black-bag stuff.

286
00:28:55,508 --> 00:28:58,301
I see it. All right, Al. Thanks a lot.

287
00:28:58,386 --> 00:29:00,470
- Any time.
- OK.

288
00:29:02,849 --> 00:29:06,726
I close in about an hour.
Maybe we can go get a drink?

289
00:29:09,313 --> 00:29:12,190
Just the fax, ma'am.

290
00:29:17,405 --> 00:29:20,657
Wait a second, I see somebody.
I'll call you back.

291
00:29:26,747 --> 00:29:28,373
The ghost of Christmas past.

292
00:29:28,457 --> 00:29:31,084
Nakatomi? LA?
You're John McClane, right?

293
00:29:31,169 --> 00:29:34,045
- Who are you?
- Sam Coleman. WNTW News.

294
00:29:34,922 --> 00:29:38,425
- Excuse me.
- Give me a break. I saw the stiff.

295
00:29:38,509 --> 00:29:40,468
Word is, that was your handiwork.

296
00:29:40,553 --> 00:29:42,888
No. I only do needlepoint.

297
00:29:48,603 --> 00:29:52,522
Great. National just shut down.
Totally iced.

298
00:29:52,607 --> 00:29:55,442
- They'll send us their planes.
- Happy holiday.

299
00:29:55,526 --> 00:29:57,861
The worst part, Mr Trudeau, is the press.

300
00:29:57,945 --> 00:30:00,864
They were here for the Esperanza story,

301
00:30:00,948 --> 00:30:04,117
so they got it right on the news,
bloodstains and all.

302
00:30:04,243 --> 00:30:07,621
I'd like to lock every damn reporter
out of the airport,

303
00:30:07,705 --> 00:30:12,751
but they'd pull that freedom-of-speech crap
on us, then the ACLU would be all over us.

304
00:30:12,835 --> 00:30:16,546
Murder on television.
Hell of a start for Christmas week.

305
00:30:18,132 --> 00:30:20,300
What is it? A gang thing like last time?

306
00:30:20,426 --> 00:30:23,762
Only if your gangs get
their training at Fort Bragg.

307
00:30:24,722 --> 00:30:27,140
- Who the hell is this?
- I'm a police officer...

308
00:30:27,266 --> 00:30:31,478
In an unauthorised area.
LA, Mr Trudeau, don't mean shit.

309
00:30:31,729 --> 00:30:34,981
That's what I said about
my last cholesterol test.

310
00:30:35,483 --> 00:30:38,443
So what's your problem,
Lieutenant McClane?

311
00:30:39,487 --> 00:30:41,655
I'm sure Captain Lorenzo has
explained to you

312
00:30:41,739 --> 00:30:44,407
the minor fracas with the minor thieves.

313
00:30:44,492 --> 00:30:46,660
Maybe he can explain this.

314
00:31:05,513 --> 00:31:08,515
- All systems tapped, Colonel.
- Fire it up.

315
00:31:23,197 --> 00:31:26,032
H minus five minutes. Stand by.

316
00:31:28,244 --> 00:31:31,955
We've got a body in the morgue
that seems to have died twice.

317
00:31:32,039 --> 00:31:34,791
Assuming it's not an error,
what do we assume?

318
00:31:34,875 --> 00:31:37,085
Somebody's about to fuck
with this airport.

319
00:31:37,169 --> 00:31:39,296
What the hell does that mean?

320
00:31:39,380 --> 00:31:43,383
I know we're dummies up here,
so give us a taste of your genius.

321
00:31:43,467 --> 00:31:45,385
A hijacking, a robbery or what?

322
00:31:45,469 --> 00:31:47,846
- I'm not sure...
- He's not sure.

323
00:31:47,930 --> 00:31:50,432
I'm stunned. I gotta lie down.

324
00:31:50,516 --> 00:31:54,561
Only professionals go to this much trouble.
Not luggage thieves or punks.

325
00:31:54,645 --> 00:31:57,814
- Professional at what?
- What the fuck do you think this is?

326
00:31:57,898 --> 00:32:01,568
The safety patrol? This is the résumé
of a professional mercenary.

327
00:32:01,652 --> 00:32:05,280
A major drug dealer is due here.
You need a slide rule to solve this,

328
00:32:05,364 --> 00:32:08,158
or another body in a bag
before you ask questions?

329
00:32:08,242 --> 00:32:11,870
You're the one that gave us
that fucking body. Remember that.

330
00:32:11,954 --> 00:32:13,913
Yeah, I remember that.

331
00:32:20,463 --> 00:32:23,923
Lorenzo, have all your
shift commanders report in. Now.

332
00:32:24,008 --> 00:32:27,677
- What?
- They're to report anything unusual,

333
00:32:27,762 --> 00:32:30,805
- no matter how trivial. Got that?
- I got it.

334
00:32:30,890 --> 00:32:33,183
- My God.
- What?

335
00:32:33,267 --> 00:32:36,102
- The runways. Look.
- What the hell?

336
00:32:36,187 --> 00:32:39,439
- They're shutting down.
- Jesus Christ.

337
00:32:45,279 --> 00:32:47,989
Go to emergency lighting. Now.

338
00:32:48,074 --> 00:32:52,369
- Emergency. We are in a code yellow.
- Backup systems won't come up.

339
00:32:52,453 --> 00:32:54,329
- Shunt to another terminal.
- Bobby, what have you got?

340
00:32:54,413 --> 00:32:55,455
Please respond. Please respond.

341
00:32:55,539 --> 00:32:59,167
- The network is down.
- Should we call the power company?

342
00:32:59,251 --> 00:33:01,211
We're on the same grid and we're hot.

343
00:33:01,295 --> 00:33:03,171
Dulles, I'm on approach.

344
00:33:03,255 --> 00:33:06,549
- Maintain position. Repeat.
- What's going on down there?

345
00:33:06,634 --> 00:33:09,344
- We're on it.
- We're unable right now. Delay.

346
00:33:09,428 --> 00:33:13,890
Fuji 604. Execute published
missed-approach procedure and hold.

347
00:33:13,974 --> 00:33:17,018
TWA 23, unable to clear you
for approach at this time.

348
00:33:17,103 --> 00:33:19,396
Climb to and maintain one zero thousand.

349
00:33:19,480 --> 00:33:22,482
I've checked all systems.
It ain't happening.

350
00:33:38,165 --> 00:33:40,917
- What's it look like?
- Approach control is gone.

351
00:33:41,001 --> 00:33:43,920
Jesus. instrument landing system is down.

352
00:33:45,256 --> 00:33:47,507
Confirmed. lLS is dead.

353
00:33:47,633 --> 00:33:51,344
Every goddamn system's dead.
And lnmac monitors are down.

354
00:33:56,851 --> 00:34:00,186
Attention all controllers.
We have a code-red alert.

355
00:34:00,980 --> 00:34:05,275
Every aircraft approaching our sector,
and not already in our landing pattern,

356
00:34:05,359 --> 00:34:08,361
gets diverted to their alternate airport.

357
00:34:08,446 --> 00:34:12,407
Everyone already on approach,
or inside our pattern,

358
00:34:12,783 --> 00:34:15,368
holds at the outer markers.

359
00:34:15,453 --> 00:34:18,329
Stack 'em, pack 'em and rack 'em. Move.

360
00:34:24,545 --> 00:34:27,046
Not a word of this leaves this room.

361
00:34:27,131 --> 00:34:31,468
There must be 15,000 people in
this airport, and we don't need panic.

362
00:34:32,178 --> 00:34:34,888
We just bought ourselves
maybe two hours.

363
00:34:35,306 --> 00:34:38,391
After that, planes low on fuel
won't be circling.

364
00:34:38,476 --> 00:34:41,436
They'll be dropping
on the White House lawn.

365
00:34:43,147 --> 00:34:46,065
McClane, this what you expected?

366
00:34:47,985 --> 00:34:49,277
No.

367
00:34:50,237 --> 00:34:52,447
This is just the beginning.

368
00:34:56,160 --> 00:34:59,412
- FAA hot line.
- How could they know already?

369
00:34:59,497 --> 00:35:00,914
They can't.

370
00:35:02,541 --> 00:35:05,210
Maybe it's the boys
who pulled your plugs.

371
00:35:05,294 --> 00:35:07,045
Put it on speaker.

372
00:35:07,922 --> 00:35:10,423
Attention, Dulles tower. Attention.

373
00:35:10,758 --> 00:35:14,511
They say blind men become very
attentive by way of compensation.

374
00:35:14,595 --> 00:35:18,765
Now that you're blind and deaf,
I think I've got your attention.

375
00:35:18,849 --> 00:35:22,519
I'm aware your recorders are active,
so I'll be quick.

376
00:35:22,603 --> 00:35:25,146
You can play me back
to your heart's content.

377
00:35:25,231 --> 00:35:28,149
How did you get on this line? Who is this?

378
00:35:28,734 --> 00:35:31,569
Who I am is unimportant. What I want...

379
00:35:32,988 --> 00:35:36,866
if you don't want planes to splash into
the Potomac as they run out of fuel,

380
00:35:36,951 --> 00:35:39,285
what I want is very important.

381
00:35:39,370 --> 00:35:42,539
A plane will be landing
at this airport in 58 minutes.

382
00:35:42,623 --> 00:35:45,500
It is FM-1: Foreign Military One.

383
00:35:45,960 --> 00:35:49,128
- I'm sure you are aware of the nature
- Esperanza?

384
00:35:49,213 --> 00:35:52,131
Of this flight, the importance of its cargo.

385
00:35:52,633 --> 00:35:55,468
This plane will not be met by anyone.

386
00:35:56,554 --> 00:35:58,972
It will land on a runway of my designation,

387
00:35:59,056 --> 00:36:02,141
where it will remain isolated
and unapproached.

388
00:36:02,476 --> 00:36:07,063
That will conclude my interest in this
aircraft and your responsibility for it.

389
00:36:07,147 --> 00:36:12,944
At the same time, I want a 747 cargo
conversion fully fuelled

390
00:36:13,028 --> 00:36:15,405
and placed at my disposal.

391
00:36:15,489 --> 00:36:20,034
You have two minutes to advise inbound
aircraft to hold at their outer radio marker.

392
00:36:20,119 --> 00:36:23,162
After that, you will be able to receive only.

393
00:36:23,581 --> 00:36:28,126
Any attempt to restore your systems,
will be met by severe penalties.

394
00:36:28,210 --> 00:36:29,794
He's bluffing.

395
00:36:30,504 --> 00:36:33,923
- Damn it, you can't do this.
- I am doing this.

396
00:36:42,308 --> 00:36:46,477
I need you to punch up a code 15.
I got an idea, and I need your help.

397
00:36:47,021 --> 00:36:51,274
If Esperanza gets to a country with
no extradition treaties, we're fucked.

398
00:36:51,358 --> 00:36:54,360
They're talking to us on our system.
They gotta be close.

399
00:36:54,445 --> 00:36:58,031
- My men will tear this airport apart.
- Just in the nick of time.

400
00:36:58,157 --> 00:37:01,159
I got a first-class unit, SWAT team and all.

401
00:37:01,243 --> 00:37:03,202
We don't need
Monday morning quarterbacks.

402
00:37:03,287 --> 00:37:08,333
My wife's on one of the planes they're
fucking with! So I'm on the playing field.

403
00:37:08,417 --> 00:37:11,586
If you'd have moved before,
we wouldn't be deep in shit.

404
00:37:11,670 --> 00:37:13,838
That's it. Security. You're outta here.

405
00:37:13,922 --> 00:37:16,966
Mr Trudeau, there are FAA regulations

406
00:37:17,051 --> 00:37:19,969
regarding unauthorised personnel
in the control tower!

407
00:37:20,054 --> 00:37:22,096
We just have to find a way to transmit.

408
00:37:22,181 --> 00:37:24,807
Run down to Radio Shack
for a transmitter.

409
00:37:24,892 --> 00:37:27,560
We have one - the terminal wing
they're building.

410
00:37:27,686 --> 00:37:30,688
20 airlines when it's done,
all with reservation computers

411
00:37:30,773 --> 00:37:32,815
in a nice antenna arrangement.

412
00:37:32,900 --> 00:37:36,778
- See Mr McClane out.
- You got no business being up here.

413
00:37:36,862 --> 00:37:39,572
Everything we need
is by the annexe skywalk,

414
00:37:39,698 --> 00:37:42,158
just sitting there, waiting to go on line.

415
00:37:42,242 --> 00:37:45,244
Goddamn it, Trudeau,
you're dealing with pros.

416
00:37:45,329 --> 00:37:47,413
You can't fuck with these people.

417
00:37:47,539 --> 00:37:51,292
Sam Coleman. WNTW News.
There are a lot of rumours flying around...

418
00:37:51,377 --> 00:37:53,878
No way, lady. Hell, no.

419
00:37:53,962 --> 00:37:56,130
This is off limits, Coleman.

420
00:37:57,758 --> 00:38:00,677
Anything you can think of,
they'll think of, too!

421
00:38:00,761 --> 00:38:04,347
- Get your fucking hands off me.
- Just get 'em out of here.

422
00:38:05,891 --> 00:38:08,851
- Lobby security, come in.
- Tomalson here.

423
00:38:08,936 --> 00:38:12,772
This is Captain Lorenzo. We've two
unauthorised personnel in the tower.

424
00:38:12,898 --> 00:38:15,817
Get your thumb out of your ass.
Get 'em out of the elevator,

425
00:38:15,901 --> 00:38:18,444
or you'll get a pink slip for Christmas.

426
00:38:18,529 --> 00:38:20,196
10-4. Let's go.

427
00:38:21,615 --> 00:38:23,116
Goddamn!

428
00:38:23,951 --> 00:38:27,704
- Anything who can think of?
- Shit. Hang on over there.

429
00:38:27,788 --> 00:38:30,373
- What for?
- Just hang on!

430
00:38:31,291 --> 00:38:34,627
Big drug dealer on his way to prison.
Gunfight at airport.

431
00:38:34,712 --> 00:38:38,881
Every controller in the coffee shop
getting beeped, and you rocking the boat.

432
00:38:38,966 --> 00:38:43,803
- Connection? Come on, just a few words.
- OK, just a few words. Fuck off.

433
00:38:43,887 --> 00:38:47,306
Thanks, but I already got
that from Colonel Stuart.

434
00:38:48,308 --> 00:38:52,562
Stuart. The guy that got canned
by Congress. That's who he was.

435
00:38:52,646 --> 00:38:55,064
Who he who? What?

436
00:38:55,149 --> 00:38:57,483
It's OK, I've done this before.

437
00:39:08,495 --> 00:39:10,413
- Hey.
- Hi.

438
00:39:10,497 --> 00:39:13,833
- Where's the other one?
- Claustrophobic, I guess.

439
00:39:15,502 --> 00:39:18,629
It's a VHF system,
but the planes are so close, it's OK.

440
00:39:18,714 --> 00:39:22,550
I can rig our frequency in 30 minutes,
and wire in a crossover.

441
00:39:22,634 --> 00:39:26,763
- You wouldn't know the difference.
- Get what you need. Borrow. Steal. Kill.

442
00:39:26,847 --> 00:39:29,015
I want my SWAT team
to go with him as cover.

443
00:39:29,141 --> 00:39:32,351
Whatever we can think of,
they can think of, too.

444
00:39:38,025 --> 00:39:40,276
Man, I can't fucking believe this.

445
00:39:40,360 --> 00:39:43,196
Another basement. Another elevator.

446
00:39:43,280 --> 00:39:46,574
How can the same shit happen
to the same guy twice?

447
00:40:07,721 --> 00:40:09,388
What the fuck?

448
00:40:44,591 --> 00:40:46,092
Who are you?

449
00:40:47,928 --> 00:40:50,137
I'm Marvin.

450
00:40:51,598 --> 00:40:54,517
I thought you was trying
to steal my records.

451
00:40:54,601 --> 00:40:56,477
I'm just the janitor.

452
00:41:03,610 --> 00:41:07,530
This is Dulles approach to all aircraft
holding at Potomac vortex.

453
00:41:07,614 --> 00:41:10,283
We are experiencing
some technical problems.

454
00:41:10,367 --> 00:41:13,119
Weather conditions,
which have deteriorated,

455
00:41:13,203 --> 00:41:17,123
have now been complicated
by an unforeseen human factor.

456
00:41:18,417 --> 00:41:23,212
This has affected all of our electronic
equipment and their redundant backups.

457
00:41:23,714 --> 00:41:26,883
As a result, our nav
and approach systems are down.

458
00:41:26,967 --> 00:41:29,844
We expect to lose voice in another minute.

459
00:41:30,262 --> 00:41:35,474
Continue holding at the outer marker as
directed, and wait for further instructions.

460
00:41:36,268 --> 00:41:39,270
As soon as we're back on line,
we'll expedite your landings

461
00:41:39,354 --> 00:41:41,314
on a fuel-emergency basis.

462
00:41:43,108 --> 00:41:44,483
Good luck.

463
00:41:46,904 --> 00:41:48,362
God bless.

464
00:41:54,077 --> 00:41:55,328
Change the boards.

465
00:42:25,525 --> 00:42:28,319
- The skywalk annexe.
- No! The annexe skywalk.

466
00:42:28,403 --> 00:42:31,948
It's the last thing I heard
before they kicked me out.

467
00:42:32,032 --> 00:42:34,200
Let me see here.

468
00:42:34,326 --> 00:42:36,827
This must be it right there. See?

469
00:42:37,412 --> 00:42:42,291
That's the raised platform and there's
the new terminal. There's your skywalk.

470
00:42:42,668 --> 00:42:46,087
Goddamn bottleneck.
Nice place for an ambush.

471
00:42:48,173 --> 00:42:49,924
What's the fastest way
you can get me out to that spot?

472
00:42:53,553 --> 00:42:56,263
This kind of thing wasn't
in my job description.

473
00:42:56,348 --> 00:43:00,476
- Mr Barnes, we'll watch your back.
- Yeah? Who watches yours?

474
00:43:12,072 --> 00:43:13,990
Main ventilation duct.

475
00:43:14,282 --> 00:43:18,244
Ventilation duct... and bingo.

476
00:43:18,704 --> 00:43:22,999
Just once, I'd like
a regular, normal Christmas.

477
00:43:25,043 --> 00:43:28,379
Eggnog, a fucking Christmas tree,

478
00:43:30,090 --> 00:43:31,716
a little turkey.

479
00:43:33,051 --> 00:43:37,263
But, no. I gotta crawl around
in this motherfuckin' tin can.

480
00:43:42,436 --> 00:43:45,271
We're in the annexe skywalk.
I can see the array.

481
00:43:45,397 --> 00:43:49,942
I'll give you a call for a protocol test
when it's hot. That's all for now.

482
00:43:50,027 --> 00:43:54,613
Sergeant, we need more equipment.
I'd like to send one of your guys for it.

483
00:43:59,578 --> 00:44:02,872
- What the hell's going on?
- Put that back on!

484
00:44:05,625 --> 00:44:10,046
- Hey, asshole, what do I look like to you?
- A sitting duck.

485
00:44:14,801 --> 00:44:16,302
Shit!

486
00:44:18,138 --> 00:44:20,639
Damn it. I hate it when I'm right.

487
00:46:07,330 --> 00:46:08,914
Stay down!

488
00:46:23,096 --> 00:46:24,430
Fuck.

489
00:46:55,921 --> 00:46:57,796
Fucking son of a bitch.

490
00:47:14,439 --> 00:47:15,773
Shit.

491
00:47:26,159 --> 00:47:28,702
I'm gonna kick your fuckin' ass.

492
00:48:02,112 --> 00:48:04,822
- Jeez.
- You all right?

493
00:48:05,615 --> 00:48:09,618
Yeah. But the antenna array,
I gotta get to it and set it up.

494
00:48:14,040 --> 00:48:15,624
Get down!

495
00:48:34,686 --> 00:48:36,061
Goddamn.

496
00:48:39,024 --> 00:48:40,357
Bait.

497
00:48:42,402 --> 00:48:43,902
Jerk us off.

498
00:48:45,238 --> 00:48:47,865
Make Lorenzo sacrifice his best men.

499
00:48:51,661 --> 00:48:53,704
Make you waste your time.

500
00:48:57,083 --> 00:48:58,584
Time we don't have.

501
00:49:13,183 --> 00:49:15,684
I think you're closer than 50 yards.

502
00:49:15,769 --> 00:49:18,937
So's that airplane. Practically.

503
00:49:19,022 --> 00:49:23,317
Yeah. There's quite a few of them.
It looks like a regular traffic jam.

504
00:49:23,401 --> 00:49:25,861
There's nothing regular about it.

505
00:49:26,529 --> 00:49:28,364
See? You're intrigued.

506
00:49:28,448 --> 00:49:31,450
That's my gift, Mrs McClane.
I notice things.

507
00:49:31,534 --> 00:49:35,704
Things other people wouldn't see.
That's how I make people curious.

508
00:49:36,289 --> 00:49:38,624
Don't you mean nauseous?

509
00:49:38,708 --> 00:49:42,419
The people have a right to know
everything about everybody.

510
00:49:42,837 --> 00:49:44,380
You got in the way of that.

511
00:49:44,464 --> 00:49:46,924
Listen, buster.
You endangered my children.

512
00:49:47,008 --> 00:49:50,719
You didn't do it
for anything as noble as "the people".

513
00:49:50,804 --> 00:49:52,346
The only time you see the people

514
00:49:52,430 --> 00:49:55,891
is when you look down to see
what you're stepping on.

515
00:49:59,979 --> 00:50:04,066
Me? I'll live,
but Lorenzo's SWAT team is dead

516
00:50:04,567 --> 00:50:06,819
and the antenna array is gone.

517
00:50:07,404 --> 00:50:09,154
Didn't you see it?

518
00:50:10,782 --> 00:50:13,158
Start looking for a new miracle.

519
00:50:17,622 --> 00:50:20,541
Hold for a second. Something's going on.

520
00:50:22,502 --> 00:50:25,421
I say again, annexe team, give us a sit rep.

521
00:50:27,006 --> 00:50:29,466
Annexe team, come in. Do you copy?

522
00:50:31,010 --> 00:50:34,555
It's got a scrambler on it.
Can you do anything with it?

523
00:50:36,307 --> 00:50:39,935
No. This scramble mode
must activate on this code panel.

524
00:50:40,019 --> 00:50:44,273
Even if we scan their frequency,
we can't listen in. These guys are pros.

525
00:50:44,357 --> 00:50:47,276
So are you. Break the code.
I wanna hear these bastards.

526
00:50:47,360 --> 00:50:50,779
This is a ten-digit control panel.
Six-digit read-out.

527
00:50:50,864 --> 00:50:53,449
Hell, there could be
a million combinations.

528
00:50:53,533 --> 00:50:57,536
Next time you kill one of these guys,
get him to enter the code first.

529
00:51:00,206 --> 00:51:05,461
Sir, we monitored a call from their chief
engineer. We took out their SWAT team.

530
00:51:05,545 --> 00:51:08,589
So they did go for the antenna array.
We're on schedule.

531
00:51:08,673 --> 00:51:11,425
Losing our team wasn't part of the plan.

532
00:51:18,057 --> 00:51:21,226
Attention, Dulles control tower.

533
00:51:21,728 --> 00:51:23,979
Mr Trudeau, I know you're listening.

534
00:51:24,063 --> 00:51:27,691
- Unfortunately, you're not obeying.
- Try me face to face.

535
00:51:27,775 --> 00:51:30,068
You were warned
not to restore your systems.

536
00:51:30,153 --> 00:51:33,906
You've wasted lives and precious time
on a futile and obvious target.

537
00:51:34,741 --> 00:51:36,742
Now you're gonna pay the penalty.

538
00:51:36,826 --> 00:51:40,913
I got five dead officers, Colonel Stuart.
Isn't that penalty enough?

539
00:51:41,247 --> 00:51:44,416
McClane, keep out of this.
You've been a pain...

540
00:51:46,044 --> 00:51:49,755
McClane. John McClane.

541
00:51:50,757 --> 00:51:54,760
The policeman hero who saved
the Nakatomi hostages.

542
00:51:54,886 --> 00:51:56,678
I read about you in People magazine.

543
00:51:56,763 --> 00:51:59,264
You seemed out of
your league on Nightline.

544
00:51:59,349 --> 00:52:04,186
Colonel, blow me. How much drug money
is Esperanza paying you to turn traitor?

545
00:52:04,270 --> 00:52:09,274
Cardinal Richelieu said it best:
"Treason is merely a matter of dates."

546
00:52:09,943 --> 00:52:14,613
This country's got to learn it can't keep
cutting the legs off of men like Esperanza.

547
00:52:14,697 --> 00:52:18,617
Men who have the guts to stand up
against communist aggression.

548
00:52:19,869 --> 00:52:24,623
Lesson one starts with killing policemen?
What's lesson two, the neutron bomb?

549
00:52:26,459 --> 00:52:29,503
No. I think we can find something
in-between.

550
00:52:31,714 --> 00:52:33,215
Watch this.

551
00:52:34,175 --> 00:52:37,302
Give me a flight number.
One that's low on fuel.

552
00:52:38,638 --> 00:52:42,891
Windsor 114. Transatlantic from London.
Fuel tank's dry as a martini.

553
00:52:43,810 --> 00:52:50,482
Activate the lLS landing system, but
recalibrate sea level... minus 200 feet.

554
00:53:15,174 --> 00:53:19,177
Jesus. They've reset
ground level, minus 200 feet.

555
00:53:19,929 --> 00:53:24,182
Windsor flight 114. This is
Dulles approach. Do you copy?

556
00:53:25,393 --> 00:53:28,895
Dulles approach, this is Windsor 114.
Where the devil have you been?

557
00:53:28,980 --> 00:53:33,066
Windsor 114.
We've been right here all along, old buddy.

558
00:53:33,526 --> 00:53:36,236
Our systems only came back on line
just now.

559
00:53:37,238 --> 00:53:42,534
Windsor 114, you are cleared
for lLS approach, runway two-niner.

560
00:53:43,077 --> 00:53:47,331
- Contact Dulles at the outer marker.
- Jesus Christ, he's gonna crash the plane.

561
00:53:47,415 --> 00:53:52,461
Roger, approach, and about time. I've got
230 people up here flying on petrol fumes.

562
00:53:52,962 --> 00:53:55,464
Roger, 114. Understand. Calibrate Dulles...

563
00:53:55,548 --> 00:53:58,258
- Jesus.
- They'll fly right into the concrete.

564
00:53:58,343 --> 00:53:59,885
Son of a bitch!

565
00:54:00,553 --> 00:54:04,056
- Why are they listening to him?
- It's our frequency.

566
00:54:04,724 --> 00:54:05,974
Damn.

567
00:54:06,059 --> 00:54:08,143
- Barnes.
- This is Dulles tower.

568
00:54:08,227 --> 00:54:10,312
We have radar contact...

569
00:54:10,980 --> 00:54:12,814
Give me your coat.

570
00:54:13,691 --> 00:54:17,611
- What are you gonna do?
- Whatever I can.

571
00:54:21,449 --> 00:54:24,993
Ladies and gentlemen,
we've started our descent.

572
00:54:25,078 --> 00:54:28,830
Sorry for the inconvenience,
but we'll all be on the ground shortly.

573
00:54:28,915 --> 00:54:31,249
Please keep your seat belts on.

574
00:54:32,085 --> 00:54:36,505
We've made arrangements for your
next flight, so you won't miss it.

575
00:54:36,589 --> 00:54:38,548
In your seat, please.

576
00:54:42,303 --> 00:54:45,972
We're just like British Rail, love.
We may be late, but we get you there.

577
00:54:46,057 --> 00:54:47,474
Don't worry.

578
00:55:04,283 --> 00:55:06,076
Good luck, McClane!

579
00:55:28,808 --> 00:55:32,310
Dulles, this is Windsor 114
inside the outer marker.

580
00:55:32,979 --> 00:55:35,856
Roger, 114. This is Dulles tower.

581
00:55:35,940 --> 00:55:38,066
We have radar contact
and show you on lLS.

582
00:55:38,151 --> 00:55:40,986
You're in the glide path and looking good.

583
00:55:50,288 --> 00:55:52,497
There's somebody out there!

584
00:55:56,502 --> 00:55:59,337
It's McClane. Christ.

585
00:56:03,926 --> 00:56:05,594
Approach flaps.

586
00:56:07,638 --> 00:56:09,389
Approach speed 140.

587
00:56:10,975 --> 00:56:12,392
130.

588
00:56:13,060 --> 00:56:16,772
- Altitude 1,000 feet.
- 800, guys. You're only at 800 feet.

589
00:56:16,856 --> 00:56:20,734
Fire and rescue. Roll everything
onto runway two-niner.

590
00:56:21,527 --> 00:56:25,280
Ref speed plus 20. 600 feet.

591
00:56:26,699 --> 00:56:31,703
Looking good, Windsor. Watch it.
30-knot crosswinds and the runway is icy.

592
00:56:32,455 --> 00:56:34,498
Attaboy. We've gotcha.

593
00:56:35,625 --> 00:56:37,209
We've gotcha.

594
00:56:50,431 --> 00:56:51,932
Pull it up!

595
00:56:52,767 --> 00:56:54,059
Jesus!

596
00:57:08,741 --> 00:57:10,242
We've gotcha.

597
00:57:37,270 --> 00:57:38,520
God.

598
00:57:43,401 --> 00:57:44,985
Motherfucker.

599
00:58:06,632 --> 00:58:09,843
That concludes our object lesson
for this evening.

600
00:58:09,927 --> 00:58:12,345
If the 747 we requested is ready on time

601
00:58:12,430 --> 00:58:15,849
and General Esperanza's plane
arrives unmolested,

602
00:58:15,933 --> 00:58:18,101
further lessons can be avoided.

603
00:58:18,185 --> 00:58:19,477
Out.

604
00:59:05,441 --> 00:59:09,361
We got no sign of survivors.
It's a goddamn nightmare.

605
00:59:24,377 --> 00:59:27,295
Barnes! We've got to warn those planes

606
00:59:27,380 --> 00:59:31,883
there's a lunatic pretending
he's the tower. Get me on the air.

607
00:59:31,968 --> 00:59:34,135
- How?
- You figure it out!

608
00:59:34,512 --> 00:59:36,388
Here's the manifest.

609
00:59:56,492 --> 00:59:58,910
I know how you must feel.

610
01:00:04,083 --> 01:00:06,751
I wanted to help those people tonight.

611
01:00:08,045 --> 01:00:10,338
I was pretty goddamn useless.

612
01:00:14,343 --> 01:00:19,139
We called the government for help.
They're gonna send in a Special army unit.

613
01:00:20,599 --> 01:00:22,684
A counterterrorist team.

614
01:00:30,192 --> 01:00:32,027
Your wife's plane...

615
01:00:33,070 --> 01:00:36,740
They're still broadcasting,
even though we can't answer.

616
01:00:38,826 --> 01:00:41,786
They're gonna run out of fuel
in 90 minutes.

617
01:00:53,507 --> 01:00:56,009
Listen, Dick. That is your name?

618
01:00:56,761 --> 01:01:02,849
Dick. if you're gonna continue to get
this close, could you switch aftershaves?

619
01:01:04,560 --> 01:01:06,144
Anything else?

620
01:01:06,812 --> 01:01:09,314
Stronger mouthwash might be nice.

621
01:01:09,899 --> 01:01:12,650
Sam Coleman is reporting
live from the accident.

622
01:01:12,735 --> 01:01:16,821
Colonel, they've done
everything we've anticipated... so far.

623
01:01:16,947 --> 01:01:19,949
But still there has been no official word.

624
01:01:20,034 --> 01:01:24,412
Despite the fact that only one runway
has been closed due to the tragedy,

625
01:01:24,497 --> 01:01:29,334
several dozen airliners are visible,
endlessly circling the field.

626
01:01:29,418 --> 01:01:32,587
Other reports say there
had been trouble in the tower,

627
01:01:32,671 --> 01:01:34,923
and that may have contributed to it.

628
01:01:35,007 --> 01:01:37,509
With weather conditions worsening,

629
01:01:37,593 --> 01:01:40,804
the problem here and in
the sky above us will grow.

630
01:01:40,888 --> 01:01:44,182
I'm Samantha Coleman
at Dulles International Airport.

631
01:01:51,649 --> 01:01:54,609
- Victor.
- Yeah, what's up?

632
01:01:54,693 --> 01:01:57,570
Did you pack the radio mikes
from the shoot or are they here?

633
01:01:57,655 --> 01:02:00,156
I wouldn't let those assholes check 'em in!

634
01:02:00,241 --> 01:02:01,616
I love you.

635
01:02:01,700 --> 01:02:03,952
Give me one of the receivers.

636
01:02:08,040 --> 01:02:10,917
Can you tune into the cockpit frequency?

637
01:02:11,377 --> 01:02:14,379
- Yeah. Why?
- I wanna hear what's going on.

638
01:02:17,007 --> 01:02:19,509
Should be right here on our band.

639
01:02:20,344 --> 01:02:22,887
- Nothing.
- You said it would work. Is it working?

640
01:02:22,972 --> 01:02:27,058
It is working, but all I'm getting
is some kind of airport beacon.

641
01:02:27,476 --> 01:02:30,478
It's weird. it's like the tower isn't there.

642
01:02:33,482 --> 01:02:35,233
Stay on it.

643
01:02:36,402 --> 01:02:39,237
Let me know
when there is something there.

644
01:03:18,110 --> 01:03:20,486
- Major Grant.
- Rollins, Department of Justice.

645
01:03:20,571 --> 01:03:22,614
Trudeau, Chief of Air Operations.

646
01:03:22,740 --> 01:03:26,868
Lorenzo, Terminal Police.
You want something, you got it.

647
01:03:26,952 --> 01:03:29,871
This is it? One fucking platoon?

648
01:03:29,955 --> 01:03:33,374
- One crisis, one platoon. Who are you?
- John McClane.

649
01:03:33,459 --> 01:03:37,754
- You showed some balls out there.
- Yeah.

650
01:03:37,838 --> 01:03:41,716
Now show some good sense.
Let the pros handle this.

651
01:03:41,800 --> 01:03:44,886
Looks like the pros
are on the wrong team tonight.

652
01:03:44,970 --> 01:03:48,306
- Isn't Colonel Stuart one of your men?
- Not any more.

653
01:03:48,390 --> 01:03:52,310
We're here to take Colonel Stuart down.
And we will take him down.

654
01:03:52,394 --> 01:03:56,064
I served with him.
I taught him everything he knows.

655
01:03:56,148 --> 01:03:59,317
Maybe he's learned
a few more things since then.

656
01:04:01,487 --> 01:04:05,240
Let's hustle. The command post will be
set up in the airport police station.

657
01:04:05,324 --> 01:04:08,076
I wanna be tied in to the tower
in 15 minutes.

658
01:04:08,160 --> 01:04:09,994
Let's do it!

659
01:04:15,626 --> 01:04:18,002
Things just get better or worse?

660
01:04:21,924 --> 01:04:25,927
- Lights. Big, portable lights.
- We set up the field, and then we...

661
01:04:26,011 --> 01:04:27,637
Wait for those lunatics to shoot 'em out?

662
01:04:27,721 --> 01:04:30,515
Where do we get the lights?
From Batman?

663
01:04:30,599 --> 01:04:35,061
- What about the air phone idea?
- 18 planes are up there. Five have phones.

664
01:04:35,145 --> 01:04:37,605
We got through to three.
We're trying the others.

665
01:04:37,690 --> 01:04:39,691
That's 13 accidents waiting to happen.

666
01:04:39,775 --> 01:04:41,693
- Are they still bucking headwinds?
- I just checked the weather.

667
01:04:41,777 --> 01:04:44,112
Headwinds are slamming everybody
over the outer marker.

668
01:04:44,196 --> 01:04:46,322
The planes with enough fuel
have been shunted to Atlanta,

669
01:04:46,407 --> 01:04:47,407
Memphis and Nashville.

670
01:04:48,867 --> 01:04:51,202
Outer marker. Damn!

671
01:04:52,329 --> 01:04:53,997
The outer marker!

672
01:04:54,665 --> 01:04:59,002
It's a beacon. it sends out this "beep
beep beep" so they know they're over it.

673
01:04:59,086 --> 01:05:02,046
- So?
- Who says that signal has to just beep?

674
01:05:02,131 --> 01:05:05,967
Right. Switch the frequency from
the tower to the one in the beacon.

675
01:05:06,051 --> 01:05:07,385
Pump up the wattage.

676
01:05:07,469 --> 01:05:12,140
We can talk to our planes, and those
bastards who did this will never know!

677
01:05:14,059 --> 01:05:17,145
Traced the signal.
Found it in the luggage area.

678
01:05:17,229 --> 01:05:19,981
They've been tapped into
your tower chatter all night.

679
01:05:20,065 --> 01:05:22,608
Punks stealing luggage, Carmine?

680
01:05:25,821 --> 01:05:28,489
- How you doin', Telford?
- No good.

681
01:05:28,574 --> 01:05:31,826
I called Lang. They'll have
a portable decoder here in two hours.

682
01:05:31,910 --> 01:05:35,830
- My wife doesn't have two hours.
- I was put on Grant's team yesterday.

683
01:05:35,914 --> 01:05:38,374
The regular guy got appendicitis.

684
01:05:38,876 --> 01:05:42,337
Word is, nobody's better
at this than Major Grant.

685
01:05:42,421 --> 01:05:44,589
Except maybe Colonel Stuart.

686
01:05:46,091 --> 01:05:49,010
I wanna hear about
the plane those bastards asked for.

687
01:05:49,094 --> 01:05:52,847
Then I'll fill you in on my orders.
Pilots' briefing room - now!

688
01:05:52,931 --> 01:05:55,933
- Keep working.
- Albertson. With me!

689
01:06:00,773 --> 01:06:02,315
No civilians.

690
01:06:13,452 --> 01:06:16,079
- What the fuck...
- What is it?

691
01:06:17,456 --> 01:06:21,084
The outer marker beeper isn't beeping.
It's talking.

692
01:06:21,919 --> 01:06:26,381
All aircraft in Dulles landing pattern.
This is chief engineer, Leslie Barnes.

693
01:06:26,673 --> 01:06:29,842
I have been authorised to brief you in full.

694
01:06:29,927 --> 01:06:33,471
At this time, this is the only
channel available to us.

695
01:06:34,306 --> 01:06:38,559
Here is the situation.
Approximately two hours ago...

696
01:06:42,231 --> 01:06:45,525
- Get a load of this.
- ..claiming to be from our tower

697
01:06:45,609 --> 01:06:48,903
unless you hear
your flight recorder access code.

698
01:06:48,987 --> 01:06:51,906
- The terrorists have got all...
- Holy shit! Get this on tape.

699
01:06:51,990 --> 01:06:54,742
...control of everything except this channel.

700
01:06:54,827 --> 01:06:57,161
Give us a second here, please.

701
01:06:59,456 --> 01:07:04,669
Do not attempt to reply on your
own frequencies to this broadcast.

702
01:07:05,170 --> 01:07:07,255
They have already caused one crash

703
01:07:07,339 --> 01:07:10,258
- by impersonating our tower.
- Jesus.

704
01:07:20,686 --> 01:07:25,356
Repeat. The terrorists have cut off
the two systems that allow you to land,

705
01:07:25,441 --> 01:07:29,777
field lights for a visual landing
and the ILS for an instrument.

706
01:07:29,862 --> 01:07:34,198
A Special US army unit is here,
preparing to take out the terrorists.

707
01:07:34,283 --> 01:07:35,867
My God.

708
01:07:37,619 --> 01:07:41,956
- Hey, you interested in a nice coat?
- It never looked good on me anyway.

709
01:07:42,040 --> 01:07:45,084
You gotta get me up
to the pilots' briefing room.

710
01:07:45,169 --> 01:07:48,713
I gotta hear what they're saying.
Which map gets me in there?

711
01:07:48,797 --> 01:07:50,715
- Don't touch it.
- Find the map.

712
01:07:50,799 --> 01:07:54,093
I'll find it. You'll mess up
my whole damn filing system.

713
01:07:54,178 --> 01:07:57,472
Pilots' briefing room,
I think that's in the main terminal.

714
01:07:57,556 --> 01:08:01,100
So would that be under P
for "pilots' briefing room"?

715
01:08:01,185 --> 01:08:05,062
- Now, Marvin!
- Or maybe under M for "miscellaneous".

716
01:08:10,194 --> 01:08:12,445
Request permission to reduce sentry duty
to 30-minute rotation.

717
01:08:14,281 --> 01:08:16,407
My men are getting cold and antsy. Over.

718
01:08:16,492 --> 01:08:20,870
This is Colonel Stuart. Have the men not
on watch assemble for a briefing. Over.

719
01:08:20,954 --> 01:08:21,996
Roger, Colonel. Over and out.

720
01:08:22,080 --> 01:08:23,831
What's the matter?

721
01:08:26,293 --> 01:08:29,587
Gentlemen, tonight the pattern ends.

722
01:08:31,006 --> 01:08:35,301
The dominoes will fall no more
and the ramparts will remain upright.

723
01:08:35,385 --> 01:08:38,888
Sir, General Esperanza's plane
just came on the scope.

724
01:08:45,562 --> 01:08:49,065
Attention, Dulles tower.
We will be lighting up a runway.

725
01:08:49,149 --> 01:08:52,902
Do not, repeat,
do not attempt to land any planes.

726
01:08:52,986 --> 01:08:55,446
Remember, we're monitoring you.

727
01:08:58,450 --> 01:09:01,994
- What do we do?
- Obey.

728
01:09:08,627 --> 01:09:13,673
Dulles tower to Foxtrot Michael One.

729
01:09:13,757 --> 01:09:17,510
This is Foxtrot Michael One, Dulles.
We read you. Over.

730
01:09:17,594 --> 01:09:22,640
Foxtrot Michael One, you are
to come in on runway 1 - 5.

731
01:09:36,905 --> 01:09:40,908
I found it on the floor, by the coat,
next to the luggage belt.

732
01:09:40,993 --> 01:09:43,536
What the hell you so excited for?

733
01:09:43,620 --> 01:09:46,831
- The code's still punched into this one.
- You like it.

734
01:09:46,915 --> 01:09:49,917
How about you give me 20 bucks for it?

735
01:09:50,002 --> 01:09:54,505
- How about I let you live?
- The man knows how to bargain.

736
01:09:55,257 --> 01:09:57,592
This is contrary to our instructions.

737
01:09:57,676 --> 01:10:00,052
We are to land at runway 1 -0,

738
01:10:00,137 --> 01:10:04,015
where we are to be met
by representatives of your Justice...

739
01:10:04,683 --> 01:10:08,978
Captain, please tell the tower
you will proceed as ordered.

740
01:10:19,948 --> 01:10:24,577
Roger, Dulles. Proceeding to runway 1 -5.

741
01:10:41,136 --> 01:10:43,804
Foxtrot Michael One. Come in, please.

742
01:10:44,014 --> 01:10:47,141
What are you gonna do now?
Are you gonna shoot me?

743
01:10:47,225 --> 01:10:48,684
So who will fly the plane?

744
01:10:48,769 --> 01:10:51,854
Don't worry about it. it's not your problem.

745
01:10:58,403 --> 01:10:59,904
Michael One. Do you copy?

746
01:11:04,576 --> 01:11:06,952
Foxtrot Michael One, come in.

747
01:11:16,129 --> 01:11:18,714
Eagle Nest. This is Falcon. Mayday.

748
01:11:23,762 --> 01:11:25,179
Go ahead, Falcon.

749
01:11:25,263 --> 01:11:28,432
I've lost cabin pressure.
Near-zero visibility.

750
01:11:29,017 --> 01:11:33,479
I must drop out of this weather and land
now, on the first accessible runway.

751
01:11:33,563 --> 01:11:38,067
Repeat. I've lost cabin pressure.
Near-zero visibility.

752
01:11:38,151 --> 01:11:39,944
I must drop out of the storm.

753
01:11:40,028 --> 01:11:44,240
I can land, but I must land now,
on the first outgoing runway.

754
01:11:44,741 --> 01:11:47,910
Repeat. I cannot circle around
to runway 1-5.

755
01:11:52,374 --> 01:11:54,333
I'll make you a deal.

756
01:11:54,418 --> 01:11:57,378
Show me out to those runways
and I'll get you a liner for that coat.

757
01:11:57,462 --> 01:12:01,006
Repeat. I cannot circle around
to runway 1 -5.

758
01:12:01,091 --> 01:12:02,299
Shit!

759
01:12:02,426 --> 01:12:04,093
Stand by, Falcon.

760
01:12:05,971 --> 01:12:08,055
He's coming in from the ocean, sir.

761
01:12:10,434 --> 01:12:12,893
A bullet damaged my instruments.

762
01:12:12,978 --> 01:12:17,231
I'm not sure of my bearings and I must
make a visual landing immediately.

763
01:12:17,315 --> 01:12:20,025
- Do you copy, Eagle Nest?
- Roger, Falcon.

764
01:12:20,110 --> 01:12:22,445
That would be 2-5 right.

765
01:12:24,698 --> 01:12:26,782
Make up your fucking mind.

766
01:12:27,659 --> 01:12:30,661
We are just up to our ass
in terrorists again, John.

767
01:12:30,746 --> 01:12:32,455
2-5 left.

768
01:12:33,165 --> 01:12:34,540
2-5 right.

769
01:12:36,126 --> 01:12:38,502
I gotta quit smoking cigarettes.

770
01:12:38,628 --> 01:12:41,255
Thank you for telling me, Eagle Nest.

771
01:12:41,339 --> 01:12:45,050
But if you could show it to me as well,
I would be grateful.

772
01:12:55,979 --> 01:12:59,398
I see the lights.
They are directly in front of me.

773
01:13:00,525 --> 01:13:03,527
Reducing airspeed. Approaching runway.

774
01:13:03,612 --> 01:13:06,197
- Wish me luck.
- Roger, Falcon.

775
01:13:08,450 --> 01:13:10,618
We copy. We'll have you in five minutes.

776
01:13:10,702 --> 01:13:14,246
That's right, asshole.
We'll have you in five minutes.

777
01:13:37,896 --> 01:13:41,065
I see your lights. ETA 90 seconds.

778
01:13:50,158 --> 01:13:52,243
Come to papa, scumbag.

779
01:14:48,133 --> 01:14:49,341
Shit!

780
01:15:49,736 --> 01:15:51,070
Freedom.

781
01:15:52,197 --> 01:15:53,572
Not yet.

782
01:15:55,408 --> 01:15:58,869
You should stay in your seat until
the plane reaches the terminal.

783
01:15:58,954 --> 01:16:01,205
No frequent-flier mileage for you.

784
01:16:01,289 --> 01:16:03,374
- Who are you?
- A cop.

785
01:16:03,458 --> 01:16:05,501
- A cop?
- Yeah, one of the good guys.

786
01:16:05,585 --> 01:16:10,589
And you're a bad guy. Now I've got your
sorry ass, I'm gonna trade it for my wife.

787
01:16:19,349 --> 01:16:20,766
Sit down!

788
01:16:31,695 --> 01:16:33,904
- Where'd he go?
- In there.

789
01:16:43,456 --> 01:16:44,665
I don't believe this.

790
01:16:44,749 --> 01:16:48,419
Two months of planning, and
you can't anticipate one pendejo of a cop.

791
01:16:48,503 --> 01:16:51,547
- Come on, General.
- Where is Colonel Stuart?

792
01:16:55,218 --> 01:16:57,511
- General!
- I'm all right.

793
01:16:57,595 --> 01:17:01,390
He said he was a policeman.
I thought you had this place secured.

794
01:17:01,474 --> 01:17:04,601
- He went in the cockpit.
- He's going to hell.

795
01:17:07,897 --> 01:17:10,065
I assume it's you, McClane.

796
01:17:10,775 --> 01:17:13,360
You're quite a little soldier.

797
01:17:13,445 --> 01:17:16,280
You can consider this a military funeral!

798
01:17:41,639 --> 01:17:44,433
- How many grenades we got?
- Three each!

799
01:17:44,726 --> 01:17:46,060
Use 'em!

800
01:17:56,654 --> 01:17:57,988
Fuck.

801
01:18:12,087 --> 01:18:13,337
Go!

802
01:18:41,116 --> 01:18:42,825
You lucky fuck.

803
01:18:45,829 --> 01:18:49,248
- Fire trucks, sir.
- Fall back to the church. Now!

804
01:19:12,021 --> 01:19:14,148
Where's the fuckin' door?

805
01:19:28,913 --> 01:19:32,624
They're getting a little nervous back there.
In fact, so am I.

806
01:19:32,709 --> 01:19:36,712
We're over Washington. See if you
can get any TV to settle 'em down.

807
01:19:36,796 --> 01:19:38,714
Works for me. I'll...

808
01:20:02,447 --> 01:20:06,450
Writing your acceptance speech
for the video sleaze awards?

809
01:20:06,534 --> 01:20:09,286
- Try Pulitzer.
- While waiting to land,

810
01:20:09,370 --> 01:20:14,166
we are turning on local Washington TV.
The sound is on channel three.

811
01:20:32,727 --> 01:20:36,480
Please, sir, we may land at any moment.
If you'll take your seat...

812
01:20:36,606 --> 01:20:39,983
- I'm gonna be sick.
- Sir, the seat-belt light is on.

813
01:20:45,156 --> 01:20:46,406
Moron.

814
01:20:46,491 --> 01:20:48,825
- WZDC.
- This is Richard Thornberg.

815
01:20:48,910 --> 01:20:51,578
- Put me through to Ruben.
- He's about to go live.

816
01:20:51,663 --> 01:20:55,207
- I know he is. That's why I need him.
- You'll have to hold on...

817
01:20:55,291 --> 01:20:58,669
Put me through, Celia,
or start typing your résumé.

818
01:20:59,587 --> 01:21:03,465
Esperanza's down... but he's hurt.

819
01:21:04,759 --> 01:21:09,263
He took a round in his shoulder. I got one
more of their guys. That's six they lost.

820
01:21:09,347 --> 01:21:12,516
If we knew how many they had,
we could get excited,

821
01:21:12,600 --> 01:21:16,436
but if they got 50 guys,
it's a little early to open the champagne.

822
01:21:16,521 --> 01:21:20,232
We appreciate your effort, but we
don't need a loose cannon here.

823
01:21:20,316 --> 01:21:23,610
What if they crash another plane
in retaliation for your stunt?

824
01:21:23,695 --> 01:21:26,113
They can't do that now, right, Barnes?

825
01:21:26,197 --> 01:21:29,116
And if I'd grabbed Esperanza,
this'd be over now.

826
01:21:29,200 --> 01:21:31,785
Maybe they're more creative
than you think.

827
01:21:31,869 --> 01:21:34,371
At least I'm thinking, goddamn it.

828
01:21:35,081 --> 01:21:38,959
We're here to jerk off that cocksucker
until he tries to take off. Period!

829
01:21:39,043 --> 01:21:42,713
You're the wrong guy
in the wrong place at the wrong time.

830
01:21:44,799 --> 01:21:46,633
The story of my life.

831
01:21:47,802 --> 01:21:50,721
Major. Pentagon situation room, sir.

832
01:21:50,805 --> 01:21:54,141
Pentagon. I'll take it in here.
Thank you, Telford.

833
01:21:54,225 --> 01:21:56,143
You men come with me.

834
01:21:58,813 --> 01:22:00,647
- McClane.
- Yeah, Barnes.

835
01:22:00,732 --> 01:22:02,482
You said those guys
showed up right away?

836
01:22:02,567 --> 01:22:03,525
Yeah.

837
01:22:03,609 --> 01:22:06,945
So that must mean they're
on the field or close.

838
01:22:07,030 --> 01:22:10,866
I think I know where.
Come here, let me show you something.

839
01:22:13,161 --> 01:22:17,831
These are the old plans with the
longer runways. That's 12 years ago.

840
01:22:17,915 --> 01:22:22,336
Looks like they've modified the site,
moved Tra-Con phones, lLS,

841
01:22:22,420 --> 01:22:25,630
all the underground stuff,
so they could handle drainage.

842
01:22:25,715 --> 01:22:29,009
If I'm right, all of it would run
along the airport property

843
01:22:29,093 --> 01:22:31,845
and go right past this neighbourhood.

844
01:22:42,774 --> 01:22:46,276
Somebody ought to get their ass
kicked for this mess.

845
01:22:47,111 --> 01:22:50,364
Unfortunately, there isn't anyone
we can blame for the weather.

846
01:22:50,448 --> 01:22:53,450
Yeah? What about that porker,
Willard Scott?

847
01:22:53,951 --> 01:22:58,455
I should have taken the bus. At least
they can pull over for food and gas.

848
01:22:58,539 --> 01:23:00,832
- Excuse me.
- Yes?

849
01:23:02,126 --> 01:23:07,798
I was just wondering. This flight originally
was supposed to be five and a half hours.

850
01:23:08,800 --> 01:23:11,676
Do we have enough fuel to keep circling?

851
01:23:11,761 --> 01:23:15,138
Of course. They anticipate
little problems like this.

852
01:23:33,324 --> 01:23:36,243
We looked at 12 fucking houses,
and we're nowhere.

853
01:23:36,327 --> 01:23:38,620
This is our last possibility.

854
01:23:39,247 --> 01:23:42,332
- Over here there's an old church.
- Let's go.

855
01:23:47,088 --> 01:23:48,296
Wait.

856
01:23:55,763 --> 01:23:58,098
There's the church over there.

857
01:24:05,940 --> 01:24:09,443
- Could be a sentry.
- He could just be out for a walk.

858
01:24:09,527 --> 01:24:12,529
Then why is he going over
his own footsteps?

859
01:24:14,740 --> 01:24:16,032
Come on.

860
01:24:18,035 --> 01:24:21,746
All right. Just stay here
and get ready to call the marines.

861
01:24:21,831 --> 01:24:25,959
- I thought they were the army.
- Who gives a fuck? Just be ready.

862
01:24:42,727 --> 01:24:46,354
Shit. Not now.

863
01:25:00,870 --> 01:25:02,871
Lorenzo, it's Barnes.

864
01:25:02,955 --> 01:25:05,081
Where the hell are you? Where's McClane?

865
01:25:05,166 --> 01:25:08,585
With me, at the community church,
to the west of the airport.

866
01:25:08,669 --> 01:25:11,588
Where? Goddamn it.
You crazy idiot, why didn't...

867
01:25:11,672 --> 01:25:15,091
This must be their operations base.
Shut up and get your ass here!

868
01:25:15,176 --> 01:25:16,927
Code red. Sit rep.

869
01:25:17,595 --> 01:25:20,847
We got positive lD on Stuart's location.
Let's move.

870
01:25:32,860 --> 01:25:36,613
Our escape plane will be ready
within 30 minutes, General.

871
01:25:37,865 --> 01:25:40,283
If there are no more surprises.

872
01:25:54,715 --> 01:25:57,467
Gentlemen, we have a situation here.

873
01:27:15,004 --> 01:27:16,880
They're over here.

874
01:27:29,185 --> 01:27:31,603
Jeez, you all right? You want a medic?

875
01:27:31,687 --> 01:27:34,981
What the hell you think you're doin'?
Playing John Wayne?

876
01:27:35,066 --> 01:27:37,067
How'd you like to spend the night in a cell?

877
01:27:37,151 --> 01:27:40,904
Shut the fuck up and do
something useful. Seal off the street.

878
01:27:40,988 --> 01:27:44,407
- Hey, you can't talk to me like that.
- No, Carmine?

879
01:27:44,492 --> 01:27:48,328
Sergeant, get this bureaucrat
out of Mr McClane's face - now!

880
01:27:48,412 --> 01:27:50,372
With pleasure, sir.

881
01:27:52,500 --> 01:27:55,919
Major, the men are in position, sir.

882
01:27:56,003 --> 01:27:59,005
Close up the back, then we go in.
Fire only on my order.

883
01:27:59,090 --> 01:28:00,632
Roger that, sir.

884
01:28:00,716 --> 01:28:05,095
Guess I was wrong about you.
You're not such an asshole after all.

885
01:28:05,388 --> 01:28:08,765
No, you were right.
I'm just your kind of asshole.

886
01:28:17,775 --> 01:28:20,193
Garber, sit rep!

887
01:28:20,277 --> 01:28:23,530
Army Special Forces
on three sides, closing in fast!

888
01:28:23,614 --> 01:28:26,783
- Another problem, Colonel?
- No problem, General.

889
01:28:27,368 --> 01:28:29,786
Gentlemen, you know what to do.

890
01:28:41,132 --> 01:28:43,091
- Down!
- Get down!

891
01:29:11,912 --> 01:29:14,497
General... it's time.

892
01:29:21,756 --> 01:29:23,673
Come on, let's move it.

893
01:29:38,272 --> 01:29:41,357
- They're pulling out... at the back.
- What?

894
01:29:49,408 --> 01:29:50,658
Move it!

895
01:30:00,669 --> 01:30:03,213
Albertson, your men around the back.

896
01:30:29,031 --> 01:30:31,324
This equipment could land our planes.

897
01:30:31,408 --> 01:30:34,160
Don't touch anything.
If it's booby-trapped...

898
01:30:34,245 --> 01:30:35,203
it is.

899
01:30:35,287 --> 01:30:38,498
Got one here. Looks like C-4.
The motherfucker is armed.

900
01:30:38,582 --> 01:30:40,959
Clear the area. Everybody, now!

901
01:30:44,588 --> 01:30:47,257
They booby-trapped the equipment.
Seal it off.

902
01:30:47,341 --> 01:30:48,591
Shit!

903
01:30:52,346 --> 01:30:54,097
Where the fuck is McClane?

904
01:31:43,689 --> 01:31:45,523
Miller, take him.

905
01:31:46,817 --> 01:31:48,651
I'll cover you.

906
01:32:35,366 --> 01:32:37,867
So much for the element of chance.

907
01:32:38,869 --> 01:32:40,578
Let's move out.

908
01:32:57,721 --> 01:33:00,723
I had the bastard in my sights. I know I did.

909
01:33:11,610 --> 01:33:13,611
Jesus Christ.

910
01:33:19,410 --> 01:33:21,119
Attention, Dulles tower.

911
01:33:21,203 --> 01:33:23,830
This is Colonel Stuart.
Is our plane prepared?

912
01:33:23,914 --> 01:33:28,084
It is. it's in hangar 11.
It's the most remote building we've got.

913
01:33:29,211 --> 01:33:34,382
We're on our way. Have a ground crew
there to confirm the condition of the plane.

914
01:33:35,009 --> 01:33:37,969
Do you believe the balls
on this son of a bitch?

915
01:33:38,053 --> 01:33:41,055
Colonel, you're capable
of confirming it yourself.

916
01:33:41,140 --> 01:33:44,350
Don't ask us to gift-wrap
potential hostages for you.

917
01:33:44,435 --> 01:33:47,770
- Major Grant, isn't it?
- If you remember me, Colonel,

918
01:33:47,855 --> 01:33:50,898
then you remember
I know the drill as well as you do.

919
01:33:51,734 --> 01:33:54,152
Check out your own fuckin' plane.

920
01:33:54,236 --> 01:33:58,239
We move out in five minutes.
Flak jackets for everybody.

921
01:33:58,323 --> 01:34:02,493
Body armour for the assault team.
Night scopes for the snipers.

922
01:34:02,578 --> 01:34:03,995
We go to the hangar.

923
01:34:04,079 --> 01:34:08,416
I will pull that detonator out of
Stuart's dead fuckin' hand myself.

924
01:34:09,376 --> 01:34:11,961
Lorenzo,
take all your men back to the airport.

925
01:34:12,046 --> 01:34:17,258
Seal off every exit in case they try to slip
past us to break out onto the ground.

926
01:34:17,342 --> 01:34:18,760
You got it.

927
01:34:20,804 --> 01:34:22,722
All right, here we go.

928
01:34:23,640 --> 01:34:26,059
This is nuts!
Every station has people at the airport.

929
01:34:26,143 --> 01:34:28,186
No one has heard a whisper of this!

930
01:34:28,270 --> 01:34:31,773
None of them is me.
You want proof, try this.

931
01:34:32,149 --> 01:34:34,901
Terrorists have murdered civilians

932
01:34:34,985 --> 01:34:38,154
and cut off the two systems
that allow you to land.

933
01:34:38,238 --> 01:34:41,824
A Special US army unit is here,
preparing to take out the terrorists.

934
01:34:41,909 --> 01:34:44,577
- Jesus Christ.
- I want you to go live now.

935
01:34:44,661 --> 01:34:48,414
Key me in from the files, a publicity shot.
Steal a map from weather.

936
01:34:48,499 --> 01:34:51,501
We're on it. We're cutting in five minutes.

937
01:34:51,627 --> 01:34:56,422
Tell the affiliates, if they want in, they got
three minutes to shout. Let's do this.

938
01:34:56,799 --> 01:34:58,466
Network, here I come.

939
01:35:01,678 --> 01:35:06,516
Telford, what was your chickenshit outfit
doing while we were taking Grenada?

940
01:35:08,477 --> 01:35:13,147
Grenada. Five minutes of firefight,
five weeks of surfing.

941
01:35:13,899 --> 01:35:17,819
- I wish I was with you guys for that.
- Yeah. Me too, kid.

942
01:35:18,570 --> 01:35:20,696
- Really, sir?
- Sure.

943
01:35:22,199 --> 01:35:24,700
Then we wouldn't have to do this.

944
01:35:39,466 --> 01:35:41,759
Eagle Nest, this is Hatchling.

945
01:35:42,719 --> 01:35:45,680
On schedule... and in position.

946
01:35:45,764 --> 01:35:48,224
Roger, Hatchling. We are secure here.

947
01:35:48,308 --> 01:35:52,645
You have a green light.

948
01:36:04,241 --> 01:36:07,869
Jesus, officer, where'd
you come from, Pearl Harbor?

949
01:36:13,208 --> 01:36:15,376
Let's clear it out, please.

950
01:36:19,173 --> 01:36:21,257
Five, four, three...

951
01:36:22,134 --> 01:36:25,011
This is a special bulletin
from WZDC News.

952
01:36:25,095 --> 01:36:29,640
There has been a plane crash at Dulles,
where other aircraft still circle,

953
01:36:29,725 --> 01:36:33,019
with no explanation
from airport or FAA officials.

954
01:36:33,103 --> 01:36:36,063
And now, with an exclusive WZDC report,

955
01:36:36,148 --> 01:36:39,901
here's Dick Thornberg reporting
from the skies over Washington.

956
01:36:39,985 --> 01:36:43,321
I'm one of the people circling our capital

957
01:36:43,405 --> 01:36:45,239
under the assumption
that whatever problem

958
01:36:45,324 --> 01:36:48,117
there was below was a normal one.

959
01:36:48,619 --> 01:36:52,330
But the truth is far from normal.
The truth is terrifying.

960
01:37:00,839 --> 01:37:03,216
Get out of the way, lady!

961
01:37:05,427 --> 01:37:07,386
This is a recording of a conversation

962
01:37:07,471 --> 01:37:10,973
between Dulles tower
and a captive aircraft overhead.

963
01:37:16,980 --> 01:37:19,732
- Lorenzo!
- Are you out of your fuckin' mind?

964
01:37:19,816 --> 01:37:23,653
- Where's the Blue Light team?
- Stuart's rigged explosives to a remote.

965
01:37:23,737 --> 01:37:24,779
Where's Grant?

966
01:37:24,863 --> 01:37:27,073
His boys are gonna kill that son of a bitch.

967
01:37:27,157 --> 01:37:30,868
- No, they're gonna take off with him.
- Get the fuck outta here.

968
01:37:30,953 --> 01:37:33,955
When the army canned Stuart,
he put his men in that unit.

969
01:37:34,039 --> 01:37:38,000
- Are you nuts? That firefight...
- Sideshow to buy him some time.

970
01:37:38,085 --> 01:37:40,711
You are completely
around the fuckin' bend.

971
01:37:40,796 --> 01:37:43,381
You're under arrest, motherfucker.

972
01:37:50,430 --> 01:37:54,058
These are the bullets they
used out there tonight. Blanks!

973
01:37:56,603 --> 01:37:58,145
Jesus Christ.

974
01:38:06,238 --> 01:38:09,740
This is Chief Lorenzo.
I want every officer recalled

975
01:38:09,825 --> 01:38:14,245
and in body armour and full weaponry
in the motor pool in five minutes.

976
01:38:16,290 --> 01:38:18,374
It's time to kick ass.

977
01:38:20,502 --> 01:38:22,753
Just like lwo Jima.

978
01:38:22,838 --> 01:38:28,634
We have learned that
the terrorists have control of the airport,

979
01:38:28,719 --> 01:38:31,595
a fact that the authorities have repressed.

980
01:38:31,680 --> 01:38:35,599
The terrorists promise more bloodshed
unless their demands are met.

981
01:38:35,684 --> 01:38:39,312
Now that the Special army commandos
have arrived at the airport,

982
01:38:39,396 --> 01:38:43,691
the likelihood of a full-scale
battle is dangerously close.

983
01:39:05,172 --> 01:39:10,092
That stupid, arrogant son of a bitch.
It's all over the airport.

984
01:39:10,927 --> 01:39:12,887
300 people have died

985
01:39:15,265 --> 01:39:18,184
and, unfortunately,
they may not be the last.

986
01:39:18,268 --> 01:39:21,562
The horrifying fact is that
no one is safe,

987
01:39:21,646 --> 01:39:25,191
either in the planes above Dulles
or in the terminal below.

988
01:39:25,275 --> 01:39:30,446
The threat of a higher body count at the
airport hangs over the heads of everyone,

989
01:39:30,530 --> 01:39:34,533
and the holiday season of peace
and love has become a nightmare.

990
01:39:41,208 --> 01:39:47,004
Listen up, all units. I want
you to converge on hangar 11, all sides.

991
01:39:47,089 --> 01:39:49,340
This car, McClane. Get in!

992
01:39:49,424 --> 01:39:51,884
When the city blue show up
with their backup,

993
01:39:51,968 --> 01:39:55,221
they'll pick up the pieces. Move out!

994
01:39:56,223 --> 01:40:00,351
- McClane, say hi to my brother Vito.
- Merry Christmas.

995
01:40:01,728 --> 01:40:03,145
Hi.

996
01:40:08,777 --> 01:40:12,947
Goddamn it to hell!
Move that piece of shit.

997
01:40:14,574 --> 01:40:17,326
Will you move that goddamn
piece of shit out of here?

998
01:40:17,411 --> 01:40:22,248
Vito, get the fuck out of the car
and get your ass in gear and help me!

999
01:40:27,129 --> 01:40:29,380
Hey, Coleman!

1000
01:40:34,302 --> 01:40:36,429
- Hey, Coleman!
- Hi.

1001
01:40:39,516 --> 01:40:43,352
...but at least the truth
is not among the hostages

1002
01:40:43,437 --> 01:40:47,606
because I, Richard Thornberg,
just happened to be here

1003
01:40:48,358 --> 01:40:54,822
to put his life and talent
on the line for humanity and country.

1004
01:40:54,906 --> 01:40:57,700
If this should be my final broadcast...

1005
01:40:59,870 --> 01:41:02,246
Amen to that, Dick.

1006
01:41:03,373 --> 01:41:07,543
Dick? We're live, Dick.
Where are you now?

1007
01:41:11,423 --> 01:41:15,384
Truck lights approaching, sir.
They're here, right on schedule.

1008
01:41:16,052 --> 01:41:18,137
The hangar door, open it.

1009
01:41:18,555 --> 01:41:19,930
Clockwork.

1010
01:41:43,288 --> 01:41:46,790
Jeez, you give me this story,
and I'll have your baby.

1011
01:41:47,250 --> 01:41:49,335
Not the kind of ride I'm looking for.

1012
01:42:01,181 --> 01:42:04,266
Colonel, if I may say so,
you are some piece of work.

1013
01:42:04,351 --> 01:42:07,436
Thank you, Major.
You're not so bad yourself.

1014
01:42:07,938 --> 01:42:11,190
- Congratulations on your escape, sir.
- Thank you, Major.

1015
01:42:11,274 --> 01:42:13,400
You should save them
until we are all safe.

1016
01:42:13,485 --> 01:42:14,485
Sir.

1017
01:42:14,569 --> 01:42:18,864
My congratulations, gentlemen.
You've won a victory for our way of life,

1018
01:42:18,949 --> 01:42:22,826
my pride, my admiration,
and a kick-ass vacation.

1019
01:42:22,911 --> 01:42:24,620
Now, get on board.

1020
01:42:55,068 --> 01:42:57,695
- Ride too rough, cowboy?
- I don't like to fly.

1021
01:42:57,779 --> 01:43:00,155
- So why are you here?
- I don't like to lose.

1022
01:43:12,377 --> 01:43:16,255
I don't know about you, but I've seen
enough snow to last me a lifetime.

1023
01:43:16,339 --> 01:43:21,343
- You don't get much of that in the tropics.
- For you gentlemen, we'll import it.

1024
01:43:23,888 --> 01:43:26,056
Shit. They left the hangar.

1025
01:43:29,519 --> 01:43:31,520
Right there. Get that.

1026
01:43:31,605 --> 01:43:33,606
- Now what?
- Get in front.

1027
01:43:33,690 --> 01:43:35,774
Block their path so they can't get out.

1028
01:43:35,859 --> 01:43:37,943
I'm not playing chicken
with a 200-ton plane!

1029
01:43:38,028 --> 01:43:40,029
I'm crazy, but not that crazy.

1030
01:43:40,113 --> 01:43:44,033
- Dulles, this is Northeast 140.
- That's Holly's plane.

1031
01:43:44,117 --> 01:43:46,452
Request emergency clearance.

1032
01:43:46,536 --> 01:43:49,496
I know you won't answer
but you better listen.

1033
01:43:49,581 --> 01:43:54,126
We're down to fumes and we have to land.
In five minutes, we're coming in.

1034
01:43:54,210 --> 01:43:56,920
That's my wife's plane.
Take it fuckin' down!

1035
01:43:57,005 --> 01:43:59,757
I'm not getting in front of that plane.

1036
01:44:04,054 --> 01:44:05,929
How about gettin' over top of it?

1037
01:44:06,222 --> 01:44:08,849
This is the captain. Your attention.

1038
01:44:08,933 --> 01:44:12,227
We have no choice
but to attempt an emergency landing.

1039
01:44:12,312 --> 01:44:15,439
Fasten your seat belts
and assume crash positions,

1040
01:44:15,523 --> 01:44:19,985
- as instructed by your cabin attendants.
- Let's have the emergency check list.

1041
01:44:20,070 --> 01:44:24,073
Attention, all air traffic in Dulles area.
This is Northeast 140.

1042
01:44:24,157 --> 01:44:26,742
We are attempting an emergency landing.

1043
01:44:31,748 --> 01:44:33,415
I don't wanna die.

1044
01:44:34,501 --> 01:44:35,918
I'm sorry.

1045
01:44:39,673 --> 01:44:40,964
God!

1046
01:44:50,600 --> 01:44:53,227
Thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.

1047
01:45:00,110 --> 01:45:02,653
- Hang on!
- What are you doing?

1048
01:45:02,737 --> 01:45:06,740
You wanted a story.
Nice and easy, boys. Get me in low.

1049
01:45:11,705 --> 01:45:15,082
- Bring me down.
- You'll get yourself killed.

1050
01:45:22,716 --> 01:45:25,300
Bring it in low. Keep over the wing.

1051
01:45:33,059 --> 01:45:34,435
Lower.

1052
01:45:43,945 --> 01:45:47,948
John, what the fuck are you doin'
out on the wing of this plane?

1053
01:45:55,457 --> 01:45:56,832
Damn!

1054
01:46:03,631 --> 01:46:05,632
There's something wrong.

1055
01:46:06,134 --> 01:46:08,677
The ailerons. We can't take off.

1056
01:46:14,851 --> 01:46:16,602
It's McClane again.

1057
01:46:17,270 --> 01:46:18,937
Son of a bitch!

1058
01:46:20,482 --> 01:46:23,942
- I'll do him.
- This time, do it right.

1059
01:46:24,027 --> 01:46:27,196
Just get us in the air, General.
You're the only man who can do it.

1060
01:46:27,280 --> 01:46:30,115
Don't shoot. That wing is fully fuelled.

1061
01:47:22,210 --> 01:47:25,212
Too bad, McClane. I kinda liked you.

1062
01:47:32,804 --> 01:47:34,680
I got enough friends.

1063
01:48:13,261 --> 01:48:15,220
Time for the main event.

1064
01:48:50,465 --> 01:48:52,799
You motherfucker!

1065
01:49:04,854 --> 01:49:06,688
How's it goin'?

1066
01:49:18,159 --> 01:49:20,202
Happy landings, asshole!

1067
01:50:11,838 --> 01:50:14,256
Yippee-ki-yay, motherfucker.

1068
01:51:05,641 --> 01:51:07,350
Holly!

1069
01:51:07,810 --> 01:51:10,353
Here's your fuckin' landing light.

1070
01:51:22,658 --> 01:51:26,036
Look! I see it.

1071
01:51:51,687 --> 01:51:54,439
They used the fuckin' fire to see.

1072
01:51:54,524 --> 01:51:56,942
They can all do that. Let's tell 'em.

1073
01:51:57,026 --> 01:52:00,112
They already know. Listen.

1074
01:52:00,196 --> 01:52:04,699
They're using the fire trail as a guide.
If they can do it, so can we.

1075
01:52:23,219 --> 01:52:26,513
Any landing you can walk
away from is a good one.

1076
01:53:37,710 --> 01:53:40,045
Holly!

1077
01:54:16,290 --> 01:54:17,832
Hi!

1078
01:54:27,802 --> 01:54:30,804
Oh, God. Oh, baby.

1079
01:54:30,888 --> 01:54:33,139
I thought I was never gonna see you again.

1080
01:54:33,224 --> 01:54:35,475
That's what I thought about you.

1081
01:54:35,559 --> 01:54:37,519
I love you so much.

1082
01:54:41,357 --> 01:54:44,150
They told me there were
terrorists at the airport.

1083
01:54:44,235 --> 01:54:46,403
Yeah. I heard that, too.

1084
01:54:54,996 --> 01:54:56,913
God, that's beautiful.

1085
01:55:00,293 --> 01:55:02,377
Yup. it sure is.

1086
01:55:04,547 --> 01:55:06,548
I love you so much.

1087
01:55:08,759 --> 01:55:13,179
John,
why does this keep happening to us?

1088
01:55:19,395 --> 01:55:21,104
Let's go home.

1089
01:55:25,901 --> 01:55:28,236
Somebody help me, please.

1090
01:55:28,321 --> 01:55:30,655
Honey, help me up here, please.

1091
01:55:30,740 --> 01:55:32,073
Asshole!

1092
01:55:35,077 --> 01:55:37,579
Hey, officer, come on!

1093
01:55:39,665 --> 01:55:42,584
Hop on in here. Get your missus in.

1094
01:55:42,668 --> 01:55:44,586
What do you say, Marv?

1095
01:55:44,670 --> 01:55:48,006
I'll be damned if
I'm gonna clean up this mess.

1096
01:55:58,184 --> 01:56:01,603
You get this parking ticket
in front of my airport?

1097
01:56:02,480 --> 01:56:03,938
Yeah.

1098
01:56:04,940 --> 01:56:08,276
What the hell. it's Christmas.

1099
01:56:13,449 --> 01:56:15,158
Take off, Marv!

1100
02:03:19,166 --> 02:03:20,166
English - US

