Start simple. Start with what
you know is the truth.
My name is Katniss Everdeen.
My home is District 12.
I was in the Hunger Games.
I escaped.
Peeta... Peeta was left behind.
Miss Everdeen?
You can't be in here.
I had a nightmare.
Just five more minutes.
You need to sleep.
We can help you sleep.
Just five more minutes.
No.
No, please, don't.
It's just five more...
Don't touch me! Don't! No!
No! Get off of me!
Finnick.
I wanted to go back for Peeta
and Johanna...
but I, uh...
I couldn't move.
They have Annie, too.
They took her.
She's, uh...
she's in the Capitol.
I wish she was dead.
I wish they were all dead,
and we were, too.
Miss Everdeen.
Colonel Boggs, District 13's
head of security.
I know you've been discharged...
but President Coin's requested
to meet with you, first.
Is there any news?
I'm just here to escort you.
We were always told there was
nothing left of 13.
Capitol bombed the surface to
rubble...
but we're military, so we learned
to survive, down here.
Preparing, training.
The war never stopped for us.
There she is.
Our Girl on Fire.
Madam President, may I present
you with The Mockingjay.
What an honor it is to meet you.
You're a courageous young woman.
I know how disorienting this
must be.
And I can't imagine what it's
like to...
live through the atrocities
of those Games.
Katniss...
President Alma Coin.
Please know how welcome you are.
I hope you'll find some comfort
with us.
We've known loss in 13, too.
This is history.
Right here at this table.
I apologize.
I wish you had more time
to recover...
but unfortunately, we don't
have that luxury.
Please, have a seat.
Are you aware of what's
happened?
When you fired your arrow
at the force field...
you electrified the nation.
There have been riots and
uprisings...
and strikes in seven districts.
We believe that if we keep
this energy going...
we can unify the districts
against the Capitol.
But if we don't, if we let it
dissipate...
we could be waiting another 75
years for this opportunity.
Everyone in 13 is ready for
this.
What about Peeta?
Is he alive?
I don't know.
And I wish that I did.
But there's no way for me
to contact...
my operatives inside the Capitol.
The Capitol has always
suppressed...
communication between the
districts...
but I know their system very
well.
I managed to break through.
All we need now is the perfect
message.
Katniss, here's what we need
to do.
We need to show them that the
Mockingjay's alive and well...
and willing to stand up and
join this fight.
'Cause we need every district...
to stand up to this Capitol.
The way you did.
So, we're gonna shoot a series
of propaganda clips...
propos, I like to call them...
on The Mockingjay.
Spreads the word...
that we're gonna stoke the fire
of this rebellion.
The fire that The Mockingjay
started.
You left him there.
You left Peeta in that arena
to die.
Katniss, there are so many...
Peeta was the one who was
supposed to live.
Miss Everdeen.
This revolution is about everyone.
It's about all of us.
And we need a voice.
Then you should've saved Peeta.
Maybe you should have rescued
the boy, instead.
Oh, no.
No, listen to me. No one else
can do this, but her.
This is not the girl you
described.
Obviously, we need to make it
personal.
Remind her who the real
enemy is.
She knows who the enemy is.
That's not the issue.
Unless she's forgotten.
There's explaining and there's
showing.
Let her see what the Capitol
did to 12.
She can't handle it.
The Games destroyed her.
This is the only choice you
have.
People don't always show up...
the way you want them to,
Madam President.
But that anger, that anger-driven
defiance...
that's what we want.
And we can redirect it.
We need to unite these people
out there...
that have been doing nothing
but killing each other...
in an arena, for years.
We have to have a lightning rod.
They'll follow her. She's the
face of the revolution.
Let her see it.
Let her go home.
Send her.
I can't believe you're going
through with this.
You can say "no."
I need to see it for myself.
This way.
13 swept everything, top to
bottom...
so, you'd be safe.
You sure you don't want me to
go with you?
Yeah.
I'm sure.
We'll have our eyes on you
from above.
Figures.
Hey!
Come on.
Don't you wanna see Prim?
There you go.
You're breakin' my heart.
Shh.
Egeria!
We need to fix these lines.
I won't say "rebels."
These are senseless acts
of defiance.
And I won't legitimize them.
We'll call them "criminals."
Mmm.
"Radicals."
Hmm.
Otherwise we're breaking my
oldest rule.
Never let them see you bleed.
Citizens...
tonight I address all of Panem
as one.
Since the Dark Days...
Panem has had an unprecedented
era of peace.
It is a peace built upon
cooperation.
And a respect for law and order.
In the past weeks, you have
heard of sporadic violence...
following the actions of a few
radicals in the Quarter Quell.
Those who choose this
destructive path...
your actions are based on a
misunderstanding...
of how we have survived.
Together.
It is a contract.
Each district supplies the Capitol.
Like blood to a heart.
In return, the Capitol provides
order and security.
To refuse work...
is to put the entire system
in danger.
The Capitol is the beating
heart of Panem.
Nothing can survive without
a heart.
The criminals that kneel
before you...
use symbols for the purpose
of sedition.
Which is why all images...
of The Mockingjay...
are now forbidden.
Possessing them will be
considered treason.
Punishable by death.
Justice shall be served swiftly.
Order shall be restored.
To those who ignore the warnings
of history...
prepare to pay the ultimate
price.
It's okay.
We're okay.
We're all here now.
Buttercup!
I smuggled him in.
I got Dad.
And I got some of your herbs,
from the kitchen.
They have strict rules.
I don't know what they'll do
if they find him here.
You should try to eat something.
Hello.
Good evening.
And a big welcome to all
in Panem.
I'm Caesar Flickerman.
And whoever you are, whatever
it is you're doing...
if you're working, put down
your work.
If you're having dinner, stop
having dinner.
Because you are going to want
to witness this, tonight.
There has been rampant
speculation...
about what really happened
in the Quarter Quell.
And here to shed a little
light...
on the subject for us is a
very special guest.
Please welcome Mr. Peeta Mellark.
Peeta, a lot of people...
feel as though they are in
the dark.
Yeah, I know how they feel.
Now, to set the stage for us.
Talk us through what really
happened...
on that final and controversial
night.
Well, first off, you have to
understand...
that when you're in the Games...
you only get one wish.
It's very costly.
You're alive.
It costs your life.
I think it costs more than
your life.
How do you mean?
What's more than your life?
I mean to murder innocent
people...
that costs everything that
you are.
Yes.
So, you hold on to that one
wish.
And that night my wish was to
save Katniss.
Yes.
I should've just run off
with her...
earlier in the day, like she'd
wanted.
But you didn't.
No.
Why? Were you caught up in
Beetee's plan?
No, I was caught up trying
to play allies.
And then they separated us...
and that's when I lost her.
And then the lightning hit...
and the whole force field around
the arena just blew out.
Yes, but Peeta...
Katniss is the one who blew
it out.
No.
You saw the footage.
No, she didn't know what she
was doing.
Neither of us knew...
there was a bigger plan going
on. We had no idea.
You had no idea?
No.
All right. Well, Peeta, there are
many who find this suspicious...
to say the least.
Mmm-hmm.
It seems as though she was
part of a rebel plan.
Do you think it was part of
her plan...
to be almost killed by Johanna?
Or part of the plan to be
paralyzed by lightning?
No, we were not part of any
rebel plan.
We had no idea what was going on.
All right. I believe you, Peeta
Mellark. Thank you.
Yeah.
And I was going to ask you to
speak about the unrest...
but I think you might be
too upset.
No, I can.
Are you sure?
Yeah, absolutely.
Thank you.
I want everyone who's watching
to stop...
and to think about what a civil
war could mean.
We almost went extinct once
before.
And now our numbers are even
fewer.
He's one of them.
Is this really what we wanna do?
He's a traitor.
Kill ourselves off?
Killing is not the answer.
I can't believe he's doing this.
Everyone needs to lay down
their weapons, immediately.
Traitor!
He's not one of us!
This is treason!
Are you calling for a ceasefire?
Yeah.
I am.
You're a puppet!
Hang him!
I want everyone to stop...
the senseless violence.
This is not the path to change.
Traitor!
It's not the path to justice.
There can't be a ceasefire.
Not after everything Snow's done.
He could have done a lot of
damage, tonight.
Most districts, people are still
too afraid to join.
They need the courage.
Why do you think he said that?
I don't know.
Maybe he was forced.
He didn't look that bad.
Maybe he made some kind of deal
to protect you.
He's still playing the game.
No! No! No!
I'm sorry.
It's just a nightmare.
That's okay.
I get 'em, too.
Peeta...
will you stay with me?
Yeah.
Always.
Hey.
Can't sleep?
Tell me what's happening.
I'm good at keeping secrets.
Even from Mom.
No one hates the Capitol
more than me.
And I wanna help.
But I just keep thinking...
even if we win this war, what
happens to Peeta?
I know he's not safe there...
but he's definitely not
safe here.
I don't think you know...
how important you are to them.
If you want something, you just
have to ask.
You could demand almost anything.
They'd have to agree to it.
I should wake you up more often,
Little Duck.
Get some sleep, now.
You too.
Thank you for agreeing to meet
with me.
I've decided I'll be your
Mockingjay.
But I have some conditions.
Peeta and the other Tributes...
Johanna Mason and Annie Cresta...
will be rescued at the earliest
opportunity.
If and when Peeta is liberated...
he will receive a full and
unconditional pardon.
No punishment will be inflicted.
And the same goes for the other
Tributes.
No.
It's not their fault you abandoned
them in the arena.
They're doing and saying whatever
they can to survive.
Individuals don't make demands
in 13.
There will be a tribunal.
And a fair judgment.
Thank you.
The Victors will be granted
immunity...
and you will announce that...
in front of the entire population
of 13.
You will hold yourself and your
government responsible...
or, you will find another
Mockingjay.
That's it.
That's her, right there.
Isn't that who I promised you?
She wears the costume...
gunfire in the background.
A hint of smoke.
Our Mockingjay.
Madam President, we're losing
ground...
because the people are losing
heart.
This is worth the risk.
She's worth the risk.
Pardons, tribunals.
Power of the people.
It can all be the bedrock of
the new Panem, but...
in wartime I think even the
noblest of causes...
can be bent a little bit.
Right?
Do you have any other conditions?
My sister gets to keep her cat.
Go away.
Is it visiting hours, again?
Miss Trinket...
you see this door?
It opens... from the inside.
I've told you, these are the
standard living quarters.
Same as everyone.
You're not a prisoner. You're
free to join the rest of 13.
Not looking like this.
Thank you very much.
We have a bigger issue than
wardrobe, Miss Trinket.
Katniss has agreed to be "The
Mockingjay."
Oh, that poor thing.
And your "Girl on Fire" is
burnt out.
I need you to join this
team, now.
I need someone she trusts.
What about Haymitch?
He's drying out in some facility,
a mile down.
Aiding rebels is not really
my forte.
Miss Trinket, your days in the
Capitol are over...
no matter what happens here.
If you wanna play a prisoner
of war, fine.
Stay here and rot.
I'll find someone else to be
The Mockingjay's escort.
Who?
Anyone... can be replaced.
Not your Mockingjay.
There isn't a soul in this
dungeon...
who knows the first thing
about Katniss.
You honestly believe one of
these cave dwellers...
is going to take my place?
No.
Good afternoon.
Thank you for interrupting
your schedules.
They have already been adjusted
to compensate for the delay.
I hardly ever see children
around here.
Please, check in with your unit
supervisors when you resume work.
A lot of them were lost in an
epidemic a few years ago.
I have an announcement for the...
Coin lost her family, too.
citizens of 13...
Daughter and a husband.
and our welcome guests from 12.
Katniss Everdeen has consented...
to be the face of our cause...
to help unite the districts
against the Capitol.
In exchange, I have promised...
several concessions.
First, we'll assess all
opportunities...
for the extraction of the
Victors...
held hostage in the Capitol.
Peeta Mellark...
Johanna Mason...
Finnick, I made the deal for
Annie, too.
and Annie Cresta.
Once freed...
they will be granted full pardon
for any and all crimes...
committed against the rebel
cause.
Good!
That's good, Katniss.
If Katniss Everdeen fails to
fulfill her duties...
the deal will be off.
Thank you for your attention.
Please, resume with your
daily schedules.
Madam President...
Effie Trinket.
Welcome to 13.
Madam President, may I say you
are so very...
concise?
Mmm.
You believe that there's more
to be said?
May I speak freely?
You don't appear to do
anything else.
I'm only talking about
salesmanship.
The thing with revolutions,
they're a tender flame.
They need to be nurtured with
a little kindling...
and warmth.
Bit of oxygen.
Oxygen.
One sure way to put it out is
to smother it.
Or to use up all the air
in the room.
Excuse me.
You know what could use a
revolution? That hair.
Effie?
Oh!
What are you doing here?
I'm a political refugee.
Plutarch rescued you?
Rescued, yes, that's what he
calls it.
You and I were both in the dark.
Now I'm condemned to this life
of jumpsuits.
It is wonderful to see you again.
Can you believe this place?
I miss coffee.
I never knew any place could
be so strict.
I mean, I thought at least...
in the higher ranks there'd
be some...
side action.
I miss my wigs.
Luckily, I remembered that this
was all the rage...
when I was coming up.
You know, everything old can
be made new again.
Like democracy.
Which brings me to this.
Cinna.
He's dead, isn't he?
Yes, dear.
He made Plutarch promise not
to show you this...
until you'd decided to be
The Mockingjay on your own.
He knew the risks.
As we all do.
He believed in this revolution.
He believed in you.
They're beautiful.
They have it.
They have the Mockingjay outfit.
There's not much of a prep team
here in 13...
but we will make you...
the best-dressed rebel in history.
Okay.
Bring up the lights.
Cinna's final touch.
Everyone's either gonna wanna
kiss you, kill you...
or be you.
Perfect.
Absolutely perfect.
Okay.
Let's bring up the setting.
Huh.
Little wind.
Okay, Katniss...
we're gonna start you down
on one knee.
Okay.
And as you rise up...
you're gonna hold your flag in
the air and deliver your line.
And remember...
you've just stormed the
outskirts of the Capitol...
arm-in-arm with your brothers
and sisters.
Okay.
Whenever you're ready.
People of Panem, we fight,
we dare, we...
Does she know the line?
I know it. I got it. I'm sorry.
Okay, All right.
Let's do it again.
She's warming up.
All right. With energy.
Go.
People of Panem, we fight!
We dare to end this hunger
for justice!
You've just been in battle!
I'm sorry.
Excuse my outburst.
You've just been in battle.
Let's try it again.
Whenever you're ready.
People of Panem, we fight!
We dare to end this hunger
for justice.
And that, my friends, is how
a revolution dies.
Hello, Katniss.
This how you greet an old friend?
Maybe I don't recognize
you sober.
I guess it looks as bad as
it feels.
People of Panem, we fight!
We dare!
We end this hunger for justice!
Uh, Madam President...
indulge me for a moment, if
you would.
Let's everybody think of one
incident...
where Katniss Everdeen genuinely
moved you.
Not where you were jealous of
her hairstyle...
or her dress went up in flames...
or she made a half-way decent
shot with an arrow.
And not where Peeta made you
like her.
No, I'd like you all to think
of one moment...
where she made you feel
something real.
When she volunteered for her
sister, at the Reaping.
Excellent example.
Okay.
I hope that wasn't important.
Uh... okay.
"Volunteer for sister."
Good.
What else?
Oh, when she sang that song
for little Rue?
Oh, yeah.
Who didn't get choked up at that?
You know, I like you better,
Effie, without all that makeup.
Well, I like you better sober.
When she chose Rue as an ally,
as well.
Mmm, yes.
Now, what do all these have
in common?
No one told her what to do.
Unscripted, yes.
So, maybe we should just leave
her alone.
And wash her face.
She's still a girl.
You made her look thirty-five.
The opportunities for spontaneity...
are obviously lacking below
ground.
So, what you're suggesting is,
we toss her into combat?
I can't sanction putting an
untrained civilian...
in battle just for effect.
This is not the Capitol.
That is exactly what I'm suggesting.
Put her in the field.
No, we can't protect her.
It has to come from her.
That's what people respond to.
You want a symbol for the
revolution?
She cannot be coached into it.
Trust me, I know.
Maybe there's someplace that's
less dangerous.
District 8. They reported
heavy bombing, last week.
There are no military targets
left.
We can't guarantee her safety.
You'll never be able to guarantee
my safety.
I wanna go.
And if you're killed?
Make sure you get it on camera.
I've made you some surprises.
Maybe you wanna try one out.
If you're gonna be a part of
Katniss' propo team...
you may as well look the part.
And this one is for you.
Plutarch wanted you to have
a weapon...
for the sake of the propos...
but I couldn't just make you
a fashion accessory.
It's beautiful.
And look here.
Regular. Incendiary.
Explosive arrows.
All color-coded.
And tell Finnick...
I've got a trident for him...
when he's ready.
Might just cheer him... cheer
him up.
Uh...
let's not fire the red ones...
in here.
You had all of this and you
just...
left the districts to fend
for themselves?
It's not that simple, Katniss.
We barely survived.
We weren't in any kind of shape...
to launch a counterattack.
Yeah, we could've bombed the
Capitol...
but they would've retaliated...
with at least twice the firepower.
Then what?
There would've been nobody
left to claim victory.
Sounds like exactly what
Peeta said...
and then you all called
him a traitor.
This way, soldier.
You are camera-ready.
Doesn't your comrade look
handsome?
Let's go.
Come back safe.
Quick introductions, Katniss.
These people have come a long
way to support the cause.
This is Cressida.
In my opinion, one of the best...
up-and-coming directors in
the Capitol.
Until I up and left.
Hey.
Let's see what you can do.
All right.
Be careful.
This is my assistant, Messalla.
It's an honor to meet you.
And your cameramen over there,
Castor.
Hello.
And Pollux.
Let's get locked in.
You're all from the Capitol?
Plutarch got you out?
Don't expect much chitchat
from him.
He's an Avox. Capitol cut his
tongue out, years ago.
And, no, it wasn't any sort of
rescue...
if that's what you mean.
We all fled on our own.
For this.
For you.
This has gotta be fast.
In and out.
Move out.
You're alive, then.
We weren't sure.
Katniss, Commander Paylor,
District 8.
Katniss has been recovering, but
she insisted on coming out...
and seeing some of your wounded.
Well, we've got plenty of those.
We have a mass grave a few
blocks west, but...
I can't spare the manpower
to move them yet.
Hospital's past that curtain.
Any hope you can give them,
it's worth it.
The Capitol's done everything
they can to break us.
Aren't you worried about having
all your wounded in one place?
I think it's better than
leaving them to die.
That's not what I meant.
Well, that's my only other
option.
You can come up with another,
I'm all ears.
It's right through here.
Don't film me in there.
I can't help them.
Just let them see your face.
Huh?
Excuse me.
Yeah.
You all right?
It's okay.
Here, it's okay.
I've got you.
It's all right.
Katniss Everdeen?
What are you doing here?
I came... I came to see you.
What about the baby?
I lost it.
Are you fighting, Katniss?
You here to fight with us?
I am.
I will.
Tighter.
Tighter, tighter.
Sir, some cameras were damaged
in the bombings...
but we confirmed it's her.
Zoom in.
She was visiting a make-shift
hospital.
We're not sure if she's still
there.
Hmm.
We can scramble hovercraft
from the border of 11.
We may be able to target her.
Hmm.
Kill the wounded.
Sir...
You wrote that speech yourself,
Egeria.
Any association with the
Mockingjay symbol...
is forbidden.
Everyone inside that hospital
has committed treason.
Show them what it costs...
to be friends with Katniss
Everdeen.
Your mom's gonna be proud of you
when she sees the footage.
Will this play in the districts?
It'll be tattooed on their eyes.
There's a problem.
What kinda problem?
Incoming bombers from the north.
We need to find cover, now.
There's a bunker in there.
Straight ahead and down
the stairs.
Katniss!
Katniss?
Everdeen!
Gale, back away from the wall!
You okay?
Move!
They're going after something
to the south.
That's towards the hospital.
They're circling back around.
Come on!
That's the hospital.
They're targeting the hospital.
Help them!
Get them out!
Katniss?
Katniss, can you tell everyone...
what you're seeing right now?
Katniss, what do you wanna say?
I want the rebels to know
that I'm alive.
That I'm in District 8...
where the Capitol just bombed
a hospital...
filled with unarmed men, women
and children.
And there will be no survivors.
If you think for one second...
that the Capitol will ever
treat us fairly...
you are lying to yourselves.
Because we know who they are...
and what they do.
This is what they do!
And we must fight back.
I have a message for
President Snow.
You can torture us, and
bomb us...
and burn our districts to
the ground.
But, do you see that?
Fire is catching.
And if we burn, you burn
with us!
We know who they are and what
they do.
This is what they do!
And we must fight back.
You can torture us, and
bomb us...
and burn our districts to
the ground.
Plutarch's faith in you wasn't
misplaced.
But, do you see that?
Thank you.
Fire is catching.
Come up with me for the beginning.
And if we burn, you burn
with us!
There is no progress without
compromise.
No victory without sacrifice.
But I stand here with The
Mockingjay...
to announce that our moment
has arrived.
Beetee has increased...
our use of the airwaves tenfold.
We will broadcast this message...
to all the districts, tonight.
The Mockingjay's words...
inspiring everyone to join
the rebellion.
Together...
we will become...
an alliance to be reckoned with.
Hoorah!
You don't like hearing a fight
song at a funeral, huh?
The more people on our side...
the closer we are to Peeta
and Annie.
Yeah.
By order of President Snow...
daily production quotas have
been increased.
All work shifts will be extended
by an extra two hours.
Failure to meet these quotas
will not be tolerated.
By order of President Snow...
daily production quotas have
been increased.
If we burn, you burn with us!
Yeah!
Whoo!
I got good news.
What?
Coin agreed to let us hunt
above ground.
He's not even afraid of us.
They've never been hunted
before.
It's almost not fair.
They want us back.
They asked us to head for
Command.
All right.
I gotta drop these off.
She was arguably...
our favorite Tribute.
And I think that's what we all
find most astonishing...
is that this girl was adored
in the Capitol.
And I think for you, Peeta...
it must be particularly painful.
I wish I could give this rose
to you, Katniss.
He's changed so much already.
What are they doing to him?
A sweet gesture for a girl
who has inspired...
such violence.
You must love her very much
to be able to forgive her.
He's shaking.
I don't think that I could.
Unless, of course, Peeta, you
think that perhaps she's being...
forced into saying...
things that she doesn't even
understand.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I think.
Even his voice is different.
I think they're using her...
to whip up the rebels.
I doubt she even knows what's
happening.
And what's really at stake.
Now, Peeta, I doubt that
the rebels...
will ever let her see this.
But if they do, what would you
say to her?
To Katniss Everdeen...
the once sweet Katniss Everdeen,
what will you say?
I would tell her to think
for herself.
Yes.
Don't be a fool, Katniss.
I know you never wanted the
rebellion.
The things that you did in
the Games...
were never intended to start
all of this.
The rebels have made you
into something...
that you're not.
Something that could destroy
all of us.
So, if you have any power, or
any say...
in what they do, or how they
use you...
please, please, urge them to
stop this war...
before it's too late.
And ask yourself...
can you trust the people you're
working with?
Do you know what they really
want?
We need to respond.
Thank you, Peeta Mellark, for
these...
revelations about the real
Mockingjay.
Did you see what he looks like?
I saw a coward.
You don't have any idea what
he's going through.
I don't care. I would never
say what he just said.
Not if they tortured me.
Not with a gun to my head.
That is the same Peeta that
defended you at the whipping post.
No, it's not. Now he's only
defending himself.
Coin's called a meeting.
We need to respond.
When did "we" become you and
Coin?
Everyone has a choice.
How can he sit there in the
Capitol and defend the people...
who destroyed his home and
murdered his family?
He doesn't know.
How could he?
Nobody's seen what the Capitol
did to 12.
I have to show them.
So, I wanna start with you...
in front of the Justice Building,
okay?
Bang.
First shot.
Katniss, tell us what happened,
here.
We were all standin' right
here...
watchin' the Games, when you
fired that arrow.
The screens just went dark.
Nobody had any idea what happened.
Peacekeepers forced us back
into our homes.
For maybe an hour, the town
was just dead quiet.
Little past 9:00, we heard
their trucks pullin' out.
All of them.
Every single Peacekeeper.
And I knew what that meant.
Me and a couple of guys from
the mines...
we started pulling people from
their houses...
and tried to get 'em to the
fence line...
but a lotta people were scared
of the forest.
So, they headed up onto the road.
Make a break for it, that way.
Stay with Gale.
915 of us made it to the fence.
Then we watched as bombers
circled back towards the road.
They firebombed them as they
ran away.
915 outta 10,000.
I should've grabbed people.
I should've dragged 'em with me.
Some of the kids I could've
carried.
You saved so many people, Gale.
Without you, there would be
no District 12.
Not even the memory of it.
This is where you kissed me.
I didn't think you remembered
that.
I'd have to be dead to forget
Maybe not even then.
I knew you'd do that.
How?
I didn't.
'Cause I'm in pain.
That's the only way that I can
get your attention.
Don't worry, Katniss.
It'll pass.
Hey.
Yeah, that's a mockingjay.
Well, now they'll never shut up.
You want me to sing?
That line was originally "necklace
of rope."
I had it changed to "necklace
of hope."
Wow.
You are a true wordsmith.
Little on the nose, but, of
course, so is war.
Every district's seeing this?
Yes.
But not the Capitol.
I designed this signal defense
system for them.
But I can't find my way
through it.
Guess I did my job too well.
At the time, I was just thinking
of the science of it all.
We'll get through it.
Are you, are you coming to the
tree?
They strung up a man, they say
who murdered three.
Strange things did happen here,
no stranger would it be...
if we met at midnight, in the
hanging tree.
Are you, are you coming to
the tree?
Where dead man called out, for
his love to flee.
Strange things did happen here, no
stranger would it be...
if we met at midnight, in the
hanging tree.
Moves... and countermoves.
Katniss, you're wanted in
Command.
Tonight, we've received reports...
of derailed trains...
of granaries on fire...
and of a savage attack on the
hydro-electric dam in District 5.
Oh, what have they done to you?
I'm begging for restraint and
decency.
We interrupt your regularly
scheduled horse manure...
to bring you...
That's it.
That's our footage.
Beetee's in.
Katniss?
He sees it.
He sees our propo.
Katniss, are you there?
Peeta.
Katniss?
Peeta, please continue.
You were telling us about these
savage attacks.
Yeah.
The attack on the dam was
a callous...
and inhuman act of destruction.
Think about it.
How will this end?
What will be left?
No one can survive this.
No one is safe now.
Not here in the Capitol...
not in any of the districts.
They're coming, Katniss.
They're gonna kill everyone.
And in District 13 you'll be
dead by morning!
He's warning us.
That was a warning.
Yes, it was.
We have to get him out before
they kill him.
Is there anything in the air?
Nothing on Doppler, ma'am.
He was in the mansion. He could
have overheard something.
Possibly.
It's time for an air raid
drill.
This is a Code Red alert.
Please, remain calm...
and begin evacuation protocol.
Prim!
Proceed to your nearest
stairwell...
and descend to level 40.
Blast doors will be sealed
in six minutes.
This is a Code Red alert.
Please, remain calm...
and begin evacuation protocol.
Proceed in an orderly fashion
to your nearest stairwell...
and descend to level 40.
Madam President...
three Capitol squadrons just
entered our airspace.
How much time do we have?
They're a few seconds from range.
Prepare to scramble the fleet.
Copy that.
Open up short-range air defense.
Arm long-range missiles for
counter-attack.
Blast doors will be sealed
in five minutes.
This is a Code Red alert.
Please, remain calm...
and begin evacuation protocol.
Proceed in an orderly fashion...
to your nearest stairwell...
and descend to level 40.
Blast doors will close in
four minutes.
This is a Code Red alert.
Please, remain calm...
and begin evacuation protocol.
Proceed in an orderly fashion...
to your nearest stairwell...
and descend to level 40.
Blast doors will close in three
minutes.
This is a Code Red alert.
Proceed in an orderly fashion...
to your nearest stairwell...
and descend to level 40.
Continue to the Supply Station
and claim one pack...
for each member of your
compartment.
Please keep all personal items
within your assigned area.
Be courteous to your fellow
citizens.
This is a Code Red alert.
All citizens should be inside
the bunker.
Blast doors will close in...
two minutes.
Mom!
Where's Prim?
I thought she went to find you.
She must still be on the stairs.
There's no one on the stairs!
She went back for the cat.
This is a Code Red alert.
All citizens should be inside
the bunker.
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Blast doors will close in
one minute.
They hit the far edge of the
north-west quadrant.
Penetrated 40 feet.
Missed the living quarters.
Only minor damage to corridors
2 and 3.
Is there any radiation?
None detected.
Doppler shows a fourth wave
approaching.
Blast doors will close in
30 seconds.
Prim!
Katniss!
This is a Code Red alert.
Blast doors will close in
15 seconds.
Get down here!
Hurry!
This is a Code Red alert.
Blast doors will close in
10 seconds.
Nine...
eight...
seven...
six...
five...
Hold the doors!
four...
three...
two...
Wait! Hold the doors!
one.
You went back for the cat?
What were you thinking?
I wasn't gonna leave him behind.
I couldn't live with myself.
Blast doors are now sealed.
I know, Prim.
Let's go.
Damage to the aquifer in the
northwest quadrant.
We lost a transport corridor.
There's nothing else in the
northwest.
Our surface-to-air launchers
just took...
a direct hit in sector 3.
Because we revealed ourselves.
They saw us firing, there.
Stand down.
Don't launch the fleet.
Another 12 Capitol bombers...
approaching sector 3 in attack
formation.
Hold fire on their approach.
Oh.
What'd they hit?
Bedrock. But there's debris
in the ventilation shaft.
They're not targeting our fleet.
Or our special weaponry.
They don't know what we have,
or where we have it.
Can you confirm that everyone's
safely in the bunker?
Already done.
Conceal all remaining
anti-aircraft guns.
Seal launching pads and
ventilation corridors.
We are gonna wait this out.
This is what we're built for.
They'll seal us in here like
a tomb.
The Capitol's working off some
outdated information.
I'd rather not update it
for them.
Madam President, I know it's
not my place...
It's not.
You're a welcome guest...
but you're out of your depth
down here.
Reduce oxygen to 14% to
conserve it.
Copy that.
Take a deep breath, Mr. Heavensbee.
It's gonna be a long night.
Prim, talk about something.
Anything.
They promoted me at the hospital.
I forgot to tell you.
They're training me to be
a doctor.
They'd be stupid not to.
Hey.
Can I sit?
Yeah.
Snow's using Annie to punish
you.
He's taunting us with them.
I didn't understand until
just now...
watching that stupid cat.
After your first Games...
I thought the whole romance
was an act.
We all expected you to continue
that strategy.
But it wasn't until Peeta's
heart stopped...
and he nearly died that
I knew I'd misjudged you.
You love him.
I'm not saying in what way.
Maybe you don't even know
yourself.
But anyone paying attention
can see it.
How do you live with it?
I drag myself outta nightmares...
and there's no relief in
waking up.
But, it's better not to give
in to it.
Takes ten times longer to put
yourself back together...
than it does to fall apart.
Katniss?
Katniss.
Come with me.
We took their best shot.
Didn't we?
Yeah.
Your mother and sister okay?
Yeah, they're fine.
I need you to do something
for us.
I need you to tell Panem...
that we survived an attack by
the Capitol...
with no casualties.
And we remain fully operational.
Okay.
You should know something.
We had eight extra minutes
of civilian evacuation...
because of Peeta's warning.
I won't forget that.
Thank you.
So, Katniss...
it's "13 is alive and well,
and so am I."
Katniss?
Katniss.
Never one to waste it in
rehearsal, I know.
Why would they drop these?
For me.
Ready to go, Katniss?
We're gonna do this, just like
District 8.
Tell me about the roses.
Tell Snow, 13 is alive and well.
He's gonna kill Peeta.
Let's try again.
Can you speak up?
We don't have a mic on you.
"13 is alive and well, and so
am I."
He's gonna kill Peeta.
I can't.
Katniss?
You can do it, Katniss.
I can't do this.
"13 is alive and well, and so
am I."
He's just gonna keep...
He's never gonna stop.
Cressida, we should cut the
cameras.
as long as I'm The Mockingjay.
It's okay, Katniss.
No. He warned me.
He warned me about this.
He's doing this because I'm
The Mockingjay.
He's punishing Peeta to
punish me.
No.
No, I can't do this.
Katniss.
Don't make me do this!
Let her go.
I gotta get out of here.
So, this is the end, huh?
Guess this means we're gonna
hide down here forever.
I can't be The Mockingjay.
Not "The Mockingjay."
Just Katniss.
You know, you're the only...
real friend I have down here.
I don't suppose they gave you...
any kind of... medication?
You're unbelievable.
Okay, but I meant what I said.
Look, the reason I'm here is
to let you know...
they're rescuing Peeta.
What?
The dam going down in
District 5...
took out most of the power to
the Capitol.
Knocked out their signal defense.
Beetee's inside their system
now...
wreaking all kinds of havoc.
A window is open to us.
How much longer?
I don't know.
I guess until the Capitol...
can get the power back on.
And President Coin?
You know, I can never fully
support that woman...
in light of the prohibition...
they have going on around
this place...
but Plutarch got word...
that Peeta and the others are
in the Tribute Center.
And with the power out...
Coin sees this as an opportunity.
She knows that Peeta..
is the Capitol's weapon.
The same way you're ours.
And as opposed to having you
two...
pointing at each other...
she's going to get him.
I have to go help.
Hey, hey, whoa, kiddo.
Wait.
Come on. What, are you just
gonna jump outta the vent...
and go storm the Capitol?
Besides, it's already underway.
Six soldiers went in.
Volunteer only.
And guess who was the first
brave soul to sign up?
Gale.
Okay, Finnick?
Yeah. Yeah.
Go in the center, there.
Those rocks.
Castor, to left.
Pollux, you're with me.
So, we'll go straight to camera.
Okay?
Finnick?
Yeah.
Okay.
Take your time.
Just remember to keep talking
and don't stop.
This is Finnick Odair.
Winner of the 65th Hunger Games.
And I'm coming to you from
District 13, alive and well.
We've survived an assault
from the Capitol.
But, I'm not here to give you
recent news.
Why is Finnick doing a propo?
It's a lot more than that.
Beetee's commandeered the
system.
Now that they're down to
generator power...
there's a more limited range of
frequencies available to them.
And I'm filling them all up
with Finnick.
Not many will see it, but
whoever does...
will think it's another propo.
What they don't know is this
broadcast...
is jamming their entire system
with noise.
Early defense warning, internal
communications, everything.
As long as the broadcast goes
through...
our team should be able to get
in and out undetected.
The truth. Not the myths about
a life of luxury.
Not the lie about glory for
your homeland.
You can't survive the arena.
The moment you leave, you're
a slave.
Mockingjay One, Mockingjay One...
you are one minute out from
perimeter defense.
Going dark.
Stay low, in case they're online.
President Snow used to sell me.
Or my body, at least.
I wasn't the only one.
If a Victor is considered
desirable...
the President gives them as
a reward...
or allows people to buy them.
If you refuse, he kills someone
you love.
Mockingjay One, you are 20 seconds
from perimeter defense.
Ten seconds.
Nine... eight...
seven... six... five...
four... three... two...
One.
No response from perimeter
defense.
We're inside Capitol airspace.
To make themselves feel better...
my patrons would make presents
of money, or jewelry.
But I found a much more valuable
form of payment.
Secrets.
Gear up.
Switching to Night View.
There.
Command, we have visual on the
Tribute Center.
Initiating final approach.
Masks on.
See, I know all the depravity...
the deceit and the cruelty...
of the Capitol's pampered elite.
But the biggest secrets are
about...
our good President, Coriolanus
Snow.
Open the door.
Command, this is Team Leader.
Prepare to deploy gas.
We will confirm once inside.
Such a young man when he rose
to power.
Such a clever one to keep it.
How, you may ask, did he do it?
One word.
Poison.
Get ready to drop.
He stopped every mutiny before
it even started.
Clear.
Command, we're inside.
Heading toward target number
one.
Cell P45, lower level 2C.
Gas.
There are so many mysterious
deaths...
to adversaries.
Even to allies who were threats.
Snow would drink from the
same cup...
to deflect suspicion.
But antidotes don't always
work...
which is why he wears roses
that reek of perfume.
Help cover the scent of blood
from sores...
in his mouth, that will
never heal.
Gale.
But he can't hide the scent
of who he really is.
He kills without mercy.
He rules with deception and
fear.
His weapon of choice...
is the only thing suited to
such a man.
Poison.
The perfect weapon for a snake.
What is this place?
Beetee?
I'm losing them.
Powering back up.
Ma'am, the Capitol air defense
system...
is rebooting.
It's coming back online.
Must be diverting power from
another source.
And filtering transmissions.
Another 60 seconds and we'll
be cut off.
Madam President, should we call
back the hovercraft?
Broadcast me.
If Snow's watching this, maybe
he'll let the signal in...
if he sees me.
Put me on the air, so he can
see me.
Yes.
Put her on.
Can we do this?
Can we still get in?
Yes.
For the moment.
The line's open.
He will only see you.
Okay, Katniss, go.
President Snow?
President Snow.
It's Katniss.
There's no guarantee he's
even watching.
I know, but he might be.
President Snow, I need to
speak with you.
Are you there?
President Snow, it's Katniss.
Can you hear me?
I need to speak with you.
President Snow, it's Katniss.
President Snow...
are you there?
Can you hear me?
President Snow...
Miss Everdeen.
What an honor.
I don't imagine you're calling...
to thank me for the roses.
I never asked for this.
I never asked to be in
the Games.
Boggs?
Come in. Boggs?
I never asked to be The
Mockingjay.
Just wanted to save my sister...
and keep Peeta alive.
Come in.
Boggs?
Please, just let him go...
and I will stop being The
Mockingjay.
I will disappear. You will never
have to see me, ever again.
Miss Everdeen...
Boggs, come in.
you couldn't run from this...
Copy.
any more than you could have
run from the Games.
Command, I need a situation
report.
Boggs, we're running out of time.
Hurry.
Let's move.
Please.
You've won.
You've already beaten me.
Release Peeta.
And take me instead.
We're long past the opportunity...
for noble sacrifice.
Then tell me what to do.
I've always kept my promises,
haven't I?
You said you didn't want a war...
and that's just what's happened.
I told you what a fragile thing
peace was...
and still, like a child...
you took pleasure in breaking it.
I know what you are.
I know you can't see past your
narrowest concerns.
But please, Miss Everdeen.
I doubt you know what honesty
is, anymore.
Command, we're at the first
target.
Preparing to extract Peeta.
Will confirm when he's in hand.
Mockingjay One, prepare hovercraft
for evac.
You asked me to convince you...
that I was in love with Peeta.
Haven't I at least done that?
Miss Everdeen...
it's the things we love most...
that destroy us.
I want you to remember that
I said that.
Don't you think I know...
your friends are in the Tribute
Center?
Cut them off.
What happened?
Boggs, come in.
Do you read me?
He knows that they're in there.
It's a trap.
Katniss, hold it.
We have to get a hold of them.
We have to tell them to get out.
He knows.
There's no signal.
We can't contact them.
No.
Haymitch...
he knew the whole time.
He was taunting me.
No, Haymitch. They're in there.
No, we don't know that.
Did I lose them both tonight?
Shh.
Did I lose them?
I lost them both.
No!
There's no news.
I'm sorry.
It's the worst torture in
the world.
Waiting, when you know there's
nothing you can do.
Especially for people like us.
But whatever strength, courage...
madness...
keeps us going, you find it...
at times like these.
You have it, soldier.
It's what's kept you alive
all this time.
And it won't fail you now.
They're back.
I don't want that.
Johanna.
Finnick!
Annie?
Annie!
You're safe.
Gale!
Are you okay?
What?
What is it?
I don't get it.
Every gun was back online...
and on us and we flew right
past them.
They let us go.
He's in there.
Gas we used on the guards...
knocked him out, too, but it's
wearing off now.
You should be there when he
wakes up.
Thank you.
Peeta.
Peeta!
Peeta! Get off!
Get off of her!
Let go!
No, Katniss. No, you're a little
swollen. Don't touch.
No, no, no.
Calm down.
You're okay.
Tell her she's awake.
Don't try to talk.
Peeta's okay.
I promise.
I just had to get him off you.
It's called "hijacking."
We don't know how long the
Capitol's been doing this...
to Peeta.
It's fear conditioning...
enhanced with tracker jacker
venom.
You were stung in your first
Games, remember?
The venom puts the subject in
a dissociative state.
And they torture him...
with shocks and beatings, and
strip down his identity.
And then, all of that suffering
and fear is redirected.
Associated with other memories,
or a person.
They can change his memories
of Katniss?
To make her seem life-threatening.
They turned him into a weapon,
Katniss.
To kill you.
But, you can reverse it?
The fear is the most difficult
thing to overcome.
We're hardwired to remember
fear best.
It's new terrain.
But we've put together a team.
I'm optimistic.
Good evening.
Yesterday, I authorized...
a covert rescue mission inside
the Capitol.
I am pleased to announce...
that the Victors have been
liberated!
Let this day mark an historic
change.
With The Mockingjay and the
Victors beside us...
we have sent a clear message
to the Capitol.
That we will never again endure
injustice.
Today...
a day on which we reunited
family...
friends, and loved ones.
Let all of Panem come together.
Not to battle for the amusement
of the Capitol...
but to join hands in this fight.
Let today be the day we promise...
never to give up, never to
give in...
until we have made a new Panem...
where leaders are elected, not
imposed upon us.
And where the districts are
free...
to share the fruits of their
labors...
and not fight one another
for scraps!
This new Panem is on the horizon.
But we must take it for ourselves.
The road there leads through
the sharp mountains...
and deep ravines of District 2.
There, in the heart...
of Panem's steepest mountain
range...
lies the Capitol's principal
military facility.
We can conquer this stronghold...
because we are one people...
one army, one voice.
Because today is our new
beginning.
Today we have freed the Victors.
Tomorrow... Panem!
Hoorah!