Subtitles by explosiveskull but rectified by me
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Mm. Those are good worms
right there.
Hey, Alex! How's the commute
treating you?
Hey, I can't complain.
- That never stopped him before.
- Right?
Well, we made
good time today.
Red was one
of my students.
Hmm?
Not sure about
the dabbing though.
Mom! Mom, did you
get my picture?
Well, this is our stop.
♪ The birds in the
sky Go through the air ♪
♪ All the way there ♪
Today, we're gonna learn
about how Red saved the eggs.
I love Red!
I gotta go
to the bathroom!
Why didn't you go
in the slingshot?
Huh?
Bomb, anything
from Piggy Island?
- Nope.
- Chuck. Anything to the north?
- Nope. Nothing.
- What's that?
Uh-oh.
Incoming pie!
- It's coming straight for us.
- What do we do?
Duck!
What?
Ah!
- I got pie all over my face!
- Hey, sorry, buddy.
What, what?
Yeah!
Those pigs...
Are gonna pay...
For our lunches!
Uh... Because of our hunger
to give them...
A taste of their own...
Quesadillas!
What?
- It's Red.
- I'm sorry, guys.
We're taking over the Blue Line.
Official business.
- Oh, yeah!
- Of course, anything for you.
Hey, Red!
Isn't it funny
how nobody liked you
until you saved Bird Island?
But now we all love you.
Ha. Thanks so much
for bringing that up.
Okay, ready?
- Three...
- Two...
Two!
- Bomb, you say "one."
- Oh, right.
One!
Yoo-hoo.
Hot sauce, please.
Yeah! Got him.
- Thank you.
- Red! Red!
I really want
the red one. The red one.
Ha, ha! Balloonie!
Heh, heh. That's it.
A little bit higher.
Ha, ha!
But I was bouncing!
You mess with the hatchlings,
you get the cannonball.
Ready, big guy?
Oh, yeah.
You ready, bigger guy?
Cannonball! Cannonball!
♪ I need a hero ♪
Why won't you
just take a bath?
Huh?
This might pinch a little.
Ah! I can't see!
Catch you later.
You stupid birds.
No! Please, don't!
Aah!
Not on my watch.
Sorry, guys.
Excuse me, sir,
but I believe
this belongs to you.
My hero.
Don't. Stop.
I said, "Don't stop."
- Leonard?
- Got him!
Hey, Leonard,
you should probably...
Huh?
That's not coming
from Bird Island.
What the heck is that?
And where did it
come from?
We're gonna need
a bigger slingshot.
Another successful day
of protecting the island.
Great job, guys.
Oh, yeah.
Woo-hoo! Woo!
You saved us, Red.
You're our hero.
Heh, what can I say?
That's what I do.
Now, why don't you
just go run along
and keep your big,
cute eyes peeled
for the next pig prank,
all right?
Pigs.
We're going to get you!
Oink, oink, oink.
Adorable.
Let's finish cleaning up
these crabs,
then we can move on to...
Done and done.
- Red, what is it?
- What the heck?
Is it a per...? Is it a head?
What is that?
Oh, look. It seems like
it's some kind of note.
What if it's
a love note?
A message in a bottle?
Or a genie in a bottle.
Guys,
there's no bottle,
so just,
you know, stop.
Nice try, piggies.
News flash:
We're not idiots.
Hey.
Uh...
I got it!
Oh, no!
- Check it out, everybody.
- Let me see that.
- A truce! A truce!
- A truce with the pigs!
- A truce?
- The prank war is over!
What?
No, this is just another
one of their pranks.
- What?
- Huh?
This is a huge relief,
right?
Who else
was getting tired
of the pranking
and retaliation?
Me! This guy!
Tired? No, no, no.
Guys, listen.
Imagine all the fun things
we can do now.
I can think of one.
You think he'll go?
I think we've piqued
his interest.
No, no, no. Guys,
we are working tirelessly,
day and night,
to save the world.
But the world
doesn't need saving.
Of course they need us.
- Red.
- Huh?
Come here, hon.
What are you so afraid of?
Afraid of? I...
What do I have
to be afraid of?
♪ All by myself ♪
♪ Don't wanna be ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
- I'm not afraid of anything.
- You know what?
I'll write you a prescription
for fun with your cool friends.
- Especially Chuck.
- Come on. Come with us.
What are you talking...?
Come to what?
We can't tell you because
you wouldn't be into it.
Oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oink, oink, oink!
Ha! Now we have
all your eggs.
And there's nothing
you can do about it,
- Red.
- Oink, oink, oink.
Laugh it up, piggies,
because you're gonna
be crying in a second
when I kick your butts
- and take those rocks back.
- Eggs.
- What?
- You said "rocks"
instead of "eggs" again.
Oh, sorry.
I don't know why
I keep doing that.
Because they are rocks.
Don't cry, Sam-Sam.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Daddy.
Just borrowing my sisters
for a minute.
Ha. Now we really have
all your eggs.
Yeah, and there's nothing you
can do about it, Red.
Oink, oink,
oink, oink, oink.
Laugh it up, piggies,
because you're gonna be
crying in a second
when I kick your butts
and take all your...
Uh... uh...
Uh, uh. Um, um, um, um.
Oh, crap.
Okay, we'll just...
What is this thing that
almost killed me? Frozen water?
Who's ever heard
of frozen water?
Courtney? Courtney,
bring me those images.
What, what, what? Oh, okay,
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Give me that.
Oh, that looks cold.
Three umbrellas in one drink?
What kind of extravagant lunatic
are we dealing with?
Mm.
♪ Nibblin' on sponge cake ♪
♪ Watchin' the sun bake ♪
There goes my toothpaste.
I am tired of this.
Woo. Yes! Hot shower.
♪ Strummin' my six string ♪
There we go.
Go, Zeta. You killing it.
Woo! Zeta!
Come on, baby. Go get it.
Let's go get it.
Go get the stick.
Ha, ha!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa.
Oh, my gosh!
I can't do this anymore.
- Okay, Debbie?
- Okay.
I'm done. I'm done living
on this frozen,
seal-infested iceberg
of an island.
Fire another ice ball!
- Uh... We can't do that, Zeta.
- Wait...
You're torturing the engineer.
Um, uh, Hello?!
My limbs are beginning
to numb.
Oh, yeah, I forgot about that.
You better tell him
to improve his aim.
It's about time we start
living that good life.
Good life, here we come.
I deserve to feel
the hot sand
squishing between
my beautiful talons.
You deserve that and more.
Yes, I do!
- Ha, ha!
- Well, here we are.
Are you ready, Red?
Love awaits!
Speed dating? No. No way.
It's mating season.
All right, lovebirds.
You all know how this works.
When you hear this sound...
...then it's time to move on
to the next table,
where your soul mate
just might be waiting.
Yeah, I'm going home.
Absolutely not.
You have nothing else to do.
I hid your keys
on some part of my body,
and I'm not telling you
where unless you stay. Ha, ha!
Yeah, let's party!
Hey, yo!
Chuck's the name.
- Speed's the game. Like games?
- Well...
You entered the love lottery,
and guess what?
You won!
Because here I am.
- Hi.
I eat dirt.
Oh. Ew.
Hey, y'all!
Who's ready to party?
Not me.
No, I'm actually not here
for the whole
speed-dating horror-show thing
going on.
Uh-uh. Shh.
This mating dance
is for you.
♪ Y'all ready for this? ♪
I'd love to hear
about you.
What's your favorite sign?
This one's mine.
You know, the flavor
can vary greatly,
depending on the minerals
in the dirt.
I can tell which kind of worms
have crawled through there.
Or what sort of roly-polies used
it to raise their family in.
Um. Are you mad?
No.
- I don't know. You look mad.
- Well, I'm not.
You know what?
Maybe it's your eyebrows.
My eyebrows are fine.
That's the way I look.
It's like you've got
resting bird face.
Oh, yeah? Well, you know,
that's not a thing.
- Yes! Amazing.
- I'm not a total animal.
But I do enjoy eating dirt.
Okay, worms, birdseed
or just garbage
- from a dumpster?
- I'm sorry, what?
Favorite food, silly.
Don't think.
Just answer from your gut. Go!
Um. Uh, toast?
Okay. Toast.
Favorite color?
- Uh.
- Stupid question. Red, duh.
If you could have one
superpower, what would it be?
Um, to disappear,
like, right now.
Okay. What do you do
in your free time?
Yeah, I mean, I don't really
have any free time.
I kinda protect Bird Island
from being attacked,
and that's a full-time gig,
so yeah.
I thought I heard something
about a truce.
Ha, ha! No. A truce, no.
That's not gonna last.
You'll have a lot
more free time
now that nobody needs you
anymore, so...
Okay. We are done here.
Are you afraid to talk
about your feelings?
You know, just because
I don't want to talk about them
doesn't mean I'm afraid.
Okay. So avoids
personal questions.
- Unusually angry.
- Talks to herself.
- Self-esteem issues.
- Doesn't answer own questions.
Left-handed.
Probably a witch.
Looks like we're
definitely incompatible.
Oh, and you needed a form
to tell you that. Okay.
Hope you have luck
annoying the next guy.
I don't need luck.
I have a formula.
Okay. Have a nice life.
Have fun being alone.
Oh, I will.
Aw.
There he goes,
like a ship in the night.
No rudder, no purpose,
no crew.
Well, have a good night.
♪ In the arms of an angel ♪
♪ Fly away from here ♪
♪ From this dark cold
Hotel room ♪
♪ And the endlessness... ♪
Loser!
♪ In the arms... ♪
Hello! Oh.
Look, Red, I know
we've had our differences.
Oh, like when you tried
to eat our young?
I come in peace.
- Ouch.
- Aah!
Look, I don't want
to see your face
any more than you
want to see mine.
We're all in danger!
- Yeah. From you.
- Ouch!
No, we have a truce.
Didn't you get my note?
It was on a balloon.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You wanted to talk.
This is not how a truce works.
Just say what
you gotta say
and then get out.
Red, we've discovered
that there's a third island,
and they're plotting
to destroy us all.
A third island?
Give me one reason
why I should believe you.
Haven't you noticed any strange
objects falling from the sky?
Giant balls of ice?
♪ But you'll look sweet ♪
♪ Upon the seat ♪
♪ Of my... ♪
♪ Bicycle built for two ♪
Nope, nothing.
Haven't seen anything.
Well, I have,
and I'll show you the proof.
Squeal Team Six!
What the...?
Hey, hey, hey.
Easy, easy. Stop.
Everybody stop.
Aah!
That image in your hand
is Eagle Island,
and those are eagles.
Eagles? How did you get these?
From a drone.
- And do you spy on us with that?
- Yes.
So have you seen me...?
Yes, and it's disgusting.
Red, this is bigger than pranks.
We need to put aside our
differences and work together.
To save our whole world
from being destroyed.
Red! Red! Red!
What we really need is a hero.
I'm in.
Wonderful!
We'll have to get
a team together.
Yes, we will.
But, hey, I'm in charge.
Actually, that position's
been filled.
- Boo-yah!
- Uh.
Yeah. By me.
Oh, man, you're gonna
love this guy.
Not the smartest bird
in the tree,
but what he lacks in smarts,
he makes up for in firepower.
Achoo!
- Happy birthday!
- Aah!
We've got a number
two at the Porta Potty.
All right, I'm going!
We're busting you out.
Uh... how?
Aah!
Like that.
Oh, I love it.
Bomb, what was that noise?
- You're still grounded!
- I'm an adult, Mom!
- Run.
- Bomb, get back here!
Aah!
This guy is so fast,
he can beat time
itself in a footrace.
Hey, Chuck, we're putting
together a team.
And I think
we're on it!
Come on, everybody.
Let's work those booties!
I'm in.
- Ha, ha, great!
- But how did you...?
BT-dubs,
you misspelled "heist."
It's "E-I,"
I corrected it.
Don't worry.
It's a common misperception.
Well, thank you.
You're right. He's fast.
Now,
this guy is kind of a ding-dong,
but he's the only
eagle we know.
Well, you've come
to the right eagle.
Tell me more.
It's a really exciting mission
to a place called Eagle...
- Eagle Island?
- Yes.
So you've heard...
Heard of it.
Nice to meet you!
Okay, so now we just need
to figure out
how this volcanic
super-weapon works, huh?
We're gonna need some kind
of engineering wizard, brainiac.
- Hm.
Oh!
Yes, Chuck. You obviously
have something
you want to say or sing.
I have got just the guy.
It's a girl.
My sister Silver.
She goes to Avian Academy,
top of her class.
- She would be perfect.
- Yeah, she totally would.
- See you at the dorm!
- Yeah, see you, Ella.
Hey, good catch!
I mean, we all just thought
she was weird, you know?
She skipped four grades,
won an Engineer
of the Year Award,
and got a scholarship
at Avian Academy.
Perfect. That is exactly
what we're looking for.
You are absolutely
gonna love her.
But don't love her too much.
That's my sister, Red.
Or I'll crush
every bone in your body!
Oh. Frisbee!
Hi, I'm Chuck. Know where
the Engineering department is?
With a combination
of over 30 silk,
wire and cotton-based
threads spun together,
I now present to you...
Super String!
I said, "It's Super String!"
More like
"Stupid String."
I know what
you're thinking, Mike.
You're like,
"What's so super about it?"
Great question, Mike.
Well, how about that
it's very easily able
to withstand the pull
of 18,000 more kilos
than any other string known to...
Snooze alert.
Known to bird-kind!
Or pig-kind,
for that matter.
What's up, sis?
Chuck?
I'm so happy to... It's really...
Great to... Jinx, jinx.
- Jinx!
- Jinx. One, two, three. I win!
You can't speak until someone
says your name.
Hello? You in here?
Hello?
- You?
You.
Wait. You know this guy?
I would
answer, but you jinxed me.
Oh, okay, Chuck,
I unjinx you.
This is one of my best buddies,
Red. These are the guys.
- Hi.
- We're the guys.
Guys, this is Silver,
the greatest kid sister
in the world.
I'm not exactly
a kid anymore, Chuck.
Oh, you'll always be
my kid sister!
Okay. Hey, everyone.
You know, I don't think
this is gonna work.
It's just that
I'm not sure
you're gonna be compatible
with the team.
Oh, wow, it is such a pleasure
to meet not you, but you!
I've never met
a pig before.
Your technological achievements
are amazing.
- May I shake your hoof?
- Why, thank you.
I like her.
- And this has to be Bomb.
- Whoa!
How'd you know that?
You have a fuse
coming out of your head.
Oh, so cool!
Backflip.
So I, um... I hear
you're some kind of
engineering wizard
or whatever.
Oh, ha. I mean, I don't like
to brag, but...
Wait. Who's that?
And why is she all over
these achievement awards?
The kid's amazing, right?
Not a kid anymore, Chuck.
Toot toot! Tickle Train
arriving at Sister Station!
Chuck, no.
I am a serious academic.
I am a serious...
Stop!
Oh, look how cute this is.
♪ We're sailing in the ocean
We must ♪
♪ Row! Row! ♪
♪ The eggs are in our sights
And we must ♪
♪ Go! Go! ♪
♪ We'll get them back
Before our parents ♪
♪ Know! Know! ♪
♪ And save the day like Red
The real ♪
♪ Hero! Row! ♪
Gotcha!
Woo-hoo! We did it.
That was so easy!
Yeah!
A little too easy,
actually.
What do you mean
by that?
Well, normally,
when things are this easy,
some dramatically
unexpected setback occurs.
- I don't get it.
- Me neither.
Well, it's kind
of hard to explain.
But it's sort of like,
you know how some...?
Oh, see? Like that.
Are you freaking
kidding me?
Each of you has
been selected because
you're the best
in your field.
- Oh.
- That we could find.
Oh.
Your skills will be
put to the test
facing this.
As you can clearly see,
this is a vol...
Volcano.
"A volcano" is what
my assistant
was going to say.
- You're the assistant!
- Let go. Let go.
- No, I'm the leader.
- I'll take that.
Actually,
it's a composite volcano.
You can tell
by the height
and the apparent
vent clusters.
Okay, forget I said "volcano."
This is a...
It's a super-weapon!
Weird, because it looks
just like a volcano.
Yep, and here's
the scary part.
This is their
psychotic leader!
Ooh! How'd that get
in there? Ha, ha. Next.
- Oh, butt shot.
- Next. No. Next. Next!
I don't even know
what I'm looking at.
Courtney!
I mean, you took them.
This is their
psychotic leader.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey. Buddy, do you know her?
What? Me? No.
No, definitely not,
absolutely not.
Never seen her
before in my life.
Who is that? I don't know!
Not terribly convincing,
but moving on.
Great.
What's the plan?
All right, here's what
we're looking at, folks.
Step one: Travel undetected
to Eagle Island.
- Hmm.
- Uh-huh.
Step two: We're gonna break
into the super-weapon.
- Got it.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And step three:
Ooh, ooh.
Deactivate the superweapon.
Once we break in there...
No plan...
hopefully, before both islands
are destroyed and we all die,
so that's, uh... That's it.
Right. So I just have
a few questions.
Why? I explained everything.
It's a foolproof plan.
Yeah. How do we sneak
onto the island?
What is the super-weapon
and how do we deactivate it?
And when you say "escape,"
how do you plan to do that?
This is a crucial
thing to figure out.
I agree.
Why isn't she in charge?
Told you she's super smart.
Hey, guys,
hold on a second, please.
- Mighty Eagle?
- What? What are you looking at?
Do you have
an Eagle Island map?
What? No. No, there's no map.
- Oh, it's a map.
- Yeah, that's a map.
Mm-hm. Okay,
I just wanna read it.
Wait a minute.
Do you guys hear that?
Do we hear what?
Sounds like a, um,
like a whistle.
It almost sounds like a:
Hey, guys?
Run!
Emergency exit,
all the way down!
Well, that's not safe.
Wait! Stop!
- Holy macaroni!
- Oh, boy.
Everyone hop on!
Rewind it. Rewind it.
Play it again.
Ha, ha. Yes, baby! We knocked
the top right off of that!
Glenn, you didn't mess
it up this time.
- Boom! Up top. Or not.
- Nailed it!
Jerry, up top.
That should send him running.
Wait. "Him"?
Who you sending running?
Yeah. Who's "him"?
"Them." I said "them."
Stop asking me stupid questions.
I'm so sorry.
- Wow.
- That was crazy.
We could have died.
Thanks for saving our lives,
Mighty Eagle!
Well, you can always
count on...
Everyone grab the map!
Hey, it's working.
Left! Left! Lean to the left!
Please tell me
that was your pants ripping.
I don't wear pants!
None of us wear pants!
Uh-oh.
Eight point one seconds.
Silver! No!
Oh.
Uh...
- Heh, heh.
- Hey!
What is this?
Oh, well, I mean,
she was, you know,
just thanking me
for saving everyone, so...
- I'm sorry. Saving everyone?
- Yeah.
You know,
the map was my idea.
It ripped.
Maybe because there's
too many birds.
I...
My mountain!
We are in trouble.
We gotta stop
that super-weapon.
Jinx!
Oh, this is bad.
This is really bad.
Eagle Mountain?
Are we gonna be okay?
Oh, my gah...
What happened
to Eagle Mountain, Mom?
Wait a minute.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Why isn't anybody leaving?
Why they not scared?
Okay. Oh, okay, okay.
Here's what we gonna do.
I want y'all to take
all of those ice balls
and fill them up with... Ha, ha...
Molten lava.
That's not possible.
What? You never heard
of thermal emulsifiers?
Well, yes, yes.
You just got to get
a polyacrylamide
to enhance the nanoparticle
and surfactant association
between the two materials.
Uh. Okay.
So you do that,
and I'm gonna go feed my baby.
Yes, I'm finally gonna
feed my baby.
There you go.
Who's my baby?
You're my baby.
What...? Don't...
You better not wink at me.
Don't you wink at me.
Who could have done this?
- I can't believe it.
- Are we gonna be okay?
- What are we gonna do?
- All right, guys, do not worry.
We got this.
Red here has got your back.
And your front
and your sides.
And my floof?
Yeah, even your cute
little floof.
Looks like
you're gonna be okay.
So are you 100 percent sure
we shouldn't evacuate?
No, Red's gonna take care
of us. Right, Red?
Yes! Everybody, please,
just stay calm.
Great news!
Thank you!
We're gonna be okay.
Red's here.
- We love you, Red!
- We need you!
Oh, thank you.
Your support means
the world to me.
Okay, Leonard,
so where's our ride?
Aw.
It's so cute.
Wow. Okay. And how are we all
supposed to fit in...?
Oh, I think we'll manage.
Boop.
Whoa, okay.
Whoa.
Oh, my gah...
All aboard!
Whoa.
Anyone want to grab
their own bag or anything?
Don't screw this up,
Red!
If we die, it's kind
of your fault.
I got this.
Wow.
Ow!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to introduce you
to our master of gadgetry:
- Garry!
This is it?
This is the amazing team
I've been working around
the clock for?
Ha, ha. Working with
what we got.
Well, that's disappointing.
Wow. Okay.
This is the part
where you get up and follow me!
Welcome to my
piggy gadget lab.
Oh, yeah.
Everywhere you
look, you'll see inventions
being tested
by my team of guinea pigs.
- Oh. This is so cool.
- I know. Right?
All the gadgets have
been designed specifically
with your current mission
in mind.
The first being Invisa-Spray.
Need to go undetected
in plain sight?
Invisa-Spray does
exactly that.
Wow, I'm invisible!
Whoa.
"Whoa," indeed.
That's amazing.
How long does
the invisibility last for?
- Forever.
- Wait. What?
Tina, we're not gonna be able
to see each other tonight.
And what does the next
gadget do? Bury us alive?
What? That would be ridiculous.
Ix-nay the shovel-ay.
And moving right along.
What are you guys doing?
This is so fun!
Oh, it's so squishy.
What is this stuff?
Oh, well,
that is a special type
of flame retardant
we call pig snot.
Why do you call it...?
You know what? Never mind.
Ugh.
Yeah! Lick it.
Now, everyone,
prepare yourselves
'cause this next one
is really something special.
Whoa. So shiny.
Yes, my friend. Bold yet sleek.
Simple while complex.
This device can detect
an eagle anywhere
within a 100-foot radius.
- Well, how does it work?
- Simply push this button,
and it does the rest.
- Whoa.
There's an eagle nearby.
- There's an eagle nearby.
- Why, yes. Clearly, there is.
- Okay, you got me, guys.
- There's an eagle nearby.
- This clever thing will...
- no doubt prove to be...
- There's an eagle nearby.
- crucial during your mission.
- Wonderful. That's amazing!
- There's an eagle nearby.
- Can you turn it off?
- It'll turn itself off.
- There's an eagle nearby.
Oh, thank goodness.
One hour after it doesn't
detect any more eagles.
- What?
- There's an eagle nearby.
- Hey! Hey!
There's an eagle near...
- There.
- Oh, thank you.
Okay, guys,
these gadgets are terri...
Hey, hey, Red,
can we chat for a sec?
I can tell you're used
to running the show.
That's great and all. But maybe
since we're all a team here,
a team you put together,
maybe you can try
to be more supportive.
The results might
surprise you, huh?
Fine. Fine, fine, fine.
Garry. Woo. Unbelievable.
Really, really good stuff.
You know what? I'm sure
I can figure out a plan to...
You know,
to use all this...
This awesomeness that you've...
Bomb!
Hi, Red.
How are we ever
gonna get up there?
I want my unborn sisters back.
It's just, the eggs are
up there, and we're down here.
Oh, how are we
ever gonna
get up there?
Oh.
You're doing great, Zoe.
Now hold it tight, okay?
Uh-oh.
Quick, let some air out!
It won't untie!
Okay, let me try. Aah!
What's...? What's the prob...?
Prob... Prob...
Problem?
♪ Ground control to
Major Tom ♪
♪ Take your protein pills
And put your... ♪
Don't worry, guys.
I'll get us out of this.
The eggs!
We got you for reals now.
Mwah!
See? I told you I would
get us out of this.
A boa constructor.
It is glorious! I'm a genius!
Yes, I love it!
This was my idea.
- Wait. Wait.
- Look out!
- Aah! I'm burning!
- I told you to look out.
Glenn, I wanted lava balls,
not lava puddles.
Uh-oh.
Glenn's messing up.
I mean, we... We're very close.
We just need two more weeks.
Two weeks? Two weeks.
Huh.
Um. It's quite
the undertaking.
Okay, okay, you know what?
I'm doing that thing again.
That thing, you know, like,
where I'm not quite sure
I heard
what I think I heard.
Hey, skinny, sassy face!
Did you hear "two weeks,"
or did you hear "tomorrow"?
Um. Uh, I heard "tomorrow"?
Fat dude,
what did you hear?
Uh. Definitely
what you said?
Okay, you know what
I'm gonna do?
I am gonna call
my old engineer, Steve.
And you know what?
You're a lot like him.
Hey, it's Steve!
Sorry I can't come
to the phone right now...
...but you know what to do.
Oh, yeah.
I had to discipline Steve.
So, what was that
that you
- had said to me?
- Tomorrow.
That's what I thought you said.
See, everybody happy now.
♪ Turn down for what ♪
No. No, no, no.
Uh-oh. Whoa. Whoa.
Careful, buddy. That's not...
Whoa.
Okay, guys, let's do this.
- Here we go.
- We got this.
We got an island
to save, kids.
Two islands. We have two
islands to save.
I can't do this.
- I've made a terrible mistake.
- What are you talking about?
Zeta.
- Who is Zeta?
- The leader of the eagles.
The one who's been trying
to destroy our islands.
And my ex-fiancée.
- Wait. What?
- Did you say "fiancée"?
Beyoncé?
And you're just
telling us this now?
Better late than never.
Heh-heh-heh.
It was many years ago,
in the 1990s.
She was the smartest girl
in school.
And I had an incredible
sense of fashion.
Whoa.
Hey.
It was love at first sight.
- Woo!
- Ha, ha!
♪ I don't want to wait ♪
"I miss you"? Aw.
♪ For our lives to be over ♪
Whoa!
She was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
But since I wasn't
quite ready to mate for life...
Oh, wow. Uh...
An engagement ring?
Uh...
Naturally, I...
I...
I abandoned her.
How could you
leave like that?
Because I am a coward.
Many of you didn't know
that about me.
Well, actually...
I assume she's been
heartbroken ever since.
It's all my fault.
So this is Beyoncé
we're talking about?
You know what?
I just remembered.
I have something
to do
back home!
Thanks for the help.
Well, that got dark.
Okay, gang, listen up.
This place is crawling
with security,
but if you guys follow me...
Hey, hey, hey,
what's going on?
What do you think, guys?
Should we show him?
Show me what?
Harvey!
Super lifelike
disguise, right?
Disguise?
We thought we'd let
you drive.
And I'm gonna help
you pedal.
Wait. You guys came up
with this idea without me?
Yeah.
♪ All by myself ♪
♪ Don't wanna be
All by myself ♪
Yeah, well,
it's not gonna work.
We think it's our best chance
of getting past the guards.
- I'm with Silver.
- Me too.
Yeah, she's smart.
Everyone is counting on me
to make sure that...
Us. Everyone's counting
on us.
Fine. Whatever.
So your plan is to get
into the super-weapon
with that?
Harvey, don't take offense.
He does not mean it.
Fine. Fine. You know what?
I'll just be up here
saving the world.
Just like I should
have been doing this whole time.
Uh, guys? I 100 percent believe
in you and this Harvey idea,
but I think this one's
gonna need me.
Well, they didn't see us.
This isn't
an "us" thing, Silver.
I've got this covered.
Go away.
Is this a good time
to talk about feelings?
No, it's not a good time!
No. No, I don't need
your help, okay?
I meant to slip.
Leave me alone!
Your hat fell off.
Yeah, I got rid of it
because it was getting heavy.
All right, guys,
beak action is a go.
- Arms, what say you?
- Armed and ready.
Two fully functional armies.
Right above our leggies.
Ha, ha.
Okay, leggies,
show me what you got.
Oh, yeah.
Woo-hoo!
We got this!
We must look amazing!
Okay, guys,
we're going live.
Come on, Jerry.
You know there's no snacking
while we're on duty.
But I had a really
small breakfast.
All right, I'll do the talking.
Hello, fellow eagle guards.
- Hm?
Oh, no.
He's doing a voice.
I'm running late
to the old job.
Commute was rough today
for some reason.
But the good news
is I made it!
Ninety-degree turn. Quick!
But the
good news is I made it.
ID, please.
Oh. Uh... ID?
Uh. Not sure I have it on me.
Act like
you're checking pockets.
It's stuck!
Stuck?
Ow! What the heck
are you doing?!
Be on alert for an intruder.
Wait a minute.
What's happening?
Shh. He's on to us.
Hmm.
We are so dead.
All right.
I know what's going on here.
I'm picking up
what you're putting down.
Jerry, you getting
a load of this?
Yeah, I think I am.
Yeah, Jerry, I know exactly
what's going on.
This right here...
is obviously...
a new guy!
Yeah, impostors in a costume.
Wait. What?
- Oh.
- Uh.
- Huh?
Yeah! You're the new guard
for the east tower.
Yes.
Yes, I am.
I knew it.
Jerry, swipe
the new guy in.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Okay, guys, we're in.
Oh, yeah.
Woo! Woo-hoo!
- We did it.
- Work it. Work it.
- Okay.
- Wiggle the butt.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Huh?
♪ I'm on fire ♪
Come on, come on.
Let's go. Let's go!
♪ Baby, baby, baby
Baby, baby, baby ♪
Get to the top
of the super-weapon. Check!
Yay!
You did it.
Okay, so how's it looking
down there?
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Do you see that?
Oh, it's the super-weapon.
No, the power supply
to the super-weapon.
All we gotta do is get
down there and cut it.
Okay, assuming we don't
get electrocuted,
there are guards there,
there and there.
And we don't have
enough rope to...
- Watch and learn.
- What? What are you doing?
He's not clipped in.
Red, are you crazy?
Trust me.
I know what I'm do...
So yeah. Rope wasn't
long enough.
I know that.
It wasn't supposed to be.
That's part of my plan.
Except I wanted to be
over on that side.
- Okay, but...
- Watch this!
Nope. No, no, no.
Oh. Hello.
Hi. Now my plan
really starts.
- Hi again.
- I swung back
to tell you something,
but I forgot what it was. Bye.
Got it. Got it.
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
Grip, grip, grip. Okay...
Huh? You hear something?
- So you want a push?
- Yes.
Ha, ha.
Hi. Oh, no.
Your feather!
The guards!
Watch out.
Silver,
what are you doing?
Oh, no.
Where's Red?
Hey, Silver.
Check it out.
This is how a hero
saves the world.
Ha, ha.
Oh, come on!
Nothing works around here!
Now we escape.
You two are coming with me.
- I... uh.
- Nice abs.
I know.
Okay, try zero-zero-zero-zero.
Try one-two-three-four.
Now try four-three-two-one.
Try 1-800-OPEN.
I don't know.
Chuck, what's your birthday?
Nothing's working!
Oh, no. Someone's coming.
Quick. Hide.
Ouch.
There's an eagle nearby.
There's an eagle near...
All right. You get started
on the lockdown sequence.
- I'm gonna hit the john.
- Yes, sir.
We gotta get that key card.
Okay, Courtney, get that card.
There's something in the way.
Chuck, what's going on
down there?
There's a divider in the way.
Maybe it's on the other side.
Okay, hold on.
Pretend to pee-pee.
Oh, no. He's leaving.
Chuck, get that card.
I got it.
Aah!
Yeah, I'm just gonna...
Boop.
We're home!
We're home, everybody.
Yay!
Woo!
Oh, we missed you so much,
Bird Island.
"Bird Island"?
This is Piggy Island,
sillies.
Bird Island
is way over there.
Ha, ha. We're in!
Oh, my goodness gravy.
I wanna see.
No. Hold on!
I just wanna see.
We don't have time.
Uh-oh.
What? What's happening?
I think he's challenging us
to a break-dance battle?
Aah!
Oh, it's on!
Woo! Whoa!
What's happening?
Looks like a popping
and locking.
A little what?
Pop, pop, pop!
Ah!
Hey, handsome.
- Hey.
- Take those two
and put them on ice.
They got Red and my sister.
We gotta go.
But the super-weapon.
That's my sister, mister.
And I'm gonna save her.
Chuck, slow down.
Slow down. Stop!
Oh, yeah!
Hmm?
Huh?
Hey.
Hey. You done?
- What happened?
- Oh, let's see.
Well, you got us captured
and trapped in ice
on top of giant pool toys.
Good job.
I just thought that
maybe if I could...
Stop me?
Yeah, you two lovebirds
just thought
y'all could sail over here
and stop me.
- Lovebirds? No way.
- No, no, no.
We're barely,
like, friend birds.
So typical.
Type-A male paired
with a strong female,
and you just can't stand it,
can you?
- Well, I...
- Let me guess.
You prefer to fly solo.
I have to save everybody
all by myself!
Just like a man.
Ooh, ouch.
That is kind of true, though.
Maybe she was
a little clingy at times.
Maybe she gave you
that engagement ring
a little bit too early.
I don't think
she's talking about us.
Maybe she's
talking about...
Mighty Eagle.
- Debbie! Turn on the TV.
- Yes.
Okay...
It's the one
with the red button on top.
Okay...
Red, Debbie.
What I'm planning
to do is take
these little-bitty,
undeveloped islands,
and turn them into
my own personal paradise.
You're insane!
I am putting myself first.
Because you know what?
I worked hard for it,
and I deserve it.
All I gotta do is clear out
all these inhabitants.
You're a monster!
Glenn, show them what
I'm talking about.
Excuse me?
Are you getting smart with me right now?
♪ I can't believe we're
soaring Through the sky! Sky! ♪
♪ All thanks to our pig pals
They are cool ♪
♪ Guys! Guys! ♪
What the heck
was that?
Piggy Island?
Attention, everyone!
It is imperative that you all
run for your lives!
Bird Island?
My mommy and daddy.
Huh?
Terence?
Where are the kids?
I don't understand.
I thought Red
was supposed to save us!
Oh, my gah...
Huh?
Oh, my gah.
Oh! Ha-ha-ha!
It actually worked.
Yes, yes, yes!
Those islands are filled
with innocent birds and pigs!
You all had the chance
to evacuate.
But for some reason,
you didn't.
So you are 100 percent sure
we shouldn't evacuate?
I am sure.
No one needs to evacuate.
Everybody just stay calm.
Sorry. Ha-ha-ha.
Not sorry.
I'm truly not sorry.
Dodged that bullet.
This is all my fault.
Red, it's not your fault.
No. It... It is my fault.
I put myself
before everyone else.
I was afraid if I wasn't
a hero anymore,
they'd all stop...
They'd all stop liking me.
Oh, Red.
So you did all of this
because you were afraid
of not being liked?
I...
Yes.
My fellow eagles,
who's tired of living
in an icy wasteland?
We are!
What is she doing?
Who is tired
of sipping
hot chocolate
and getting brain freeze?
Aah! Me!
Who's tired of frozen dinners?
Whoa, frozen dinners?
Come on, Bomb,
let's go.
Who's tired of playing only
only Vanilla Ice,
Ice-T and Ice Cube?
I am.
Who wants to live worry-free
under a beautiful tropical sun?
Me! I want to be hot!
I want it hot!
There's no turning back!
The future we deserve
is about to be ours!
Glenn! Activate the weapon!
Start the countdown.
Ten minutes to launch.
All right, stand back.
- Wait, did you hear that too?
- Bomb?
What in the...?
- Really, guys?
- What? No. We weren't...
Uh. Yeah, they were.
Guys, why is that clock
counting backwards?
- We've only got 10 minutes.
- It's now or never.
Pig-kind and bird-kind
are depending on us.
What are we gonna do, Red?
Well, I, uh..
I think...
in times like these,
we need someone who can lead.
We need a hero.
You know what we need?
We need Silver.
Huh?
Oh.
Got any ideas?
I've got a few, actually.
Okay.
That's the heart
of the super-weapon,
and if you look closely,
you can see
that it's powered
by air pressure.
Moisture around
a composite volcano
instantly vaporizes,
sending a plume
of highly pressurized steam
to the surface.
That steam is contained
by the pressure chamber.
And that's the part
we need to destroy.
Only problem is,
it's surrounded by armed guards.
Bomb. Do you think you can
take out those guards?
Some of them look
kind of tough.
It won't be easy.
Yeah, right.
Of course. Got it.
Great.
Chuck, I need you
to disable
the security cameras.
There's a bunch,
so you'll have to work fast.
Fast? Don't even worry
about it, sis.
Red, you and I
have to get inside
one of those ice balls.
Inside an ice ball?
I... Sure. Okay.
Leonard, Courtney, Garry,
do you see that giant lever
near the orange lava tube?
Copy that.
I need you to pull it.
That will create
a ramp so
when Red and I roll down
in the ice ball,
we'll be launched
through the air
at the perfect trajectory
to take out the super-weapon.
- Got it?
- Now you're talking.
Great plan, Silver.
Mama would be so proud.
Okay, everyone put
your wings and hooves in.
Go, team!
Chuck, let us know when
you've disabled the cameras.
Okay. On it.
Easy, boys.
Heh-heh-heh.
Heh.
Huh? Hey, Jerry.
Yeah?
- Come here. Look at this.
- What's up?
Uh... It says
everything's normal.
Jerry, are you seeing this?
Uh... I don't see anything.
No, not that one.
Not over here.
Oh, I think this one's it.
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Is it me
You're looking for? ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
♪ You're all I've ever wanted ♪
We just need to
get over to that track
and follow it up to the lever.
Okay.
- Phew.
- Ow!
Don't touch the lava tube.
I don't know if I'm gonna fit.
Just suck in your butt.
Does anyone smell bacon?
Ow!
Aah!
No one can see me.
Light on my toes.
♪ I'm sneaking
I'm sneaking up real quiet ♪
♪ Who took you out?
I don't know ♪
♪ Because I didn't hear
Them coming ♪
♪ Because they snuck up
On me ♪
Captain, you seeing this?
No one sees me.
Take them out.
So why didn't you
just team up with Chuck?
He's definitely
faster than me.
Nope, he's too light.
Why not Bomb, then?
You know, he's heavier than me.
Too slow. You're perfect.
Oh, that's funny.
I thought we weren't compatible.
Yeah. Well, um, you know...
Some of the variables
changed, so...
Oh, variables, huh?
So, uh, what are we doing here?
We're on a mission.
Oh, yeah, the mission.
Of course.
Okay, Bomb, we are in position.
Time to take out those guards.
Copy that.
Come on, Bomb,
hold it together.
Tighten up. You can do this.
We got a 10-91G
in the control room.
Roger that.
Oh!
You can do this, Bomb.
Just take them out.
Just take them out!
Thanks for taking us out, man.
Even Glenn's
having a good time!
♪ Baby shark, doo, doo
Doo, doo, doo, doo ♪
♪ Baby shark
♪ Baby shark ♪
All together!
Silver, baby sharks
have taken the bait.
Roger that. Okay, Leonard.
Time for Plan X.
Plan X? I thought
you said spandex.
Spandex?
♪ I'm too sexy for my shirt ♪
♪ Too sexy for my shirt ♪
Well, I'm working
with what I got.
Looking good, guys.
Looking good.
You gotta swing your arms.
I am swinging my arms.
I'm swinging them
like this.
Yes!
Three minutes to launch.
Debbie, we are
starting over, girl.
This is like New Year's.
Oh, my gosh, yes, okay.
I'm gonna get some
glitter and decorations.
This is gonna be
so much fun!
Zeta!
We have a problem.
Oh, my good...
Aah!
Go find them!
Okay. That's where
the ice balls are made.
We've gotta jump in that hole
at the exact moment
that the jaws open up.
- Are you sure about this?
- Uh. Actually, no.
- Going with my gut this time.
- Whoa. Didn't expect that.
Attention, all eagles.
The prisoners have escaped.
♪ Doo, doo
Daddy shark ♪
All right, guys,
back to work!
Go! Let's do this!
Guys, guys, guys!
Whoa, hold on!
We're not done hanging out
and having a good time.
Silver, we've got a problem.
♪ Back to work
Doo, doo, doo ♪
♪ Doo, doo, doo
Back to work ♪
- Jump on the count of three.
- Got it.
One, two...
- three!
- Whoa!
Whoa!
Ha, ha. It worked! Red?
Ha, ha. We did it!
- Oh, no. What the...?
- Lava injectors!
I got this one.
Oh, whoa, Red!
Aah! Aah!
Well, it's all downhill
from here.
Whoa!
- Okay, now what?
- If my calculations are correct,
we should be tall enough
to reach that lever
if all three of us...
Garry?
Uh... Hang in there!
Whoa!
Okay, new plan.
We need to get
to 65 miles per hour.
Left, right,
left, right.
At least we're gonna
get all our steps in.
Two minutes to launch.
Two minutes, everybody!
Two minutes to launch!
Left, right, left, right.
We gotta break
that super-weapon!
- Leonard.
- Yeah?
Is the ramp elevated?
We're working on it.
What are we gonna do?
- Uh...
- Okay, let's just
- figure this out.
- I have an idea.
Yeah. Now is not the time,
Courtney.
I'm just trying
to figure out
how we're gonna get up
to that lever.
- Hey. Leonard.
- Huh?
Oh, that could work!
Silver!
How we doing on speed?
We're maxing out
at 59 miles per hour.
We need to get to 65!
It's stuck!
We need more weight!
Okay. Here goes.
It... It's moving!
Oh, that's not good.
Aah!
Sixty-three, 64...
- One more minute!
- Yes!
- One minute.
- Let's just
clear these houses
from your beachfront view.
- The lever is broken!
- Broken?
Leonard, don't you have
any gadgets you can use?
- We're almost to the ramp.
- Gadgets?
Gadgets!
Forty-five seconds.
Attention, all personnel.
- Initiating launch sequence.
- Initiating.
Garry, any way
you can bring me the gadgets?
No, there isn't.
Chuck, I need Garry's backpack.
On it.
Garry, where are you?
Chuck, over here!
Hi-yah!
Yes! We've reached 65 miles
per hour!
Fifteen seconds.
Ha, ha! Let's do this!
Fourteen, 13, 12...
11...
- Ten. Nine.
- Leonard, it's now or never.
- Oh, no.
- Got to raise that ramp!
Seven. Six.
Five.
Four. Three.
Two.
And one!
There's an eagle nearby.
- Yeah!
- There's an eagle nearby.
No!
Huh?
That's my sister!
- It didn't work?
- I... I don't get it.
Of course it didn't work.
You must really love
your little islands
to risk your lives
trying to save them!
Well, guess what?
I don't care.
Because this right here
is ice-cold, baby.
No!
- Zeta!
- What?
Wait!
- What? What...?
- Mighty Eagle!
Yeah!
I'm the cause of all this.
I ran out on you
on our wedding day.
And ever since then,
you've been tormented inside.
Now? This is when you
choose to do this?
So take me!
Not these islands.
You have got some
flipping nerve!
I know!
I ripped your heartstrings
right out.
- That's it. Super String.
- What?
...has been burning a hole
in your sanity!
- Set yourself free...
- Okay, I'm seeing it.
Yeah.
- Go ahead. Do your worst to me.
- Chuck.
I deserve it.
You think this
is about you, Ethan?
Ethan?
Oh, that is so hilarious
/ embarrassing
/ I hadn't thought about
your fat butt in 20 years.
Wait, what?
You are a lazy,
uncoordinated,
fish-eyed fool.
You ain't worth the salt
in your bread.
You are nothing to me!
You are nothing!
I don't think
about you at all.
I don't think about
your stinking feet.
your rusty hands.
I don't think about
your rusty elbows...
Wait, so you have
or you haven't thought about me?
News flash, bro:
I am over you,
I'm over this place,
and I am ready to get
that upgrade situation
going for me
and my daughter.
Hey.
Well, our daughter.
What?
- That's my dad?
- I have a daughter?
Yes, you do!
And I raised her all by myself
in this icy wasteland.
But now I'm gonna be
sipping piña coladas
on those warm tropical islands
like I deserve to!
- Stop!
- Oh, no.
Huh?
- It's working!
- Yes!
Oh, no.
Gotcha!
You can do it!
Hold on to that string!
The hatchlings.
Oh, no! They're in trouble!
Jump!
- Everyone...
- Run!
Let's go!
No, no, wait.
This is not happening.
Gotcha!
- I'm freaking out!
- Me too!
- We did it.
Debbie?
Where is she? Where's Debbie?
Debbie, no.
What have I done?
Oh, Debbie.
Are you okay?
Sweetie?
Honey pie?
Love of the last
one minute of my life?
Dad?
Yes.
You are so strong!
He saved my life!
Oh, Debbie.
Mom, can we keep him?
Please?
Oh, I, uh...
Wait. Wait.
Before you answer,
you should see something.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mm-hmm.
And the one closest to my heart.
♪ I don't want to wait ♪
♪ For our lives to be over ♪
♪ Will it be yes
Or will it be ♪
♪ Sorry? ♪
Oh, no.
♪ Doo, doo, doo
Doo, doo ♪
You are so pitiful.
♪ Yeah ♪
I've never been
to a wedding before!
Oh, okay,
who's getting married again?
Oh, Terence, this is like our
wedding but expensive. Ha, ha.
Flowers for you,
flowers for you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
birds and pigs,
we are gathered here today
because of these two characters.
Not only because they're being
joined in holy matrimony,
but also because one of them
tried to destroy our islands
for her own selfish reasons.
Guess who.
Oh, it's such
a beautiful wedding.
It really is.
But Mighty Eagle swooped
in at the last second
and got all the credit
for stopping her.
Yes, you did, baby.
I love you.
Wrap it up.
I now pronounce you
eagle and husband.
- You may now kiss the...
- Come here, you.
Ugh!
All right.
Get it, Mighty Eagle.
Oh, that is disgusting!
Go, Zeta! Go, Dad!
Attention!
Attention, everybody.
Eyes on me. Hi.
Hi. Look up here.
I would like to propose a toast
to the bird who made
all of this possible.
Our hero, Red.
- Give it up for Red!
- Yeah!
Red! Red! Red!
You're our hero, Red!
Oh. Easy, guys.
Hollow bones.
I've got hollow bones.
- Who loves you, Red?
- Yeah, Red!
Oh, wow. I mean, thanks, guys.
I... Thank you.
Speech, speech, speech!
Looks like they still
love you, Red.
Um, okay, well,
you know, I'm...
I'm honored, everybody.
Really, I... And I just, um...
Give me two seconds.
I'll be right back.
Woo! Good speech! Yeah!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Excuse me. I'm just trying
to squeeze through here.
Hey, hey, hey! Silver!
Huh?
Wow. I, um...
Thank you, guys.
Thank you for this. And for
all the support and love.
You know, it means...
Well, it means everything to me.
But, um, I don't deserve it.
She does.
What just happened?
Is that the nerd
from our physics class?
This is the real hero
right here.
Silver is the one
who came up
with the plan
to stop the super-weapon
and ultimately saved
all our lives.
Red, I didn't do this
all on my own.
Right. Because we're a team.
We couldn't have
done anything without
Chuck and Bomb,
- or Courtney and Garry.
- Thank you.
Or Leonard.
Actually, we probably
could've done it
without Leonard.
Let's be honest, huh?
Leonard's the man!
I did everything!
I got the sub!
And even Mighty Eagle.
- So handsome.
- Ethan!
And last,
but certainly not least,
those adorable hatchlings.
We are strongest
when we all band together.
Just like Super String.
- Let's hear it for Silver!
- Yes!
I want to be an engineer.
- All right! Yeah, Silver!
- We love you, Silver!
- Okay, Garry, now.
- On it.
Oh, my gosh!
- We're famous!
- Look at that.
Oh, look! It's me!
You see, these guys
are the real heroes.
They're the ones who deserve
your love, not me.
We love you even
more now, Red!
Yeah, Red! We love you!
See? You're not
in this alone.
I'm married now. Let's party,
y'all! I's married!
Debbie,
get away from the punch bowl, girl!
Come over here
and dance with your mama!
Mm-mm!
- Hey, y'all!
- Mom, watch this!
Oh, yeah! Hey,
where's Red and Silver?
♪ The only one for me
Is you ♪
- Okay, worms or birdseed?
- Huh?
Kidding.
I know it's toast.
Ha, ha. Toast.
You know, I was actually
being sarcastic
when I said that
was my favorite,
just for the record.
What? You?
Sarcastic?
- No way.
- I see what you're doing.
- Okay.
- Maybe you can teach me sometime.
Maybe I will, when you're not
too busy saving the world.
You know, I actually
just finished doing that,
so I'm pretty free.
Oh, no way.
Because I'm pretty free too.
Well, I don't have anything
to do either!
Wait a minute.
What's that sound?
Tickle Train?
Coming to Third Wheel Station!
Chuck, no!
Jinx, jinx, jinx!
Laugh it up, everybody.
Ha-ha-ha.
No one can stop me.
I'll stop you, Zeta.
Ha-ha-ha.
Well, you can't stop me from...
showing you how cute
my little sisters are
when they're sleeping.
Yay!
Aw, they're so cute.
I kind of thought
they'd be hatched by now.
They're hatching!
Yay!
Here they come!
Oh, my gosh! I see one!
Mama!
Uh-oh.
Can I help you?
Oh. Sorry.
Mama?
Hi.
My baby sisters!
Yay!
Bye.
Mama!
Oh, baby sisters.
We love you so much.
We should take
good care of them
and never let them
out of our sights.
Yeah. We'll never let them
Huh?
Bye-bye.
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ Hey, you ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The Best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be the best day
Of your life, of your life ♪
♪ Uh, I took a walk
This mornin' ♪
♪ The sun was shinin' for me ♪
♪ It got me feelin' like oh
Oh, oh, oh-ooh ♪
♪ The sky is lookin' so blue
So I do what I want to ♪
♪ I'm feelin' myself like oh
Oh, oh, oh-ooh ♪
♪ I'm feelin' so nice ♪
♪ I ain't got no
Negative energy ♪
♪ High fives and good vibes ♪
♪ Wrote this one for all
My friends and enemies ♪
♪ Hey, you ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ Go live it up ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh, I tell them
It's my birthday ♪
♪ Who doesn't want
That free cake? ♪
♪ Let's celebrate like oh
Oh, oh, oh-ooh ♪
♪ I'm dancing in my foyer
'Cause I'm my own employer ♪
♪ Why don't you all come over
Yeah? ♪
♪ I'm feelin' so nice ♪
♪ I ain't got no
Negative energy ♪
♪ High fives and good vibes ♪
♪ Wrote this one for
All my friends and enemies ♪
♪ Hey, you ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ Go live it up ♪
♪ La-la-la
La-la-la-la ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ La-la-la
La-la-la-la ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ This is gonna be
The best day of your life ♪
♪ Of your life
Of your life ♪
♪ You're from one side
Of the tracks ♪
♪ And I live on the other ♪
♪ Why we don't see eye-to-eye ♪
♪ Really ain't no wonder ♪
♪ But you got the rock
And I got the roll ♪
♪ You got the heart
And I got the soul ♪
♪ So let's just be friends ♪
♪ Ain't gotta fight about it
Let's find our way around it ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, what do you say? ♪
♪ If we don't even know
What we were fussin' about ♪
♪ Don't you think it's time
We work it out? ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, let's just be friends ♪
♪ Yeah, we're pretty good alone
But I bet that together ♪
♪ We could make some noise this
Town would talk about forever ♪
♪ We've been back and forth
And pickin' sides ♪
♪ When you ain't wrong
And I ain't right ♪
♪ So let's just be friends ♪
♪ Ain't gotta fight about it
Let's find our way around it ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, what do you say? ♪
♪ If we don't even know
What we were fussin' about ♪
♪ Don't you think it's time
We work it out ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, let's just be friends ♪
♪ You're big city
And I'm small town ♪
♪ The best of both worlds is
What it sounds like ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Aw, let's just be friends ♪
♪ Ain't gotta fight about it
Let's find our way around it ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, what do you say? ♪
♪ If we don't even know what
We were fussin' about ♪
♪ Don't you think it's time
We work it out ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, let's just be friends ♪
♪ Aw, let's just be friends ♪