They're here!
Hurry, Muse!
What the hell are you doing?
Why aren't you out on the water?
You know what you're supposed to do!
You should be out there
earning money!
But we caught a ship last week.
That was last week!
The boss wants money today!
Bring Garaad another ship soon...
...or you will answer for it!
Everybody, get back to work now!
Stay out of my way today.
Hufan!
I'm going to get us something big!
Those who want to make money,
come.
Muse, take me with you.
Does your sister know you're here?
She's selling khat up there.
This is her best stuff.
When we get a big ship,
you will be well paid.
You want to work?
Do you know how to steer a boat?
Go, go.
I'm ready.
- What do you have for me?
-Money.
- When are you gonna give it to me?
-As soon as we're paid.
Spread out!
Let my other man choose his crew.
Next time bring me something
if you want to work.
Come on, Bilal.
Hey, Skinny, I can steer your boat.
If you choose me, you won't regret it.
Okay, Elmi.
I need somebody strong.
Somebody like this?
I want him.
Get out of my way!
Why did he pick him?
He's from another village.
Move!
Faster, move faster!
See if you can get more power.
Okay.
You!
Get over here!
Come help us!
Their main route is packed
with ships...
...but we can't attack a herd.
This one is alone.
She's really big! Get ready!
You worry about yourself, skinny rat!
Brothers,
we're going to make a lot of money!
Slow down! The waves are too big!
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
We've got to get out of here!
Turn back, turn back!
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Come on! Keep going!
Faster, faster!
Hurry, hurry! Go!
We're pushing this engine too hard!
Faster, faster!
Come on, let's go!
This thing is busted.
- Then fix it!
-I'm trying!
The ocean was rough. Really rough.
Hufan, I'm telling you,
our boat couldn't take it.
Nothing was working for us.
Hurry UP-
We need a bigger one for that ship.
I want this welded by the morning...
...by tomorrow, got it?
Elmi.
When will that engine be ready?
We've gotta fix it.
This thing is old and weak.
It's a piece of shit.
Shut up and fix it
for your crew of women.
Why don't you give me your engine?
Shut up, Skinny. You talk too much.
I may be skinny, but I'm not a coward.
What did you say?
Say I'! again!
You think you're somebody?
The coward is the first one in the grave.
Get ready.
They're not stopping.
Show them who we are, Muse.
Shoot at them!
Turn!
It's clear over there!
Untie the ladder.
Shoot him!
Let's go, let's go!
Hurry up, Bilal.
Move your ass, kid.
Stop him!
Higher. Get it higher.
Hook it on!
Get out of my way.
Get away. Get over there.
From now on
this one is called Irish, okay?
Hey, calm down! Calm down.
Watch this ugly one.
What are you doing?
I'm going to fix it.
Do you know how?
Hold the gun on him.
I've got him, don't worry.
Don't mess with anything
you don't know.
Come on, man.
- What are you doing?
-Just take care of that guy.
Stop the games.
Get that one
and put him against the wall.
Wait.
Take his radio.
Take his flashlight.
Check this room.
I heard something!
Check the other side.
There's no one here.
Please, let's go back.
Look, man, get us out of here.
Hey, take him upstairs.
I can't move.
Take him upstairs
and tell Najee to come.
If one of them moves,
send them to their graves.
Here.
What happened to you?
They put glass down for me.
They got me.
Where is Muse?
In the engine room.
He wants Najee to come down.
Hey! Get me out of here!
Listen to what these guys have to say.
What happened?
They cut my hand, bad.
We'll straighten everything out later.
Just get me out of here.
Give Irish the radio.
I'll give it to him now.
Thirty thousand is nothing.
I want millions!
Hey, Bilal, check it out.
If anyone moves, kill them.
Kill them!
What's going on, Skinny?
Do what they say
and get me out of here.
Be strong, man.
Watch him.
Bilal, hold the gun on him.
Go!
Go.
Irish, it's only us now.
Hufan, do you read me?
Hufan, can you hear me?
Where's your boss?
He should be with us by now.
Don't worry. He's coming.
Stupid hand.
Stop whining.
You sound like a little girl.
You wanted to come with us.
You asked for this.
I didn't think this would happen.
I could lose my foot.
You have to be ready for anything.
This game isn't for the weak.
What is it?
It's a gift.
Give me some khat.
Why?
You've had more than your share.
Says who? Give me some more!
Shut up!
Both of you, shut up.
Just take it.
This is it?
That's all I have.
- Where is the rest?
-I don't have any.
It's all gone.
You are useless.
I should have taken it from you.
They'll fix him when we get back.
He's got a knife!
Go back. Get back there.
Drive this thing right!
Calm down. We're on the ocean.
I should throw you off this boat
right now!
You need to sit down and relax.
That's enough.
Take it away.
From now on this water is only for us.
Stop being such an asshole.
You've got to control him.
Just drive and shut up.
Hufan, can you hear me?
What's wrong with you?
Don't talk to me.
Hufan, can you hear me?
We should be heading northwest.
We've got to get to Garaad's port.
I am, but there's a lot of wind.
- Just go!
-Okay, then let me do it.
Muse? Are you there?
Are you there?
Hufan, where are you?
I'm having trouble with the engine.
Head home.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Hey, we're alone out here.
We need you to pick us up.
We've got to get out of this lifeboat.
Shut up and listen to me.
You screwed up getting the ship...
...so Garaad says
bring back that captain...
...or don't come back at all.
I need air.
When are we going to be home?
I can't feel my foot anymore.
It's like hell in here.
You think you have any power here?
- Let him go.
-I should shoot you and be done.
Take your gun off him.
I'm the captain.
Who do you think you are?
You're taking his side?
You let the American
do whatever he wants!
I'm losing control!
It's the Americans.
Get something to tie the doors.
Calm down, brother.
We're here for the captain, not for you.
They have a spy with them.
Hey, you. Who are you?
My name is Nemo.
I work with the U.S. Navy.
We just want to talk.
It's not that easy...
...but we'll work on it.
In the meantime,
what if I bring you some food and water?
They're coming.
Bilal, watch him.
Watch him closely.
Open your door!
We are here with your supplies.
Calm down, brother.
We're just here to help you.
Listen, we need to see our guy.
We've got supplies,
food, water for you...
...but we need to see our captain.
- They want to see him.
-Bring him out.
Get him back inside.
Shut up and don't move.
Calm down, we just want to talk.
We've got your supplies here.
Food, water.
Listen, you're hurt.
We've got doctors on board.
- Let us take care of you.
-Hurry up!
They're treating us like children.
It's not that easy...
...so we need time.
We've got to talk about this.
Hurry up, I said!
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
- You'll get us all killed!
-Do you have to talk all day?
You're crazy.
What do you think you're doing?
All you do is talk!
Move.
You have to be strong
to get what you want.
Hey, this situation has gotten bad.
There are two more ships,
one on either side.
That one is huge.
Bilal, get the ropes.
The other ropes.
He got out!
Turn the boat around!
Bilal, you idiot!
Turn it! Faster, faster!
Move, or we'll leave you!
Find him. Don't kill him.
Don't shoot!
Stop! What are you doing?
He's getting away!
- Don't kill him!
-Better to kill him than let him escape!
There he is!
I'm ordering you. Don't kill him.
Where is he?
Here he is! Here he is!
He's here!
Are you crazy?
Stop him!
That's enough!
Don't kill him!
If you kill him, We'll all die!
- What do you want me to do with him?
-What is he doing?
It's a helicopter!
Get to the other side!
Hurry! Go!
I'm trying.
Go!
They think you are playing games.
Do something!
Do you want to go
to an American prison?
Is that what you want?
I know how to handle America.
Give me the pistol.
They think I'm playing games, huh?
They have no respect for us.
We have to play games?
Give me the radio.
The helicopter is coming back.
They know us.
It's a lie.
It's an ambush.
You need to be strong.
Don't let anyone in.
Whatever happens, don't stop.
It's my job.
What's going on?
I can't see.
Give me the radio.
Keep it steady. Keep it steady.
If he moves again, shoot him.
It's getting rough.
Keep it straight.
What kind of games are they playing?
I can't hold it straight.
Be a man. Just shut up and steer.
Stop him.
Bilal, stop him.
Bring the rope!
Tie him!
What are you doing?
Shut up!
Get a blindfold!
Blindfold him.
Don't kill him!
The elders are coming.
We will get our money.
You are both idiots.
No one is coming.
That's it. We Will all die if you kill him.
Everything they told you was a lie!
They Will kill us all...
...and he is behind everything!