(SWAN LAKE PLAYING)
(WOMAN LAUGHS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(RAGGED BREATHING)
(CAWS)
(WHIMPERS)
(TOE SHOES CLACKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Mmm.
(BONES CRACKING)
I had the craziest
dream last night.
I was dancing
the White Swan.
It was different
choreography, though.
It was more like
the Bolshoi's.
It was the prologue, when
Rothbart casts his spell.
(CUTLERY RATTLING)
(NINA GASPS)
Look how pink!
So pretty.
BOTH: Pretty!
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
You're in
a good mood.
Mmm-hmm. He promised to
feature me more this season.
Well, he certainly should.
You've been there long enough.
And you're the most dedicated
dancer in the company.
Up.
What's that?
What?
There.
Nothing.
Sure you don't want me
to come with you?
You sweet girl.
(TRAIN BRAKES SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
MAN: (ON SPEAKER) This is a
Downtown 1 train to South Ferry.
Next stop, 72nd Street.
Stand clear of the
closing doors, please.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
VERONICA: Did you
see Beth today?
I can't believe
she's back.
Of course
What, she can't
take a hint?
Company is broke.
No one comes to see her anymore.
Nobody actually comes to
see ballet, full stop.
That's not true.
I heard The Royal had one
of their best seasons yet.
He just needs to try
something new, that's all.
No, someone new.
(GALINA CHUCKLES)
Like who?
Like someone who's not
approaching menopause.
It's sad.
What's sad?
Beth's such a
beautiful dancer.
Yeah, so is
my grandmother.
(WOMEN GIGGLE)
Well, Fonteyn
danced into her 50s.
Yeah, we know.
Hey! Oh ! Soloists?
Great!
(CHUCKLES) I fucking
missed my stop.
Had to hoof it
all the way from 79th.
VERONICA: (WHISPERING)
Who's that?
GALINA: (WHISPERING) It's that
new girl from San Francisco.
Okay.
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
BALLET MISTRESS:
And up, two, three, four.
Good, one. . .
Two, three, four, up. . .
Beautiful
as always, Nina.
Relax.
And one, and two,
and three, and four, and. . .
BALLET MISTRESS: Stop, John.
One second.
(MUSIC STOPS)
BALLET MISTRESS:
Okay, take position.
(MUSIC RESUMES)
And one, and two,
and three, and up.
One, and two,
and three, and four. . .
How are you, dear?
Good, thanks.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
We all know the story.
Virginal girl,
pure and sweet,
trapped in the
body of a swan.
She desires freedom,
but only true love
can break the spell.
Her wish is nearly granted
in the form of a prince.
But before he can
declare his love,
her lustful twin,
the Black Swan,
tricks and seduces him.
Devastated,
the White Swan
leaps off a cliff,
killing herself,
and in death
finds freedom.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Good morning, company.
ALL: Good morning.
We open our season
with Swan Lake.
Done to death, I know.
But not like this.
We strip it down,
make it visceral
and real.
A new production needs
a new Swan Queen.
A fresh face to
present to the world.
But,
which of you can
embody both swans?
The white and the black.
All the soloists
I tapped,
go to your scheduled
rehearsals this afternoon.
And the girls
I didn't tap,
meet me in the principals'
studio at 5:00.
Thank you.
(WOMEN WHISPERING)
BALLET MISTRESS: All right, let's go.
Did we do left side?
DANCER: Yes, mistress.
BALLET MISTRESS:
Let's repeat one more time.
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(HUMMING)
(BOTTLE CLINKS)
(WOMAN GRUNTS)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Fuck! Fuck!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
What?
(DISTORTED SHUDDER)
(BROKEN GLASS CLINKS)
(PIANO PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
If I was only casting the
White Swan, she'd be yours.
But I'm not.
Maestro, Odile's coda, please.
Now show me your
Black Swan, Nina.
(CLEARING THROAT)
(PLAYING PIANO)
No, not so controlled.
Seduce us.
Not just the Prince,
but the court,
the audience, the entire world.
Come on !
Your fouettees are like
a spider spinning a web.
Attack it! Attack it!
Come on !
(DOOR OPENS)
(GASPS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
THOMAS: Well, good
of you to join us.
Sorry.
THOMAS: Girls,
this is Lily.
Straight off the plane
from San Francisco.
She's filling Rebecca's old spot.
LILY: Hey.
Get warmed up.
No, it's okay.
I'm good.
Should I go again?
No, thanks, Nina.
I've seen enough.
Veronica, the White Swan variation.
Come on, come on, please.
All right, maestro.
Two, three. . .
(RETCHING)
(FLUSHES)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(RINGING STOPS)
(CELL PHONE SNAPS SHUT)
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
ERICA: So, how'd it go?
You were late, so I called
Susie in the office.
An audition. I can't believe
he just sprang that on you.
So?
It was fine.
Just fine?
(SOBBING)
Oh, sweetheart.
Oh, you tell me
about it.
ERICA: I know, Susie, but he
just can't expect these girls
to come back from break and
dance like Beth Macintyre.
It's completely unrealistic.
And they can do the work,
but they don't
have Beth's magic. . .
(ERICA CONTINUES CHATTERING)
Well, she's miserable. . .
(SIGHING)
(CREAKING)
(CRACKS)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
Ow! ERICA: Nina,
everything all right?
I'm fine.
(HISSES)
(GASPS)
Oh. Shh.
Almost done.
You're working
yourself too hard.
We all have off days.
If that girl
hadn't barged in. . .
I'm sure she didn't mean to.
Remember when
you first started?
If I hadn't taken you
to each of your classes,
you would have been
completely lost.
I'm going to talk
to him tomorrow.
I'm going to tell him
I finished it.
You don't need to lie.
It won't convince him
one way or the other.
Oh, sweetheart.
I know it's disappointing.
And when you start getting
older, there's all this
(CHUCKLES)
ridiculous pressure.
God knows I understand.
But it's all right.
No matter what.
You'll probably get to dance
the pas de quatre again.
(CHUCKLES)
That's such
a wonderful part.
(DANCE OF THE SWANS PLAYING
ON MUSIC BOX)
Or maybe he'll make you a Big Swan.
Either way, you'll shine.
I know.
Everything will be
better in the morning.
It always is.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Sweet girl.
(THOMAS AND WOMAN CHATTERING)
Yes, Nina?
Do you have a minute?
If now is not
a good time. . .
Now is perfect.
So?
Um. . .
I just wanted
to tell you that
I practiced the coda last
night and I finished.
I thought you should know.
Okay, Nina, listen.
Honestly, I don't care
about your technique.
You should know
that by now.
Yeah, but yesterday. . .
No.
Anyway, I've already
chosen Veronica.
Sorry.
Okay. Thank you.
That's it?
You're not going to try
and change my mind?
You must have thought
it was possible.
Otherwise, what are you
doing here, all dolled up?
I came to ask for the part.
Well. . .
The truth is,
when I look at you,
all I see is
the White Swan.
Yes, you're beautiful,
fearful, fragile.
Ideal casting.
But the Black Swan?
It's a hard fucking job
to dance both.
(SOFTLY) I can dance
the Black Swan, too.
Really?
In four years,
every time you dance,
I see you obsess, getting each
and every move perfectly right,
but I never see you
lose yourself.
Ever.
All that discipline,
for what?
(WHISPERS) I just
want to be perfect.
You what?
I want to be perfect.
(LAUGHS)
Perfection is not
just about control.
It's also about letting go.
Surprise yourself, so you
can surprise the audience.
Transcendence.
And very few
have it in them.
I think I do have it in. . .
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(EXCLAIMING)
You bit me?
I can't believe you bit me!
I'm sorry.
Now, that fucking hurt!
You were great.
Thanks.
(WHISPERING) What?
Why is she always staring at me?
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
GALINA: She's obsessed
with you.
Hey, it's been posted.
Hey, it's up.
Veronica?
Congratulations.
(EXCITED CHATTERING)
Hey!
Why would you
say that? Hmm?
Your idea of
some sick joke?
What?
Fuck you.
WOMAN: Oh, my goodness!
(EXCITED CHATTERING)
Hey, Nina!
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Oh, Nina, congratulations.
You were so beautiful
in your audition.
I knew you were
going to get it.
Congratulations!
(LINE RINGING)
ERICA: Hello?
Hi.
What it is?
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
What is it?
He picked me, Mommy.
Did you hear me?
For Swan Lake?
I'm gonna be
the new Swan Queen.
(LAUGHING) Oh, my God!
Well, um. . .
I'll be home soon.
I just wanted to let you know.
l love you.
I love you, too.
Hurry home!
(STIFLED SOBS)
(SIGHING)
(KEYS JINGLING)
Mom?
Mom, are you in your room?
(FAINT LAUGHTER)
(FAINT SHUDDER)
ERICA: Nina, are you home?
Nina, when you get out,
I'm in the kitchen.
Come on, sweetie.
My daughter,
the Swan Queen.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
It's our favorite.
Vanilla with strawberry filling.
Oh, Mom, not too big.
That's way, way too much.
It's a celebration.
It's just this once.
Mom. My stomach's
still in knots.
Fine.
Fine. Then it's garbage.
No, Mom.
Don't. I'm sorry.
I'm just. . .
I'm just so proud of you.
It looks so yummy.
Mmm.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
(PIANO PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(TEMPO INCREASES)
THOMAS: Okay,
thank you. Thank you.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Thank you, Nina.
It's very nice.
But I knew the White Swan
wouldn't be a problem.
The real work will be your
metamorphosis into her evil twin.
And I know I saw
a flash of her yesterday.
So get ready to give
me more of that bite.
Up, and. . .
(BALLET MISTRESS
WHISPERING ENCOURAGEMENT)
Excellent.
That evil force
is pulling you,
that you can't escape. That's just like.
. . (EXHALES) Out of your control.
You sense it.
You get aware of it more.
"It's taking.
It's taking me."
A little bit more
desperate. Right.
And you can maybe go up a
little bit, and then come down.
That's it.
(PIANO PLAYING)
BALLET MISTRESS: Long arms.
Feel the space. That's beautiful.
Step, and step, and. . .
BALLET MISTRESS:
Epaulement, and again.
Watch the way she moves.
Imprecise, but
effortless.
She's not faking it.
BALLET MISTRESS: Long arms.
Gorgeous. Yes.
(GASPS)
BALLET MISTRESS: Okay,
that's beautiful. Sorry.
We'll start again
from the beginning.
LILY: Okay. Sorry.
SUSIE: Welcome to
the principals' room.
You room with Beth from now
on, so be considerate.
NINA: Thanks, Susie.
Those are for you
from Mr. Leroy.
They're beautiful.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
THOMAS: I'll be back
in a second.
Let me come back
to you, please.
Okay, let's go.
Ready to be thrown
to the wolves?
We need their cash.
So please, don't forget to smile.
Ladies and gentlemen, please
may I have your attention?
(MUSIC STOPS)
Good evening.
Let me make this very
important announcement.
You all have had the chance
and the privilege
to be enchanted,
transported,
and even sometimes devastated,
by the performances
of this true artist
of our company.
She's been a crucial
inspiration to my work,
a role model to all dancers,
and even more than that,
a deeply appreciated
presence on our stage.
You all know who
I'm talking about.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Beth Macintyre.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
But as we all know,
every great career
has to come to an end.
Beth is retiring at
the end of the season.
(CROWD MURMURS)
She will be giving her farewell
performance as Melpomene,
the role she originated
in my first ballet.
My little princess.
We honor you.
You will be greatly missed
and never forgotten.
But as we bid adieu
to one star,
we welcome another.
We're opening our season with
my new version of Swan Lake.
Taking the role of
our new Swan Queen,
the exquisite Nina Sayers.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
(LILY GIGGLING)
You'll soon have the pleasure
of seeing her perform,
but right now, please
let's raise a glass.
To all of us, to Beth,
to Nina,
to beauty.
(ALL CHATTERING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Just a second.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Just a second.
(GASPS)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
LILY: Come on !
I'm about to burst.
Hey! It's you !
I don't think we ever
officially met. I'm Lily.
Hi. I'm Nina.
Yes! Our new Swan Queen.
Here. Hold this?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, you must be
so excited.
Oh !
Are you freaking out?
Yeah.
Yeah?
It's okay.
I'd be losing my mind.
I should get back.
No! No, no. Come on, stay.
Keep me company.
Excuse me.
There you are. Come on.
THOMAS: Hey.
They tried to eat you alive,
but here you are.
You did well.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
Where are you going?
Upper West Side.
Stop at my place for a drink.
It's on the way.
MRS. FITHIAN: Thomas.
You need to say hello
to Karen Halloway.
A minute more of
ass-kissing, I'll be back.
Wait for me here,
all right?
THOMAS: Hello, Karen,
my dear.
(GASPS)
Beth !
I'm so sorry to hear
you're leaving the company.
Oh !
What did you do
to get this role?
Huh?
He always said you were
such a frigid little girl.
What did you do to make
him change his mind?
Did you suck his cock?
Not all of us have to.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(LAUGHING)
You fucking whore!
You're a fucking
little whore!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What's going on here?
Hey. I need
to talk to you.
I think you're drunk.
You should go home.
No, don't you do that.
Don't you dismiss me like that.
Beth.
My little princess, please,
hold it together.
BETH: I'm coming by later.
Come on.
I have something for you.
It's a token of
my appreciation.
THOMAS: Right.
BETH: You make the
most of it, Nina!
Don't worry.
It's typical.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Please.
I thought it would be good
to talk about the role.
Ground us a little.
Yeah.
I don't want there to be
any boundaries between us.
No, me neither.
Good.
So. . .
You got a boyfriend?
No.
And you had
many in the past?
A few, but no one serious.
You're not a virgin,
are you?
No.
So there's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And you enjoy
making love?
Excuse me?
Oh, come on. Sex.
Do you enjoy it?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
We need to be able
to talk about this.
I got a little homework
assignment for you.
Go home
and touch yourself.
Live a little.
It's late.
Lots of work tomorrow.
The doorman will
find a cab for you.
Sounds like
quite an evening.
I wish I could
have been there.
You know I asked.
I know you did.
Susie told me.
I guess he wanted
you all to himself.
That's not why.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't blame him.
Hmm.
Where did you get these?
They're fake.
(LAUGHS) Fooled me.
I can do it.
He must have been
by your side all night,
showing you off.
Oh, Nina.
It's just a rash.
Just a rash?
What are you talking about?
It was worse a few days ago.
It's fine already.
You've been scratching
yourself again.
No, I haven't. Mom !
I thought you'd outgrown
this disgusting habit.
Jesus Christ. I thought you
were done with this, Nina.
Shrugs. You keep
wearing the shrugs.
I have been.
Sit down.
You have the white one and the
pink one, and that will hide it.
And then I'll dig out
that expensive cover-up.
We still have some.
No one will see it.
Mom, please.
It's the role, isn't it?
It's all this pressure.
I knew it'd be
too much. I knew it.
Ow!
Oh !
Are you all right?
You all right?
It'll be all right.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(MOANING)
(PANTING)
(BALLET MISTRESS
SPEAKING FRENCH)
(PIANO AND VIOLIN PLAYING)
(DOOR BANGS OPEN)
(SOBBING)
BALLET MISTRESS:
What happened?
GALINA: Beth is
in the hospital.
She had an accident.
Oh, no.
(MUSIC STOPS)
GALINA: I don't know.
She's really hurt.
Her legs are
completely broken.
(ALL CHATTERING)
GALINA: I don't know.
She was crossing the street.
NINA: What happened?
THOMAS: She walked into the
street and got hit by a car.
And you know what?
I'm almost sure
she did it on purpose.
How do you know?
Because everything Beth
does comes from within.
From some dark impulse.
I guess that's what makes
her so thrilling to watch,
so dangerous.
Even perfect at times.
But also
so damn destructive.
Was it right after
we saw her?
No, wait, wait.
This has nothing to do with you.
It's not your problem, so don't
let yourself be distracted.
This is your moment,
Nina. Don't let it go.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(PHONES RINGING)
(GASPS)
What are you doing?
(SNIFFLING)
(ERICA SOBBING SOFTLY)
(SOBBING)
ERICA: Nina?
Sweetie, you were
looking for me?
And. . .
Come on.
Forget about control, Nina.
I want to see passion !
Come on. Reach !
More! You're stiff!
Stiff like a dead corpse.
Let it go.
Let it go. Let it go.
And again.
PHYSIOTHERAPIST:
It feels like you have. . .
Your diaphragm is in
a bit of a contraction.
Okay.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
I want you to breathe
into this hand.
Breathe into this hand.
Breathe in, breathe in, breathe in.
All the way.
Good. And exhale.
(NINA EXHALES SLOWLY)
Does it feel jammed in the
front every time you plie?
NINA: Sometimes,
not always.
(CRACKING)
One more pull, okay?
Okay.
(CRACKS)
(GASPS)
Is that okay?
Mmm-hmm.
(PIANO PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
David, can I ask
you a question?
Honestly, would
you fuck that girl?
(SCOFFS)
No.
No one would.
Nina, your dancing
is just as frigid. . .
(NINA GASPS)
THOMAS: Fuck.
THOMAS: (WHISTLES) Oh !
(SIGHS)
We're still working here,
please! Lights!
The lights!
Thank you.
Okay. Guys,
you can go.
Thanks for your patience.
(EXCLAIMING)
You stay. You stay.
Have fun, you two.
Hey. Oh !
Okay.
Come here.
Come, come, come.
I'll be the Prince.
(HUMMING)
(NINA BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THOMAS CONTINUES HUMMING)
Let it go, let it go.
Feel my touch.
Respond to it. Come on.
(GASPS)
Open your mouth.
Open it. Open it. Open it.
(NINA MOANS)
That was me
seducing you,
when it needs to be
the other way around.
Please.
(CRYING SOFTLY)
Who is that?
Hey.
You okay?
You can't smoke in here.
Well, I won't tell
if you won't.
So. . .
Big day's getting
closer and closer, huh?
Well, I can't wait.
I think you're going to be amazing.
Thanks.
Come on.
(INHALING DEEPLY)
So. . .
Do you want
to talk about it?
(SOBS)
I just had a hard day.
Leroy playing a little
too rough for you?
Come on, Nina.
He's a prick.
He's brilliant.
Sure.
But it's not like
he's all warm and fuzzy.
You don't know him.
Someone's hot for teacher.
Come on, it's okay.
I don't blame you.
I should go home.
Oh, Nina, come on.
I'm just playing around.
Nina!
(SHUDDERS)
(DISTANT LAUGHTER)
(GASPS)
ERICA: Sweetie?
What are you doing in there?
(PANTING)
(PIANO AND VIOLIN PLAYING)
(DANCERS PANTING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Again.
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Again.
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Do you have
any corrections?
Lily told me that
she saw you crying.
That you were very upset
and that I should
take it easy on you.
I didn't tell her that.
Maybe you need
a little break.
Like a day or two.
Thomas.
Maybe a month.
What do you think?
She shouldn't have
said anything.
No, you shouldn't be whining
in the first place.
I didn't!
You could be brilliant,
but you're a coward.
(WHISPERS) I'm sorry.
Stop saying that!
That's exactly what
I'm talking about.
Stop being so fucking weak!
Again !
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(DANCERS CHATTERING)
Lily?
Oh ! Look who's decided to
grace us with her presence.
I need to talk to you.
Okay.
Now!
Ow! Ow!
Shut up. Come on.
What's up?
You told Thomas
about last night?
Oh. Yeah, I ran into
him in the morning
and he said you guys
were having some trouble.
Why would he talk to you?
Excuse me, Your Highness.
I told him that you
were working your ass off
and that I think
you'll be great.
Well, you shouldn't have.
(LAUGHS HUMORLESSLY)
Okay.
(KISSING)
Has he tried
anything with you?
He has a reputation.
I have a right to
be concerned, Nina.
You've been staying late so
many nights, rehearsing.
I hope he isn't taking
advantage, that's all.
He's not.
Good.
I just don't want you to
make the same mistake I did.
Thanks.
Not like that.
I just mean as far as my
career was concerned.
What career?
The one I gave up
to have you.
You were 28.
So?
And only in the. . .
Only what?
Nothing.
What?
How's your skin?
It's fine.
Are we leaving
it alone?
Mmm-hmm.
Let me see.
Take off your shirt.
No!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
ERICA: Can I help you?
WOMAN: Is Nina around?
ERICA: Sorry, she's not here.
Who was that?
It was no one.
It was no one!
NINA: Hello?
Hey!
What are you doing here?
I just came by
to apologize.
You're right, I should've never
spoken to him about you.
Sweetheart. . .
Give me a second.
Your dinner.
Mom, please!
She's a trip.
(CHUCKLES)
How do you know
where I live?
I have my ways.
(LAUGHS) Jesus!
Relax, I got it from Susie in the office.
I feel really shitty
about what I did,
and I just really want
to make it up to you.
So how about I take
you out to dinner?
I don't think. . .
Okay, that's fine.
What about drinks?
Sweetie, you need to rest.
Jesus!
Wait.
What are you doing?
Going out.
What?
Stairs.
ERICA: Nina! You're on
the stage tomorrow.
I can't believe
he calls her that.
It's so gross.
I think it's sweet.
"Little princess"?
He probably calls every girl that.
No way.
That's just for Beth.
I bet he'll be calling you
"little princess" any day now.
I don't know about that.
Oh, sure he will.
You just got to let him
lick your pussy.
WAITER: Cheeseburger,
extra bloody.
Mmm. (THANKING IN GERMAN)
Let me know if that's
juicy enough for you.
Oh, I will.
You got enough cheese?
No, but you do.
Enjoy.
Okay.
Want to spruce up?
What? I carry a spare.
In case I wake up
somewhere unexpected.
So, how is he?
Thomas.
I wouldn't know.
Come on.
I really don't want
to talk about that.
Oh. Okay.
You really need to relax.
One for you
and one for me.
Oh. And don't worry,
it's pure, I promise.
I brought it with me
straight from San Francisco.
What is it?
What, are you kidding?
You've never rolled?
It'll relax you,
it'll loosen you up.
Let you see the night sky.
How long does it last?
Couple of hours, tops.
It's okay.
Okay.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
I was. . .
That's very sweet of you.
(GASPING)
LILY: Hey! Hi !
Okay. I thought maybe you and I
could use a couple of drinks.
NINA: I'm going to head out.
So, this is Tom,
and this is Jerry!
Actually, it's Andrew.
TOM: Tom.
Hi.
Um, I have to go.
No, come on. You can't go,
I just got us some drinks.
I shouldn't.
We're on the stage tomorrow.
So what are you going to do?
Go home to Mommy?
Hey.
Come on. Live a little.
It's just a couple
of hours, right?
Tops.
Here you go.
Thank you.
ALL: Cheers.
ANDREW: You haven't told
me who you are.
I'm a dancer.
No, I mean your name.
Oh, uh, Nina.
So, are you two sisters?
Yes.
No.
Blood sisters.
We dance in
the same company.
Oh, ballerinas.
No wonder you two look alike.
You know, Tom and Jerry
here are gay lovers.
TOM: Very funny.
LILY: I like to amuse myself.
I've never been to the ballet.
Oh, really?
Well, then you are
definitely not gay.
I mean, it's kind of
boring though, isn't it?
TOM: Be honest.
No, it's not.
No, you know what?
It's just not for everyone.
You guys should
come sometime.
I can comp you tickets
whenever you want.
Yeah.
Yeah, that would
be neat. Thanks.
LILY: Well, I think it is
time for another round.
Bottoms up.
Four, please.
ANDREW: So, what are
you guys working on now?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
I'm sorry.
(RINGING STOPS)
Swan Lake.
Okay. Yeah?
You know it?
No, not really.
Heard of it.
What's it about?
It's about a girl
who gets turned into a swan
and she needs love
to break the spell.
Okay.
But her prince falls
for the wrong girl, and. . .
(CLEARS THROAT)
So she kills herself.
So, a happy ending, then?
It's beautiful, actually.
ANDREW: Like you.
Huh?
I said, you're beautiful.
(LAUGHS)
That's funny?
My hands are sweaty.
LILY: Hey!
(SIGHING)
Oh, hey.
It looks like someone
might be rolling.
All right, come on.
Come on, it's time to go dance.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC PAUSES)
(WOMAN CACKLING)
FEMALE VOICE:
Sweet girl, sweet girl.
LILY: Hey! Nina!
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(MUFFLED MUSIC)
Hey, what the fuck?
Where are you going?
(TECHNO MUSIC CONTINUES)
(PANTING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
LILY: Nina!
Where are you going?
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(SIGHS)
(LAUGHS)
(GIGGLING) Shh !
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(CLATTER)
(SHUSHING)
(GIGGLING)
ERICA: Do you have
any idea what time it is?
Mmm-hmm.
Late?
Where have you been?
To the moon and back.
(MOUTHING)
You've been drinking.
(MIMICKING BELL)
What else?
Mmm?
What else have
you been doing?
Oh.
You want to know
their names?
(LAUGHS)
You need to sleep this off.
There were two.
There was Tom, there was Jerry.
Be quiet, Nina.
And I fucked them both.
Shut your mouth !
Don't come in here!
What's this?
It's called privacy!
I'm not 1 2 anymore.
You're not my
Nina right now.
Leave me alone!
(BOTH MOANING)
(NINA MOANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SHUSHING)
(MOANING)
(CONTINUES MOANING)
(MOANING LOUDLY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHING)
Sweet girl.
(GASPING)
NINA: Why didn't
you wake me up?
I'm moving out.
(SWAN LAKE PLAYING)
My music.
Thomas, I'm so sorry.
Keep on going.
Go get warmed up.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(ALL APPLAUDING)
That was good.
Actually, really good.
Okay, let's take ten.
LILY: Hey!
Look, he just
wanted to mark it,
and asked me
to step in. Okay?
I overslept.
(LAUGHS) Oops.
Hey, at least you
had a good time, right?
You put something
in my drink.
Yeah.
And then you just
took off in the morning?
In the morning?
Yeah, you slept over.
Um. . .
No.
Unless your name is Tom
and you got a dick.
But we. . .
But we what, Nina?
Did you have some sort of
lezzy wet dream about me?
Stop.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God !
You did !
You fantasized about me!
Shut up!
(GASPS) Was I good?
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING)
(RETCHING)
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(DANCE OF THE SWANS PLAYING
ON MUSIC BOX)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING)
THOMAS: The final act.
Your final dance.
You tasted your dream,
touched it,
only to have it crushed.
Your heart is broken,
wounded.
Your life force fading.
The blood drips.
The Black Swan
stole your love.
There's only one way
to end the pain.
You're not fearful,
but filled with acceptance.
And you look
down at Rothbart,
and then at the Prince,
and then, yes,
at the audience.
And then you jump!
Come on, go ahead.
Jump, you'll be fine. Jump!
(GASPS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Okay, everybody gets a drink of
water, then it's notes. Mmm?
(EXHALES)
You lost weight.
GEORGINA: Take off your
shrug, please.
Okay.
Very good.
(EXHALES)
GEORGINA: Face front.
We're almost done.
And that's it.
Okay, you're done.
Thank you very much.
LILY: Georgina?
GEORGINA: Yes.
I'm Lily. Thomas said
I should come.
Yes, we have to get you measured
for your Swan Queen costumes.
What's she doing here?
He made me your alternate.
Look, it's just in case.
Thomas. Thomas.
Thomas!
Yes?
It can't be her.
Why don't you just go on,
I'll catch up later.
What's going on?
Lily.
You made her my alternate?
Well, there's always
an alternate.
Lily's the best choice.
No, but she wants my role.
Every dancer in the
world wants your role.
No, this is different.
She's after me.
She's trying to replace me.
Nobody's after you.
(SOBBING) No,
please believe me!
Hey! (SHUSHING)
I know it's been a struggle.
But you just had a
breakthrough this morning.
Tomorrow is yours.
Just give a great performance
and you won't have to worry
about Lily or anybody else.
Now go home and rest.
(SIGHING)
From the vision again.
(PLAYING PIANO)
(MUSIC STOPS)
What happened?
I've got a life.
Don't work too hard.
It's your big day tomorrow.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(GASPS)
Hey!
I'm still working in here. . .
Could you please
turn the lights back on?
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
Hello?
(BOTH MOANING)
(GASPING)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLS)
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
What are you doing here?
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry!
I know how it feels now.
She's trying to replace me.
(SOBBING) What do I do?
You stole my things?
I was just trying to
be perfect, like you.
Perfect?
Oh, I'm not perfect.
I'm nothing.
Nothing.
(GASPING)
Nothing ! Nothing !
No!
(SNARLS)
Nothing ! Nothing !
(ERICA SOBBING)
(ERICA CONTINUES SOBBING)
FEMALE VOICE:
(WHISPERING) Sweet girl.
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(RETCHING)
(COUGHING)
(ERICA SOBBING)
Mommy?
Sweet girl. Sweet girl.
(VOICES CHATTERING)
My turn. My turn. My turn.
Stop!
(VOICES STOP)
What are you doing?
Sweetie?
(BONES CRACKING)
(EXCLAIMING IN PAIN)
ERICA: Nina?
Nina!
Go away!
Open the door!
(BONES CRACKING)
(GROANS)
(POUNDING AT DOOR)
ERICA: Open the door,
Nina! Nina!
(GRUNTS)
ERICA: Nina!
Get out!
What's wrong with you?
You're sick!
Get out!
(SCREAMING) Get out!
Nina!
(ERICA SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(DANCE OF THE SWANS PLAYING)
(MOANS)
(SHUSHING)
It's okay.
I'm here.
You were scratching
all night.
Where's my clock?
Don't worry about that.
What time is it?
(SHUSHING)
My show is tonight,
I have to. . .
No, no.
No, don't worry.
I called the theater and I told
them you weren't feeling well.
I have to go.
No, lie down.
Let go of me!
You're staying in here
until you feel better.
Where is it?
ERICA: This role is
destroying you.
Move.
Nina. . .
Move!
What happened
to my sweet girl?
She's gone!
(SCREAMING) Nina!
No, please!
ERICA: You're not well.
Let go of me!
You can't handle this!
I can't?
I'm the Swan Queen !
You're the one who never left the corps!
ERICA: Nina!
(PANTING)
DANCER: (WHISPERING)
It's Nina.
THOMAS: I have complete
confidence in you. Okay?
Stay focused and you'll be fine.
This is your moment.
What are you
doing here?
Nina?
You were supposed to. . .
She was supposed to be sick.
Wait, wait. . .
Give us a minute.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Nina. . .
Nina.
What?
I've already asked Lily.
Have you announced it?
After Beth, do you really
need another controversy?
I'm here, Thomas.
I'm doing it.
The only person standing
in your way is you.
It's time
to let her go.
Lose yourself.
STAGE MANAGER: White Swan,
entrance in ten.
(WINCES)
(GASPING)
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING)
What are you doing?
You need to be upstage.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHING)
Hey.
We sucked !
Okay, Nina.
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(GRUNTS)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
(WHISPERING)
What the fuck?
(STIFLED SOBBING)
MAN: Are you okay?
Nina, are you okay?
What happened out there?
(ALL CHATTERING)
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
Can you tell me what
the fuck happened?
(BOTH SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
It wasn't my fault.
He dropped me!
It's a fucking disaster!
(THOMAS SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
LILY: Rough start, huh?
Must have been
pretty humiliating.
Get out of my room.
See, I'm just worried
about the next act.
I'm just not sure
you're feeling up to it.
Stop. Please, stop!
How about I dance
the Black Swan for you?
Leave me alone!
(CHOKING)
It's my turn !
My turn !
(WHIMPERING)
(GASPING)
(SOBBING)
STAGE MANAGER: Black Swan,
places in five.
(GASPING)
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
Wow!
(MOANING)
(EXHALING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
(CONTINUES CHEERING)
Get back out there.
Come on ! They want. . .
(CHUCKLES)
Great job.
Fifteen to the last act.
(DANCERS LAUGHING)
(FAINT TAPPING)
(GASPS)
LILY: Hey!
You were amazing.
Seriously, I know that things got a
little messed up between us, but. . .
I mean, holy shit, you
completely blew me away!
Okay, well, I guess that's it.
So, I'll let you finish.
(GASPS)
(SOBBING)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
THOMAS: Can you hear them?
They love you !
My little princess.
I always knew
you had it in you.
Come on,
let's take your bow.
(GASPING)
Go get some help.
Go get some help!
What did you do?
I felt it.
What?
Perfect.
It was perfect.
(AUDIENCE STILL CHEERING)
(SWANS CALLING)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
ripped by mighty carrot
subscene.com