Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Detroit Theater
continues our legendary talent contest
with the indefatigable Stepp Sisters!
I’m lookin’ for something, baby
Something that’l/ give me a rise
l’m lookin’ for something, baby
Like a real nice surprise
Something that you have got
l’m lookin’ for something, baby
And it’s gonna be real hot
Ladies, you can't go.
What about Jimmy?
What about the show?
Marty, you know I can talk.
Now watch me walk.
Sugar, Jimmy was just being Jimmy.
You know he's crazy about you.
Just crazy.
Oh, really?
Well, give the crazy man
a message from me.
Tell him I got his number.
His phone number.
Now, baby...
At home, where he lives, with his wife.
Come on, Joann.
Our limousine is waiting.
We don't have to put up with this shit.
Shit.
l’m lookin’, lookin’, lookin’ for something
l’m lookin’ for something now
Hey, mister.
Thanks, man.
Can I interest you
in the sound of tomorrow?
Oh, my God. We're too late.
Excuse me?
Hey. You go on yet?
About an hour ago.
l’m lookin’ for something, baby
l’m lookin’ for something now
The unstoppable Stepp Sisters!
Let's hear it!
All right now. Won't be long now, y'all.
Coming your way is the wildest man
in show business, Detroit’s own
James "Thunder” Early
will be kicking off
his national tour right here
on stage tonight.
Mercy. Mercy, mercy. Ladies? Ladies?
I've got the break of your lives.
The great Jimmy Early is looking
for some backup help tonight...
Now / want you to turn it on
for Little Albert and the Tru-Tones!
Me and my baby goin’ downtown
Me and my baby gettin’ down tonight
-Me and my baby goin’ downtown
-Downtown
Me and my baby gonna
check, check, check out the sights
We ’re looking around
On the town with my sweet lady
Looking around
Oh, we’re gonna have us a time tonight
Checking it over
Checking it out
-l'm so sorry, Mr...
-Taylor. Curtis Taylor, Jr.
Look, I know we're late, but my mama
don't like me going out on weeknights.
So I had to wait for her to go to bed.
She's a grade-school teacher.
Who are you?
Deena Jones!
I'm one of The Dreamettes.
You were supposed to go on second.
I know, but my mama wouldn't
go to bed, so I couldn't go out.
Hey, tough luck, kid. The show's over.
Let me lay something on you
right quick, brother.
Check it out, man.
Look, I know you're a great man
and you're the boss with all the ladies,
so I don't want you
coming up weak in here,
but low-rating people, that's not
why you're in this business, right?
No!
That's good, so why don't we
give these girls a break tonight?
Okay, I'll put you on last.
-Right after Tiny Joe Dixon.
-Thank you.
Excuse me, which one is Tiny?
We ’re going downtown
Check out the sights
Okay, we’re going to get down and dirty
with my man, Mr. Tiny Joe Dixon!
Baby, I’m takin’ the long way home
’Cause my baby don ’t live there no more
I got the music to the drummer.
C.C., we're on next.
-Where is Effie?
-l'm right here.
God, I need to rest.
Where's our dressing room?
Effie, there's no time for that.
We go on in two minutes.
-What?
-Come on, let's warm up.
Move, move...
We're ruined unless
we can find new wigs.
Why do we need wigs in the first place?
Because we need a look.
-I got it! Turn the wigs around.
-What?
No, really.
Come on, turn the wigs around.
Oh, Deena, it's so different.
It's sophisticated looking. Come on!
Frontways or backways,
store-bought hair ain't natural.
And what about these dresses?
I mean, this dress does nothing
for my body.
-You got the same wig I got?
-Yeah.
-You got the same dress I got?
Then shut up.
Say, Miss?
I think you look just great.
She left with all her clothes
Her bedroom in a mess
/ don ’t know why she went away
’cause I gave her all my best
Baby, I’m takin’ the long way home
’Cause my baby don ’t live there no more
-What's the name of your group again?
-The Dreamettes.
Nice, baby.
Yeah.
Let’s hear it for Mr. Tiny Joe Dixon!
And now for our ﬁnal act of the evening,
the courageous, the curvaceous,
Creamettes!
It's The Dreamettesl The Dreamettesl
Move, move
Move right out of my life
You better move
You’re steppin’ on my heart
I said, move
You’re tearin’ it apart
Please move
Oh, what am I gonna do?
My heart
ls breakin’, breakin’ up over you
You’ve got such magnetic power
That just keeps holding me down
/ feel just like a flower
That you’re keeping stuck
in the ground, ground, ground
Move, move
Move right out of my life
Move it, move it
Out of my life
Move right out of my life
Move it, move it
Out of my life
Move, move
Move right out of my life
You are so horribly satanic
The way you lead me around
/ feel just like the Titanic
I’m always going down
Move, move
You’re steppin’ on my style
Yes, you are
I said, move, move
I want to breathe for a while
Hey, baby
Get out of my life
There ’s too much pain and strife
So why don ’t you pack it up
and move it?
Take the cat, kit and caboodle
Take your broken-down car
Your smelly cigar
And just move right out of my
Move right out of my life
Come on! Come on! You can do better!
Let’s hear it for the delectable,
deﬁant Dreamettes!
Hey, Mister. Five dimes
say The Dreamettes don't win.
You got it.
They weren't going to win anyway.
Now remember,
the winner of this year’s contest gets
a week’s paid engagement right here
at the famous Detroit Theater.
All right now.
And that very lucky,
very talented star of tomorrow is
Mr. Tiny Joe Dixon!
Does this mean
we're not going to be famous now?
Well, not tonight.
Come on, let's go home.
VVhy?
Because I'm tired
and I got to get up early for work.
I mean, what's the point?
Lorrell, how old were we
when we first started singing together?
Twelve.
And C.C., how many dances
you got dreamed up for us?
How many songs written there
in your notebook?
I don't know. Maybe a hundred.
And, Effie, have you ever met anyone
who could sing as crazy as you?
No.
And still we get nowhere?
So I'm asking you, what's the point?
The point is you don't need
an amateur contest,
because there's nothing
amateur about you.
What you need is a break,
and I'm here to give it to you.
Thirty bucks each
to sing behind Mr. Jimmy Early tonight.
Jimmy Early?
And a guaranteed 10-week
engagement on the road
starting tomorrow morning
at $400 a week.
-$400?
-Yes.
-You swear?
-If I'm lying, I'm dying.
By the way, Mr. Early said
he'd hire my Aunt Ethel
to watch after you gals
while you're away from home.
Mama's going to love that!
Effie, do you hear this?
We're singing behind
Jimmy Early tonight!
-I don't do backup.
-Come on, girl.
All we got to do is just sing
a few "oohs" and "aahs."
I don't do "oohs" and "aahs."
Now, you look, Effie.
-This could be our big break.
-Singing backup is a trap.
Now, I'm sorry, Mister,
but we cannot accept your offer.
All right, all right, all right.
Look, I know you're good.
And you know you're good, too.
And very talented.
And not only that,
you are a stone cold fox.
But that ain't enough.
A girl like you can get hurt out there
if you ain't got somebody protecting you.
Now, I'm here to do that for you, baby.
But you got to believe me.
You got to trust in me.
I ain't gonna disappoint you.
-Come on, Effie? What do you say?
-Come on, Effie.
-Well, Mr...
-Curtis Taylor, Jr.
Curtis Taylor, Jr., our manager,
says we're singing behind
Mr. Jimmy Early tonight!
Oh, baby, I love you!
This business sure has got
a lot of ups and downs!
Are you ready for the Thunder Man?
and he ain't coming up
unless he can hear you!
Let's hit it, boys. Showtime.
Hey, Marty, I said no mayonnaise, man.
How many times I got to tell you?
No mayonnaise
on the chicken sandwich!
We got bigger problems, baby.
I warned you to lay off
the women that you work with.
There's plenty other ladies out there.
Well, who got time
to go out and find them, Marty?
I'm always working, baby.
Yeah, 'cause Marty always
keeps you working.
Hell, yeah. That's why I keep letting you
give me the wrong sandwich.
Let's go get this money now.
-ls everything set?
-Yeah, Jimmy's down with the two girls.
This is a group.
It's either three or nothing.
Hey, man, who is this guy?
My clients always work together.
I know you.
Didn't you sell me my Cadillac?
Yeah, yeah. In addition to
my management company,
l have a Cadillac dealership
on Woodward Avenue.
Yeah, well, my kitty needs a tune-up.
And Jimmy only works with two, baby.
Sorry, brother, it's two or nothing.
Those the girls right there?
I think three is gonna work outjust fine.
Ladies!
Ladies. Ladies, thank you so much.
You're saving Jimmy's life.
Thank you so much, ladies.
I'm at your feet.
You see that? I'm at your feet, baby.
Thank you so much.
And I'd do anything for y'all. Anything.
You hear what I'm saying? Anything.
Exactly what would you like
Jimmy to do for you, baby?
Well, Mr. Early,
you could teach us the song.
Thirteen years
of solid gold platters
Rising costs
And cocktail chatter
Fat deejays
Stereophonic sound
on, baby
The game of hits
Goes round and around
But you can fake your way to the top
Round and around
Try that part right there, baby.
Fake your way to the top
Round and around
Yeah, you fell right in there,
didn't you, sweetheart?
You can fake your way to the top
Round and around
Shit, I knew you'd have it.
But it’s always real, so real
Always so real
When you’re coming down
Yeah, yeah, been around
Oh, / know what’s happening
I’ve been around
Faking my way
Through every town
I’ve made my living
Off of my sound
And the game of hits
It goes around and around
and around and around
Around and around
A man gets lonely
Workin’ hard on the road
He’s away from his woman
It’s a heavy load
That back there is Harlem.
This is Hollywood.
And you ain't welcome in Hollywood.
A man needs help
Tryin’ to make it all alone
He has a part-time baby
So he won ’t be alone
Time to bring up the lights!
Yeah, let’s see which one of these girls
is going home with Jimmy tonight?
I got a nice, warm bed waiting on you.
Jimmy, my bed.
All right now. Come on now.
Who wants to sit on Daddy’s lap?
Yeah!
Is your man here?
What? He’s in the bathroom?
Hey, somebody go up there
and lock that bathroom up.
Well, / don ’t wanna get in no trouble
up in here tonight.
My bed, with my bad self.
Come on! Break it down.
Make me feel so real
Feel so real
Don ’t it feel so real?
Yeah, it feels real
Yeah
I don't believe
all this all can be happening to me.
Miracles happen all the time
in the world of R&B, baby.
-What's R&B mean?
-Rough and black.
Mr. Early, you're so crazy.
Call me Jimmy, baby. Jimmy.
Oh, Mr. Jimmy. You're so crazy.
That does feel nice.
I mean, it feels funny.
You're married, aren't you?
Everybody say yeah
Yeah
Say yeah
Everybody knows
Jimmy's married, baby.
Then...
Then you get your married hands off!
So it's gonna take two weeks.
/ faked my way to the top
Round and around
Oh, yeah
/ faked my way to the top
Round and around
You know / faked my way to the top
It’s always real, so real
When you’re coming down
/ faked my way, yes, I did
Help me, Jesus
Help, help, help me, Jesus
/ faked my way to the top
Did you notice
the seats are periwinkle blue
to go along with
your pretty blue dress? And...
-Would you excuse me?
-Certainly.
Wayne? Help me out.
Hi.
How can I help you today?
Here. This is our periwinkle blue.
Matches your dress.
I'm just saying, you might do better
if you were just a little more, you know...
-Shy? Sugar-sweet, like you?
-Boys seem to like it.
Well, I am not interested
in boys, Deena.
What are you ladies jawing about?
Well, Curtis, we were just wondering...
Do you cheat on your wife,
like Mr. Jimmy Early?
Hey, Effie! I don't know her.
Deena's right.
It's really none of our business.
We don't even know if you're married.
l was married. It didn't work out.
Well, was she one of those teeny little
tweety-birds like little Miss Deena here?
Or do you prefer a real woman?
Well, actually, lwas raised
by my older sisters,
and they were just as real as you are.
Well, why don't you sit down
and tell me about them?
You know, lwould love to,
but give me a minute.
It ain't working, Marty.
That faint used to kill 'em.
-It used to slay 'em in the aisles.
-Slay 'em in the aisles, baby.
But now you got everybody doing it.
You got Otis, J.B.
Everybody doing my shit.
You're right, Jimmy.
Everybody's doing it.
Well, who's the original?
Who was the first one to fall down
and start screaming?
-That was you.
-l'm the first!
And you killed 'em tonight, baby.
It was beautiful, Jimmy. Beautiful.
Marty, you're full of shit, man.
I need something.
Man, I need something...
That's what I need.
Sweet Mother Jesus.
I need that right there!
What you need is a new sound.
What I need is a new Caddy.
That one you sold me is dripping oil.
Hey, Jimmy, you remember C.C.,
Effie's brother?
He's a very talented composer.
Yeah, I remember you.
You wrote that song, Move On.
Move.
The girls be, "Move, move, move."
Yeah, that was me, man.
-All right.
-Yeah.
What did you think of that song, Marty?
Well, I think it was kind of...
You know...
-Kind of boring, I thought.
-Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's boring, kid.
I'm no kid, mister.
I'm sorry, baby,
but when Jimmy's involved,
the song got to have some soul!
Damn! Lord have mercy!
Got to have soul!
Soul, gospel, R&B, jazz, blues,
everything else the man
has grabbed from us.
Listen, there's got to be a better way
for us to get our music
to a broader audience,
only this time
with our artists and our money.
Marty, this man is handing me
a line of crap.
Yeah, I know, baby.
Got me a Cadillac
Cadillac, Cadillac
Got me a Cadillac car
Got me a Cadillac
Cadillac, Cadillac
Look at me, mister, I’m a star
I know what you cats are trying to do,
and you can forget it.
James Early ain't no street-corner punk
looking for his first date.
He's an established artist
with a recording contract.
On a shitty local label
that can't get him to the pop charts.
We can't do nothing about that.
All I'm asking is one record, man.
One song with a simple hook.
"Look at me in my pretty car,
makes me feel like a movie star."
You know where all the hits
happen these days? In cars, man.
Songs that make you feel good
while you're driving your automobile.
Yeah?
Jimmy's fans like taking the bus.
Let's hit it, Jimmy.
Hey, what do you think about
using that bridge there, baby?
Movin’ out
Mo vin’ up
Mo vin’ on
Sounds a little tick-tock, boys.
Let's stay in the pocket.
Going to work! Shut it down!
Recording, Cadillac Car. Take nine.
I got me a Cadillac
Cadillac, Cadillac
I got me a Cadillac car
Got me a Cadillac
Cadillac, Cadillac
Look at me, mister, I’m a star
I’m on the move
I’m gettin’ on
l’m breakin’ out
And it won ’t take long
Behind the wheel
Got a song
Pedal’s down
And I’m gone
We ’ve got that coming up
in the next hour,
but for now,
let me get a hold of your ear.
It's a different sound
for the Thunder Man.
And I think you're gonna enjoy it.
Got me a Cadillac
Cadillac, Cadillac
Oh, my God, Lorrell!
Do you hear that? That's us!
We're on the radio, Curtis!
-What's happening?
-Black station, the signal's too weak.
Turn this boat around! Hurry up!
C.C., fix it! What are you waiting for?
Antenna's up
Top is down
Peelin’ out
Don ’t care where I’m bound
Got these four wheels
Spinnin’ round
Me and my two-tone Caddy
Gonna blow this town
Movin’ out
Cadillac Caris No. 8 on the R&B charts,
and No. 98 on the pop charts.
Movin’ out
Mo vin’ up
Mo vin’ on
Right to the top
Got me a Cadillac
Cadillac, Cadillac
Got me a Cadillac car
Oh, I’ve got me a Cadillac
Cadillac, Cadillac
Look at me, mister, I’m a star
Look at me, mister
I’m a star
That’s Dave & the Sweethearts
with their marvelous
new recording, Cadillac Car.
You hear this shit?
They act like we don't even exist!
Is that how it works, Curtis?
The man decides he wants something,
he just takes it?
I mean, how can they do that?
That's my song.
Our song.
Marty says this happens all the time.
Once something...
That's bullshit, man!
He should have protected us!
They stole our hit.
I never thought...
You got me to think for you now
I’ve tried to make good
Without much success
You’ve got me to think for you now
Every time / try for more
/ wind up with less
You gotta put your soul
on a moral break
Get to the point
You just gotta
take
Who was the first artist
to sing Hound Dog?
Elvis Presley.
Big Mama Thornton. She had
the No. 1 single on the R&B charts,
but white stations wouldn't play it
because to them it was
just another race record.
We are gonna make friends with the
most important deejays in this country.
It's strictly pay-for-play with those boys.
That takes money. Real money.
What is that? Chicken scratch?
Let's get to work.
Steppin' to the bad side
Gonna take a mean ride
The smile / had is gone away
Those that steal are gonna pay
Steppin' to the bad side today
I’m telling you now, it’s got to end
No more trusting them, my friend
Change our style
Change our tone
Make the songs we sing our own
Steppin' to the bad side
Gonna take a mean ride
I’ll get you all the breaks you need
In just two years, we’ll be in the lead
Can’t sit back, it’s plain to see
Open your eyes and trust in me
Steppin' to the bad side
Gonna take a mean ride
l was a man who tried to be good
l was always misunderstood
You can’t play fair or be too meek
You gotta get way down
and show your danger streak
Steppin' to the bad side
Here's a great new song
from Jimmy Early and The Dreamettes.
Gonna take a mean ride
...a new hit from Jimmy Early
and The Dreamettes.
It's called Steppin' to the Bad Side.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome
to the Apollo Theater’s legendary stage
Jimmy Early and The Dreamettes,
singing their No. 1 hit,
Steppin' to the Bad Side.
Steppin' to the bad side
I had to step into the bad side
I had to take myself a mean ride
You know that smile I had is gone away
Those that steal are gonna pay
Steppin' to the bad side today
A man just stole my woman from me
He took her down to Tennessee
She was the best girl / ever knew
If it wasn’t for him, she’d still be true
Always been a good man, it’s been said
When / catch the man
He’ll wish he was dead
Men like him make good men mad
Starting today I’m gonna be bad
l’m steppin’ to the bad side
l have to take myself a mean ride
You know that smile I had is gone away
Those that steal are gonna pay
Steppin' to the bad side
Steppin' to the bad side today
-Step on
-Step on to the bad side
Step on to the bad side
-Step on
-Step on to the bad side
Steppin' to the bad side
-Step on
-Step on to the bad side
Step, step
Steppin' to the bad side
-Step on
-Step on to the bad side
Step on to the bad side
Step on up to the bad side
Got to step to the bad side
The motor is now cranked up
and we are moving up
the highway of freedom
toward the city of equality.
And we can’t afford to stop now,
because our nation
has a date with destiny.
We must keep moving.
l have a dream this afternoon
that one day right here in Detroit,
Negroes will be able to buy a house
anywhere that their money
will carry them,
and they will be able to get a job.
Made my peach cobbler!
Curtis!
-Hey, baby, you know my sisters.
-Tell me something.
Do you think it's right to promote
an amateur performer
over a professional?
I don't know what this is about.
It's about fairness, Curtis.
It's about people paying their dues.
Ain't that what you keep telling me?
"Get in line, Effie. Wait your turn."
So why am I sitting here without
so much as a B-side on the 45
when an amateur like
Martin Luther King, Jr.
gets his own freakin' album?
I mean, can he even sing?
All right, that was a good one.
You're a great man, Curtis.
Isn't your brother a great man?
Never met a man
Quite like you
Doin’ all he can
Makin’ my dreams come true
You’re strong and you’re smart
You’ve taken my heart
And I’ll give you the rest of me, too
You’re the perfect man for me
llove you, I do
llove you
Hold it, hold it. I promise
I'll get to all of you in a minute,
but right now I need
someone that can type.
Anybody got some
secretarial experience?
-I can do it.
-You? Come on.
What's all this?
All right, come in.
/ never felt
Quite like this
Good about myself
From my very ﬁrst kiss
I’m here when you call
You’ve got it all
And conﬁdence like / never knew
You’re the perfect man for me
llove you, I do
You’ve got the charm
You simply disarm me every time
As long as you drive
l’m along for the ride your way
You said it before
There won ’t be a door
That’s closed to us
l’m puttin’ all my trust in you
’Cause you, you’ll always be true
/ never could have known
This would be
You and you alone
All for me
/ know you’re the best
You’ve passed every test
It’s almost too good to be true
You’re the perfect man for me
llove you, I do
C.C. wrote it for me.
What do you think, Curtis?
It's too light.
We want light, but not that light.
Not that light?
Okay, but when we fix it,
you're gonna put it in the show, right?
First things first.
I got to get Jimmy booked
down in Miami,
even if I got to buy my own hotel.
But you promised I wouldn't spend
my life singing backup, Curtis.
And I still promise that.
I'm not gonna let this beautiful voice
go to waste.
You just got to trust me.
-Can we talk about it more tonight?
-All night.
-All right.
-Bye, man.
All right.
Boy, you're a real snake.
A cheap, second-rate hustler.
Street-corner con artist.
Look, you want to buy a car, Marty?
Why don't we talk about it in my office?
I'm away a week,
and you cancel dates behind my back.
I spent six months
setting up this tour for Jimmy.
Jimmy's too big for
that Chitlin Circuit shit.
I'm trying to get him booked
at the Paradise in Miami.
-Miami?
-Miami.
You're really drifting out there, chump.
You couldn't get Sammy Davis, Jr.
in there.
That place is so white, they
don't even let our boys park the cars.
I got him an audition.
-Luck, man. Hustler's luck.
-That's just the beginning.
Then we're gonna do the Copa,
the Americana.
He could even do American Bandstand.
I've been in this business
too many years
-to listen to some hotshot talk bullshit.
-Not bullshit, Marty. Change.
I'm talking change. Can't you see?
The time is now.
Jimmy needs a new act, something
classier, with a catchier sound.
That'll go down better with white folks.
That'll put him where he should be,
making the type of money
he should be making.
He's at the top of the pop charts.
He's hot.
-We can do this for him.
-We?
-Yeah, we.
-We do nothing.
Jimmy's mine, so back off, Curtis.
Jimmy's mine.
Jimmy don't belong to no one.
Are you defending
this car salesman, Jimmy?
Can't you see he's using you?
Ain't nobody using Jimmy, all right?
Nobody.
Who do you think you're
talking to, baby? It's Marty.
The man who found you singing for
pennies when you were 10 years old.
It's a whole new day, Marty,
and a brand new Jimmy.
You want him, brother? You got him.
I'm through.
-Hey, what you doing?
-You can't have it all, baby.
Hey, come on, Marty, don't go.
I want you to stay.
I love you, Jimmy.
But you can't have it all.
Lady, you got to be Jewish.
Of course, yeah, of course.
It’s 105 degrees in here, and you’re
the only one wearing a mink stole.
Hey, my friend, what’s your nationality?
"Nationality. " / know it’s a big word.
What are you, Cuban?
Of course. You’re Cuban.
You’re Cuban, I’m a Jew.
You know, lsay this
from the bottom of my heart.
A Negro, if he had enough money,
could move into my neighborhood.
You, not a chance.
Tonight, though,
we ’re here to make history.
The ﬁrst Negro headliners
to ever play Miami Beach.
What do you think of that?
Come on.
It’s a very convenient arrangement.
These are good people.
/ mean, they can sing, they can dance,
they can even mop up aften/vards.
You can’t ﬁnd help like that.
Anyway, please give a warm round
of applause to the very talented
Jimmy Early and The Dreamettes!
Come on!
/ want you, baby
/ want you
And / need you, baby
/ need you
on, baby
Baby
You got me on my knees
Got me on my knees
You got me begging
Baby, baby
Baby, please
/ know you don ’t trust
the way / feel
You know, we can always create
a younger look for American Bandstand.
Yeah.
You got me on my knees
You got me beggin’
Baby, baby
Oh, yeah
Oh, / want you, baby
And / need you, baby
Yes, I do
/ want you
Baby, you got me, baby
Now I’m yours, baby
Yes!
I love me some Jimmy, but he's
gonna have to stop calling me "baby."
I'm a woman now.
Did you see the man
Curtis was sitting with?
Did you hear what I said, Deena?
I am a woman now.
-Lorrell, I know.
-What do you mean, you know?
-Has Jimmy talked?
-He didn't have to.
How could you?
Come on, you're just a baby, Lorrell.
I am not, Deena. I'm a woman now.
I'm 18, so I'm a woman.
Yeah, she's a mature woman, like me,
and she loves Jimmy
just as much as I love Curtis.
-lt's not wrong when you love someone.
-ls that all you two can think about?
-Yeah.
Well, there's no doubt
my mama brought me up fit.
-Deena, you're just jealous.
-Let yourself go just once.
It's so wonderful
to have somebody to love.
-You ladies decent?
-Well, I am.
-I can't speak for these two.
-Hey, babe.
Curtis, how did it go
with American Bandstand?
Timing's not right.
Well, maybe they'll be more
interested after we play the Copa.
-Y'all ain't playing the Copa.
-What?
I'm breaking you and Jimmy up.
I know what you're doing, Curtis!
You're breaking us up 'cause
you don't want me with Jimmy.
None of you do!
Because you're all jealous!
Well, nothing's breaking me
and Jimmy up! Nothing!
I'm breaking you up because
Jimmy is going back out on the road,
while you stay here
and open your own act.
Did you say our own act?
Finally, Curtis! This is what
I've been waiting for. I love you.
Oh, well, honey, I'm fine with that.
I mean, I love me some Jimmy,
but I don't want to be singing
behind him the rest of my life.
Ladies and gentlemen,
presenting The Dreams.
The Dreamettes were little girls.
You're women now.
-You see, Deena, I told you!
-We open in a week,
so we got a lot of work to do.
We're gonna have a lot of changes.
I'm bringing on Jolly Jenkins
to stage a whole new show.
He's done movies, Broadway,
clubs acts, you name it.
New wigs, the expensive kind.
Brand-new costumes
to appeal to a younger crowd.
And...
Effie?
-Deena's going to sing lead.
-Deena's doing what?
-Lead.
-What do you mean?
-I always sing lead. Tell him, C.C.
-We're trying something new, Effie.
-You knew about this?
-Curtis and I talked it over.
He said it's only temporary.
We finally get the chance
to have our own act
and Deena's doing lead?
She can't sing like I can.
She's right, Curtis. I can't.
I don't want to.
Now, y'all gonna do what I tell you to do.
This is a new sound with a new look.
New look?
Nobody can see her on a record!
The only way we'll be able to change
things is by appealing to kids,
and kids today watch television.
So Deena's going to sing in the lead
'cause you like the way she looks?
Am I ugly to you, Curtis?
Baby, come on. You know
how I feel about you. Come on.
-Don't make it personal.
-Well, what am I supposed to do?
Deena's beautiful and she's
always been beautiful!
But I've got the voice, Curtis!
I've got the voice!
You can't put me in back! You just can't!
Well, you'll be singing backup with me.
What's so wrong with that?
Let Deena do all the work for a change.
Your voice alone is too special.
We need a lighter sound
to cross over to the pop charts.
It's what we need.
What about what I need?
Curtis says it's the
best thing for the group.
What about what’s best for me?
He feels The Dreams can cross over.
What about how / feel?
Effie, do it for me.
What about me?
It’s more than you
It is more than me
No matter what we are
We are a family
This dream is for all of us
This one can be real
And you can’t stop us now
Because of how you feel
It’s more than you
It is more than me
Whatever dreams we have
They’re for the family
We’re not alone anymore
Now there are others there
And that dream is big enough
For all of us to share
So don ’t think you’re going
You’re not going anywhere
You’re staying and taking your share
And if you get afraid again
I’ll be there
We are a family
Like a giant tree
Branching out toward the sky
We are a family
We are so much more
Than just you and l
We are a family
Like a giant tree
Growing stronger, growing wiser
We are growing
free
We need you
We are a family
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Crystal Room is proud to present
the club debut of America ’s newest
recording stars, The Dreams!
Every man has his own special dream
And your dream’s
just about to come true
Life’s not as bad as it may seem
If you open your eyes
To what’s in front of you
We ’re your dream girls
Boys, we’ll make you happy
Yeah
We ’re your dream girls
Boys, we’ll always care
Dream girls will never leave you
No, no
And all you’ve got to do is dream, baby
We 7/ be there
Dream
Dream girls will help you
through the night
Dream
Dream girls will make you feel all right
Dream girls keep you dreamin’
your whole life through
Your dream girls can make
your dreams come true
We ’re your dream girls
Boys, we’ll make you happy
Yeah, yeah, yeah
We ’re your dream girls
Boys, we 7/ always...
I'm amazed, Mr. Taylor.
Much as I love my daughter,
I never thought
she had much of a voice.
Deena has something better.
She has a quality.
-You make her sound like a product.
-Product. I like that.
We’ll be there.
Dream
Dream girls will help you to survive
Dream girls will keep
your fantasies alive
Dream girls always love you
and they’ll be true
Your dream girl can only
make love to you
I’m not the dream that you had before
I’m the dream that will give you
more and more
We ’re your dream girls
Boys, we’ll make you happy
Yeah, yeah, yeah
We ’re your dream girls
Boys, we’ll always care
Dream girls
Dream girls will never leave you
And all you’ve got to do is dream
All you’ve got to do is dream
Baby, we 7/ be there
We ’re your dream girls
Oh, yeah
Dream girls
All you’ve got to do is dream
Just dream, baby
We 7/ be there
We will be there
Who was the first one
to wear shiny clothes?
-Little Richard.
-That was me, baby! I started that.
You remember that burgundyjacket
I had with the bolt lightning on the back?
Lightning was in glitter.
Glitter's shiny, baby.
-Hey, Jimmy.
-...Deena Jones and The Dreams.
Rumors at Abbey Road say
George Martin is keen to work with
the talented trio.
Could they be ready to record
with the Fab Four?
Well, the boys will just have to wait.
These girls are busy
blazing a trail across the globe.
People ask me
how I came up with the sound.
I tell them it's like
making a great sundae.
You start outwith two scoops
of ice cream, some sauce,
-and then you put a cherry on top.
-And is Deena the cherry?
Why, Miss Jones is the cherry,
the nuts, the sauce, the cream
-and the banana, too.
-Miss Jones, right here.
We look on with shock and dismay at
the images we ’re bringing you tonight.
Detroit under siege and in flames
as rioters and looters storm the city.
President Johnson has declared
a state of emergency.
You used to be so light and free
You used to smile just looking at me
Now all you give is jealous hate
Come on, baby
Better lose some weight
Heavy, heavy
You got so heavy, baby
Stop!
Effie, what's going on?
You are still too loud.
-I'm trying, Curtis.
-If you don't ease up, I'll do it for you.
Maybe we should
just come back in the morning.
You know we can't.
The album's already a month late.
Look, I know you're tired.
You're tired, right?
-Can Ijust get one more?
-Okay.
All right? Okay.
Let's get it right.
Record Heavy, Heavy. Take 30.
Heavy, heavy
You got so heavy, baby
You got so heavy on me
-Where do you think you're going?
-You're a liar, Curtis.
You'd better watch your mouth.
You're sleeping with her
and everyone knows!
Hey, hey, hey, don't go out there!
Burn it up!
-We're black-owned!
-Yeah!
-You all right?
-I don't feel well, Curtis.
CBS’s Star Cavalcade
presents the incredible Dreams
singing their latest hit, Heavy, Heavy.
You got so heavy, baby
Heavy, heavy
You got so heavy on me
You used to want nothing from me
You used to say, "Let’s both be free"
You used to dance instead of walk
-Tighten up on camera two. Tighten up.
-Move in, camera two.
Heavy, heavy
You got so heavy, baby
Talk, talk, talk
Heavy, heavy
Heavy, heavy, heavy, heavy
You got so heavy, baby
Yeah, yeah
Heavy, heavy
You got so heavy on me
Effie, you're going crazy!
Tell me, what have I done?
You stole my dream, Deena,
and you stole my man!
I don't want to hear that kind of talk
out of you...
Don't act like you don't know
what this is about!
Effie, stop screaming.
Everybody can hear you.
I don't care! Let them all hear!
I'm warning you, Effie, you stop
bringing us down! And get back there!
Why, Curtis? You don't need me.
All you care about is her bony ass!
You better back off.
Or what?
I didn't think so.
Love, love me, baby
Love, love me, chi/d
’Cause, baby, baby, baby
You’re driving me wild
Listen, listen, listen.
The mirrors got to turn together, guys.
They got to dance.
Mr. Taylor? We have
a bigger problem on our hands.
Do I have to remind you
that it's New Year's Eve?
Burt, don't worry about it.
I've got it taken care of.
These people are paying 50 bucks.
They expect to see three girls.
Trust me.
-Curtis, I just don't feel right about this.
-It's done.
Wardrobe needs you first.
We are a family
Like a giant tree
Branching out toward the sky
We are a family
-I'm sorry I'm late.
-Effie.
C.C., sorry I missed rehearsals.
But I went to the doctor,
and I am feeling much better now.
Look, don't try to make it tonight.
What are you talking about, baby?
It's New Year's Eve.
Yeah.
Curtis just stepped out to make a call.
Why don't you go up to your room
and later he'll come up and talk to you?
I said, I'm fine.
Excuse me. I have to get dressed now.
Oh, God, I'm so nervous.
I got all the steps down,
but those harmonies...
C.C., what's going on?
Lorrell, what's going on?
-Effie, Curtis was supposed to...
-Love me.
Curtis was supposed to love me.
There you are, Effie.
I've been looking all over.
/ turn my back and ﬁnd myself
out on the line
You could have warned me
But that would have been too kind
I've been warning you for months
to clean up your act.
You've been late, you've been mean,
giving all kinds of bullshit flack.
That’s a lie, that’s a lie
It’s just I haven ’t been feeling that well
Effie, please!
Stop excusing yourself.
You've been late, you've been mean,
and getting fatter all the time.
Now, you’re lyin’, lyin’
I’ve never been so thin!
You’re lyin’, you’re lyin’
Who thinks she’s better than everybody
She ain't better than anybody!
She’s nothing but common!
Now, who you calling common
You self-indulgent, self-absorbed,
non-professional?
You! I’m calling you
I’m calling you the common piece
he’s knocking off
Now, you listen to me
Miss Blame It On The World
See, I’ve put up with you
for much too long
l have put up with your bitching
I’ve put up with your nagging
And all your screaming, too
Now, when are you two gonna stop
all this ﬁghting?
Stay out of this, Lorrell.
This is between Deena and me.
Yeah? Well, it’s between me, too!
I’m as much a part of this group
as anybody else
And I’m tired, Efﬁe, I’m tired
of all the problems you’re making us
/ always knew you two were together
What?
/ always knew you two
were ganging up on me!
She had nothing to do with this change
It was you, it was you
Always thinking of you!
/ knew you were trouble from the start
Trouble?
You were real bad trouble from the start
Curtis, I'm your woman.
But you’re getting out now
I’m not building this group
to have you tear it apart
Go ahead and rant and scream
and shout!
Don’t worry, baby, I’ll buy you out
There's no money
dirty enough to buy me out.
You remember that, Curtis.
Lay off, Efﬁe
Just take the money and run
You're in this with him, C.C.?
Cool it, Efﬁe
This time you know what you done
So they bought
your black ass, too, huh?
I said, cool it, Efﬁe
This time you’ve gone too far
Oh, I can go further! I can go further!
I don ’t want to stay around this
I’m just breakin’ into this business
This is between all of you
-This is none of my affair
-Yeah?
Well, it’s between you, too
Now, little sister
This snow job is as much your sin
Look at me! Look at me!
How much did you put out to get in?
Now, you watch your mouth
Watch your mouth, Miss Efﬁe White
’Cause I don ’t take that talk
from no second-rate diva
who can’t sustain
I’m not feeling well, I’ve got pain
Efﬁe, we all got pain!
For seven years, I’ve sung with you
/ was your sister
You were our trouble
And now you’re telling me it’s all over
And now we’re telling you it’s all over
And now I’m telling you / ain’t going
It’s all over
/ ain’t going
And / am telling you
I’m not going
You’re the best man I’ll ever know
There’s no way I can ever go
No, no, there’s no way
No, no, no way I’m living without you
I’m not living without you
I don ’t want to be free
I’m staying, I’m staying
And you, and you
You’re gonna love me
And / am telling you
I’m not going
Even though the rough times
are showing
There’s just no way, there’s no way
We’re part of the same place
We’re part of the same time
We both share the same blood
We both have the same mind
And time and time
We’ve had so much to share
No, no, no, no, no, no way
I’m not waking up tomorrow morning
And ﬁnding that there’s nobody there
Darling, there’s no way
No, no, no, no way
I’m living without you
I’m not living without you
You see, there’s just no way
There’s no way
Please don ’t go away from me
Stay with me, stay with me
Stay, stay and hold me
Please stay and hold me, Mister Man
Try it, mister, try it, mister
/ know you can
Tear down the mountain
Yell, scream and shout
You can say what you want
I’m not walking out
Stop all the rivers
Push, strike and kill
I’m not gonna leave you
There’s no way / will
And / am telling you
I’m not going
You’re the best man I’ll ever know
There’s no way I could ever, ever go
No, no, no, no way
I’m living without you
I’m not living without you
Not living without you
I don ’t want to be free
I’m staying, I’m staying
And you, and you, and you
You’re gonna love me
Yes, you are
Love me!
Love
You’re gonna love
me
Ladies and gentlemen, the showroom
at Caesar’s Palace is proud to present
Deena Jones and The Dreams.
Love, love me, baby
Love, love me, chi/d
’Cause baby, baby, baby
You’re driving me wild
l’m somebody, somebody
And nobody’s gonna hold me down
No, nobody, nobody, nobody’s
gonna hold me down
l’m somebody
It all started on the streets of Detroit,
where three girls named
Deena, Lorre/l and Michelle
dreamed about one day
becoming singing stars.
Since their triumphant Las Vegas debut,
they’ve had No. 1 albums
for each of the last six years.
And they’re showing no signs
of slowing down anytime soon.
But for Deena Jones,
none of these exciting events compare
to the day she
became Mrs. Curtis Taylor, Jr.
With his wife at his side,
Mr. Taylor has built his music empire
into the most successful Afro-American
business in the United States,
producing such sensations
as The Family Funk,
Jimmy Ear/y,
and the phenomenal
Campbell Connection.
Deena Jones has conquered
the worlds of music and television.
And soon, she hopes to take on
her biggest challenge yet,
the epic, untold story
of Cleopatra ’s early years
all set to the music of today.
No, nobody, nobody, nobody’s
gonna hold me down
l’m somebody
Thank you.
Now, I saved the bad news
for last, Curtis.
Paramount passed on Cleopatra.
VVhy?
Too period.
And they're not convinced
Deena's got the chops.
Fuck it.
We'll finance the movie ourselves.
I just don't know
how you're going to swing it.
You're spreading yourself
too thin as it is.
The music side is starting to suffer.
-Music runs itself.
-Those days are over, Curtis.
Just putting Deena's name on a record
don't make it a hit anymore.
And our acts are dying on the road.
Especially Jimmy.
-He needs new material.
-No, Jimmy needs to sober up.
Wayne, start pitching the networks
on the anniversary special.
We'll do a greatest hits tie-in.
We'll rake in enough green
to make 10 movies,
and pay for all of you
useless motherfuckers.
Have a good day.
-How's my beautiful wife?
-Curtis.
-I'm not sure how to tell you this.
-Tell me what? Just say it.
I know how much time
you've invested in this movie.
But I can't play that part.
I promised you I was gonna
make you a movie star, right?
Cleopatra is gonna get us there.
I mean, this is the queen of a nation,
not some hooker, junkie, maid.
I know. I know.
It's a very important story.
And it's more than you.
Think about all the beautiful black
women that ain't even born yet.
When they grow up they're gonna say,
"I can play any part I want to.
"Look at Deena Jones. She did it."
But it's ridiculous. Come on.
She's 16 years old
for most of the movie.
Well, baby, you'll always be 16 to me.
Maybe that's the problem.
Maybe you just don't see me
for who I am.
When / ﬁrst saw you
I said, "Oh, my"
lsaid, "Oh, my, that’s a dream
"That’s my dream"
I needed a dream
When it all seemed to go bad
Then / found you
And / have had the most
beautiful dreams
Any man’s ever had
When / ﬁrst saw you
I said, "Oh, my
"Oh, my, that’s my dream
"That’s my dream"
I needed a dream to make me strong
You were the only reason I had to go on
You are my dream
All the things / never knew
Who could believe
they could ever come true?
And who would believe
the world would believe
in my dreams, too?
When / ﬁrst saw you
I said, "Oh, my
"Oh, my
"That’s my dream"
-What would make you happy, Deena?
-You know.
We got plenty of time for that.
Please, Curtis. Let me have your child.
-Magic, read your book.
-I'm done.
Then read it again!
Did you look for work this week,
Miss White?
Mister, you can keep
asking me that question.
But the answer's always
gonna be the same.
The only thing I know how to do is sing.
And since there ain't nobody
letting me do that no more,
no, I did not look for ajob.
Have you considered asking
the girl's father for help?
Magic don't have a father.
Listen.
/ know you have questions
Same ones as me
How long has it been?
How long will it be?
When will come the morning
to drive the night away?
Tell me, when will come the morning
of a brighter day?
Yeah
Patience, little sister
Patience, little brother
Patience, patience, yeah
Take each other by the hand
Yeah, yeah
Patience, little sisters
Patience...
-It's from your brother.
-Send it back.
-There's cash in here.
-You spend it.
Effie White, you are a mule.
Come on, baby, it's time to go to bed.
Just as stubborn as your mother.
Go home, old man.
Magic, come on, baby.
And a mountain to climb
Patience, patience
It’s gonna take some time
Yeah, yeah
We must walk in peace
We got to walk in peace
It’s the only
Only way, yes
If we want to see that morning, yeah
Of a brighter day
Patience
Come on!
Little sister
Patience
Little brother
Patience, patience, yeah
I’m gonna ﬁnd a way
Patience
Little sister
Little brother
Nice to see you, Effie.
Of a brighter day
Patience
-Teddy, get yourself back to the party.
-I'm waiting for Deena.
It's good. It's real good.
We wanted to surprise you, Curtis.
That's why we went ahead
and recorded it first.
This is exactly what I need
right now, Curtis.
It's what you've been always
talking about to me, a new sound!
Still, it's a message song.
It tells the truth.
People are angry out there.
I'm angry.
My brother's over in Vietnam
fighting in a pointless war,
and I'm angry about it.
That's right, Curtis.
Isn't music supposed to express
what people are feeling?
Music is supposed to sell.
Look, don't worry about it, Jimmy.
We'll find you some new material.
Deena, I want you to meet this guy
out here.
And about the shirt, you should lose it.
It's messing up your image.
I'm so sorry, Jimmy.
Deena.
Honey, you don't need to be
doing that stuff right now.
Come on, brother. It's Christmas.
Jimmy? Baby?
I'm not staying around for this.
Brother...
Yeah, but what about Holiday?
I had Billie here every winter
from '42 to '58.
Great voice. Bad tipper.
Well, I tell you, Effie White is the best
singer this town has seen since then.
Yeah, but the last time she performed,
the girl fell apart.
That was years ago.
She just lost her confidence for a while.
She's different now.
Max, please. For the old days?
They're gone, Marty.
Sorry, Marty, but the babysitter was late.
Effie White, this is Max Washington.
Hi, Max.
Marty said you needed a singer.
I was just telling Max
that you're serious about working.
He knows all about you.
You do, huh?
Daddy, you don't know the half.
One night after you hire me,
we'll sit down and I'll tell you
all about how I blew through
half a million dollars in two years!
-Hey, come on.
-Drinking.
You don't want to take up too much
of the man's time.
-Now, Carl knows all the songs.
-Carl? Where's Bernard?
He has a job in Evanston.
But I can't sing
with someone I don't know.
Effie. You got to.
Marty, I don't have the time.
Max, please. Just give me a minute.
Now, you listen, Effie White.
For four months, I've been your money.
I've taken you to every club
in this freezing town,
and I'm telling you that this is it.
It's time that you stop making excuses
so that you don't have to prove anything.
You're gonna have to start proving it,
just like the rest of us.
I don't know.
Maybe Curtis was right about you.
You want all of the privileges
but none of the responsibilities.
Hey, Max. Thanks anyway, man.
Sorry for wasting your time.
Do you know the song?
I told you I didn't want to see her.
Well, you are, mister. You are.
Look at me
/ am changing
Trying every way / can
I’ll be better than I am
I’m trying to ﬁnd a way
to understand
But I need you
/ need you
/ need a hand
/ am changing
Seeing everything so clear
I’m gonna start right now, right here
I’m hoping
To work it out
And / know that I can
But I need you
/ need a hand
All of my life, I’ve been a fool
who said I could do it all alone
How many good friends
have / already lost?
And how many dark nights
have / known?
Walking down that wrong road
There was nothing / could ﬁnd
All those years of darkness
Could make a person blind
But now I can see / am changing
Trying every way / can
/ am changing
And I’ll be better than I am
But I need a friend
To help me start all over again
That would be just ﬁne
/ know it’s gonna work out this time
’Cause this time / am
This time / am
/ am changing
I’ll get my life together now
Yes!
/ know how I’m gonna start again
I’m gonna leave my past behind
Right, baby! Sing it loud!
I’ll change my life
I’ll make a vow
Nothing’s gonna stop me
HOW
Tonight, live from the Dorothy Chandler
Pavilion in Los Ange/es, California,
it’s The Sound of Tomorrow,
celebrating 10 years of hits
from Rainbow Records.
Every day at school, girl
I see your smiling face
The teacher tries to call on me
But I can’t concentrate
I’m too busy thinkin’
All about your face
lknow I’m in love with you
But you don ’t even know my name
Girl meets boy, boy meets girl
They could fall in love in a perfect world
But if boy and girl never meet
Then a perfect world can never be
Come on, girl!
Come on
llove you!
Come on, Jimmy, drink this.
-Five minutes, Mr. Early.
-Yeah, all right.
I thought you were going
to stay clean tonight, baby.
You know how important this is.
Yeah, lwas doing fine, too, till Melba
came out and messed with me.
All that, "You never take me nowhere,"
and, "I'm tired of staying in the house
night after night," shit.
Next thing I know, she's coming
down the stairs in her party dress.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me that your wife is
out there right now?
What was I supposed to do, baby?
That's why I needed to relax.
-Here, sugar, have a drink.
-Yeah, help me out here. I'm frazzled.
You know,
it's our anniversary, too, baby.
Don't you remember?
-Yeah, I remember that.
-Let me give you a kiss for each year.
That's sweet.
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight.
Eight years of unmarried life.
Hey, come on, now. Don't tell me
we're going to start this shit again.
We'll deal with this
after the show, all right?
Don't you walk out on me, Jimmy Early!
Girl meets boy, boy meets girl
Fall in love, perfect world
But if boy and girl never meet
Then a perfect world can never be
Come on, girl!
-I'm going to tell her, baby, I promise!
-But when, Jimmy? When?
Please, Ijust need
a little more time, all right?
Time's run out, Jimmy. I get it now.
-What you talking about?
-You never really loved me.
Lorrell. Baby, you know I love you.
I do. But right now, I got a show to do.
...three, two...
And now, the mellow sounds
of Jimmy Ear/y.
I meant you no harm
/ never meant to make you cry
You were the only one
I’ve ever loved in my life
And though it’s hard for me to show it
I’ve got to let you know it
’Cause, darling
/ love you more each day
But the words got in my way
Oh, I meant you no harm
And / would die
If you ever said goodbye
llove you
I meant you no harm
/ never, never meant to make you cry
You were the only one
I’ve ever loved in my life
Hey, hold it.
I can’t do it no more.
/ can’t sing no more sad songs.
Hey, Curtis, this is supposed to be
your night, right?
Let’s have some happy times.
Right, I’m gonna give you a count-off.
The rest of you all come in
when / tell you, all right?
What the hell's he doing?
One! Two! Three! Hit me!
Bass man, come on up!
Sound good! Yeah! Saxophone!
On the four!
One! Two! Three! Hit it!
Come on! Horns! Hit it!
Hey, Cur/y, let’s rap with Jimmy Ear/y
Got a home in the hills
Mercedes-Benz, hot swimming pool
Got lots of friends
Got clothes by the acre
Credit to spare
I could wake up tomorrow
and ﬁnd nobody there
But Jimmy want more
Jimmy want more
Jimmy want, Jimmy want
Jimmy want more!
Listen!
Jimmy want a rib
Jimmy want a steak
Jimmy want a piece
of your chocolate cake
But more than all that
Jimmy wants a break
’Cause Jimmy got soul, Jimmy got soul
Jimmy got, Jimmy got, Jimmy got soul!
Sooner or later, the time comes around
For a man to be a man
Take back his sound
I gotta do somethin’ to shake things up
/ like Johnny Mathis
But I can’t do that stuff
’Cause Jimmy got soul, Jimmy got soul
Jimmy got S-O-U-L soul!
I can’t do rock, I can’t do roll
What I can do, baby, is show my soul
’Cause Jimmy got soul, Jimmy got soul
Jimmy got, Jimmy got, Jimmy got soul!
Take it out.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please stay in your seats.
We ’re back live in two minutes.
-What'd you think of my show, baby?
-You made a fool out of yourself.
What are you talking about, man?
I was just being Jimmy.
Lorrell, will you please tell him,
if you can?
Jimmy keeps begging you for something
new, but all you do is ignore him.
Of course he's confused.
It don't take a whiz to know that only
a desperate man would drop his pants
in living color on network television.
Thanks, Lorrell. You told it like it is.
Yeah, well, that ain't all
I got to say to you, sugar.
My brother, we're through.
What you talking about?
What do you mean, we're through?
Come on, Jimmy, your time has passed.
Hey, man, I got soul!
You can't kill a man with soul!
Come on, man.
Let's at least end as friends, man.
If you ever need some help,
just give me a call.
Whatever.
Hey, Curtis, Idon't beg! Idon't crawl!
I'm an original!
Hey, where are you going?
You can't leave me, girl. I love you.
And Lorre/l loves Jimmy
Lorre/l loves Jimmy
It’s true
But Lorre/l and Jimmy
are through
I got a show to do.
Don't you remember, baby?
on, baby
I got a show to do
And now, please welcome the brightest
star in the Rainbow constellation,
Deena Jones
with the incredible Dreams!
Hello, America.
What a wonderful evening.
-/ love you all.
-I love you, Deena!
llove you, too.
Curtis, baby, this is for you.
We are a family, like a giant tree
Branching out toward the sky
We are a family
We are so much more
More than just you and l
Time to go, Mr. Early.
We are growing free
Yeah!
I don ’t beg, Curtis!
I don ’t crawl!
’Cause I was here long before you
And I’ll be here long after
You all
You're an incredibly beautiful woman.
-Thank you, Jerry.
-No, you're too beautiful.
This movie is about three grifters
heading to Vegas for one final score.
When Dawn goes down on
that truck driver,
you've got to smell the desperation.
I know that. That's what I love about her.
There's no pretense.
No fucking bullshit.
America's sweetheart here
has got a potty mouth.
Of course, if I were to become involved,
we have to do a little work on the part.
What do you mean?
I spent a year on the script, so...
I know, and it's good.
But she's not real yet.
To start with,
what kind of name is Dawn?
I'm from the projects in Detroit and
I ain't ever met a sister named Dawn.
Well, the script's just a blueprint.
It's not written in stone.
I hear Curtis is still trying to get
that crazy black Cleopatra made.
Is it true he's got some
mob money tied up in this?
My husband has his hands full
with the music side right now.
That's why I didn't want to bother him
with our meeting today.
So, say we do decide
to get in bed with you on this,
will Curtis even let you do it?
I hear he's got you
on a pretty tight leash.
That won't be a problem, Jerry.
Step, step, step on over
Wanting you, wanting you
Needing you, needing you
Shit.
-Hey.
-I didn't think it was possible, Curtis.
But I think you can squeeze
even more of the soul out of my music.
-We just made it danceable, that's all.
-What about the lyrics?
That rhythm takes all the feeling
out of the music!
This is what you've been asking for.
A totally new sound.
It's gonna be bigger than R&B
and rock and roll put together!
People are getting ready to boogie,
and when they do
they're gonna do it to our music.
Your music, Curtis.
It has nothing to do with me.
Come on, brother,
you know you're my main man.
Kiss my ass,
brother.
What the hell is going on now?
No, no!
The body was found at the
Tropicana Hotel in Hollywood.
Police say Mr. Early had been dead
for over a day,
the apparent victim
of a heroin overdose.
The 43-year-old R&B singer was
recently released from his contract
at Rainbow Records.
She won't let me see him, Deena.
She won't let me see my Jimmy.
Plans are being made to fly the body
back to Detroit
where there will be a private burial.
What a thing.
Bad, bad scene.
Well, thanks for the drink.
Tell Lorrell I'll stop by tomorrow.
C.C., man, no matter what troubles
we had, you know, we're still a family.
That's the most important thing.
It's over, Curtis.
Oh, come on, man. Jimmy did this
to himself. You know that.
Michelle?
0.0. can quit. You can't.
What's a wake?
It's when friends get together
and share their love for someone.
-Mama, why are you so slow?
-'Cause I'm old, baby. I'm old.
Who are you?
Effie!
-Who's that man?
-That's your uncle, little girl.
Effie! Shit.
Jimmy had so much life.
First time / met him
was right here in this club.
He wasn’t "Thunder” Ear/y then,
just little Jimmy.
-How old was that boy, Marty?
-I don't know. Probably 12.
Well, he had hands
the size of a fellow twice his age,
and he wasn’t shy
about using them either.
Yeah, Jimmy was a real little shit.
-A real little shit.
-Shit.
lmiss you, old friend
Can I hold you?
And though it’s been a long time
Old friend
Do you mind?
There were so many things
/ wish / had said
lmeant to love you
But I hurt you instead
I’ve come here now
To make amends
Can I sit down beside you?
Can we be close again?
’Cause I, lmiss you, old friend
Can I hold you?
And though it’s been a long time
Old friend
Effie?
What gives you the nerve, C.C.,
coming here after all of these years?
Effie, all I can say is I was young
and I made a mistake.
I'm telling you. I won't be used.
Not by you, not by anybody.
I promised you I would write you
a hit song. Let me do it for you now.
I don't need you.
No, Effie, I need you.
Efﬁe, it’s been all these years
You haven ’t even said hello
I’m your brother, Efﬁe
Say hello
Come on, Efﬁe, you know I’m sorry
/ should have come before today
Hold me, is all I have to say
You’ve always been the baby
But I’m trying to change
And so am /
It’s taken all these years to be free
from loving that man
Finding myself
And getting a hold of the anger in me
Efﬁe, lhave a song
And only you can sing it
the way it should be
I’ve waited so long
To hear you say that to me
Say it again, say it again
Efﬁe, sing my song the way it should be
You want all my love and my devotion
You want my loving soul
Right on the line
l have no doubt
That I could love you forever
The only trouble is
You really don ’t have the time
You’ve got one night only
One night only
That’s all you have to spare
Let’s not pretend to care
One night only
Come on, big baby, come on
We only have till dawn
In the morning this feeling will be gone
It has no chance going on
Something so right
has got no chance to live
So let’s forget about chances
It’s one night / will give
One night only
You’ll be the only one
Then you have to run
One night only
There’s nothing more to say
Words get in the way
One night only
-Trying to make a fool of me.
-Well, Nicky said that
the song's only got local distribution.
Detroit stations mostly.
C.C. wrote it,
so that means we own it, right?
Well, technically, yeah.
Look, I'll get the lawyers
to draw up an agreement,
we'll demand half the royalties.
No, no. This is the perfect song
to launch my new sound.
I want Deena to re-record it
with the girls.
Come on, Curtis,
the song's already moving.
If I can buy a hit, I can buy a flop.
Hey, man. This is Effie's big break.
-There's other songs.
-It's business. Get on it.
Come on, baby
One night only
You want all my love and my devotion
You want my loving soul
right on the line
l have no doubt
That I could love you forever
The only trouble is
/ real/y don ’t have the time
I’ve got one night only
One night only
That’s all I have to spare
Let’s to not pretend to care
I’ve got one night only
One night only
Come on, big baby, come on
We only have till dawn
One night only
One night only, yeah
Come on, come on
One night only
Oh, Cecil Osborne.
Cecil Osborne finally committed.
And he's soaking me
for a million bucks, but I don't care,
because he's great with actors,
Cleopatra is your first movie,
and I don't want anything
but the best for you, sweetheart.
What's wrong?
Nothing, Curtis. I guess
I never thought it would really happen.
You made it happen!
I mean, you are the queen of disco.
Maybe I'm just tired.
Yeah, you got your interviews
and your photo shoot with Vogue,
private meetings by the pool.
You think I'm stupid?
When was you gonna tell me?
I'm sorry, Curtis.
I know I should have talked to you.
It's just that this part is perfect.
It's exactly the kind of movie
I should be making.
Curtis, baby, nobody knows music
the way you do.
It's in your blood.
But movies are different.
Deena, you know why
I chose you to sing lead?
Because your voice
has no personality, no depth.
Except for what I put in it.
See, nobody knows you like I do.
Well, they offered me the part
and I'm taking it.
Do you read contracts,
or are you just pretty?
You can't even take a shit and wipe
your own ass unless I say it's okay.
-Well, I'll get myself a lawyer.
-What do you think they're gonna do?
You think them honkies
are gonna wait around
while you try to drag me into court?
Forget about it! It's over!
Listen, I don't want
those men handling you,
because they don't know how.
And, Deena,
I forgive you.
Curtis will always be here for you.
Listen to the song here in my heart
A melody I start but can’t complete
Listen to the sound from deep within
It’s only beginning to ﬁnd release
Oh, the time has come
for my dreams to be heard
They will not be pushed aside
and turned into your own
All ’cause you won ’t listen
Listen
/ am alone at a crossroads
I’m not at home in my own home
And I’ve tried and tried
to say what’s on my mind
You should have known
Now I’m done believing you
You don ’t know what I’m feeling
I’m more than what you made of me
/ followed the voice you gave to me
But now I’ve got to ﬁnd my own
You should have listened
There is someone here inside
Someone I thought had died
So long ago
Oh, I’m screaming out
And my dreams will be heard
They will not be pushed aside or worse
into your own
All ’cause you won ’t listen
Listen
/ am alone at a crossroads
I’m not at home in my own home
And I’ve tried and tried
to say what’s on my mind
You should have known
Now I’m done believing you
You don ’t know what I’m feeling
I’m more than what you made of me
/ followed the voice you gave to me
But now I’ve got to ﬁnd my own
/ don ’t know where / belong
But I’ll be moving on
If you don ’t
If you won ’t listen
To the song here in my heart
A melody I start
But / will complete
Now I’m done believing you
You don ’t know what I’m feeling
I’m more than what you made of me
/ followed the voice
you think you gave to me
But now I’ve got to ﬁnd my own
My own
Marty. Long time.
Yeah, Curtis.
And you're still a second-class snake.
First-class to you.
Gentlemen, give me a break.
Why, Curtis? Did you give Effie one?
-I could kill you for what you did to her.
-You couldn't kill shit.
I assume you guys have a reason
for barging in here
other than to insult me.
Mr. Taylor, we're planning to go
to the federal authorities.
Yeah, we'll tell the feds how
you killed Effie's record. Payola, man.
You remember, Curtis, Iwitnessed it all.
The whole dirty operation going back
to Steppin' to the Bad Side.
That's right you did,
but who's going to believe you?
All you are is a guy that's pissed off
'cause you got fired.
We have documented evidence,
Mr. Taylor.
Falsified sales records
to cheat investors out of their profits,
goods-quality merchandise listed
as cutouts to disguise the fraud,
mob-backed loans,
and a payola operation
stretching back 11 years.
Who gave you this?
Believe me, I had no idea
what Curtis was trying to do to you.
Effie, are you all right?
I'm happy now, Deena.
I have a child who loves me.
-You have a baby?
-Magic's not exactly a baby anymore.
She's almost nine now.
I wanted to tell you.
At the time, I really wanted to tell you.
Deena, he doesn't know.
Effie, Effie, Effie.
Well, I see you're just as much trouble
as you ever were.
Hello, Curtis.
You haven't changed much, either.
Actually, I take that back.
You are looking a little heavy, baby.
You could lose some weight.
I'll deal with you later.
Mr. Taylor agrees it's in everyone's
interest to resolve the situation
without resorting
to draconian legal measures.
Say that in English.
Nationwide distribution of our
version of One Night Only, Effie.
-On our own label.
-That sounds good to me.
And remember, Curtis,
if these negotiations fall apart
you're going straight to jail.
That's right, Curtis.
You stopped me once,
but you'll never stop me again.
’Cause this time
Efﬁe White’s gonna
win
Deena! Get your ass out here!
Hello, Curtis.
Hey, May. What are you doing here?
I mean, I thought you said you hate LA.
Oh, I do. But my daughter said
she needed me, so I'm here.
Go wait in the car, Mama.
That was a dirty trick you pulled on me.
I had to do something
to stop you, Curtis.
-How could you do that to Effie?
-I had to do what I had to.
Where do you think you're going?
Out looking for a new sound, baby,
just like you.
-You can't leave.
-Why? Because you own me?
You can sue me.
You can take everything I have!
It don't matter, 'cause I'll start over.
Effie did it and so can I.
Listen, I'm not living without you.
I love you.
I'm sorry, Curtis.
I can't do this anymore.
Good bye.
Good to see you, Curtis.
Mr. Taylor?
Mr. Taylor, this must be
a bittersweet night.
How does it feel
to say goodbye to The Dreams?
I don't believe in goodbyes, just hellos.
And I want you all to say hello
to Tania Williams.
We're releasing Tania's first album
next month
and let me tell you, it is dynamite.
Ladies and gentlemen, back in Detroit
for their farewell performance,
the incredible Dreams.
We didn’t make forever
We’ve each got to go our separate way
And now we’re standing here helpless
Looking for something to say
We’ve been together a long time
We never thought it would end
We were always so close to each other
You were always my friend
And it’s hard to say goodbye, my love
It’s hard to see you cry, my love
Hard to open up that door
When you’re not sure
what you’re going for
We didn’t want this to happen
But we shouldn’t feel sad
We had a good life together
Just remember all the times we had
You know I’ll always love you
You know I’ll always care
And no matter how far! may go
In my heart you’ll always be there
And it’s hard to say goodbye, my love
It’s hard to see you cry, my love
It’s hard to open up that door
When you’re not sure
what you’re going for
But we’ve got to grow
We ’ve got to try
Though it’s hard, so hard
We have to say goodbye
We didn’t make forever
But / will always love you
It’s so hard
Baby, it’s so hard
I’ll always love you
It’s so hard
Baby, it’s so hard
Yeah!
Well, I guess it’s about that time.
The last song.
You know, we’ve been together
a very long time.
And / promised Lorre/l / wouldn’t cry.
And I’m not.
I’m very happy.
All of our family is here tonight.
You know, there really aren’t
three Dreams.
There are four.
And we’re all here
to sing that song for you.
Efﬁe.
Every man has his own special dream
And that dream’s
just about to come true
Life’s not as bad as it may seem
If you open your eyes
to what’s in front of you
We ’re your dream girls
Boys, we’ll make you happy
Boys, we’ll always care
We 7/ always care
We ’re your dream girls
Dream girls will never leave you
Never, never, never, never,
never leave you
And all you’ve got to do is dream
All you’ve got to do is dream
Just dream and, baby
we 7/ be
there
We 7/ be there