Subtitle created by - Aorion -
Batman vs Superman: Dawn of Justice (2016)^(Run time 02:23:35)
There was a time above...
A time before...
There were perfect things.
Diamond absolutes.
But things fall...
Things on Earth,
and what falls...
- ... is fallen.
- Master Wayne.  Bruce!
Bruce, are you alright.
Martha...
In the dream,
they took me to the light.
A beautiful lie.
METROPOLIS
HUMANITY KNOWS SUPERMAN
- Jack.
- Bruce.
Jack, listen to me.
I want you to get everyone
out of the building. Right now.
You understand?
Let's go.
Come on, start moving now, people.
The boss wants us out
of the building.
So, let's make it happen.
Jack.
Jack!
We're sorry.
All services are busy now.
Will you please try
you call again later.
Heaven god.
Creator of heaven and earth.
Have mercy on my soul.
JACK !!!
Mr. Wayne!
I can't feel my legs.
- I can't feel my legs.
- We need help over here!
Help me.
I can't feel my legs.
You're going to be okay,
you hear me?
Wallace.
What do they call you, Wally?
Huh?
You're the boss, Boss.
Alright.
- You're going to be okay.
- Easy, easy.
Come on.
Oh my god.
I can't feel my legs.
I can't...
It's okay.
You're going to be okay.
You're okay, alright.
Huh.
Okay, you know what?
We're going to find your mom.
Where is she?
18 MONTHS LATER
SOMEWHERE IN THE INDIAN OCEAN
NAIROMI, AFRICA
Are you a terrorist, general?
They did not tell me
the interview was with a lady.
I'm not a lady,
I'm a journalist.
What I am,
is a man with nothing,
except a love of my people.
Uh, don't open...
You just exposed...
Who's paying for these
security contractors, general?
Who pays for the drones that
passed over our heads at night?
One question begs another.
Yes?
CIA.
They're tracking us.
No!
Not her.
We just used her credentials as cover.
She doesn't know anything.
It's okay, Lois.
I...
I didn't know.
Ignorance
is not the same...
as innocence.
Miss Lane.
Get up!
Stand up!
Move out!
Take 1 step,
you will see the inside of her head.
The women in the village
heard a noise.
Like the sky
crack open.
He came down,
so many dead.
Even worse came after.
The government attacked.
No mercy in the villages.
My parents tried to run...
The world has been so caught up
with what Superman can do,
that...
no one has asked what he should do.
Let the record show that
this committee holds him responsible.
He'll never answer to you.
He answers to no one.
Not even I think, to god.
- Hey.
I was going to cook.
Surprise you.
They held hearings about what happened.
- They're saying that...
- I don't care.
I don't care
what they're saying.
The woman I love could have
been blown up or shot
- Think of what could have happened.
- Well, think about what did happen.
I didn't kill those men if
that's what they think.
If that's what you're saying?
I'm saying I want to
understand what happened.
I'm saying,
thank you for saving my life.
I'm saying there's a cost.
I just don't know
if it's possible.
Don't know what's possible?
For you to love me
and be you.
Clark, you're going to
flood the apartment.
Mmm-hmm.
There has been a report of screaming
at location 1939 Harbor Way
Possible shots fired.
Go.
It saved us.
A devil.
It's okay.
We're-We're going to help.
It saved us.
Okay, we're going to
get you out of here.
Okay?
It's still here.
I - I don't understand.
AH!
Christ!
I saw him.
I never saw him before.
I didn't know...
You almost took my face off.
How about you don't shoot
the good guys, huh?
Oh.
Jesus Christ.
He branded him.
Still working.
You're getting slow in
your old age, Alfred.
It comes to us all,
master Wayne.
Even you got too old to die young,
and not for lack of trying.
Funnel, fairy, bubblebath.
There's nothing wrong
with the microphone.
It's this new layer or armor.
I'll just have to rewire.
So...
last night was productive?
Nope. He's too low level,
he knew nothing.
This, is a man who knows things.
Anatoli Knyazev.
He's Russian.
Contracts all over the globe but
he's base out of the port of Gotham.
Weapons and human trafficking.
So, the "White Portuguese" is a Russian,
that's the theory.
No.
The theory is that the Russian
lead me to the man himself.
If he is indeed a him.
You don't know if he exist.
He could be a phantasm.
One that wants to bring
a dirty bomb into Gotham?
Ah, high state front.
New rules.
Gotham Free Press
BAT BRAND OF JUSTICE!
We're criminals, Alfred.
We've always been criminals,
nothing's change.
Oh.
Yes it has, sir.
Everything's change.
Men fall from the sky.
and gods hurl thunderbolts.
Innocents die.
That's how it starts.
The fever, the rage,
the feeling of... powerlessness
that turns good men...
cruel.
Justice turn dark across the harbor
when police found an alleged sex trafficker
apparently tortured and branded
by the Gotham bat.
The man is the second criminal
found baring the bat brand.
The first victim, an accused child predator
later was assaulted in prison
and remains in critical care
from his injuries.
One source tells Metropolis,
that many believed
the mark of the Bat brand in prison
essentially is a death sentence.
In other news, the mayor
has announced that Metroplis...
Frank, your D!
(Defense)
Woo.
Ah!
A hoi hoi.
I didn't know you were here.
- Man on the marquee.
- Stop, don't believe it.
My father named the company after himself.
He was the Lex in front of the Corp.
- Hi, how are you doing?
- Oh, really great.
Really great?
Good. Good.
Uh.
Follow me.
You know, Dad was born
in east Germany.
He grew up eating uh...
stale crackers.
And every other Saturday,
he had to march in a parade
and waved flowers at tyrants.
So, I think it was providence
that his son,
me, would end up with this.
One of my rebuild Metropolis crews
found it.
A little souvenir from
the Kryptonian World Engine.
What's a rock have to do
with Homeland Security.
Homeland Security?
Mmm.
No, no, no... ma'am.
Planetary Security.
The fragment is of a
radioactive Xeno mineral
We suspected it might have
bio interactions,
so, we took the sample
to AMRIID.
Where they keep the remains
of the Kryptonian decedent.
And, when we exposed
general Zod to the mineral,
this happened.
Profound biodegradation,
decaying Kryptonian cells.
We concluded the mineral could be weaponized,
if a large enough sample was found.
And then, among the fishes,
a whale!
Lying at the bottom
of the Indian Ocean,
Emerald City.
Beautiful.
Now, Rocky is radioactive,
but,
what he needs from you
is an import license.
And why would we
want to weaponize this material?
As a deterrent.
A silver bullet to keep in reserve
to use against the Kryptonians.
So, the day doesn't come, Madame.
when your children are waving daisies
at a reviewing stand.
Last I looked,
the only one of those
flying around up here
was Superman.
Ha.
Yes, Superman.
Yeah, but, there are...
there are more of them.
- The meta-human thesis.
- Yes, the meta-human thesis.
More likely than not.
These exceptional beings live among us.
The bases of our myths.
Gods among men upon our...
our little blue planet here.
You don't have to use
the silver bullet,
but, if you forge one...
Well, then...
We don't have to depend
upon the kindness of monsters.
Daily ☮Planet
- SUPERMAN PREVENTS MISSILE STRIKE!
- HEROIC SUPERMAN RESCUE
BRUCE WAYNE RESCUES EMPLOYEE
Sir.
Get down.
Sir, I said,
get down, now!
Can we get some backup here?
Hey. Hey.
Don't do it!
HEY!
Lois.
Crime Lab, on 3.
This is Lane.
Kent, you're sports today.
I want you to follow
up on the football.
Underdog dreams dashed
10 yards between Gotham and glory.
Hey.
Are you guys watching this?
Emergency responders quickly created
a precautionary perimeter around Heroes Park
while they brought the man down
from this beloved monument.
The suspect has been identified
as Wallace Vernon Keefe.
I work for Bruce Wayne!
There'll be arraign on charges of
vandalism, resisting arrest
FALSE GOD
- and a felony charge of making terrorist threats
that carries up to
40 years in prison.
Poor son of a bitch.
- Jenny.
- Mm?
Headline.
"End of love affair
with man in the sky?"
Okay.
There're ways
we can help each other.
Ah.
Could you step
into my office here?
Yes!
What's your wish list?
Uh.
Access to the wreck of the
crashed Kryptonian ship.
Done.
The complete remains
of the dead alien for testing.
You want Zod's body?
Okay.
It's cherry.
- Show him what you got!
- Dude, let's go!
*Make sure to hit his left.
Come on.
Throw a punch, will you?
Let's go!
Come on!
Thank you.
The house treats luck like an insult.
Good luck for one has always
gives others misfortune.
But, eventually,
all accounts will be settled.
3 nights with a Bolshoi ballerina,
the line was all she tell me.
Not all I'm sure.
Good evening.
DEVICE CLONING
SUCCESSFUL
It's like a 1 man reign of terror.
This bat vigilante has been
consistently targeting the port
and the adjacent projects
and tenements.
And as far as I can tell
the cops are actually helping him.
Crime wave in Gotham.
Other breaking news.
Water, wet.
- Did you file the football yet?
- Why aren't we covering this?
Poor people don't buy papers?
People don't buy papers,
period, Kent.
Perry, when you assign a story, you're
making a choice about who matters...
- ... and who's worth it.
- Good morning, Smallville
The America conscious died
with Robert, Martin and John.
Sorry.
No match.
My guys in the crime lab,
never seen one before.
It's called a bullet.
You shoot people with it.
Recovered from the scene
of the fire fight in the desert.
Not sold anywhere commercially
in the world, even black market.
So?
So, who gave prototype military rounds
to tribe fighters in the Sahara.
The ass, Lois.
Flight to DC tonight,
a couple of days there.
Go.
Coach.
No extra leg room.
Economy plus.
Coach!
Senator.
My dad always said that,
Kentucky mash
was the secret to health.
This was his room.
I left it just the way it was.
It's silly.
The magical thinking of orphan boys.
I'm blocking the import license
for your mineral.
The Red Capes are coming!
You and your hearings...
galloping through the streets
to warn us.
One, if by land.
Two, if by air.
Do you know the oldest lie
in America, Senator?
- Can I call you June?
- You can call me whatever you like.
Take a bucket of piss and
call it Granny's peach tea.
Take a weapon of assassination
and call it deterrence.
You won't fool a fly on me.
I'm not going to drink it.
Hey, you don't think
Dad would mind, do you?
If I change just...
... just one thing in this room.
Because, that should be upside down.
Now, we know better now,
don't we?
The devils don't come from
hell beneath us. No.
No, they come from the sky.
MARTHA WAYNE
1946 - 1981
Wrong room, miss.
Secretary Swanwick, you haven't been
returning my phone calls.
Miss Lane, if you like an interview,
Major Farris is just outside that door.
You're treating me like a stranger?
I'm treating you like a reporter.
Alright.
Is the US providing experimental
military arms to rebels in Africa?
You know with balls like yours.
You belong in here.
Who's your source on this?
A tin foil hat?
No, not tin,
but it's metal.
Fired in the Superman incident.
Experts at the Pentagon can't ID it.
- We haven't been told the truth.
- Here's the truth.
A reporter got greedy for a scoop
and went where she shouldn't have.
Superman acted like some... rogue combatant
to rescue her and people died.
Don't invent a conspiracy theory
to put back his halo.
Or yours.
- Major.
- Sir.
Oh.
I hope the next generation of Waynes
won't inherit an empty wine cellar.
Don't think there's a likely
to be a next generation.
Thank you, sir.
This is every call made
from the Russian's phone.
Two mentions of business
with the "White Portuguese" and
it's continuing transmitting black out
data to the personal residence
of Alexandra Luthor.
You think Lex Luthor
is the "White Portuguese"?
I can't see that he needs
the income from imported arms.
Regardless, I'll need to
put a 'leech' in his house,
and I'm going
to need the suit.
The Bat interrogated 6 people
and came away with nothing.
It was Bruce Wayne
that got the information.
Well, Bruce Wayne can't
break into Lex Luthor's house.
Bruce Wayne won't have to.
He's been invited.
HA HA HA
Joke's on you
BATMAN
- That's him right there!
- There he is! Get a shot!
- Bruce, over here!
- Bruce, Bruce.
- Wayne, have a shot.
- Mr. Wayne!
- Right here, one second.
- This way, Mr. Wayne!
Who's that?
You must be new to the
let them eat cake beat.
That is Bruce Wayne.
Philanthropist.
Bibliophile.
True friend of the library of Metropolis.
Mr. Lex Luthor.
Nikki.
You're embarrassing me.
Speech. Speech.
Uh, blah blah blah.
Open bar.
The word Philanthropist,
comes from the Greek.
Meaning a lover of humanity
It was coined about,
2,500 years ago...
Alright, where am I going, Alfred?
Approach the elevator,
to your left.
That where it must be.
It's in the service
corridor in the basement.
Go down the stairs.
Prometheus went with us,
and he ruined Zeus' plan
to destroy man kind
and for that, he was given a thunderbolt.
Chooo!
Hm.
That seems unfair.
On the serious note,
the library of Metropolis...
Down the stairs.
It's the only way in, down the stairs.
But, at one time,
Dad could not either.
No, my father could not
afford the books, so...
He had to root through the garbage
for yesterday's newspaper.
Now you got the kitchens
on your right.
To the left.
Right in front of you,
that's where you want to be.
May I help you, Mr. Wayne?
Uh, I just...
thought the bathroom was down here.
I must have...
That last Martini was a...
too too many, I think.
- Men's room is upstairs.
- Great, I'm okay.
I like those shoes.
I can't stay down here, Alfred.
Go upstairs and socialize.
Some young lady from Metropolis
will make you honest.
In your dreams, Alfred.
Books are knowledge,
and knowledge is puff worth.
And I am...
Heh heh heh, no.
I, umm.
No, what am I?
Alright, what am I suppose to say?
No.
The bitter sweet pain among man
is having knowledge with no power.
Because...
Because that is paradoxical,
and umm...
Thank you for coming.
Please, drink, it's free.
Mr. Wayne.
Clark Kent, Daily Planet.
Oh, my foundation has already issued
a statement in support of the... cause.
I'm sorry?
Wow. Pretty girl. Bad habit.
Don't quote me, alright?
What's your position on the
bat vigilante in Gotham?
Daily Planet.
Wait, do I own this one?
Or was that the other guy?
Civil liberties has been
trampled on in your city.
Good people living in fear.
Don't believe everything you hear, son.
I've seen it, Mr. Wayne.
He thinks he's above the law.
The Daily Planet criticizing those
who think they're above the laws.
A little hypocritical, wouldn't you say?
Considering every time your hero
saves a cat out of a tree,
you write a puff piece editorial,
about an alien who...
if he wanted to,
could burn the whole place down.
There wouldn't be a damn thing
we can do to stop him.
Most of the world doesn't share
your opinion, Mr. Wayne.
Maybe it's the...
Gotham City and me, we just...
... have a bad history with
freaks dressed like clowns.
Boys!
Mm, Bruce Wayne meets Clark Kent.
Ah, I love it!
I love bringing people together!
- How are we?
- Lex.
Hello, good.
Hi, hello.
Lex. It is a pleasure... Ow!
Wow, that is a good grip!
You should,
not pick a fight with this person.
So, after all these years,
we've finally got you over to Metropolis.
- Well, I thought I come drink you dry.
- Well, you're welcome.
You should hop the hub more often though,
I love to show you my labs.
Maybe we could,
be partner on something.
My R&D is up to
all sorts of no good.
TRANSFER COMPLETE
- That's 7 minutes.
Look likes the transfer's complete.
- Mr. Luthor.
- Yes.
- The governor.
- Governor.
- Excuse me.
- Next time.
- Governor, hi.
- Lex, it's good to see you.
"... a deadly factory fire has interrupted
the Day of the Dead celebration in Juarez."
Excuse me.
"I can't believe they're
going to let that poor girl die."
We, as a population on this planet,
have been looking for a savior.
90% of people believe
in a higher power.
And every religion believes
in some sort messianic figure.
And when this savior character
actually comes to Earth,
we want to make him abide
by our rules?
We have to understand that
this is a paradigm shift.
We have to start thinking
beyond politics.
Are there any
moral constraints on this person?
We have international law.
On this Earth,
every act is a political act.
Is it really surprising,
that the most powerful man in the world
should be a figure of controversy?
To have an individual engaging
in the state level interventions
should give us all pause.
Human beings have a horrible track record
of following people with great power,
down paths that lead to
huge human monstrosities.
We have always created icons
in our own image.
What we've done is we project
ourselves on to him.
The fact is, maybe he's not
some sort of devil or Jesus character.
Maybe he’s just a guy
trying to do the right thing.
We’re talking about a being
whose very existence
challenges our own sense of
priority in the universe.
If you go back to Copernicus,
where he restored
the sun and the center of the
known universe, displacing Earth.
And you get to Darwinian evolution
and you find out,
we're not special on this Earth
we're just one among
other life forms.
And now we learned, that we're not
even special in the entire universe
because there is Superman.
There he is, an alien,
among us.
We're not alone.
Are you, as a United State Senator,
personally comfortable
saying to a grieving parent,
"Superman could've saved your child,
but on principle
we did not want him to act."
I'm not saying he shouldn't act.
I'm saying he shouldn't act unilaterally.
What are we talking about here then?
Must there be a Superman?
There is.
Keefe, you made bail.
Open Two.
Who paid?
Who the hell are you?
- Just a man.
- Yeah?
Well, what do you want?
To help you stand for something.
Your 3 o'clock's here.
He made me half a man.
Let me face him.
So, I logged into your drop box
to find a copy.
There's a copy, alright.
But, nothing about football.
Nothing about...
Friends of the Metropolis Library,
just...
The god damn Gotham bat thing,
I told you not to pursue.
The police won't help,
the press has to do the right thing.
You don't get to decide
what the right thing is.
When the Planet was founded,
it stood for something, Perry.
So could you, if it was 1938,
but it's not 1938.
WPA aren't hiring no more.
Apples don't cost a nickel.
Not in here. Not out there.
You drop this thing.
Nobody cares about Clark Kent
taking on the Batman.
It's the sword of Alexander.
It's the blade that
cut the Gordian Knot.
- It's a triumph.
- Yes.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
It's a fake.
The real was sold in '98
on the black market.
- Now it hangs...
- Over the bed of the Sultan of Hajar.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Miss.
The other night, you took something
that doesn't belong to you.
Stealing's not polite.
Is it stealing if you steal
from another thief?
Who are you?
Someone interested in
the same man you are.
Is that right?
I believe Mr. Luthor has
a photo that belongs to me.
Did you get it?
As it happens, no, I didn't.
The data you copied
is military grade encryption.
You know.
I bet with that dress
9 out of 10 men would let you
get away with anything.
But, you're the 10th.
Mmm.
I guess I am the first,
to see through that babe
in the woods act.
You don't know me,
but, I've known
a few women like you.
Oh, I don't think you've ever
known a woman like me.
You know, it's true what
they say about little boys:
born with no natural
inclination to share.
I didn't steal your drive.
I borrowed it.
You'll find it in the
glove compartment of your car.
Mr. Wayne.
[ INITIATING DECRYPTION ]
DECRYPTING [01%]
DECRYPTING [02%]
Did you get it?
The rock?
Yeah, we got it.
LEXCORP
I'm sorry.
Get down!
Get down! Now!
NOOOOO!
She was my world.
And you took her from me.
GGAAHHHHH!
Bruce!
Listen to me now!
It's Lois!
It's Lois Lane!
She's the key!
Am I too soon?
DAMN!
I'm too soon!
You're right about him!
You've always been right about him!
Fear him!
Find us, Bruce!
You have to find us...
find us...!
DECRYPTING [100%]
[ DECRYPTION COMPLETE ]
BAT BRAND OF JUSTICE!
HUMAN TRAFFICKER GETS
THE MARK OF BATMAN
LEX
CORP
WHITE PORTUGUESE
JUDGE
Jury
EXECUTIONER
JUSTICE?
WHITE PORTUGUESE harbored in - Gotham
WHITE PORTUGUESE
The "WHITE PORTUGUESE" is not a man.
It's a ship.
Master Wayne.
Since the age of 7, you have
been to the art of deception
as Mozart to the harpsichord.
But you've never been
too hot of lying to me.
The WHITE PORTUGUESE
isn't carrying a dirty bomb.
What is it carrying?
It's a weapon.
It's a rock.
A minerals, capable of
weakening Kryptonian cells.
The first sample big
enough to mean something
turned up in the
Indian Ocean 3 months ago.
It is now aboard the White Portuguese
being delivered to Lex Luthor.
Who I am going to steal it from.
To keep it out of Luthor's hands.
To destroy it.
No.
You're going to go to war?
That son of a bitch brought
the war to us, 2 years ago.
Jesus, Alfred.
Count the dead.
Thousands of people.
What's next?
Millions?
He has the power to wipe out
the entire human race
and If we believe there even a
1% chance that he is our enemy,
we have to take it
as an absolute certainty.
And we have to destroy him.
But, he is not our enemy.
Not today.
20 years in Gotham, Alfred.
We've seen what promises are worth.
How many good guys are left.
How many stay that way.
Kent, I want to talk to you.
Daily Planet
Kent!
Where does he go?
Where does he go, Jenny?
I don't-I don't know.
Clicks his heels 3 times,
goes back to Kansas I suppose.
Son of a ...
I don't have a halo over me,
Mr. secretary.
I went into the desert,
people died.
It keeps me awake.
It should!
If you think Superman is a murderer
then throw it away.
But, I don't believe you think that.
WHITE PORTUGUESE
LEXCORP Industries
Move out!
Go, go, go, go!
Harpoon
Noooo!
Where is he?
Next time they shine
your light in the sky,
don't go to it.
The Bat is dead.
Bury it.
Consider this mercy.
Tell me.
Do you bleed?
You will.
SEARCHING FOR TRANSPONDER SIGNAL
LEXCORP RESEARCH PARK
How do we determine what's good?
In a democracy, good is a conversation
not a unilateral decision.
So, I urge Superman, to come to
this hearth of the people tomorrow .
To see those who have suffered.
The world needs to know
what happened in that desert.
And to know what he stands for.
How far will he take his power.
Does he act by our will,
or by his own.
People hate what they don't understand
But they see what you do,
and they know who you are.
You're not a killer.
A threat?
I never wanted this world
to have you.
Be their hero, Clark.
Be their monument.
Be their angel.
Be anything they need you to be.
Or be none of it.
You don't owe this world a thing.
You never did.
CIA thinks the desert was a setup.
Somebody wanted Superman to look guilty.
The bullet?
The metal was developed
by a private company.
What company?
LEXCORP.
Lex Luthor?
He also had private security contractors
in the desert compound.
Go on record.
Not a chance.
It's classified.
I happen to like my job.
It doesn't make sense.
You said that the ambush was
arranged to frame Superman,
but how could they know
that he'll show up in the...
... in the middle of the desert.
Thank you.
Alright, come on through.
The Senate hearing is expected
to get under way in any minute now.
Of course the big unknown
in all of this is:
Will Superman show up? That is
what they're really waiting to see.
Mr. Keefe. Mr. Keefe.
Soledad O'Brien "In the Moment"
Quick question for you.
You're heading in to meet with the senators.
What would you tell them?
Um. I've come here
to tell them to wake up.
This is flesh and blood.
He's delivered a war here.
And this...
This is what war looks like.
I have nothing.
There are plenty of people, sir,
who would say he's their hero.
He is not a hero!
Grace can you get Greg
up here please, right now.
Senator!
Hi, you.
Don't go anywhere.
I want to talk to you.
You know what, Mercy? You go in and...
make sure no one takes my seat.
So, what'd you been up to?
I'm just here to tell my story.
That I was willing to finance
a Kryptonian deterrent,
but a certain junior Senator from Kentucky
decided to block it.
Yes, the Chair of the Committee
on Superman is soft on security.
Greg, why hasn't he
been getting our checks?
He is, Mr. Wayne.
He gets a check from the
victims fund every month.
BRUCE WAYNE, OPEN YOUR EYES
- He returns them.
An employee of Wayne financial
who lost both his legs
in those horrific events in Metropolis
that happened 2 years ago.
Bruce, NO TRUCE
- Jesus.
- B WAYNE, I HAUNT YOU
- BRUCE WAYNE = BLIND
Why haven't I seen this?
I'm sorry.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
And there he is.
Superman is here.
He's actually at the
United States capitol.
This is really a historic moment.
Nor we expect that Superman would give
some kind of a statement to the Senate
to the American people,
and of course to the world.
He's here.
He came.
- He's above the Capitol.
- Ow.
You are going to be on the
hot seat in there, June bun.
I grew up on a farm.
I know how to wrestle a pig.
Do you know the oldest lie
in America, Senator?
It's that power can be innocent.
Good luck.
Freddy, good to go.
- SUPERMAN=ILLEGAL ALIEN
- THIS IS OUR WORLD, NOT YOURS!
- EARTH BELONGS TO HUMANS
- GOD HATES ALIENS
GET OUT!
Another one came this morning
Mr. Wayne.
Let me say at the outset that
I am grateful to our witness
for coming before us today.
This is how a democracy works.
We talk to each other.
We act by the consent
of the govern, sir,
I have sat here before
to say that shadow interventions
will not tolerate by this Committee.
Neither will lies.
Because today is a day for truth.
Because only by speaking...
Only by working...
together, can we...
can we...
can we create a free and a...
GRANNY'S PEACH TEA
Mr. Lex Luthor
CEO - Lexcorp
Oh, my God!
WAYNE TOWER DEVASTATED
YOU LET YOUR FAMILY DIE
LEXCORP
Capitol Police are confirming to CNN
that the suspected bomber is
Wallace Vernon Keefe
Now these sources also say...
Clarke, it's me again.
Can you...
gotten explosive device
into the hearing
by concealing them
inside his wheelchair.
As for Superman, he was in the room,
but obviously failed to stop him.
I didn't see it, Lo.
Standing right there
and I didn't see it.
Clark, there are people behind this.
I'm afraid I didn't see it
because I wasn't looking.
All this time.
I've been living my life
the way my father saw it.
Mending wrongs for a ghost.
Thinking I'm here to do good.
Superman was never real.
It's just a dream of
a farmer from Kansas.
That farmer's dream is
all some people have.
It's all that gives them hope.
This means something.
It did on my world.
My world doesn't exist anymore.
Wel..
Wel... come...
Welcome.
Analysis revealing ship operating at
37% efficiency.
Would you, like to assume command?
Yes, I would.
Very well.
Let's begin.
The Kryptonian archives contains knowledge
from 100,000 different worlds.
Good.
Teach me.
Lex Luthor
META_HUMAN
Subject: WW
2012_Central_IMPORT
SURVEILLANCE_MBANK
22 JUNE 2015,   CAMERA 01
Paris, France
RECORDED DATA
BELGIUM, NOVEMBER 1918
Alexander Luthor, your security override
has been accepted.
Genesis Chamber ready
to analyze genetic sample.
Acknowledging presence
of genetic material.
Analyzing.
I've identified the host as
General Zod of Kandor.
Acknowledging presence
of foreign genetic material.
- Oh.
- Analyzing.
You flew too close to the sun.
Now look at you.
Advising.
Action forbidden.
It is been decreed
by the Council of Krypton
that none will ever again
give life to a deformity
so hateful to sighted memory.
The desecration without name.
And where is the Council of Krypton?
Destroyed, sir.
Then proceed.
Very well.
Preparing chrysalis and
commencing metamorphosis.
"And so, we are left to wonder,
" If Superman was aware
of the threat and did nothing,
"was he then complicit
in the Capitol tragedy?"
Still no Kent?
"His disappearance raises questions."
No.
"How could he simply have disappeared
at a time when we, as a nation,
need him more than ever?"
WAS SUPERMAN INVOLVED?
Burn him!
Something, isn't it?
We met Kansas, live on a pancake
so we come to the mountains.
All downhill from here.
Down to the flood plain.
The farm is at the
bottom of the world.
I remember one season
water came bad.
I couldn't been 12.
Dad had out the shovels
and we went at it all night.
We worked until
I think I fainted.
But we managed to
stop the water.
We saved the farm.
Your grandma baked me a cake.
She said I was a hero.
Later that day we found out.
We blocked the water, alright,
we sent it upstream.
All alike farm washed away.
While eating my hero cake,
their horses were drowning.
I used to hear them
wailing in my sleep.
Did the nightmares ever stop?
Yeah.
When I met your mother.
She gave me faith that
there is good in this world.
She was my world.
I miss you, son.
I miss you too, Dad.
You know you can't win.
It's suicide.
I'm older now than
my father ever was.
This maybe the only thing
I do that matters.
20 years of fighting criminals
amount to nothing?
Criminals are like weeds, Alfred.
Pull 1 up, another
grows in it's place.
This is about the future
of the world.
It's my legacy.
You know, my father sat
me down, right here.
Told me what Wayne manor
was built of.
Railways, real estates
and oil.
The first generation made their
fortune trading with the French.
Pelts and skins.
They were hunters.
We got to wait for more evidence,
but the question still remains,
where is he?
If Superman was not involved,
If he's got nothing to hide,
then why hasn't he been seen
since the day of this tragedy?
Look, you can't...
The knight is here.
Excuse me.
Don't I know you...
Plain lo, in the morning
Lola in slacks.
Lois Lane.
Mmm.
Come see the view.
Now, the secret is the height.
It's the building material.
it's light metals, which...
sway a bit in the wind.
And you know something about LEXCORP metals,
don't you, Miss Lane?
I've proven what you've done.
Wow, you're feisty.
Unfortunately, that will blow away.
Like sand in the desert.
You're psychotic.
That is a three syllable word for
any thought too big for little minds.
Next category: Circles.
Round and round and round
they go to find Superman.
Wrong category, boy.
No, not triangles.
Yes, Euclidean triangle inequality
The shortest distance between
any 2 points is a straight path.
And I believe the swiftest path
to Superman...
.. is a pretty little road.
Mmm, called Lois Lane.
Aahhhhhh!!
You came back.
Boy, do we have problems up here!
The problem of,
of evil in the world.
The problem of absolute virtue.
I'll take you in without breaking you.
Which is more than you deserve.
The problem of you
on top of everything else.
You above all.
Ah.
'Cause that's what God is.
Horus. Apollo.
Jehovah. Kal-El.
Clark Joseph Kent.
See. What we call God depends
upon our tribe, Clark Jo.
Because God is tribal.
God takes sides.
No man in the sky intervened
when I was a boy
to deliver me from Daddy's fist
and abominations. Mm mm.
I've figured it out way back,
if God is all powerful,
he cannot be all good.
And if he's all good
then he cannot be all powerful.
And neither can you be.
They need to see
the fraud you are.
With their eyes.
The blood on your hands.
What have you done?
And tonight they will.
Yes. Because you, my friend,
have a date!
Across the bay.
Ripe fruit, his hate.
2 years growing.
But it did not take much
to push him over actually.
Little red notes, big bang.
You let your family die!
And now, you will fly to him,
and you will battle him,
to the death.
Black and Blue.
Fight night!
The greatest gladiator match
in the history of the world.
God vs man.
Day vs night.
Son of Krypton vs
Bat of Gotham.
You think I'll fight him for you?
Yes, I do.
I think you'll fight, fight, fight
for that special lady in your life.
She's safe on the ground.
How about you?
Close, but I'm not
talking about Lois.
No. Every boy's special lady
is his mother.
Huh!
Martha, Martha, Martha.
The mother of a flying demon
must be a witch.
The punishment for witches, what is that?
That's right.
Death by fire.
Where is she?
I don't know!
I wouldn't let them tell me!
If you kill me, Martha dies.
And if you fly away, Martha also dies.
but if you kill the Bat...
Martha lives.
There we go.
And now God,
bends to my will.
Now the cameras are waiting
at your ship.
For the world to see
the holes in the holy.
Yes, the all mighty comes clean about
how dirty he is when it counts.
To save Martha,
bring me the head of the Bat.
Mother of God,
would you look at the time.
When you came here,
you had an hour.
Now it's less.
CNN's Brooke Baldwin is on the scene.
Brooke, you're live on the air.
What do you see?
There's something happening at the ship.
It's sending massive power surges.
The police created a barricade
around this containment center.
And we're trying to get a little bit closer
here to find out what's going on.
It is absolute chaos.
You can see that lightning.
Those surges are like increasing and
they seem to be getting
stronger by the minute.
Daily Planet.
Lois.
I have to go to Gotham
to convince him to help me.
Who?
Or he has to die.
Clark.
No one stays good in this world.
Metropolis in the dark /
power surges from ship
Wayne, Bruce
Boys Share Too
Cracked Luthor's Drive found your photography.
But it doesn't belong to you.
...it IS you.
Who are you?
Where have you been?
Lex Corp - Meta Human Research
Open Attachment
Subject: FL
FL_surveillance_ camera_ 01
Subject: AQ
TONGA TRENCH   (21,582 FT)
PROPERTY OF US UUV ALPHA 1
TONGA TRENCH   (21,702 FT)
PROPERTY OF US UUV ALPHA 2
Subject: CY
Laboratory 03
PROPERTY OF S.T.A.R. LABS
2400 hours and 2 minutes.
Subject declining rapidly.
All procedural interventions have failed.
Outcome...
would be death.
Dr. Silas Stone suspending
all clinical protocol.
Aww! Aww!
AAWWWWW !!!
I need a chopper to Gotham.
Call the heliport.
Chopper?
We can barely afford a bicycle.
You want to chase a story?
Go to the ship.
Superman's probably there already.
Perry, it's not for a story.
Jenny, get her a
chopper to Gotham.
And forget the heliport,
put her on the god damn roof.
On the roof, Lois!
Where're we headed?
There!
Well.
Here I am.
Bruce.
Please
I was wrong.
You have to listen to me.
Lex wants us...
You don't understand.
There's no time!
I understand.
Stay down!
If I wanted it,
you'd be dead already!
Breathe in.
That's fear.
You're not brave.
Men are brave.
I bet your parents taught you,
that you mean something.
That you're here for a reason.
My parents taught me
a different lesson.
Dieing in the gutter.
For no reason at all.
They taught me the world only
makes sense, if you force it to.
You were never a god.
You were never even a man.
You're letting him...
kill Martha.
What does that mean?
Why did you say that name?
Find him!
Save...
Martha.
MARTHA WAYNE
1946 - 1981
Martha.
WHY DID YOU SAY THAT NAME?
Martha!
Why did you say that name?
Clark!
Stop!
Please!
WHY DID YOU SAY THAT NAME?
It's his mother's name.
We're no getting any answers.
We're still right outside the containment center.
A dangerous situation.
Military and police personnel
surrounding the area.
Luthor.
He wanted your life for her's.
She's losing time.
The scout ship seems to be
drawing power from the city.
It's got to be Lex.
They need you at that ship.
I'll find her.
- My mother needs me.
- Wait!
I'll make you a promise.
Your mother won't die tonight.
- Master Wayne.
- Alfred.
Uh, I'm sorry for listening in.
But I've tracked the Russian's phone
to a warehouse near the port.
You're locked on to it.
I'm afraid, this is goodbye.
I heard everytime we say goodbye,
you die a little.
Go!
You got to take it, Alfred.
Ah.
Right.
Commencing drone mode.
Thermal imaging is showing me
two dozen hostile's on the third floor.
Why don't I drop you off
on the second?
Drop it.
I said, drop it!
I'll kill her.
Believe me, I'll do it!
I believe you.
It's okay.
I'm a friend of your son.
I figured.
The cape.
"Late, late", says the White Rabbit.
30 seconds to animation.
Right, rabbit?
Hmm.
Out of tricks.
Out of time.
And 1 bat head short.
20 seconds to animation.
Ah. That will be the cook.
Excuse me.
Ah, Gotham roast.
Well done.
Hello.
Break the bad news.
I'd rather do the
breaking in person.
10 seconds to animation.
You lost.
9.
8.
I cannot let you win.
I gave the bat a fighting chance to do it.,
but he was not strong enough.
So, If man won't kill God,
2.
1.
the Devil will do it!
- Perry.
- Alright. Stay calm, everybody!
We're getting reports,
there are total blackouts
in the north and to the
northwest of the city.
Federal authorities are trying to determine
if this is part of a larger terrorist attack.
Ancient Kryptonian deformity.
The blood of my blood.
Born to destroy you.
Your Doomsday.
Now God is good...
as dead.
POTUS joining.
- Mr. President.
- What the hell is it, Calvin?
These are live images from the
top of the LEXCORP tower
in downtown metropolis.
Military aircraft are on the scene.
This thing emerged from the
Kryptonian crash site just moments ago.
Thankfully the work day is over
in the downtown core,
it's nearly empty
Now.
Military aircraft
Those are Apache helicopters,
they have now just arrived.
The image...
We have uh... We just lost
connection with Metropolis 8 news.
Now, it's not clear
what just happened.
What happening there, Alfred?
How best to describe it?
Metropolis airspace has been closed briefly.
- Excuse me.
- I kindly ask you to stay in your seats.
Excuse me?
Miss Prince?
Sir.
Look, they cleared the city.
Looks like he's taking it into space.
We can go straight to Key RED,
Mr. President.
Not yet.
Are you crazy?
They are high enough and we can
nuke them with no casualties. Sir.
One casualty, Mr. President.
Superman.
God have mercy on us all.
- Key is hot.
Red Birds,
are armed to deploy, Sir.
Fire at will.
3. 2. 1.
Oh, God.
Projectile 1.
Impact.
Stryker's Island, east of Metropolis.
That's uninhabited.
Projectile 2.
No apparent re-entry.
Projectile 2?
Superman, Mr. President.
Projectile 2 is Superman.
Sir.
It's moving.
The shock waves are getting stronger.
Everytime we hit it,
we make it more powerful.
We can't attack.
What're you saying, Calvin?
I'm saying it's unkillable.
- Master Wayne, are you receiving me?
- Alfred.
It's Kryptonian.
Only Kryptonite weapons can kill it.
It might,
if you have any left.
I only got 1 round left.
The spear.
Alfred, the spear.
It's pure kryptonite.
It's back in Gotham.
If I can penetrate the skin,
the spear will kill it.
- It would in theory.
- I got to get it to chase me.
Back to the city.
Back to the kryptonite.
Oh, shit.
Why did you bring him
back to the city?
The port is abandoned.
And there's a weapon here
that can kill it.
Did you find the spear?
I've been a little busy.
This thing, this creature,
seems to feed on energy.
This thing is from another world.
My world.
I've killed things
from other worlds before.
Is she with you?
I thought she was with you.
Clark.
Are you alright?
I love you.
No.
No, Clark, you can't.
This is my world.
No, Clark, don't.
You are my world.
No.
Please.
Clark!
SUPERMAN DEAD
NIGHT OF TERROR, MORNING OF LOSS
Daily Planet Reporter Clark Kent
Killed Reporting Gotham Battle
Lex Luthor Arrested In Connection
With Capitol Bombing.
Hi.
Clark had this sent here
so he can surprise you.
All the circuses back east,
burying an empty box.
They don't know how
to honor him.
Except as a soldier.
I've failed him,
in life.
I won't fail him in death.
Help me find the others like you.
Perhaps they don't want to be found.
They will.
And they'll fight.
We have to stand together.
A 100 years ago
I walked away from mankind.
From the century of horrors.
Man made a world where
standing together is impossible.
Man is still good.
We fight.
We kill.
We betray one another.
But we can rebuild.
We can do better.
We will.
We have to.
IF YOU SEEK HIS
MONUMENT
LOOK AROUND YOU
The others like me.
Why did you say
they'll have to fight?
Just a feeling.
Turn around and face the wall.
Place your forehead
against the wall.
Put your hands behind your back,
so that I can come in
and restrain you.
Whatever you do.
Wherever you go.
I'll be watching.
But, the bells are already been rung,
and they've heard it.
Out in the dark.
Among the stars.
Ding dong, the God is dead.
The bells, cannot be unrung!
He's hungry.
He's found us.
And he's coming!
Ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding.
ding ding ding ding ding.
Ding ding ding ding
Subtitle created by - Aorion -