1
00:02:07,754 --> 00:02:09,047
♪ <i>Mud</i> ♪

2
00:02:10,840 --> 00:02:12,217
♪ <i>Sand</i> ♪

3
00:02:14,177 --> 00:02:15,428
♪ <i>Water</i> ♪

4
00:02:17,222 --> 00:02:18,306
♪ <i>Straw</i> ♪

5
00:02:19,098 --> 00:02:20,642
♪ <i>Faster</i> ♪

6
00:02:20,725 --> 00:02:23,353
♪ <i>Mud and lift</i> ♪

7
00:02:23,770 --> 00:02:26,523
♪ <i>Sand and pull</i> ♪

8
00:02:27,065 --> 00:02:28,233
♪ <i>Water</i> ♪

9
00:02:28,316 --> 00:02:31,778
♪ <i>And raise up
Straw</i> ♪

10
00:02:31,861 --> 00:02:32,904
Faster!

11
00:02:32,987 --> 00:02:39,327
♪ <i>With the sting of the whip
on my shoulder</i> ♪

12
00:02:39,410 --> 00:02:45,625
♪ <i>With the salt of my sweat
on my brow</i> ♪

13
00:02:45,834 --> 00:02:48,711
♪ <i>Elohim, God on high</i> ♪

14
00:02:48,920 --> 00:02:51,840
♪ <i>Can you hear your people cry?</i> ♪

15
00:02:52,048 --> 00:02:58,972
♪ <i>Help us now, this dark hour</i> ♪

16
00:02:59,556 --> 00:03:00,765
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

17
00:03:01,724 --> 00:03:04,352
♪ <i>Hear our call, deliver us</i> ♪

18
00:03:04,811 --> 00:03:07,939
♪ <i>Lord of all, remember us</i> ♪

19
00:03:08,022 --> 00:03:12,235
♪ <i>Here in this burning sand</i> ♪

20
00:03:12,402 --> 00:03:13,570
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

21
00:03:14,404 --> 00:03:18,491
♪ <i>There's a land you promised us</i> ♪

22
00:03:18,950 --> 00:03:20,159
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

23
00:03:20,243 --> 00:03:24,956
♪ <i>To the Promised Land</i> ♪

24
00:03:48,146 --> 00:03:52,275
♪ <i>My son, I have
nothing I can give</i> ♪

25
00:03:52,358 --> 00:03:55,653
♪ <i>But this chance
that you may live</i> ♪

26
00:03:56,112 --> 00:03:59,490
♪ <i>I pray we'll meet again</i> ♪

27
00:03:59,574 --> 00:04:01,743
♪ <i>If He will deliver us</i> ♪

28
00:04:01,826 --> 00:04:03,036
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

29
00:04:03,119 --> 00:04:07,540
♪ <i>Hear our prayer
Deliver us from despair</i> ♪

30
00:04:07,749 --> 00:04:13,421
♪ <i>These years of slavery
Grow too cruel to stand</i> ♪

31
00:04:14,339 --> 00:04:16,174
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

32
00:04:16,716 --> 00:04:20,303
♪ <i>There's a land you promised us</i> ♪

33
00:04:20,887 --> 00:04:22,430
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

34
00:04:22,513 --> 00:04:24,599
♪ <i>Out of bondage</i> ♪

35
00:04:24,682 --> 00:04:28,978
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

36
00:04:29,062 --> 00:04:34,359
♪ <i>To the Promised Land</i> ♪

37
00:04:47,038 --> 00:04:50,124
♪ <i>Hush now, my baby</i> ♪

38
00:04:50,208 --> 00:04:53,711
♪ <i>Be still, love, don't cry</i> ♪

39
00:04:54,170 --> 00:05:00,551
♪ <i>Sleep as you're rocked
by the stream</i> ♪

40
00:05:01,010 --> 00:05:03,888
♪ <i>Sleep and remember</i> ♪

41
00:05:03,972 --> 00:05:07,433
♪ <i>My last lullaby</i> ♪

42
00:05:07,725 --> 00:05:10,853
♪ <i>So I'll be with you</i> ♪

43
00:05:10,937 --> 00:05:14,315
♪ <i>When you dream</i> ♪

44
00:05:22,532 --> 00:05:25,326
♪ <i>River, oh, river</i> ♪

45
00:05:25,410 --> 00:05:29,080
♪ <i>Flow gently for me</i> ♪

46
00:05:29,163 --> 00:05:35,420
♪ <i>Such precious cargo you bear</i> ♪

47
00:05:36,045 --> 00:05:39,090
♪ <i>Do you know somewhere</i> ♪

48
00:05:39,173 --> 00:05:42,802
♪ <i>He can live free?</i> ♪

49
00:05:42,885 --> 00:05:49,809
♪ <i>River, deliver him there</i> ♪

50
00:07:16,354 --> 00:07:19,440
♪ <i>Brother, you're safe now</i> ♪

51
00:07:19,524 --> 00:07:22,860
♪ <i>And safe may you stay</i> ♪

52
00:07:23,236 --> 00:07:29,117
♪ <i>For I have a prayer
just for you</i> ♪

53
00:07:30,535 --> 00:07:33,329
♪ <i>Grow, baby brother</i> ♪

54
00:07:33,538 --> 00:07:37,208
♪ <i>Come back someday</i> ♪

55
00:07:37,416 --> 00:07:43,089
♪ <i>Come and deliver us too</i> ♪

56
00:07:51,139 --> 00:07:52,682
Mommy.

57
00:07:54,142 --> 00:07:55,560
Come, Rameses.

58
00:07:55,643 --> 00:07:58,146
We will show Pharaoh
your new baby brother.

59
00:07:59,605 --> 00:08:00,731
Moses.

60
00:08:00,815 --> 00:08:03,109
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

61
00:08:03,192 --> 00:08:07,780
♪ <i>Send a shepherd
to shepherd us</i> ♪

62
00:08:08,239 --> 00:08:10,575
♪ <i>And deliver us</i> ♪

63
00:08:10,658 --> 00:08:15,163
♪ <i>To the Promised Land</i> ♪

64
00:08:16,956 --> 00:08:19,333
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

65
00:08:19,542 --> 00:08:26,299
♪ <i>To the Promised Land</i> ♪

66
00:08:30,595 --> 00:08:35,850
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪

67
00:08:42,148 --> 00:08:43,191
Ha-ha!

68
00:08:43,274 --> 00:08:46,360
Faster, you beasts!
You run like mules!

69
00:08:50,656 --> 00:08:51,657
Hey, Rameses,

70
00:08:52,200 --> 00:08:54,368
how would you like your
face carved on a wall?

71
00:08:54,619 --> 00:08:55,828
Someday, yes.

72
00:08:55,912 --> 00:08:57,038
How about now?

73
00:09:02,460 --> 00:09:03,544
You almost killed me!

74
00:09:03,628 --> 00:09:04,670
Aw, come on.

75
00:09:04,754 --> 00:09:06,130
Where is your sense of fun?

76
00:09:06,297 --> 00:09:08,007
Oh, it's fun you want.

77
00:09:23,606 --> 00:09:24,815
Moses?

78
00:09:46,587 --> 00:09:49,465
Come on, Moses. Admit it.
You've always looked up to me.

79
00:09:49,548 --> 00:09:51,926
Yes, but it's not
much of a view.

80
00:09:53,427 --> 00:09:54,470
Hyah!

81
00:09:58,557 --> 00:09:59,558
Hey!

82
00:10:00,059 --> 00:10:02,228
Second born, second place.

83
00:10:02,311 --> 00:10:03,896
Not for long.

84
00:10:42,852 --> 00:10:43,853
Jump!

85
00:11:28,606 --> 00:11:30,608
You don't think we'll get in
trouble for this, do you?

86
00:11:30,691 --> 00:11:32,777
No, not a chance.

87
00:11:33,778 --> 00:11:36,405
Why do the gods torment me

88
00:11:36,489 --> 00:11:38,991
with such reckless, destructive,

89
00:11:39,075 --> 00:11:40,743
blasphemous sons?

90
00:11:40,826 --> 00:11:41,827
Father, hear what I...

91
00:11:41,911 --> 00:11:44,372
Be still! Pharaoh speaks.

92
00:11:45,956 --> 00:11:48,584
I seek to build an empire,

93
00:11:48,709 --> 00:11:51,629
and your only thought
is to amuse yourselves

94
00:11:51,712 --> 00:11:53,339
by tearing it down.

95
00:11:53,798 --> 00:11:55,299
Have I taught you nothing?

96
00:11:55,383 --> 00:11:57,843
You mustn't be so hard on yourself,
Your Majesty.

97
00:11:57,927 --> 00:11:59,178
You're an excellent teacher.

98
00:11:59,512 --> 00:12:02,807
It's not your fault your
sons learned nothing.

99
00:12:02,890 --> 00:12:04,725
- Well, they learned blasphemy.
- True.

100
00:12:05,059 --> 00:12:07,937
Father, the fault is mine.

101
00:12:08,062 --> 00:12:09,397
I goaded Rameses on,

102
00:12:09,480 --> 00:12:11,065
and so I am responsible.

103
00:12:11,190 --> 00:12:13,317
Hmm. "Responsible."

104
00:12:13,651 --> 00:12:16,779
And do you know the meaning
of that word, Rameses?

105
00:12:17,071 --> 00:12:18,322
I understand, Father...

106
00:12:18,406 --> 00:12:20,741
And do you understand the task

107
00:12:20,825 --> 00:12:23,035
for which your birth
has destined you?

108
00:12:23,369 --> 00:12:25,663
The ancient traditions.

109
00:12:25,871 --> 00:12:27,706
When I pass into
the next world,

110
00:12:27,790 --> 00:12:30,668
then you will be the
morning and evening star.

111
00:12:30,876 --> 00:12:32,628
One damaged temple
does not destroy

112
00:12:32,711 --> 00:12:33,796
centuries of tradition.

113
00:12:33,963 --> 00:12:35,339
But one weak link

114
00:12:35,423 --> 00:12:38,884
can break the chain
of a mighty dynasty!

115
00:12:49,395 --> 00:12:51,272
You have my leave to go.

116
00:12:51,856 --> 00:12:53,190
Father.

117
00:13:07,705 --> 00:13:09,039
Father?

118
00:13:10,374 --> 00:13:12,585
You know it was really my fault.

119
00:13:13,085 --> 00:13:15,629
Must you be so hard on him?

120
00:13:15,963 --> 00:13:19,592
Moses, you will never
have to carry a burden

121
00:13:19,675 --> 00:13:22,428
like the crown I
will pass to Rameses.

122
00:13:22,720 --> 00:13:27,641
He must not allow himself
to be led astray,

123
00:13:27,975 --> 00:13:30,478
not even by you, my son.

124
00:13:32,354 --> 00:13:36,192
All he cares about
is your approval.

125
00:13:36,275 --> 00:13:38,903
I know he will live up
to your expectations.

126
00:13:39,111 --> 00:13:41,405
He only needs the opportunity.

127
00:13:41,614 --> 00:13:43,324
Maybe.

128
00:13:43,616 --> 00:13:45,159
Maybe so.

129
00:13:46,452 --> 00:13:47,495
Go now.

130
00:13:47,578 --> 00:13:50,206
I shall see you both tonight.

131
00:14:04,011 --> 00:14:05,262
Well, that went well.

132
00:14:05,346 --> 00:14:06,847
Just go away.

133
00:14:07,181 --> 00:14:08,390
Could have been worse.

134
00:14:08,474 --> 00:14:10,518
"The weak link in the chain."

135
00:14:11,060 --> 00:14:12,520
That's what he called me.

136
00:14:14,647 --> 00:14:17,691
Well, you are rather pathetic.

137
00:14:18,025 --> 00:14:20,819
Irresponsible,
ignorant of the traditions.

138
00:14:20,903 --> 00:14:23,781
He practically accused me
of bringing down the dynasty.

139
00:14:23,864 --> 00:14:26,450
Yeah, I can see it now.
There go the pyramids!

140
00:14:28,327 --> 00:14:30,037
You can laugh about it.

141
00:14:30,120 --> 00:14:31,956
Statues cracking
and toppling over,

142
00:14:32,039 --> 00:14:33,374
the Nile drying up.

143
00:14:33,832 --> 00:14:35,334
Single-handedly,

144
00:14:35,417 --> 00:14:38,712
you will manage to bring the
greatest kingdom on Earth to ruin.

145
00:14:38,796 --> 00:14:40,005
Tell me this, Moses.
Tell me this.

146
00:14:40,089 --> 00:14:42,716
Why is it that every time
you start something,

147
00:14:42,800 --> 00:14:45,135
I'm the one who
ends up in trouble?

148
00:14:47,596 --> 00:14:48,847
Man! Oh!

149
00:14:49,723 --> 00:14:50,724
It's Rameses.

150
00:14:50,808 --> 00:14:51,934
You're in trouble, young man.

151
00:14:52,017 --> 00:14:53,018
Rameses, get down here!

152
00:14:53,143 --> 00:14:55,145
- I think you owe us an apology!
- Oh!

153
00:14:55,229 --> 00:14:56,772
My new thing!

154
00:14:56,855 --> 00:14:58,315
I am so upset!

155
00:14:58,399 --> 00:15:00,442
- You might as well.
- You'll pay for this!

156
00:15:00,526 --> 00:15:01,777
We're gonna tell the pharaoh!

157
00:15:01,860 --> 00:15:03,821
We're telling the
pharaoh and that's...

158
00:15:03,946 --> 00:15:06,407
Oh!

159
00:15:06,490 --> 00:15:08,033
Look at me.
I'm drenched again.

160
00:15:08,117 --> 00:15:09,660
Hey, I figured it out.

161
00:15:09,910 --> 00:15:11,495
You know what your
problem is, Rameses?

162
00:15:11,579 --> 00:15:13,747
- What?
- You care too much.

163
00:15:14,123 --> 00:15:16,458
And your problem is
you don't care at all.

164
00:15:16,542 --> 00:15:19,211
Oh, in that case, I suppose you
care a lot more than I do

165
00:15:19,295 --> 00:15:22,131
that we're late for the banquet,
for example.

166
00:15:26,176 --> 00:15:28,429
I'm done for.
Father will kill me.

167
00:15:28,512 --> 00:15:30,055
Don't worry.

168
00:15:30,347 --> 00:15:32,766
Nobody will even
notice us coming in.

169
00:15:38,230 --> 00:15:40,649
"Nobody will even notice."

170
00:15:43,277 --> 00:15:45,446
Ah, the young princes.

171
00:15:46,238 --> 00:15:49,575
Rameses, you were just
named Prince regent.

172
00:15:49,658 --> 00:15:53,412
You are now responsible for
overseeing all the temples.

173
00:15:53,495 --> 00:15:56,624
I suggest you get over there,

174
00:15:56,707 --> 00:15:59,501
and thank your father.

175
00:15:59,960 --> 00:16:01,712
Apparently, Moses,

176
00:16:01,795 --> 00:16:06,884
someone thought he...
just needed the opportunity.

177
00:16:09,803 --> 00:16:10,846
My lord Pharaoh,

178
00:16:11,263 --> 00:16:13,849
I propose that the high
priests offer tribute

179
00:16:13,932 --> 00:16:15,517
to their new regent.

180
00:16:15,684 --> 00:16:18,437
- An excellent idea.
- Hotep, Huy!

181
00:16:18,520 --> 00:16:20,189
- Huy.
- Hmm?

182
00:16:20,397 --> 00:16:22,775
- The Midian girl.
- That's a good idea.

183
00:16:22,858 --> 00:16:24,193
Go get her.

184
00:16:25,319 --> 00:16:27,655
By the power of Ra,

185
00:16:28,322 --> 00:16:31,200
we present for your
delectation and delight

186
00:16:31,283 --> 00:16:35,621
an exotic apparition
stolen from a faraway land.

187
00:16:43,587 --> 00:16:46,840
We offer you this
delicate desert flower.

188
00:16:54,014 --> 00:16:56,850
Let us inspect this desert flower.

189
00:16:59,603 --> 00:17:01,814
More like a desert cobra.

190
00:17:01,897 --> 00:17:03,774
Not much of a snake charmer,
are you?

191
00:17:03,982 --> 00:17:06,235
That's why I give her to you.

192
00:17:06,318 --> 00:17:07,653
No, no, no,
that's generous, but...

193
00:17:07,736 --> 00:17:09,988
I won't be given to anyone.

194
00:17:10,239 --> 00:17:13,158
Especially an arrogant,
pampered palace brat!

195
00:17:13,534 --> 00:17:15,703
Are you gonna let her
talk to you like that?

196
00:17:15,828 --> 00:17:18,330
You will show the proper respect

197
00:17:18,414 --> 00:17:19,707
for a Prince of Egypt.

198
00:17:19,790 --> 00:17:23,877
But I am showing you all the
respect you deserve. None!

199
00:17:25,045 --> 00:17:26,630
No. Wait!

200
00:17:27,047 --> 00:17:28,882
- Be still.
- Untie this rope!

201
00:17:28,966 --> 00:17:30,259
I demand you set me free!

202
00:17:30,342 --> 00:17:32,428
- Be still.
- Let go!

203
00:17:33,053 --> 00:17:34,471
As you wish.

204
00:17:47,985 --> 00:17:49,111
You there,

205
00:17:49,194 --> 00:17:50,487
have her dried off

206
00:17:50,612 --> 00:17:53,741
and sent to Prince Moses' chambers.

207
00:17:54,116 --> 00:17:56,243
If it pleases you, Father,

208
00:17:56,326 --> 00:17:58,412
my first act as regent

209
00:17:58,495 --> 00:18:00,581
is to appoint Moses

210
00:18:00,998 --> 00:18:04,293
as royal chief architect.

211
00:18:31,904 --> 00:18:33,071
Uh...

212
00:18:33,489 --> 00:18:35,199
Well.

213
00:18:36,033 --> 00:18:37,117
Right.

214
00:18:52,758 --> 00:18:53,842
Shh.

215
00:18:53,926 --> 00:18:55,427
Come on.

216
00:19:04,770 --> 00:19:05,813
Guards.

217
00:19:07,231 --> 00:19:09,107
Prince Moses.

218
00:19:12,528 --> 00:19:13,737
Uh...

219
00:19:15,572 --> 00:19:18,200
There is a man
tied up in my room.

220
00:19:19,618 --> 00:19:21,078
- Well, look into it.
- Right away, sire.

221
00:19:36,718 --> 00:19:38,554
Please, I need water.

222
00:19:38,637 --> 00:19:40,347
I have a long journey ahead of me.

223
00:19:40,556 --> 00:19:42,641
May God protect you.

224
00:19:42,850 --> 00:19:44,184
Thank you.

225
00:20:01,368 --> 00:20:04,746
Oh! Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I...

226
00:20:05,539 --> 00:20:07,416
Oh, please forgive me. I...

227
00:20:07,749 --> 00:20:11,670
I didn't expect
to see you here,

228
00:20:12,087 --> 00:20:15,424
of all places, at our door.

229
00:20:15,507 --> 00:20:16,675
Mmm.

230
00:20:16,758 --> 00:20:17,926
At last!

231
00:20:18,135 --> 00:20:19,887
- "At last"?
- Didn't I tell you, Aaron?

232
00:20:19,970 --> 00:20:20,971
Didn't I tell you?

233
00:20:21,054 --> 00:20:22,556
I knew he would return
to us when he was ready.

234
00:20:22,639 --> 00:20:23,849
Miriam, do you want us flogged?

235
00:20:23,932 --> 00:20:25,809
- I knew you cared about our freedom.
- Miriam.

236
00:20:25,893 --> 00:20:28,145
"Freedom"? Why would
I care about that?

237
00:20:28,353 --> 00:20:29,938
Because you're...

238
00:20:30,230 --> 00:20:31,815
You're our brother.

239
00:20:32,357 --> 00:20:33,525
- What?
- They...

240
00:20:37,821 --> 00:20:39,323
They never told you?

241
00:20:39,531 --> 00:20:40,908
Who never told me what?

242
00:20:42,993 --> 00:20:45,412
But you're here. You must know.

243
00:20:45,495 --> 00:20:46,538
Be careful, slave.

244
00:20:46,622 --> 00:20:48,248
Oh, my good Prince.

245
00:20:48,332 --> 00:20:49,750
Um, she's...

246
00:20:49,833 --> 00:20:51,585
She's exhausted from
the day's work.

247
00:20:51,668 --> 00:20:53,170
Uh, not that it was too much.

248
00:20:53,253 --> 00:20:54,671
We...we quite enjoyed it.

249
00:20:54,755 --> 00:20:56,548
But she's confused,

250
00:20:56,632 --> 00:20:58,300
and knows not to
whom she speaks.

251
00:20:58,383 --> 00:21:01,178
I know to whom I speak, Aaron.

252
00:21:01,261 --> 00:21:02,471
I know who you are.

253
00:21:02,679 --> 00:21:04,973
- And you are not a Prince of Egypt.
- Miriam.

254
00:21:05,265 --> 00:21:06,308
What did you say?

255
00:21:06,391 --> 00:21:07,684
Your Highness, pay her no heed.

256
00:21:08,018 --> 00:21:10,145
Come, Miriam. May I discuss
something with you?

257
00:21:10,228 --> 00:21:11,355
No, Aaron.

258
00:21:11,563 --> 00:21:13,607
- No. Please, Moses, you must believe.
- That's enough.

259
00:21:13,732 --> 00:21:15,859
- You were born of my mother, Yocheved.
- Stop it.

260
00:21:15,943 --> 00:21:17,527
You are our brother!

261
00:21:17,778 --> 00:21:19,279
Now, you go too far.

262
00:21:19,738 --> 00:21:21,531
- You shall be punished.
- No.

263
00:21:21,615 --> 00:21:23,659
Please, uh, Your Highness.

264
00:21:24,242 --> 00:21:25,994
She's ill. She's very ill.

265
00:21:26,078 --> 00:21:27,079
We beg your forgiveness.

266
00:21:27,496 --> 00:21:29,331
- Please, Miriam, let us go.
- No, Aaron.

267
00:21:29,456 --> 00:21:32,417
Our mother set you adrift in
a basket to save your life!

268
00:21:33,210 --> 00:21:34,795
Save my life? From who?

269
00:21:34,878 --> 00:21:36,964
Ask the man that you call Father.

270
00:21:38,674 --> 00:21:41,927
- How dare you?
- God saved you to be our deliverer.

271
00:21:42,010 --> 00:21:43,971
- Enough of this.
- And you are, Moses.

272
00:21:45,013 --> 00:21:46,890
- You are the deliverer.
- I said enough!

273
00:21:49,935 --> 00:21:52,062
You will regret this night.

274
00:21:59,945 --> 00:22:04,074
♪ <i>Hush now, my baby</i> ♪

275
00:22:04,408 --> 00:22:07,828
♪ <i>Be still, love, don't cry</i> ♪

276
00:22:09,162 --> 00:22:15,460
♪ <i>Sleep as you're rocked
by the stream</i> ♪

277
00:22:16,753 --> 00:22:20,007
♪ <i>Sleep and remember</i> ♪

278
00:22:20,090 --> 00:22:23,969
♪ <i>My last lullaby</i> ♪

279
00:22:24,845 --> 00:22:28,473
♪ <i>So I'll be with you</i> ♪

280
00:22:28,932 --> 00:22:32,728
♪ <i>When you dream</i> ♪

281
00:22:48,869 --> 00:22:49,911
Stop him.

282
00:22:51,204 --> 00:22:52,873
Did you see him? It's Moses.

283
00:22:53,206 --> 00:22:54,207
Moses.

284
00:23:13,226 --> 00:23:15,062
♪ <i>Gleaming in the moonlight</i> ♪

285
00:23:17,022 --> 00:23:20,025
♪ <i>Cool and clean and
all I've ever known</i> ♪

286
00:23:20,442 --> 00:23:22,652
♪ <i>All I ever wanted</i> ♪

287
00:23:25,489 --> 00:23:27,866
♪ <i>Sweet perfumes of incense</i> ♪

288
00:23:29,326 --> 00:23:32,287
♪ <i>And graceful rooms
of alabaster stone</i> ♪

289
00:23:32,496 --> 00:23:36,333
♪ <i>All I ever wanted</i> ♪

290
00:23:36,416 --> 00:23:39,002
♪ <i>This is my home</i> ♪

291
00:23:39,377 --> 00:23:41,379
♪ <i>With my father,
Mother, brother</i> ♪

292
00:23:41,463 --> 00:23:44,174
♪ <i>Oh, so noble, oh, so strong</i> ♪

293
00:23:44,424 --> 00:23:46,885
♪ <i>Now I am home</i> ♪

294
00:23:47,677 --> 00:23:53,141
♪ <i>Here among my trappings
and belongings I belong</i> ♪

295
00:23:53,475 --> 00:23:55,519
♪ <i>And if anybody doubts it</i> ♪

296
00:23:55,602 --> 00:23:59,856
♪ <i>They couldn't be more wrong</i> ♪

297
00:24:00,065 --> 00:24:02,526
♪ <i>I am a sovereign
Prince of Egypt</i> ♪

298
00:24:02,734 --> 00:24:05,695
♪ <i>A son of the proud
history that's shown</i> ♪

299
00:24:06,071 --> 00:24:09,699
♪ <i>Etched on every wall</i> ♪

300
00:24:10,200 --> 00:24:13,912
♪ <i>Surely this is
all I ever wanted</i> ♪

301
00:24:14,121 --> 00:24:17,707
♪ <i>All I ever wanted</i> ♪

302
00:24:18,083 --> 00:24:24,923
♪ <i>All I ever wanted</i> ♪

303
00:27:14,217 --> 00:27:17,304
The Hebrews grew too numerous.

304
00:27:18,388 --> 00:27:20,724
They might have risen against us.

305
00:27:21,433 --> 00:27:23,268
Father, tell me you didn't do this.

306
00:27:24,811 --> 00:27:28,815
Moses, sometimes,

307
00:27:28,898 --> 00:27:31,192
for the greater good,

308
00:27:31,609 --> 00:27:34,195
sacrifices must be made.

309
00:27:41,995 --> 00:27:43,955
"Sacrifices"?

310
00:27:47,334 --> 00:27:49,210
Oh, my son.

311
00:27:50,420 --> 00:27:52,714
They were only slaves.

312
00:28:11,149 --> 00:28:12,317
Moses?

313
00:28:14,069 --> 00:28:16,613
Is this where you found me?

314
00:28:17,072 --> 00:28:20,450
Moses, please try to understand.

315
00:28:23,703 --> 00:28:27,499
So...so everything I thought,

316
00:28:28,208 --> 00:28:31,920
everything I am, is a lie.

317
00:28:32,128 --> 00:28:33,463
No.

318
00:28:33,797 --> 00:28:35,507
You are our son,

319
00:28:36,341 --> 00:28:37,592
and we love you.

320
00:28:39,386 --> 00:28:41,221
Why did you choose me?

321
00:28:42,347 --> 00:28:44,182
We didn't, Moses.

322
00:28:44,933 --> 00:28:46,684
The gods did.

323
00:28:53,358 --> 00:28:57,112
♪ <i>This is your home, my son</i> ♪

324
00:28:57,570 --> 00:28:59,614
♪ <i>Here the river brought you</i> ♪

325
00:28:59,697 --> 00:29:03,618
♪ <i>And it's here the river meant</i> ♪

326
00:29:04,452 --> 00:29:07,288
♪ <i>To be your home</i> ♪

327
00:29:08,373 --> 00:29:10,750
♪ <i>Now you know the truth, love</i> ♪

328
00:29:10,834 --> 00:29:14,462
♪ <i>Now forget and be content</i> ♪

329
00:29:14,671 --> 00:29:17,382
♪ <i>When the gods send you a blessing</i> ♪

330
00:29:17,590 --> 00:29:22,512
♪ <i>You don't ask why it was sent</i> ♪

331
00:29:39,362 --> 00:29:42,991
Last night, the gods
granted me a vision.

332
00:29:43,324 --> 00:29:45,577
I'm not merely going to
restore this temple.

333
00:29:45,869 --> 00:29:47,454
I will make it more grand,

334
00:29:47,537 --> 00:29:50,331
more splendid than any other
monument in upper or lower Egypt.

335
00:29:50,415 --> 00:29:51,499
I'll make you...

336
00:30:22,864 --> 00:30:25,033
Moses. Look,

337
00:30:25,116 --> 00:30:27,911
fate has turned our
little misadventure

338
00:30:27,994 --> 00:30:29,037
into a great opportunity.

339
00:30:29,120 --> 00:30:30,205
Get up, old man.

340
00:30:30,288 --> 00:30:32,749
I know Father will be so
pleased with what you and I...

341
00:30:32,832 --> 00:30:35,043
Put your back into it!

342
00:30:36,211 --> 00:30:37,504
Faster!

343
00:30:39,380 --> 00:30:41,257
And this is just the beginning.

344
00:30:41,966 --> 00:30:45,470
A gateway will open to an entire
new city of white limestone,

345
00:30:45,553 --> 00:30:46,888
more dazzling than the sun.

346
00:30:47,514 --> 00:30:49,766
And here, a statue of Hapi...

347
00:30:49,891 --> 00:30:52,810
- I said, hurry!
- ...god of the Nile flanked by
two great columned halls.

348
00:30:53,102 --> 00:30:54,395
- Stop it!
- Miriam, no.

349
00:30:54,479 --> 00:30:55,605
Somebody's got to stop this.

350
00:30:55,688 --> 00:30:56,731
There's nothing that we can do.

351
00:30:59,400 --> 00:31:02,153
Let's raise the roof over here...

352
00:31:09,118 --> 00:31:11,204
Stop it. Stop.

353
00:31:11,496 --> 00:31:13,998
Stop it. Leave that man alone!

354
00:31:15,500 --> 00:31:16,543
Moses.

355
00:31:27,136 --> 00:31:29,430
Out of my way.
Out of my way. Move!

356
00:31:31,975 --> 00:31:33,560
Who did this?

357
00:31:33,893 --> 00:31:35,353
Up there.

358
00:31:35,645 --> 00:31:37,438
It's him. Up there.

359
00:31:51,077 --> 00:31:52,203
Moses.

360
00:32:03,506 --> 00:32:05,425
Moses, what's going on?

361
00:32:05,508 --> 00:32:06,509
Moses!

362
00:32:14,892 --> 00:32:16,269
Moses!

363
00:32:19,147 --> 00:32:20,773
- Moses.
- Let me go!

364
00:32:20,857 --> 00:32:22,775
- No, wait.
- You saw what happened.

365
00:32:22,984 --> 00:32:25,069
I just killed a man.

366
00:32:25,403 --> 00:32:27,822
We can take care of that.

367
00:32:28,114 --> 00:32:29,907
I will make it so
it never happened.

368
00:32:29,991 --> 00:32:32,952
Nothing you can say can
change what I've done.

369
00:32:33,286 --> 00:32:34,746
I am Egypt,

370
00:32:34,829 --> 00:32:36,873
the morning and the evening star.

371
00:32:36,956 --> 00:32:39,292
If I say day is night,
it will be written,

372
00:32:39,375 --> 00:32:42,211
and you will be what
I say you are.

373
00:32:42,587 --> 00:32:44,756
I say you are innocent.

374
00:32:45,048 --> 00:32:46,633
What you say does not matter.

375
00:32:46,924 --> 00:32:48,509
You don't understand.

376
00:32:49,385 --> 00:32:50,928
I can't stay here any longer.

377
00:32:51,012 --> 00:32:52,013
Moses...

378
00:32:52,096 --> 00:32:55,933
No! All I've ever known
to be true is a lie.

379
00:32:58,853 --> 00:33:01,105
I'm not who you think I am.

380
00:33:01,356 --> 00:33:03,399
What are you talking about?

381
00:33:04,359 --> 00:33:07,820
Go ask the man I
once called Father.

382
00:33:11,074 --> 00:33:12,325
Moses?

383
00:33:15,745 --> 00:33:16,954
Please.

384
00:33:24,253 --> 00:33:25,755
Goodbye, brother.

385
00:33:31,761 --> 00:33:33,304
Moses!

386
00:33:34,764 --> 00:33:36,641
Moses!

387
00:34:41,956 --> 00:34:43,082
No.

388
00:35:54,403 --> 00:35:55,988
Hey, wait.

389
00:35:57,740 --> 00:35:58,950
Please.

390
00:36:23,766 --> 00:36:24,976
What are you doing?

391
00:36:25,059 --> 00:36:26,435
Help! Stop!

392
00:36:26,519 --> 00:36:28,312
- Let our sheep drink!
- Go away!

393
00:36:28,396 --> 00:36:31,399
- Leave us alone!
- Get away from me!

394
00:36:31,524 --> 00:36:33,609
- Leave us alone!
- Get away!

395
00:36:33,693 --> 00:36:35,945
- Stop it!
- Stop it!

396
00:36:36,070 --> 00:36:38,114
- We'll do what we want.
- My father's the high priest of Midian...

397
00:36:38,239 --> 00:36:39,949
- Get away!
- ...and you'll be in big trouble.

398
00:36:42,410 --> 00:36:44,120
Hey, you.

399
00:36:44,912 --> 00:36:46,789
Aren't these your camels?

400
00:36:48,332 --> 00:36:50,251
- Hut-hut.
- No, no.

401
00:36:50,334 --> 00:36:51,377
- No, no, wait!
- No!

402
00:36:51,711 --> 00:36:53,296
- Wait, stop!
- No!

403
00:37:09,979 --> 00:37:11,564
What are you girls doing?

404
00:37:11,689 --> 00:37:14,191
We're trying to get the
funny man out of the well.

405
00:37:14,358 --> 00:37:16,611
Trying to get the funny
man out of the well.

406
00:37:16,819 --> 00:37:18,738
Well, that's one I've
never heard before.

407
00:37:20,323 --> 00:37:23,534
Oh, my. Oh...
Don't worry down there.

408
00:37:23,701 --> 00:37:25,369
We'll get you out. Hold on.

409
00:37:30,833 --> 00:37:31,876
You.

410
00:37:31,959 --> 00:37:32,960
Huh?

411
00:37:39,884 --> 00:37:40,885
Mmm-hmm.

412
00:37:43,804 --> 00:37:47,266
That's why Papa says
she'll never get married.

413
00:37:51,562 --> 00:37:53,230
You don't have to do this.

414
00:37:53,314 --> 00:37:54,565
Ladies, please, I'm really...

415
00:37:54,774 --> 00:37:55,858
I'm really quite...

416
00:37:56,025 --> 00:37:57,818
No, not there, please.

417
00:37:57,902 --> 00:37:58,903
That tickles.

418
00:37:58,986 --> 00:38:00,947
Ladies, you've cleaned
every inch of me.

419
00:38:01,322 --> 00:38:03,324
Whoa! I...I was wrong.

420
00:38:03,991 --> 00:38:06,619
Let me through.
Let me through.
I want to see him.

421
00:38:06,994 --> 00:38:08,120
Ah!

422
00:38:08,663 --> 00:38:11,332
You are most welcome.

423
00:38:11,457 --> 00:38:13,584
You should not be a
stranger in this land.

424
00:38:13,793 --> 00:38:16,253
You have been sent as a blessing.

425
00:38:16,545 --> 00:38:18,047
And tonight,

426
00:38:18,130 --> 00:38:20,341
you shall be my honoured guest.

427
00:38:21,509 --> 00:38:25,388
My father,
Jethro, High Priest of Midian.

428
00:38:35,272 --> 00:38:36,315
Psst.

429
00:38:36,607 --> 00:38:37,858
Sit with me.

430
00:38:39,318 --> 00:38:40,736
All right.

431
00:38:43,322 --> 00:38:44,448
Psst.

432
00:38:44,907 --> 00:38:45,950
Not yet.

433
00:38:46,075 --> 00:38:47,284
Oh, sorry.

434
00:38:47,535 --> 00:38:48,828
My children,

435
00:38:49,537 --> 00:38:52,957
let us give thanks
for this bountiful food.

436
00:38:53,958 --> 00:38:55,751
And let us also give thanks

437
00:38:56,043 --> 00:38:58,754
for the presence of
this brave young man

438
00:38:59,255 --> 00:39:00,798
whom we honour here tonight.

439
00:39:02,883 --> 00:39:05,052
Please, sir,
I wish you wouldn't.

440
00:39:05,344 --> 00:39:07,972
I've done nothing in my
life worth honouring.

441
00:39:12,435 --> 00:39:15,646
First, you rescue
Tzipporah from Egypt,

442
00:39:15,855 --> 00:39:17,732
then you defend my
younger daughters

443
00:39:17,815 --> 00:39:18,858
from brigands.

444
00:39:19,525 --> 00:39:21,527
You think that is nothing?

445
00:39:22,403 --> 00:39:24,989
It seems you do not know
what is worthy of honour.

446
00:39:26,198 --> 00:39:28,325
♪ <i>A single thread in a tapestry</i> ♪

447
00:39:28,409 --> 00:39:30,327
♪ <i>Though its colour brightly shine</i> ♪

448
00:39:30,870 --> 00:39:32,788
♪ <i>Can never see its purpose</i> ♪

449
00:39:32,872 --> 00:39:35,708
♪ <i>In a pattern of
the grand design</i> ♪

450
00:39:37,001 --> 00:39:39,628
♪ <i>And the stone that
sits on the very top</i> ♪

451
00:39:39,712 --> 00:39:41,672
♪ <i>Of the mountain's mighty face</i> ♪

452
00:39:41,756 --> 00:39:44,050
♪ <i>Does it think it's
more important</i> ♪

453
00:39:44,133 --> 00:39:48,262
♪ <i>Than the stones
that form the base?</i> ♪

454
00:39:48,471 --> 00:39:51,098
♪ <i>So how can you see
What your life is worth</i> ♪

455
00:39:51,307 --> 00:39:53,184
♪ <i>Or where your value lies</i> ♪

456
00:39:53,392 --> 00:39:57,063
♪ <i>You can never see
through the eyes of man</i> ♪

457
00:39:57,480 --> 00:39:59,648
♪ <i>You must look at your life</i> ♪

458
00:40:00,274 --> 00:40:03,611
♪ <i>Look at your life
through heaven's eyes</i> ♪

459
00:40:13,704 --> 00:40:14,872
Dance with me.

460
00:40:15,081 --> 00:40:17,249
No, I don't know how.

461
00:40:28,427 --> 00:40:30,179
♪ <i>A lake of gold
in the desert sand</i> ♪

462
00:40:30,262 --> 00:40:32,389
♪ <i>Is less than a cool,
fresh spring</i> ♪

463
00:40:32,473 --> 00:40:34,600
♪ <i>And to one lost
sheep a shepherd boy</i> ♪

464
00:40:34,683 --> 00:40:36,894
♪ <i>Is greater than
the richest king</i> ♪

465
00:40:38,395 --> 00:40:41,190
♪ <i>If a man lose
everything he owns</i> ♪

466
00:40:41,273 --> 00:40:43,192
♪ <i>Has he truly lost his worth?</i> ♪

467
00:40:43,400 --> 00:40:45,444
♪ <i>Or is it the beginning</i> ♪

468
00:40:45,528 --> 00:40:49,490
♪ <i>Of a new and brighter birth</i> ♪

469
00:40:49,824 --> 00:40:52,451
♪ <i>So how do you measure
the worth of a man</i> ♪

470
00:40:52,535 --> 00:40:54,453
♪ <i>In wealth or strength
or size</i> ♪

471
00:40:54,537 --> 00:40:57,873
♪ <i>In how much he gained
or how much he gave?</i> ♪

472
00:40:58,916 --> 00:41:01,127
♪ <i>The answer will come</i> ♪

473
00:41:01,418 --> 00:41:05,005
♪ <i>The answer will come
to him who tries</i> ♪

474
00:41:05,089 --> 00:41:09,218
♪ <i>To look at his life
through heaven's eyes</i> ♪

475
00:41:09,802 --> 00:41:12,012
♪ <i>And that's why we share
all we have with you</i> ♪

476
00:41:12,096 --> 00:41:14,306
♪ <i>Though there's little
to be found</i> ♪

477
00:41:14,390 --> 00:41:16,767
♪ <i>When all you've got is nothing</i> ♪

478
00:41:16,851 --> 00:41:19,395
♪ <i>There's a lot to go around</i> ♪

479
00:41:21,605 --> 00:41:23,858
♪ <i>No life can escape
being blown about</i> ♪

480
00:41:23,941 --> 00:41:26,152
♪ <i>By the winds of change
and chance</i> ♪

481
00:41:26,235 --> 00:41:28,779
♪ <i>And though you never know
All the steps</i> ♪

482
00:41:28,863 --> 00:41:29,864
- Dance with me.
- No, I...no.

483
00:41:29,947 --> 00:41:33,075
♪ <i>You must learn
to join the dance</i> ♪

484
00:41:34,201 --> 00:41:37,830
♪ <i>You must learn
to join the dance</i> ♪

485
00:42:02,271 --> 00:42:06,150
♪ <i>So how do you judge
what a man is worth</i> ♪

486
00:42:06,233 --> 00:42:08,694
♪ <i>By what he builds or buys</i> ♪

487
00:42:08,986 --> 00:42:11,655
♪ <i>You can never see
with your eyes on Earth</i> ♪

488
00:42:11,739 --> 00:42:13,949
♪ <i>Look through heaven's eyes</i> ♪

489
00:42:14,033 --> 00:42:15,868
♪ <i>Look at your life</i> ♪

490
00:42:16,202 --> 00:42:18,412
♪ <i>Look at your life</i> ♪

491
00:42:18,579 --> 00:42:25,544
♪ <i>Look at your life
through heaven's eyes</i> ♪

492
00:42:47,441 --> 00:42:48,859
I love you.

493
00:43:29,316 --> 00:43:31,944
It's too early for this.

494
00:44:30,669 --> 00:44:32,921
<i>Moses.</i>

495
00:44:34,882 --> 00:44:37,176
<i>Moses.</i>

496
00:44:38,761 --> 00:44:40,929
<i>Moses.</i>

497
00:44:41,221 --> 00:44:42,765
<i>Moses.</i>

498
00:44:45,851 --> 00:44:47,353
Here I am.

499
00:44:49,313 --> 00:44:52,107
<i>Take the sandals from your feet,</i>

500
00:44:53,442 --> 00:44:56,820
<i>for the place on which you
stand is holy ground.</i>

501
00:45:05,204 --> 00:45:06,747
Who are you?

502
00:45:08,957 --> 00:45:11,919
<i>I am that I am.</i>

503
00:45:14,838 --> 00:45:16,382
I don't understand.

504
00:45:17,257 --> 00:45:19,760
<i>I am the God of your ancestors,</i>

505
00:45:19,843 --> 00:45:23,347
<i>Abraham, Isaac and Jacob.</i>

506
00:45:26,350 --> 00:45:28,227
<i>You were born of
my mother, Yocheved.</i>

507
00:45:28,310 --> 00:45:30,229
<i>You are our brother.</i>

508
00:45:33,690 --> 00:45:35,943
What do you want with me?

509
00:45:37,528 --> 00:45:41,782
<i>I have seen the oppression
of my people in Egypt</i>

510
00:45:41,990 --> 00:45:44,618
<i>and have heard their cry.</i>

511
00:45:45,536 --> 00:45:47,830
<i>Stop it!
Leave that man alone!</i>

512
00:45:48,288 --> 00:45:49,456
<i>So I have come down</i>

513
00:45:49,540 --> 00:45:51,291
<i>to deliver them out of slavery,</i>

514
00:45:53,001 --> 00:45:56,088
<i>and bring them to a good land,</i>

515
00:45:57,005 --> 00:46:02,177
<i>a land flowing with
milk and honey.</i>

516
00:46:03,929 --> 00:46:06,557
<i>And so, unto Pharaoh,</i>

517
00:46:07,266 --> 00:46:11,103
<i>I shall send you.</i>

518
00:46:12,438 --> 00:46:15,816
Me? Who am I to
lead these people?

519
00:46:16,358 --> 00:46:18,652
They'll never believe me.
They won't even listen.

520
00:46:18,735 --> 00:46:21,405
<i>I shall teach you
what to say.</i>

521
00:46:21,613 --> 00:46:24,199
<i>Let my people go!</i>

522
00:46:25,117 --> 00:46:26,952
But I was their enemy.

523
00:46:27,327 --> 00:46:28,579
I was the Prince of Egypt,

524
00:46:28,662 --> 00:46:31,623
the son of the man who
slaughtered their children.

525
00:46:32,040 --> 00:46:34,293
You've...you've chosen
the wrong messenger.

526
00:46:34,376 --> 00:46:36,753
How can I even speak
to these people?

527
00:46:37,212 --> 00:46:39,882
<i>Who made man's mouth?</i>

528
00:46:39,965 --> 00:46:43,802
<i>Who made the deaf, the mute,
the seeing or the blind?</i>

529
00:46:43,969 --> 00:46:45,345
<i>Did not I?</i>

530
00:46:45,721 --> 00:46:46,889
<i>Now go!</i>

531
00:46:59,693 --> 00:47:01,820
<i>Oh, Moses,</i>

532
00:47:02,488 --> 00:47:06,450
<i>I shall be with you when
you go to the King of Egypt.</i>

533
00:47:07,993 --> 00:47:10,621
<i>But Pharaoh will not listen.</i>

534
00:47:14,458 --> 00:47:17,586
<i>So I will stretch out my hand,</i>

535
00:47:17,669 --> 00:47:23,050
<i>and smite Egypt
with all my wonders.</i>

536
00:47:26,595 --> 00:47:29,556
<i>Take the staff
in your hand, Moses.</i>

537
00:47:31,183 --> 00:47:37,356
<i>With it, you shall
do my wonders.</i>

538
00:47:41,652 --> 00:47:44,988
<i>I shall be with you, Moses.</i>

539
00:47:45,989 --> 00:47:48,033
<i>Moses.</i>

540
00:47:49,743 --> 00:47:52,079
<i>Moses.</i>

541
00:49:11,825 --> 00:49:13,243
But, Moses,

542
00:49:13,952 --> 00:49:16,413
you are just one man.

543
00:49:20,334 --> 00:49:22,044
Tzipporah.

544
00:49:24,087 --> 00:49:25,797
Please.

545
00:49:33,722 --> 00:49:35,557
Look at your family.

546
00:49:39,144 --> 00:49:40,896
They are free.

547
00:49:42,064 --> 00:49:43,774
They have a future.

548
00:49:44,107 --> 00:49:46,652
They have hopes and dreams,

549
00:49:46,943 --> 00:49:50,030
and the promise of
a life with dignity.

550
00:49:52,658 --> 00:49:55,285
That is what I want
for my people.

551
00:49:56,953 --> 00:50:01,500
And that is why I must do the
task that God has given me.

552
00:50:14,805 --> 00:50:16,348
I'm coming with you.

553
00:51:45,645 --> 00:51:47,063
Rameses.

554
00:51:48,607 --> 00:51:49,649
Moses?

555
00:51:49,733 --> 00:51:50,859
Is it really?

556
00:51:56,656 --> 00:51:59,284
- Moses, where have you been?
- Rameses.

557
00:51:59,367 --> 00:52:00,535
I took you for dead.

558
00:52:02,954 --> 00:52:04,706
Look at you.

559
00:52:05,707 --> 00:52:08,043
- Pharaoh.
- Well, look at you.

560
00:52:08,126 --> 00:52:09,961
What on Earth are
you dressed as?

561
00:52:11,129 --> 00:52:12,964
Oh, Rameses,

562
00:52:13,048 --> 00:52:14,716
it's so good to see you.

563
00:52:15,008 --> 00:52:16,718
Excuse me, uh, Your Majesty.

564
00:52:17,427 --> 00:52:19,429
We are compelled to
remind you that this man

565
00:52:19,513 --> 00:52:21,973
committed a serious crime
against the gods.

566
00:52:22,057 --> 00:52:23,725
We are loathe to
bring it up, mind you.

567
00:52:23,809 --> 00:52:25,268
Yet the law clearly states

568
00:52:25,352 --> 00:52:26,978
the punishment for such a crime...

569
00:52:27,062 --> 00:52:29,105
- Death.
- We hesitate to say it.

570
00:52:29,189 --> 00:52:30,482
Be still.

571
00:52:31,066 --> 00:52:32,567
Pharaoh speaks.

572
00:52:33,777 --> 00:52:36,655
I am the morning
and the evening star.

573
00:52:36,738 --> 00:52:38,031
Rameses.

574
00:52:38,114 --> 00:52:40,450
It shall be as I say.

575
00:52:41,493 --> 00:52:45,539
I pardon forever all crimes
of which he stands accused,

576
00:52:45,622 --> 00:52:48,041
and will have it
known that he is

577
00:52:48,124 --> 00:52:50,293
our brother Moses,

578
00:52:50,377 --> 00:52:52,379
the Prince of Egypt.

579
00:52:56,716 --> 00:52:58,343
Rameses.

580
00:52:59,886 --> 00:53:02,138
In my heart,
you are my brother,

581
00:53:03,056 --> 00:53:05,600
but things cannot
be as they were.

582
00:53:05,934 --> 00:53:07,811
I see no reason why not.

583
00:53:09,646 --> 00:53:11,565
You know I am a Hebrew,

584
00:53:12,107 --> 00:53:14,568
and the God of the
Hebrews came to me.

585
00:53:15,068 --> 00:53:16,152
What?

586
00:53:17,112 --> 00:53:20,824
He commands that you
let His people go.

587
00:53:24,870 --> 00:53:26,288
Commands?

588
00:53:31,334 --> 00:53:32,878
Behold,

589
00:53:33,378 --> 00:53:35,088
the power of God.

590
00:53:50,395 --> 00:53:53,940
Well, impressive, but...mmm.

591
00:53:55,817 --> 00:53:57,736
Very well, Moses.

592
00:53:57,819 --> 00:53:59,279
I'll play along.

593
00:54:00,071 --> 00:54:02,574
Hotep. Huy.

594
00:54:02,657 --> 00:54:06,578
Give this snake
charmer our answer.

595
00:54:27,223 --> 00:54:29,559
♪ <i>By the power of Ra</i> ♪

596
00:54:30,268 --> 00:54:31,937
♪ <i>Mut</i> ♪

597
00:54:32,145 --> 00:54:34,064
♪ <i>Nut</i> ♪

598
00:54:34,314 --> 00:54:35,315
♪ <i>Khnum</i> ♪

599
00:54:35,398 --> 00:54:36,483
♪ <i>Ptah</i> ♪

600
00:54:36,691 --> 00:54:37,692
♪ <i>Nephthys</i> ♪

601
00:54:37,776 --> 00:54:38,777
♪ <i>Nekhbet</i> ♪

602
00:54:38,860 --> 00:54:40,695
♪ <i>Sobek </i> ♪
♪ <i>Sekhmet</i> ♪

603
00:54:40,946 --> 00:54:42,906
♪ <i>Sokar</i> ♪
♪ <i>Selket</i> ♪

604
00:54:43,198 --> 00:54:45,033
♪ <i>Reshpu</i> ♪
♪ <i>Wadjet</i> ♪

605
00:54:45,116 --> 00:54:46,785
♪ <i>Anubis</i> ♪
♪ <i>Anukis</i> ♪

606
00:54:46,993 --> 00:54:48,912
♪ <i>Seshmu</i> ♪
♪ <i>Meshkent</i> ♪

607
00:54:49,162 --> 00:54:50,997
♪ <i>Hemsut</i> ♪
♪ <i>Tefnut</i> ♪

608
00:54:51,164 --> 00:54:52,749
♪ <i>Heket</i> ♪
♪ <i>Mafdet</i> ♪

609
00:54:52,832 --> 00:54:54,542
♪ <i>Ra, Mut, Nut, Ptah</i> ♪

610
00:54:54,626 --> 00:54:56,670
♪ <i>Hemsut, Tefnut, Sokar
Selket, Seshmu</i> ♪

611
00:54:56,753 --> 00:54:57,796
♪ <i>Reshpu, Sobek, Wadjet</i> ♪

612
00:54:57,879 --> 00:54:59,839
♪ <i>Heket, Mafdet,
Nephthys, Nekhbet</i> ♪

613
00:55:00,006 --> 00:55:01,299
♪ <i>Ra</i> ♪

614
00:55:04,511 --> 00:55:09,099
♪ <i>So you think you've got
friends in high places</i> ♪

615
00:55:10,225 --> 00:55:14,521
♪ <i>With the power to
put us on the run</i> ♪

616
00:55:15,063 --> 00:55:20,193
♪ <i>Well, forgive us these
smiles on our faces</i> ♪

617
00:55:21,027 --> 00:55:25,573
♪ <i>You'll know what power
is when we are done</i> ♪

618
00:55:26,282 --> 00:55:28,076
♪ <i>Son</i> ♪
♪ <i>Son</i> ♪

619
00:55:29,285 --> 00:55:32,956
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

620
00:55:34,165 --> 00:55:37,127
♪ <i>Playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

621
00:55:37,335 --> 00:55:38,920
Oh, that's pretty.

622
00:55:39,129 --> 00:55:41,381
♪ <i>Every spell and gesture</i> ♪

623
00:55:41,464 --> 00:55:43,049
♪ <i>Tells you who's the best</i> ♪

624
00:55:43,133 --> 00:55:46,261
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

625
00:55:46,594 --> 00:55:47,595
♪ <i>By the power of Ra</i> ♪

626
00:55:47,679 --> 00:55:50,181
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

627
00:55:50,265 --> 00:55:51,933
♪ <i>Mut, Nut, Khnum, Ptah</i> ♪

628
00:55:52,017 --> 00:55:54,561
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

629
00:55:54,644 --> 00:55:56,438
♪ <i>Hemsut, Tefnut,
Sokar, Selket</i> ♪

630
00:55:56,771 --> 00:55:58,690
♪ <i>Stop this foolish mission</i> ♪

631
00:55:58,940 --> 00:56:00,650
♪ <i>Watch a true magician</i> ♪

632
00:56:01,067 --> 00:56:04,487
♪ <i>Give an exhibition how</i> ♪

633
00:56:04,821 --> 00:56:06,823
♪ <i>Pick up your silly twig, boy</i> ♪

634
00:56:06,906 --> 00:56:10,201
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

635
00:56:11,411 --> 00:56:13,204
♪ <i>By the power of Ra</i> ♪

636
00:56:13,496 --> 00:56:17,208
♪ <i>Mut, Nut, Khnum, Ptah</i> ♪

637
00:56:17,417 --> 00:56:21,129
♪ <i>Sobek, Sekhmet, Sokar
Selket</i> ♪

638
00:56:21,963 --> 00:56:25,425
♪ <i>Anubis, Anukis, Hemsut
Tefnut, Meshkent, Mafdet</i> ♪

639
00:56:25,508 --> 00:56:29,012
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

640
00:56:29,345 --> 00:56:32,807
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

641
00:56:33,725 --> 00:56:37,520
♪ <i>By the might of Horus
You will kneel before us</i> ♪

642
00:56:37,687 --> 00:56:40,231
♪ <i>Kneel to our splendorous power</i> ♪

643
00:56:40,982 --> 00:56:42,817
♪ <i>You put up a front
You put up a fight</i> ♪

644
00:56:42,901 --> 00:56:44,944
♪ <i>And just to show
we feel no spite</i> ♪

645
00:56:45,028 --> 00:56:46,613
♪ <i>You can be our acolyte</i> ♪

646
00:56:46,696 --> 00:56:49,199
♪ <i>But first, boy,
it's time to bow</i> ♪

647
00:56:49,282 --> 00:56:50,533
♪ <i>Kowtow!</i> ♪

648
00:56:50,617 --> 00:56:52,327
♪ <i>Or it's your own grave
you'll dig, boy</i> ♪

649
00:56:52,410 --> 00:56:54,537
♪ <i>You're playing with
the big boys now</i> ♪

650
00:56:54,621 --> 00:56:58,249
♪ <i>Playing with the big boys
Playing with the big boys</i> ♪

651
00:56:58,333 --> 00:57:02,045
♪ <i>Playing with the big boys
Playing with the big boys</i> ♪

652
00:57:02,128 --> 00:57:04,672
♪ <i>Playing with the big boys now</i> ♪

653
00:57:05,924 --> 00:57:07,342
They love it.

654
00:57:24,567 --> 00:57:26,152
All right, Moses.

655
00:57:26,236 --> 00:57:27,612
I know you.

656
00:57:27,862 --> 00:57:29,823
What's this really about?

657
00:57:31,908 --> 00:57:33,576
Rameses,

658
00:57:33,785 --> 00:57:34,869
look.

659
00:57:35,537 --> 00:57:37,038
What do you see?

660
00:57:41,126 --> 00:57:44,629
A greater Egypt than
that of my father.

661
00:57:44,879 --> 00:57:46,506
That is not what I see.

662
00:57:48,383 --> 00:57:51,594
Moses, I cannot change
what you see.

663
00:57:52,345 --> 00:57:55,849
I have to maintain
the ancient traditions.

664
00:57:55,932 --> 00:57:59,227
I bear the weight
of my father's crown.

665
00:57:59,477 --> 00:58:02,230
Do you still not understand
what Seti was?

666
00:58:02,897 --> 00:58:05,525
He was a great leader.

667
00:58:05,900 --> 00:58:09,195
His hands bore the blood
of thousands of children.

668
00:58:09,279 --> 00:58:10,613
Slaves.

669
00:58:10,947 --> 00:58:12,407
My people.

670
00:58:12,907 --> 00:58:15,410
And I can no longer hide in
the desert while they suffer

671
00:58:17,245 --> 00:58:18,746
at your hands.

672
00:58:22,625 --> 00:58:24,002
So,

673
00:58:25,003 --> 00:58:26,796
you have returned

674
00:58:28,256 --> 00:58:29,757
only to free them.

675
00:58:41,477 --> 00:58:42,896
I'm sorry.

676
00:58:51,988 --> 00:58:53,573
Yes.

677
00:58:55,325 --> 00:58:58,703
I had hoped, but...

678
00:59:13,051 --> 00:59:14,761
I do not know this god.

679
00:59:15,970 --> 00:59:18,514
Neither will I let
your people go.

680
00:59:18,640 --> 00:59:20,350
Rameses, please,
you must listen...

681
00:59:20,433 --> 00:59:22,769
I will not be the weak link.

682
00:59:31,152 --> 00:59:33,655
Tell your people, as of today,

683
00:59:33,905 --> 00:59:36,532
their workload
has been doubled,

684
00:59:36,950 --> 00:59:38,868
thanks to your god.

685
00:59:40,870 --> 00:59:42,705
Or is it thanks

686
00:59:43,581 --> 00:59:44,707
to you?

687
00:59:51,256 --> 00:59:52,840
It's Moses.

688
00:59:55,093 --> 00:59:56,094
Moses.

689
00:59:58,513 --> 01:00:01,057
So, Moses, how does it feel

690
01:00:01,140 --> 01:00:03,226
when you get struck to the ground?

691
01:00:04,644 --> 01:00:07,647
I didn't mean to
cause you more pain.

692
01:00:07,855 --> 01:00:10,692
I'm just trying to
do as God told me.

693
01:00:10,775 --> 01:00:11,901
God?

694
01:00:12,235 --> 01:00:14,445
When did God start caring
about any of us?

695
01:00:14,904 --> 01:00:18,616
In fact, Moses, when did you
start caring about slaves?

696
01:00:19,075 --> 01:00:21,202
Was it when you found out
that you were one of us?

697
01:00:21,286 --> 01:00:23,037
Don't listen to him.

698
01:00:23,496 --> 01:00:25,748
No, he's...he's right.

699
01:00:26,666 --> 01:00:30,545
I did not see because I
did not wish to see.

700
01:00:30,628 --> 01:00:33,256
Oh, you didn't see because
you didn't wish to see.

701
01:00:33,381 --> 01:00:34,549
Ah.

702
01:00:34,799 --> 01:00:37,218
Well, that makes everything
fine then, doesn't it?

703
01:00:37,302 --> 01:00:39,762
Aaron, you shame yourself.

704
01:00:43,099 --> 01:00:44,267
Miriam.

705
01:00:48,354 --> 01:00:50,189
I'm so sorry.

706
01:00:59,991 --> 01:01:01,200
Moses,

707
01:01:01,993 --> 01:01:03,703
hear what I say.

708
01:01:04,495 --> 01:01:06,539
I have been a slave

709
01:01:06,706 --> 01:01:08,207
all my life,

710
01:01:09,042 --> 01:01:12,420
and God has never answered
my prayers until now.

711
01:01:13,254 --> 01:01:15,214
God saved you from the river,

712
01:01:15,298 --> 01:01:18,009
He saved you in all
your wanderings,

713
01:01:18,092 --> 01:01:19,344
and even now,

714
01:01:19,427 --> 01:01:21,387
He saves you from
the wrath of Pharaoh.

715
01:01:22,388 --> 01:01:24,515
God will not abandon you.

716
01:01:25,850 --> 01:01:27,810
So don't you abandon us.

717
01:02:01,302 --> 01:02:03,262
Miriam, where are you going?

718
01:02:03,888 --> 01:02:05,056
Miriam.

719
01:02:19,654 --> 01:02:21,614
The ball disappears.
Now, where is it?

720
01:02:21,697 --> 01:02:23,533
It's in his hand.
How about that?

721
01:02:26,119 --> 01:02:27,453
Rameses!

722
01:02:29,122 --> 01:02:31,290
Let my people go!

723
01:02:33,126 --> 01:02:36,212
Still gnawing away
at that bone, are we?

724
01:02:37,130 --> 01:02:38,256
Carry on.

725
01:02:38,381 --> 01:02:40,425
You cannot keep ignoring us.

726
01:02:40,925 --> 01:02:44,637
Enough. I will hear no more
of this Hebrew nonsense.

727
01:02:44,720 --> 01:02:45,972
Bring him to me.

728
01:02:48,599 --> 01:02:49,642
- Moses!
- No!

729
01:03:04,157 --> 01:03:07,702
<i>Take the staff
in your hand, Moses.</i>

730
01:03:37,273 --> 01:03:38,357
Father.

731
01:03:38,441 --> 01:03:39,984
- It's...
- Blood!

732
01:03:40,318 --> 01:03:42,695
Blood! Blood!

733
01:03:53,706 --> 01:03:54,999
Hotep, Huy.

734
01:03:55,082 --> 01:03:56,584
Explain this to me.

735
01:03:57,835 --> 01:03:59,837
- Ah...
- Rest assured, Your Majesty.

736
01:03:59,962 --> 01:04:05,051
Yes, we were going to demonstrate
the superior might of our gods.

737
01:04:05,176 --> 01:04:06,219
Uh...

738
01:04:08,596 --> 01:04:11,015
By the power of Ra.

739
01:04:26,948 --> 01:04:29,951
Abandon this
futile mission, Moses.

740
01:04:30,576 --> 01:04:32,912
I've indulged you long enough.

741
01:04:33,412 --> 01:04:36,249
This must now be finished.

742
01:04:39,085 --> 01:04:40,753
No, Rameses.

743
01:04:41,170 --> 01:04:43,089
It is only beginning.

744
01:04:43,714 --> 01:04:44,757
But, Moses,

745
01:04:44,840 --> 01:04:46,842
didn't you see what happened?

746
01:04:46,968 --> 01:04:49,345
The priests did the same thing.

747
01:04:49,637 --> 01:04:52,515
Pharaoh still has the
power over our lives.

748
01:04:55,518 --> 01:04:56,852
Yes, Aaron, it's true.

749
01:04:56,936 --> 01:04:58,729
Pharaoh has the power.

750
01:05:00,898 --> 01:05:02,400
He can take away your food,

751
01:05:02,483 --> 01:05:05,152
your home, your freedom.

752
01:05:05,695 --> 01:05:09,323
He can take away your
sons and daughters.

753
01:05:10,449 --> 01:05:12,201
With one word,

754
01:05:13,035 --> 01:05:15,913
Pharaoh can take away
your very lives.

755
01:05:18,040 --> 01:05:21,377
But there is one thing he
cannot take away from you.

756
01:05:22,044 --> 01:05:23,462
Your faith.

757
01:05:26,382 --> 01:05:27,717
Believe,

758
01:05:28,217 --> 01:05:30,970
for we will see God's wonders.

759
01:05:40,730 --> 01:05:42,815
♪ <i>Thus saith the Lord
Thus saith the Lord</i> ♪

760
01:05:42,898 --> 01:05:46,068
♪ <i>Since you refuse to free my people
Since you refuse</i> ♪

761
01:05:46,277 --> 01:05:48,362
♪ <i>Since you refuse
to free my people</i> ♪

762
01:05:48,446 --> 01:05:50,364
♪ <i>All through the land of Egypt</i> ♪

763
01:05:50,698 --> 01:05:54,910
♪ <i>I send a pestilence, a plague
into your house, into your bed</i> ♪

764
01:05:55,077 --> 01:05:56,996
♪ <i>Into your streams
Into your streets</i> ♪

765
01:05:57,079 --> 01:05:59,040
♪ <i>Into your drink
Into your bread</i> ♪

766
01:05:59,123 --> 01:06:01,250
♪ <i>Upon your cattle
On your sheep</i> ♪

767
01:06:01,334 --> 01:06:03,377
♪ <i>Upon your oxen in your field</i> ♪

768
01:06:03,461 --> 01:06:05,463
♪ <i>Into your dreams
Into your sleep</i> ♪

769
01:06:05,546 --> 01:06:08,007
♪ <i>Until you break
Until you yield</i> ♪

770
01:06:08,382 --> 01:06:11,802
♪ <i>I send the swarm
I send the horde</i> ♪

771
01:06:11,886 --> 01:06:16,390
♪ <i>Thus saith the Lord</i> ♪

772
01:06:17,558 --> 01:06:19,435
♪ <i>Once I called you brother</i> ♪

773
01:06:19,644 --> 01:06:22,313
♪ <i>Once I thought the chance
to make you laugh</i> ♪

774
01:06:22,521 --> 01:06:24,398
♪ <i>Was all I ever wanted</i> ♪

775
01:06:24,607 --> 01:06:26,108
♪ <i>I send the thunder
from the sky</i> ♪

776
01:06:26,317 --> 01:06:28,152
♪ <i>I send the fire raining down</i> ♪

777
01:06:28,361 --> 01:06:31,614
♪ <i>And even now I wish
that God had chose another</i> ♪

778
01:06:31,822 --> 01:06:34,617
♪ <i>Serving as your foe
on his behalf</i> ♪

779
01:06:34,825 --> 01:06:36,535
♪ <i>Is the last thing
that I wanted</i> ♪

780
01:06:36,744 --> 01:06:40,998
♪ <i>I send a hail of burning ice
on every field, on every town</i> ♪

781
01:06:41,332 --> 01:06:43,626
♪ <i>This was my home</i> ♪

782
01:06:43,709 --> 01:06:46,212
♪ <i>All this pain and devastation</i> ♪

783
01:06:46,295 --> 01:06:48,923
♪ <i>How it tortures me inside</i> ♪

784
01:06:49,131 --> 01:06:51,133
♪ <i>All the innocent who suffer</i> ♪

785
01:06:51,217 --> 01:06:53,052
♪ <i>From your stubbornness and pride</i> ♪

786
01:06:53,135 --> 01:06:55,221
♪ <i>I send the locusts on the wind</i> ♪

787
01:06:55,304 --> 01:06:56,972
♪ <i>Such as the world
has never seen</i> ♪

788
01:06:57,056 --> 01:06:59,183
♪ <i>On every leaf, on every stalk</i> ♪

789
01:06:59,266 --> 01:07:01,018
♪ <i>Until there's nothing
left of green</i> ♪

790
01:07:01,435 --> 01:07:03,270
♪ <i>I send my scourge</i> ♪

791
01:07:03,646 --> 01:07:05,439
♪ <i>I send my sword</i> ♪

792
01:07:05,523 --> 01:07:07,316
♪ <i>Thus saith the Lord</i> ♪

793
01:07:07,400 --> 01:07:08,984
♪ <i>You who I called brother</i> ♪

794
01:07:09,068 --> 01:07:11,696
♪ <i>Why must you call
down another blow</i> ♪

795
01:07:11,779 --> 01:07:13,614
♪ <i>I send my scourge</i> ♪

796
01:07:13,698 --> 01:07:16,117
♪ <i>I send my sword</i> ♪

797
01:07:16,242 --> 01:07:17,868
♪ <i>Let my people go</i> ♪

798
01:07:17,952 --> 01:07:19,954
♪ <i>Thus saith the Lord</i> ♪

799
01:07:20,037 --> 01:07:26,085
♪ <i>Thus saith the Lord</i> ♪

800
01:07:29,922 --> 01:07:31,716
♪ <i>You who I called brother</i> ♪

801
01:07:31,882 --> 01:07:34,468
♪ <i>How could you have
come to hate me so</i> ♪

802
01:07:34,635 --> 01:07:36,595
♪ <i>Is this what you wanted?</i> ♪

803
01:07:36,679 --> 01:07:39,765
♪ <i>I sent the swarm
I sent the horde</i> ♪

804
01:07:39,849 --> 01:07:41,851
♪ <i>Then let my heart be hardened</i> ♪

805
01:07:41,934 --> 01:07:44,854
♪ <i>And never mind how
high the cost may grow</i> ♪

806
01:07:45,062 --> 01:07:46,856
♪ <i>This will still be so</i> ♪

807
01:07:47,106 --> 01:07:52,862
♪ <i>I will never let
your people go</i> ♪

808
01:07:52,945 --> 01:07:55,072
♪ <i>Thus saith the Lord</i> ♪

809
01:07:55,156 --> 01:07:57,408
♪ <i>Thus saith the Lord</i> ♪

810
01:07:57,491 --> 01:08:03,497
♪ <i>I will not let your people go</i> ♪

811
01:08:03,581 --> 01:08:09,795
♪ <i>Let my people go</i> ♪

812
01:08:56,884 --> 01:08:58,677
Rameses?

813
01:09:01,055 --> 01:09:02,473
Rameses?

814
01:09:03,140 --> 01:09:05,267
Oh. Let me guess.

815
01:09:06,811 --> 01:09:12,274
You want me to
let your people go.

816
01:09:15,236 --> 01:09:17,613
I hoped I would find you here.

817
01:09:17,822 --> 01:09:18,823
Get out.

818
01:09:21,826 --> 01:09:26,121
Rameses, we must
bring this to an end.

819
01:09:31,585 --> 01:09:34,421
Rameses, please, talk to me.

820
01:09:35,214 --> 01:09:37,591
We could always talk here.

821
01:09:47,351 --> 01:09:48,811
This place.

822
01:09:50,604 --> 01:09:52,940
So many memories.

823
01:09:56,068 --> 01:09:58,237
I remember the time you

824
01:09:58,821 --> 01:10:02,491
switched the heads of the
gods of the Temple of Ra.

825
01:10:04,577 --> 01:10:05,953
Ah.

826
01:10:06,453 --> 01:10:08,289
If I recall correctly,

827
01:10:08,372 --> 01:10:12,585
you were there switching
heads right along with me.

828
01:10:13,794 --> 01:10:14,920
No, it was you.

829
01:10:15,004 --> 01:10:16,130
I didn't do that.

830
01:10:16,338 --> 01:10:17,339
Oh, yes, you did.

831
01:10:17,423 --> 01:10:20,843
You put the hippo on the
crocodile, and the crocodile...

832
01:10:20,926 --> 01:10:22,678
- On the falcon.
- Yes.

833
01:10:22,761 --> 01:10:24,597
And the priest thought
it was a horrible omen,

834
01:10:24,680 --> 01:10:26,181
and fasted for two months.

835
01:10:26,307 --> 01:10:27,474
Father was furious.

836
01:10:27,558 --> 01:10:29,768
You were always getting
me into trouble.

837
01:10:36,859 --> 01:10:38,360
But then...

838
01:10:40,779 --> 01:10:43,032
You were always there to

839
01:10:44,199 --> 01:10:47,161
get me out of trouble again.

840
01:10:53,959 --> 01:10:57,421
Why can't things be the
way they were before?

841
01:10:58,964 --> 01:11:00,132
Father.

842
01:11:01,634 --> 01:11:02,676
It's so dark.

843
01:11:04,803 --> 01:11:06,597
I'm frightened.

844
01:11:07,848 --> 01:11:09,266
Why is he here?

845
01:11:12,895 --> 01:11:15,189
Isn't that the man
who did all this?

846
01:11:17,983 --> 01:11:19,193
Yes.

847
01:11:20,235 --> 01:11:22,821
But one must wonder

848
01:11:23,447 --> 01:11:24,865
why?

849
01:11:25,699 --> 01:11:29,662
Because no kingdom should be
made on the backs of slaves.

850
01:11:30,454 --> 01:11:32,498
Rameses, your stubbornness

851
01:11:32,581 --> 01:11:34,500
is bringing this
misery upon Egypt.

852
01:11:34,583 --> 01:11:38,087
It would cease if only you
would let the Hebrews go.

853
01:11:38,253 --> 01:11:40,673
I will not be dictated to.
I will not be threatened.

854
01:11:40,756 --> 01:11:43,425
I am the morning
and the evening star.

855
01:11:43,509 --> 01:11:45,052
I am Pharaoh.

856
01:11:45,177 --> 01:11:46,470
Something else is coming.

857
01:11:46,553 --> 01:11:48,806
Something much worse
than anything before.

858
01:11:49,139 --> 01:11:52,226
Please, let go of your
contempt for life

859
01:11:52,309 --> 01:11:54,520
before it destroys everything
you hold dear.

860
01:11:54,687 --> 01:11:56,563
Think of your son.

861
01:11:57,606 --> 01:11:59,191
I do.

862
01:11:59,358 --> 01:12:01,694
You Hebrews have been
nothing but trouble.

863
01:12:02,361 --> 01:12:03,988
My father had the right idea

864
01:12:04,071 --> 01:12:06,407
about how to deal
with your people.

865
01:12:06,532 --> 01:12:08,951
- Rameses...
- And I think it's time

866
01:12:09,034 --> 01:12:11,161
- I finished the job.
- Rameses.

867
01:12:11,245 --> 01:12:14,581
And there shall be a
great cry in all of Egypt,

868
01:12:14,665 --> 01:12:18,252
such as never has been
or ever will be again.

869
01:12:32,683 --> 01:12:35,477
Rameses, you bring
this upon yourself.

870
01:12:45,904 --> 01:12:47,781
<i>God has come to me again,</i>

871
01:12:47,865 --> 01:12:50,492
<i>saying, "Take a lamb</i>

872
01:12:52,244 --> 01:12:53,787
<i>"and with its blood,</i>

873
01:12:54,288 --> 01:12:56,832
<i>"mark the lintel
and posts of every door.</i>

874
01:13:00,836 --> 01:13:05,299
<i>"For tonight, I shall pass
through the land of Egypt</i>

875
01:13:07,217 --> 01:13:10,596
<i>"and smite all the firstborn.</i>

876
01:13:16,643 --> 01:13:19,938
"But when I see the
blood upon your door,

877
01:13:21,690 --> 01:13:24,359
"I will pass over you

878
01:13:25,986 --> 01:13:29,615
"and the plague shall not enter."

879
01:16:06,438 --> 01:16:08,690
You and your people

880
01:16:10,192 --> 01:16:13,528
have my permission to go.

881
01:16:18,325 --> 01:16:19,910
Leave me!

882
01:17:54,087 --> 01:17:57,799
♪ <i>Many nights we've prayed</i> ♪

883
01:17:58,008 --> 01:18:02,763
♪ <i>With no proof
anyone could hear</i> ♪

884
01:18:02,971 --> 01:18:07,059
♪ <i>In our hearts a hopeful song</i> ♪

885
01:18:07,142 --> 01:18:11,063
♪ <i>We barely understood</i> ♪

886
01:18:11,396 --> 01:18:16,026
♪ <i>Now we are not afraid</i> ♪

887
01:18:16,109 --> 01:18:20,364
♪ <i>Although we know
there's much to fear</i> ♪

888
01:18:20,947 --> 01:18:24,368
♪ <i>We were moving mountains</i> ♪

889
01:18:24,451 --> 01:18:30,165
♪ <i>Long before we knew we could</i> ♪

890
01:18:30,499 --> 01:18:34,294
♪ <i>There can be miracles</i> ♪

891
01:18:34,378 --> 01:18:38,090
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

892
01:18:38,382 --> 01:18:41,426
♪ <i>Though hope is frail</i> ♪

893
01:18:41,802 --> 01:18:44,805
♪ <i>It's hard to kill</i> ♪

894
01:18:46,556 --> 01:18:50,268
♪ <i>Who knows what miracles</i> ♪

895
01:18:50,477 --> 01:18:54,314
♪ <i>You can achieve</i> ♪

896
01:18:54,523 --> 01:18:57,526
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

897
01:18:57,734 --> 01:19:02,447
♪ <i>Somehow you will</i> ♪

898
01:19:02,697 --> 01:19:09,246
♪ <i>You will when you believe</i> ♪

899
01:19:10,497 --> 01:19:13,708
♪ <i>In this time of fear</i> ♪

900
01:19:14,334 --> 01:19:18,422
♪ <i>When prayers so often
proved in vain</i> ♪

901
01:19:18,630 --> 01:19:21,925
♪ <i>Hope seemed like
the summer birds</i> ♪

902
01:19:22,134 --> 01:19:25,971
♪ <i>Too swiftly flown away</i> ♪

903
01:19:26,096 --> 01:19:30,142
♪ <i>Yet now I'm standing here
Now I'm standing here</i> ♪

904
01:19:30,225 --> 01:19:34,604
♪ <i>With heart so full
I can't explain</i> ♪

905
01:19:34,688 --> 01:19:38,400
♪ <i>Seeking faith
and speaking words</i> ♪

906
01:19:38,483 --> 01:19:42,654
♪ <i>I never thought I'd say</i> ♪

907
01:19:43,280 --> 01:19:46,867
♪ <i>There can be miracles</i> ♪

908
01:19:46,992 --> 01:19:48,785
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

909
01:19:48,869 --> 01:19:50,745
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

910
01:19:50,871 --> 01:19:53,874
♪ <i>Though hope is frail</i> ♪

911
01:19:54,166 --> 01:19:56,376
♪ <i>It's hard to kill</i> ♪

912
01:19:56,460 --> 01:19:58,462
♪ <i>It's hard to kill</i> ♪

913
01:19:58,628 --> 01:20:02,591
♪ <i>Who knows what miracles</i> ♪

914
01:20:02,799 --> 01:20:04,718
♪ <i>You can achieve</i> ♪

915
01:20:04,801 --> 01:20:06,595
♪ <i>You can achieve</i> ♪

916
01:20:06,678 --> 01:20:09,598
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

917
01:20:09,931 --> 01:20:14,311
♪ <i>Somehow you will</i> ♪

918
01:20:14,519 --> 01:20:18,565
♪ <i>You will when you believe</i> ♪

919
01:21:24,631 --> 01:21:28,301
♪ <i>There can be miracles</i> ♪

920
01:21:28,510 --> 01:21:32,264
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

921
01:21:32,472 --> 01:21:35,517
♪ <i>Though hope is frail</i> ♪

922
01:21:35,725 --> 01:21:38,019
♪ <i>It's hard to kill</i> ♪

923
01:21:38,103 --> 01:21:40,188
♪ <i>It's hard to kill</i> ♪

924
01:21:40,397 --> 01:21:44,150
♪ <i>Who knows what miracles</i> ♪

925
01:21:44,359 --> 01:21:46,486
♪ <i>You can achieve</i> ♪

926
01:21:46,570 --> 01:21:48,238
♪ <i>You can achieve</i> ♪

927
01:21:48,405 --> 01:21:51,116
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

928
01:21:51,366 --> 01:21:55,370
♪ <i>Somehow you will</i> ♪

929
01:21:55,620 --> 01:21:59,874
♪ <i>Now you will</i> ♪

930
01:22:00,166 --> 01:22:04,671
♪ <i>You will when you believe</i> ♪

931
01:22:04,754 --> 01:22:08,633
♪ <i>When you believe</i> ♪

932
01:22:08,717 --> 01:22:12,721
♪ <i>You will when you</i> ♪

933
01:22:12,804 --> 01:22:18,226
♪ <i>Believe</i> ♪

934
01:24:24,519 --> 01:24:26,354
<i>With this staff,</i>

935
01:24:26,813 --> 01:24:29,899
<i>you shall do</i>

936
01:24:30,066 --> 01:24:32,152
<i>my wonders!</i>

937
01:25:49,270 --> 01:25:50,271
Leave it!

938
01:26:25,640 --> 01:26:27,100
Yeah, me too.

939
01:27:05,346 --> 01:27:08,558
Don't just stand there!
Kill them!

940
01:27:09,809 --> 01:27:11,227
Kill them all!

941
01:27:13,271 --> 01:27:15,148
The soldiers! They're coming!

942
01:27:19,736 --> 01:27:21,321
Moses! Moses!

943
01:27:21,529 --> 01:27:24,282
- Hurry! Hurry! I got you.
- Look! The shore!

944
01:27:49,724 --> 01:27:53,227
No!

945
01:29:23,860 --> 01:29:25,194
Thank you.

946
01:29:53,431 --> 01:29:57,518
Moses!

947
01:30:02,690 --> 01:30:06,694
Moses!

948
01:30:10,198 --> 01:30:12,158
Goodbye, brother.

949
01:30:34,013 --> 01:30:35,264
Look.

950
01:30:35,848 --> 01:30:38,893
Look at your people, Moses.

951
01:30:42,313 --> 01:30:44,357
They are free.

952
01:31:48,254 --> 01:31:53,759
♪ <i>Deliver us</i> ♪