[GRUNTING]
You couldn't hide, Johnny.
Nobody hides from us.
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
Shit! Benny, get me some ice.
I think I broke my goddamn hand.
Sure, boss.
Fuck you! Just do me quick.
Sure, Johnny. But first,
Mr. Canelli wants a little souvenir.
Open up. Open up!
We're gonna forward this to
your buddies in Witness Protection.
See if it sings on its own.
They can take it to the trial.
Open up, Johnny. Open up!
[CLATTERING]
Benny?
Hello?
Who in the hell are you?
[CRACKS]
-Close your eyes.
-Who are you?
Shut up!
Who--?
-You too.
JOHNNY: It's okay.
You do what he says.
Don't move. You're dead.
I need the clothes you're wearing.
And your ring, your watch...
-...all your IDs. Now.
-Uh--
Shh! Do it.
You come with me.
Grab the other one.
Let's go.
Put your clothes on them. Move!
[BEEPING]
Yes, there's been a murder
at 232 Alden Drive.
-Send the police.
-What are you doing?
They killed you, then they
turned on each other.
Right.
Those sons of bitches.
[SIRENS WAILING]
-Shit!
-Don't worry.
This doesn't work without an audience.
Outside. Let's go.
Get in.
Thank you. Thank you, man.
Anything you ever need, anything,
you just ask me.
You endangered your life and the lives
of U.S. marshals protecting you.
-What are you talking about?
-You were spotted at your old restaurant.
You went back to Gennaro's?
Johnny, what are you, stupid?
Hey, it's the osso buco.
I haven't had a decent meal in six months.
I was fucking dying, okay?
The next time, you're dead.
This only happens once.
Get out.
What are you doing? That was our ride.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Let's go. Go.
You'll never see me again,
but I'll know every move you make.
Use your heads, lie low,
and I promise no one will hurt you.
If you try to skip out on your testimony,
I'll deliver you to the Canelli family myself.
-I promise.
JOHNNY: Hey, listen, man.
Look, I owe you bigtime.
I'm a standup guy, you got it?
You ever need anything, anything,
you let me know. Hey, what's your name?
-Easy, I don't think he wants to be pen pals.
MAN: Smile.
You've just been erased.
MAN:
Go ahead.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Hey, John, would you look at something?
One of these is from our shop and
the others are real. What do you think?
That's the fake.
-Who the hell was that?
-I could tell you, but I'd have to kill you.
Now shut up and run this again.
DEGUERIN:
So with a little sleight of hand...
...one very dead John Doe trades places
with one very live scumbag.
-Robert, sit down.
-John.
You know...
...if God was as forgiving as WitSec...
-...hell would be one empty joint, no?
-God doesn't have our court system.
So I understand you had a busy night.
A couple of witnesses got careless.
-I see.
-I had to defuse the situation.
Did that--? Did that include
breaking into the county morgue?
Someone once taught me that
improvisation is the heart of fieldwork.
-I think it was you.
-In the old days. The weather's changed.
Now you got every asshole in Congress,
you know, down our backs.
I'm telling you to walk softly.
Is that why Beller called me in?
Because of the morgue?
Oh, no, no, no.
The old man doesn't know anything about
that, and personally, I don't think he has to.
Shadow Ops still has some privileges.
You're right.
Oh, and John...
-...that's good work.
-I had a good teacher.
Bullshit. You had the best.
Fourteen thousand, six hundred and forty
some-odd people under WitSec protection...
-...and not one with a profile like this.
-That bad?
That good.
This young lady, Miss Cullen...
...is a real live, bona fide...
...honest person.
Then why does she need us?
She's a senior executive
at Cyrez Corporation. Hear of it?
Yeah, major defense contractors.
Mostly top-secret weapons research.
Looks like someone inside Cyrez
is selling out Uncle Sam.
Feds need her to prove their case.
If they do...
...she'll be the key witness
in the hottest scandal since Iran-Contra.
-When does this go down?
-Tomorrow.
The sting's all in place.
Soon as it's over, she's all yours.
Seal file on relocate. Your eyes only.
As usual, only you and I'll be privy
to your witness' exact location.
But, John...
...there are some serious players
here in Washington that...
...could be badly burned.
Then so could she.
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
WOMAN [OVER SPEAKERS]:
Welcome to Cyrez Corporation.
All visitors are required to step in
the security stations on the right.
Please be prepared
to present valid identification.
-Good morning, Dave.
-Good morning.
She's in.
MAN 1: She giving us anything yet?
-Not yet.
MAN 2: That's right, Lee.
We're right here with you.
We're on.
-Can you hear me?
-We hear you, Lee.
-I look okay?
-Tell her she looks great.
Not bad, Miss Cullen.
Not bad for an amateur.
We're right with you, Lee.
-Yeah.
-Then let's do it.
-Good morning, Miss Cullen.
LEE: Good morning.
Station C?
-Yes.
-And how long today?
Ten minutes, max.
Okay.
You're doing just fine, Lee.
Let's hope we bought
the right combination, gentlemen.
[CLICKS]
Bingo!
-Shit!
-No, it's okay.
We lose transmission in the vault.
-What do we do now?
-Now we wait.
She better move fast because she's only
got five minutes till the shift change.
What's taking so long?
Come on, sweetheart,
you got two minutes left.
-We should have never used her.
-Shit! She's out of time.
-Hey!
-Yes!
Welcome back, Lee.
We're right here with you.
Miss Cullen, Mr. Donahue's office called.
He'd like to see you.
-Tell him I'll be up in a minute.
-He said, "Right now."
-What's going on?
-I think they made us.
Check the directory. I wanna know
where Donahue's office is.
-Twenty-fifth floor.
-I know where it is.
Twenty-fifth floor.
Get backup ready to roll.
This whole thing could go south.
What is it, William?
That's someone I trusted for five years.
Someone I told others could be trusted.
-Well, I was pulling the stack--
-Don't!
We're way beyond bullshit here.
Who are you working for?
Shit, we're dead.
I should ask you that question.
I used to think
it was for the U.S. government.
Oh, come on, Lee.
What do you think we do here?
This isn't the Red Cross.
We make weapons,
things that kill people.
If the government
isn't willing to pay the price...
...it's my job to find somebody who will.
I didn't know treason
was part of the corporate strategy.
I asked who you were working for.
You didn't tell me.
-Oh, my God.
-Holy shit.
Christ.
Get her out of there.
Get her out of there now!
What is this?
A camera?
I'm working for the FBI, William.
They heard everything you just said.
They're watching us right now.
And you think that makes you safe?
You have no fucking idea!
How could you do this to me?
I hope you understand, Lee.
You leave me no choice.
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Welcome to Cyrez Corporation.
All visitors are required to step in
the security stations on the right.
Security.
Wait a minute. Stop her!
MAN:
Stop! Hey!
Lee.
Go, go, go!
Suspect's fleeing--
MAN 1:
Our hard evidence.
It's all yours, gentlemen.
We've handled these
types of situations before.
You still haven't answered my question.
We told you there'd be risks.
You also told me I would be under
complete protection the entire time.
The operation didn't go
as smoothly as we anticipated.
I'd say that's an understatement.
Remember, Miss Cullen, you came to us.
I came to you with a clerical error.
You asked for my help.
MAN 2:
And we got it.
If Cyrez is selling weapons technology,
that's high treason.
This disk and your testimony will help us put
them and their coconspirators behind bars.
You've done a great service
for your country, Miss Cullen.
Now it's time to think about your safety.
MAN 3: This is U.S. Marshal John Kruger
of the Witness Protection Program.
He'll be handling your personal security.
My protection?
Your new identity, relocation.
I'll take you through it step by step.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going anywhere.
You're in an extremely high-risk situation,
Miss Cullen.
That should have been explained to you.
Your boss was just a middleman, Lee.
There are more dangerous people
involved.
So you expect me to, what,
give up my whole life over this?
Just until the trial.
Then you'll be completely out of danger.
And how do you know that, huh?
-How do you know?
-Miss Cullen--
No, look, I will keep up my end
of the bargain. I will testify.
But that's it.
I'm going home.
Put people on her right away...
...or we'll need a séance
to get her testimony.
-Who brought her into this?
MAN 1: She volunteered.
She had security clearance,
we had the vault code so--
You told her it's a walk in the park.
When she finds out that her life
isn't her own anymore, it's too late.
-We had no case without her.
JOHN: Right.
It's a lot easier to put her ass on the line
than yours, isn't it?
[BUZZES]
-Sully.
-Frediano, how you doing?
-Good. I have a little something for you.
SULLY: Let's see what you got.
-Your receipt.
-Thank you.
SULLY:
Gentlemen, always a pleasure.
It's me.
Your music has arrived.
Get Mr. Morehart down here
immediately.
[PHONE RINGS]
-Hello?
LEE: It's me.
Lee? Jesus, I heard about Donahue.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. You're right.
-I shouldn't have trusted them.
-Of course not. The feds are idiots.
They'll either blow the case or bury it.
-Lee?
-The feds are here now.
They're watching me.
You let me write this story and
I will nail Cyrez all over the front page.
It may not be safe to talk on this phone.
-I'll call you later.
-Wait. Did you make a copy?
-Yeah.
-That's your insurance, Lee.
You go public
and they won't dare touch you.
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
Lee? Lee, what's wrong?
I don't know. I gotta go.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
-Hi, baby.
-Darryl, what the hell are you doing here?
Been waiting for you. Getting cleaned up.
How you doing?
So, what, you just let yourself
into my house, huh?
I've been worried about you, that's all.
I haven't heard from you in days.
Well, there's nothing left to talk about.
It's over, and you know that.
Come on, Lee.
That doesn't hurt you to say that?
LEE:
It hurt me three months ago.
But after the phone calls, after
the notes on my car and tonight...
...believe me, it's getting a lot easier.
MAN [WHISPERING]:
Get down.
You're seeing someone, aren't you?
-Come on, Darryl.
-I know you're seeing somebody.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
-Let's see who that is.
-Darryl.
Oh, what's this? And a card.
JOHN:
Get down!
Hey!
Oh, shit! Go, go, go!
Come here.
Stay down.
I don't have a shot.
[GROANING]
You, go, go.
[GAS HISSING]
-What are you doing?
-Lighting a fuse.
[SCREAMING]
-Are you hit?
-What?
-Are you hurt? Are you bleeding?
-I don't think so.
-Are they following us?
-No. Just calm down.
You're gonna be fine.
I'm not gonna be fine.
Look, they just tried to kill me.
And Darryl.... Darryl's dead.
Lee, you're alive,
and I'll keep you that way.
Your hand.
There's a first-aid kit under your seat.
That weapon,
or whatever the hell it was...
...it was from your company, Cyrez,
wasn't it?
Yeah, it's an E.M. prototype.
It's not even supposed to exist.
-E.M.?
-Electromagnetic pulse.
No gunpowder, no conventional bullets.
They fire aluminum rounds
at almost the speed of light.
You're talking about a rail gun.
Yeah, that's another name for them.
The Navy has been working on them
for years.
The smallest one I've ever heard of
is mounted on a battleship.
Well, Cyrez was contracted
to scale them down...
...to design a compact
hypervelocity pulse weapon...
...the most powerful assault rifle on earth.
They took millions,
then said the physics were impossible.
It looked real enough to me.
Maybe Cyrez found a higher bidder.
Well, they're connected everywhere:
Defense, CIA, NSA...
...maybe even your people,
for all we know.
You still want to put them away?
Yes.
I'll hide you until the hearings.
No one will know where.
Not my boss, not WitSec.
-No one.
-Can you do that?
The feds knew this would be
a death sentence for you...
...and let you walk right into it.
I was stupid.
You trusted them, that's all.
Now trust me.
This is Morehart. We have a problem.
Go ahead. This line's secure.
-The Cullen woman is still alive.
-Are you serious?
It gets worse. She has a disk.
She tried to access our program with it.
You have any idea the risk I took
to get this back?
I know. I know.
She must have made a duplicate.
Then get it. Whatever it takes, get it!
Understood.
One other thing.
-I checked her phone records.
-And?
She called a woman named Isaacs.
A reporter for the Washington Herald.
I see.
I think you know what has to be done.
Do it.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
The Joint Chiefs are ready,
Mr. Undersecretary.
Tell them I'll be right with them.
Lieutenant, thank you.
That's it. That's everything I am.
No, that's nothing.
It's a few numbers and some plastic.
What you are is in here...
...and no one can take that from you.
They're gonna try.
We'll stop them.
I need the rest.
-That's all there is.
-No, this.
-This?
-Yeah.
It's St. George.
It's silly, but when I was a kid I used to
have these nightmares about dragons so--
-He watched over you.
-Yeah.
Well, that's my job now.
Get some sleep.
We leave at dawn.
-Okay.
Night.
JOHN: There's a place I know
where it's easy to disappear.
There's a woman there I've helped before.
She testified against the yakuza bosses
in San Francisco.
Her new name is Mei-Ling.
You'll be safe with her until the hearings.
Thank you.
Your new name is Deborah Elliott.
Is that how you think of me,
as a Deborah?
I don't know.
I guess I could have
used something more fun, like...
...Debbie?
-Deb?
-Deborah's fine.
I gave you AAA credit.
-What's my limit?
-No, it's not a license to shop.
I want you to lay low right now.
Mei-Ling will take good care of you.
Okay? You know the signal.
Nine-one-one. I get out of the apartment.
Remember, go straight to the pay phone
and wait for my call.
Anything happens, it's a public place
with six exits and six ways out.
One more thing.
I work alone.
If anyone comes to you
and claims that I sent them...
...use this.
All you have to do is pull the trigger.
I guess I won't see you again.
If everything goes well, no.
Well, at least not until the trial.
Thanks.
Thank me when it's over.
[MUSIC PLAYS ON TV]
MAN [ON TV]:
Undersecretary of Defense, Daniel Harper...
...spoke before Congress today
about the controversial Cyrez scandal.
HARPER: The use of private contractors
is totally within the parameters...
...of Defense Department spending.
I look forward to the Cyrez hearing,
and I'm absolutely confident...
...that we will be vindicated
of any mismanagement of funds.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman, for
the opportunity. Thank you very much.
Hey, John.
Thanks for coming.
You know I don't like meeting
outside of our normal channels.
It's not my choice.
Are they with you?
Yeah.
Whether I like it or not.
Listen, John...
-...we got a serious problem.
-What's going on?
Someone's been murdering our witnesses.
We've got three confirmed kills
in the last 48 hours.
-Who?
-Not one of yours.
It's not one of mine. Not yet anyway.
-Did they break cover?
-No.
No, that is the problem.
And there's no way anyone could know
all three of their locations.
There's a mole inside WitSec.
Beller thinks so. He may be right.
Hell, all three singers were witnesses
in some high-profile federal cases.
All with international ties.
That's our common thread.
-There are other singers that fit the profile.
-Six, to be exact.
One of them's yours
and one on them's mine. So...
...we have to live-contact
and replant them immediately.
The jet is fueling as we speak.
I work alone. You know that.
Not today. Beller's orders.
Buddy system, CIA escorts...
...three teams. We're one of them.
Fine. We do yours first.
Gentlemen, this is John Kruger.
John, these are Agents Schiff and Calderon.
I forgot which is which.
-I'm Schiff.
-And I'm Calderon.
-You know her?
-Should I?
She was a reporter doing a piece on Cyrez.
There could be a connection to your witness.
JOHN: Did someone take her out?
CALDERON: Peeled her like an onion.
If she knew anything, she talked.
Oh, John, this here is Deputy Monroe.
He's one of ours.
Monroe, you're looking at a legend.
This is Mr. John Kruger.
-Deputy.
-Sir, it's a pleasure.
Nice rig.
-How many of these you got?
-Three.
In different parts of the country.
Handy for quick relocates.
Sometimes we run violent felons
for the feds.
Chauffeurs for degenerates.
Don't you ever get tired
of babysitting scum?
Yeah.
But in your case, I'll make an exception.
Hey.
-Who the hell does this guy think he is?
-Him?
Well, he thinks
he's the best guy in the game.
I think he's right.
Try not to piss him off, okay?
DEGUERIN:
Guys...
...you're east, you're west...
...you're north. Here.
We got the boathouse,
the garage, the back door.
-We take the front entrance?
-You and me, old buddy.
Look, I don't feel like
getting shot today...
...so keep your goddamn safeties on.
We'll probably find her
inside baking muffins.
Now, this is my witness.
Her name is Allison.
She's a very, very nice lady...
-...so let's bring her out safely, gentlemen.
-Here you go.
Let's go, big guy.
The engine's still warm.
[GUNSHOT]
[FLOORBOARDS CREAK]
[WOMAN GROANING]
[MAN WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN:
Shut up.
-You're early.
-You're late.
[GLASS BREAKING]
JOHN:
Hey. Psst.
Hush, hush, hush.
Hush, now. Hush, now. Shh, shh.
He won't hurt you.
He won't hurt you anymore.
She's hit, get an ambulance.
Go on.
Sorry, honey.
We lost her.
Why send five men to kill one woman?
They were waiting for us.
We've been set up.
Is she yours?
-Yeah.
-Call her now, John.
There are no phones.
We have to live-contact her.
-Where is she?
-Atlanta.
Okay. Well, let's move, then, huh?
Here. You'll like this better.
You all right there, Monroe?
Yeah, I think so, sir.
-First time under fire?
-Yeah.
It's okay to be shaky.
I mean, hell, I'm shaky. All right?
The thing is, sir...
...I don't know what I feel.
-I mean, it was terrible and all--
-What, exciting at the same time?
-Yeah.
-Hey...
...it's nothing to be ashamed of. It's the
most natural thing in the whole world.
-Tell him.
-Yeah, it's natural.
The whole game's that way.
It's like a drug. You get hooked,
there's no turning back.
Now, you take me.
My old man...
...a little nobody in D.C.
Nice, quiet guy.
Anyway, on his deathbed...
...he tells me that all those years
he was working for the CIA.
I had to be part of that world.
I joined the CIA, couple of years,
here I am at WitSec.
[PAGER BEEPING]
Hey, buddy.
What about you, sir?
Why did you join WitSec?
Sir, is something wrong?
Well, answer the kid, John.
Go ahead, tell him.
Sir?
DEGUERIN:
Come on, John.
You.
Sir, what the hell is going on?
Shit, he cleared the numbers.
-Sir, what the hell is going on?
-Quiet.
Hey, did you capture that call?
Got it. New York prefix.
Taxi!
City Zoo.
DEGUERIN:
New York. Tell him to change course.
MONROE: I'll call WitSec.
-What? No, that won't be necessary.
We're supposed to report
any change in the flight plan.
Monroe. Monroe, you did great work
back there. Sit down.
Sit down.
Did I give you your evaluation yet?
-Evaluation?
-Yeah.
[GUNSHOTS]
A-plus, kid.
Goddamn it. Get me a Wet-Nap
or something, will you?
-Who do we have in New York?
-Four or five guys we can trust.
Get them ready.
Clean this mess up.
Confused, pal?
New York.
You're off course.
No, no, no. No, we're not.
You're gonna take us to her, John.
You did a very, very bad thing, John.
You killed Monroe.
Now that makes you the mole.
No.
That makes you a murderer.
Easy, Big John.
I'm a businessman.
A very, very serious businessman.
A businessman?
Selling weapons
with your old CIA pals, huh?
Is it just the money?
Trying to start your own
dirty little war somewhere?
Wars? Wars? Wars, John?
John, John.
I mean, wars, they come and go.
What? We did Nam, we lost.
We did the Gulf, we won. Hey.
What changed, John?
Nothing. Nothing ever does.
The only difference is who gets rich
and who gets dead.
Personally, John, I prefer rich, no?
You must be a very rich man by now.
You know, it doesn't have to end like this,
John. I can make you part of it. A big part.
All you have to do is give up the girl.
What do you say?
Drop your gun.
What?
If you drop your gun now...
...I promise I won't kill you.
I guess I'll have to
take my chances, John.
John!
I can't believe you nailed me
with this cheap piece of mail-order shit!
Think about it, John.
You jump, you'll go through
like shit through a goose!
You're right!
Engine fire! Fire, Number 3, Bob.
DEGUERIN:
Turn this thing around.
We got a mayday.
I'm trying to keep us in the air.
You turn it around and take him out now.
All right.
I want his face all over this windshield.
[DOG BARKING]
Oh, man. Did that hurt?
It had to hurt. I saw it.
-Where is this?
-Earth. Welcome.
-Is that your daddy's truck?
-Yeah.
Do you think he'd mind if I borrow it?
I don't know.
Is this yours?
-Do you like it?
-Oh, yes.
What about a trade?
Fifty bucks.
Fifty bucks?
[BOY AND GIRL LAUGHING]
Hey!
Shit.
We traced her number to Chinatown,
but she was long gone.
No shit, Dick Tracy.
That was a run signal.
-What about the cab companies?
-Three pickups of solo women...
...in the vicinity
within 15 minutes of the call.
Where were the drop-offs?
Madison and 53rd,
89th and Central Park West...
...and the New York City Zoo.
-That's it. That's it.
-The zoo?
First a run signal, then straight
to a public meeting place.
-Where are your shooters?
-Standing by.
Get them. I want two teams to sweep
from the north and the south. Let's go, now.
Go!
MAN [OVER SPEAKERS]:
Ladies and gentlemen, your attention.
The zoo will be closing in 10 minutes.
-Please proceed to the nearest exit.
MAN: Miss Cullen?
It's-- It's all right, ma'am, I'm here to help.
I'm a U.S. marshal.
Where's John Kruger?
He's on his way. He sent me to be sure
you're safe until he gets here.
Really?
Then he must have shown you
the secret handshake.
Right.
[GUNSHOT]
God! Shit!
DeGuerin!
-Yeah?
-That bitch just shot me!
We're on our way. Take her down if you
have to, but don't kill her, you hear me?
What's going on?
-U.S. marshal. Close the gates, exits.
-There's still people inside.
-Well, fine, then get them out, now!
-All right, let's go.
You two, right here.
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen, please exit the zoo.
Let's go. Let's go, immediately!
Police emergency. Thank you.
[HORN HONKING]
Come on!
Come.
He's here.
[POUNDING ON DOORS]
Hold your fire! Come on, Lee...
...it doesn't have to be like this.
Just drop your weapon.
[GUN CLICKS EMPTY]
Go! Move! Go!
-You're late.
-Traffic.
-How's your ammo?
-I'm out.
Damn it. Two rounds left.
-Move!
-Are you ready to go?
-Yeah.
-Stay down.
When I tell you, head for the door.
Go.
No! No!
Let's go.
You're luggage.
[SIRENS WAILING]
BELLER:
You said how many casualties?
Total, three of my men.
Kruger took them out like that, cold.
-I can't believe this.
-His prints were all over the weapon.
You've run prints on him already?
That's moving fast, Robert.
Hey, I was there. I saw it.
Doesn't make sense.
Why would he do a thing like this?
Look, the man has no family,
he has no friends.
He has nothing to keep him honest.
He's been bought.
-It's just I've known John for years--
-Sir, we're losing time.
I mean, if he is innocent,
you tell me why he's on the run.
What about his witness?
She's in it with him.
-What the hell do you mean?
-Hey, hey.
We approached her, we identified ourselves.
She shot one of my men.
All right, fine.
Do whatever it takes. You bring him in.
-But, Robert?
-Sir?
You bring him in alive.
-Hey, captain.
-Sir?
I want you to put out a citywide APB.
I want this town locked up so tight,
it'll make his balls ache.
[BEEPING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Beller here.
-Captain.
-John, where are you?
DeGuerin is the mole. He's after my witness.
He's killed the others just to flush her out.
-You have to come in.
-I have to protect my witness.
You're putting her in danger.
You'll both end up dead.
DeGuerin has been bought.
My witness knows too much.
I've got federal agents
that say you are the shooter.
-John?
-I'll call you back.
-When?
-When I have proof.
It's gone too far.
We're on our own.
LEE:
What are we gonna do?
We can't stay on the run for long.
We need some hard evidence.
Lee?
You kept a copy?
I was supposed to give it to a friend of
mine, a reporter at the Washington Herald.
-She asked me--
-Claire Isaacs?
How'd you know?
Lee, she's dead.
They killed her.
No way they could have known
about her.
-I didn't tell anyone.
-I know. It's not your fault.
They probably tapped her phone.
There's many ways--
-Everything's gonna be all right, okay?
-I was just trying to cover myself.
I didn't know who I could trust.
-Now I'm gonna get us both killed.
-No.
This may be the only thing
that keeps us alive.
-I don't even know what's on that.
-We have to find out.
I've tried. It's completely hacker-proof.
There's no way to run it outside Cyrez.
Then we run it from the inside.
John, that place is like a fortress. We
can't go back there. They'd expect that.
-I'd hate to disappoint them.
MAN: John.
The streets are clear. The police returned
to the safety of their doughnut shops.
-Lee, this is Father Rodriguez.
-Hi.
Pleasure.
Of course,
I was not always Father Rodriguez.
Could say I was born again,
with a little help from our friend.
Some of his Colombian associates wanted
to introduce him to God personally.
I've been given a second chance at life.
This time, I'm using it to do God's work.
Is there anything else I can do?
We need a car, just for a day or two.
Done. It burns as much oil
as it does gas, but it's yours.
Are you sure about this?
There's no one else I can trust.
[THE WEATHER GIRLS' "IT'S RAINING MEN"
PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
[LIP-SYNCING]
JOHN:
Hello, Johnny.
-You!
-I need to talk to you right away.
I got one question for you.
Was it your idea to hook me up
with the Village People here?
Well, you're safe, aren't you?
Well, from the Mob, yeah.
I mean, no self-respecting wiseguy
would be caught dead in a joint like this.
Oh, look, do me just one favor.
Don't-- Don't let on that I'm straight, okay?
I don't wanna break any hearts or nothing.
Trust me. Remember when you told me
if I ever need anything, I could come to you?
-Yes.
-Well, I need your help.
Well, wait a minute. You need my help?
Right now.
You got it. Kevin?
Cover me for a few seconds.
I'm gonna help a friend.
Who's he? He looks rough.
Please don't start.
Maybe you two need a moment alone?
We're fine, thank you.
Just an idea.
Kevin just worries about me.
Don't ask.
You want me to help you
break into Cyrez?
-Yeah.
-What, are you shitting me?
I thought you wanted help
to move a sofa or something.
Pull over up ahead.
Look, I'm gonna help you out.
All we're gonna need is some tanks,
a couple of rocket launchers...
...and a set of balls
like the king of Bayonne.
JOHN:
All you need are these.
I'll meet you back at his place.
What, I look like I got gas or something?
-Gentlemen.
-You wanna tell me what's going on?
-I'll have the situation contained in 24 hours.
-Not good enough.
We have problems. They're solvable.
-We have to cancel the shipment.
-That's not an option.
What do we do with 10 tons of assault
weaponry that's not supposed to exist, huh?
I am the eyes and ears of your world,
gentlemen...
-...and there's too much heat.
HARPER: You don't get it, do you?
The money has changed hands.
These are not the kind of people
you cancel on!
Get those guns out of the country tonight
or you're a dead man.
Now...
...how do you intend
to contain the situation?
Kruger has to show up at Cyrez.
When he does, I'll be waiting.
Well, why would he risk that?
He needs to know what's on that disk.
That's the only thing that'll clear them.
Fine. This better work.
The disk, the girl, the guns.
By dawn, they don't exist. Are we clear?
Yeah, crystal.
The House Armed Services Committee
announced that two weeks from today...
...it will begin official hearings
into the Cyrez scandal.
-Sources tell us the committee--
MAN: Perfect.
The place is crawling with reporters.
We've gotta keep a lid on this mess.
Do what I tell you, and by tomorrow you'll
be chuckling about this in your country club.
-Now, who's running this game room?
-I am.
-This is James Haggerty, head of security.
-Good.
We're gonna keep everything
nice and low-profile.
-You ever do any wetwork?
-Only on three different continents.
Yeah. Well, you wanna impress me, Slick,
do your fucking job.
How many people can you bring in?
Twelve experienced professionals.
They'll do whatever it takes.
Plus 20 more on the security force.
They'll follow orders.
Well, that's fine.
My man is at the main entrance.
Make sure he receives your full cooperation.
He's dialed in. We've got every possible
point of entry under surveillance...
-...from the rooftop to the sewer system.
JOHN: Well, this fucker's a ghost.
Believe me. If he wants in, he'll get in.
Where's he gotta go to run this disk?
The central vault.
No other terminal can access that program.
If he wants to read the disk,
there's only one way in.
That's outstanding, gentlemen.
I guess all we gotta do is sit back
and wait for Mr. Kruger to come to us.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where do you think you're going?
Take it easy there. I got a delivery
for Blevens, 14th floor.
We can't accept
any unauthorized deliveries.
"We can't accept any deliveries."
I'm just messing with you, man.
Why not...
...call Blevens, get him to authorize it?
I got a pepperoni and cheese here.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
GUARD: Maybe you don't understand.
-Who's that?
This is a high-security facility.
Maybe you don't understand, my friend.
This is a Papa Genoche's pizza, okay?
If Blevens doesn't get it while it's hot,
he gets two for free, out of my pocket.
-I'm trying to save.
-Search him.
Get your hands off me!
Hey, listen, I got a bad heart
and a very good lawyer, all right?
Shut up.
He's clean.
Cheese and pepperoni.
All right, pal, hit the road.
I said, hit the road.
-What's the hell's going on down there?
-Some pizza-delivery guy is having a seizure.
Which moron ordered a pizza?
This is all we need. Get him to the infirmary
immediately and call an ambulance.
Out of the way! Coming through!
[PHONE RINGS]
-Yeah?
DEGUERIN: How we doing?
We'll be on the road in an hour.
They need to be rolling
or I need to know why.
Yes, sir.
All right, come on, guys.
Let's move it!
[SIREN WAILING]
They've been expecting you.
Infirmary is straight through
the loading dock.
-Is the patient stable?
-I'm not sure. Better hurry.
Thank you.
WOMAN: All right, he looks stable.
Give him some low O2.
[EKG BEEPING]
[EKG FLATLINING]
JOHNNY: Hey. It's all right.
-He's fibrillating! Code blue!
No--
Get off me.
WOMAN:
Give me some gel.
-No! No! No!
-Clear!
Right this way. They're waiting for you.
Here we go again. Clear!
All right, increase the voltage.
Let's do it one more time.
-Let's not.
-Oh, my God.
You, over there, against the wall.
Get down on the floor.
Face the wall.
-Get on the floor.
-Oh, my God, terrorists!
You want terror? Yeah, huh?
You want some freaking terror?
You want some terror?
-Get your ass up here, I'll jump-start it!
-Here, tape them up.
Okay, face the wall.
There.
Keep the room secure.
-You think you can handle that?
-Get out of here.
Let's go.
We got a problem.
What? What is it?
-He's running the disk.
-Shit!
That's impossible.
-Station 1, any activity at your location?
-All clear.
All clear, my ass. He's in,
he just didn't use the door.
Come on, get your men down there now.
Let's go!
What?
-What are you doing?
-No, I know this.
-We change it every week.
-Screw that. Get out of the way.
Go ahead, check it.
Somebody talk to me.
He must be running the disk from a remote
terminal somewhere in the building.
-You said he couldn't do that.
-He can't.
-Donahue designed it so no outside ac--
-Donahue--
Donahue is dead.
And you're gonna wish you were too
unless you find out what is going on...
...and you find out now.
-Holster your weapon.
-Take a hike, junior.
I said, holster your--
You know, some people take things for
granted, like the ability to chew solid food.
I can find him.
How?
I can scan the terminals
and I can eliminate them one by one.
If he stays online, I'll nail him.
Then do it.
LEE: How we doing?
-You were right about Donahue.
He left himself a back door.
But we still have to break his code.
I figure we've got another five
or six minutes until they trace us.
-Do you recognize any of this?
LEE: No.
But we're getting warm.
It's an accounting format.
Okay. Stop me if I get lucky.
-How we doing?
-Eliminating low-clearance programs.
Okay, south wing is clean.
Two more to go.
I've got two federal investigators
downstairs who wanna talk.
Fine, go talk. Do what you
gotta do, but get rid of them.
-You can't be seen here.
-I won't be. Just go.
-I need a chopper on the roof ready to go.
-Right.
Those are offshore banking deposits.
"UBS." That's United Bank of Syria.
Fifty-two million dollars.
If it's an arms sale, it's a major one.
Let's see who their buyer is.
[LEE READS ON-SCREEN TEXT]
-Who's that?
-Bad news.
He heads a cartel in the Russian Mafia...
...selling drugs, guns, influence
to some very unpleasant people.
-He's somewhere in the north wing.
-North wing. Get moving.
Let's go.
-How much longer?
-I don't know.
There's 15 terminals running
secure programs in there.
You got five minutes.
You find them, you call me.
Let's go.
There it is. "Delivery date:
Tonight, midnight."
A thousand units for delivery
at Baltimore Harbor.
A thousand units of what?
An E.M. gun.
A thousand E.M. guns.
Are they insane?
If these things get offshore....
There will be a whole new era
of world terrorism.
Got him. Twenty-fifth floor,
Donahue's office.
Scramble. Alpha chief
to the north wing, now!
They're on to us.
They're erasing the goddamn disk.
Come on.
-I'll cover you. Meet me at the ambulance.
-No, I can't--
Go!
Lee, run!
You listen up, John!
We're playing my rules now!
You mess with me and I'll slice her up
and mail her back to you in little pieces.
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
Fire alert. Fire alert.
This is not a drill. Please proceed
to the nearest exit.
In this car, I can get us to Baltimore
in 40 minutes.
Johnny, you're not coming with me.
-I'm gonna drop you off.
-No.
Please don't give me
this "I work alone" shit.
You've already done enough.
This is not your fight.
Look, no. Look, just--
Just indulge me for a minute, okay?
If it weren't for you...
...my tongue would be hanging on Canelli's
trophy wall like a freaking trout.
Now, look, you need me.
My cousin Tony runs those docks.
If your ship is there, he will find it.
-You're short one envelope here.
-Infantino didn't pay.
What do you mean, he didn't pay?
What'd he say?
He said, "Tell that fat fuck,
Tony Two-Toes...
...I ain't gonna pay him another dime."
I know that voice...
...but it can't be him.
Not unless he's a ghost.
Boo.
Johnny C.
I thought you got whacked!
-It must have been some other guy.
-Yeah?
Some other guy rat out Canelli too?
Hey, Canelli's a piece of shit.
I got no love for Canelli either.
But this time--
This time you went over the line, John.
I'm still here.
What you did was wrong.
What he did got a drug dealer
and his poison off the streets.
Who's the tree trunk?
This is the guy that saved my ass.
That's my cousin, Tony Two-Toes.
That's Sallie boy.
And that's Little Mike.
Your funeral was absolutely beautiful, man.
Listen, Canelli finds out he's still breathing--
Screw Canelli. We got bigger problems
than that. Tell him.
There's a major arms deal going down.
A U.S. contractor's selling out
to international terrorists.
[LAUGHING]
Mr. 60 Minutes. Tell me something
I don't know.
It's going to happen tonight
on your docks.
That I didn't know.
Quite a lot of security.
Expecting trouble?
-I'm a Boy Scout. Always be prepared.
-Is that why you brought her?
DEGUERIN: No. Just think of her
as an insurance policy...
...you know, in case
someone crashes the party.
Something you're not telling me?
DEGUERIN: Just a little bump in the carpet.
Nothing for you to worry about.
Relax, Sergei.
You'll be out of here in 20 minutes.
What do I do with her?
Whatever you want.
Once you're in international waters,
her policy expires.
Personally...
...I'd put a bullet in her head
and throw her overboard.
It would be such a shame.
Don't even think about it.
I think what I like and I do what I like.
You will soon learn about this.
Uh.
Last crate's on its way.
I'll leave you two lovebirds alone.
DeGuerin.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
This is Kruger. Get me Beller.
-Start a trace on this.
MAN: Yes, sir.
-John?
-I've got the proof.
Cyrez is selling weapons
on the black market.
Daniel Harper's in on it.
Undersecretary of Defense Harper?
Yes. DeGuerin is their facilitator.
He is the mole. It all goes down tonight.
Come and get me. Baltimore docks.
Pier 57.
BELLER:
John? John?
E.M.T., report.
Range is clear.
Not a creature is stirring.
MAN:
Clear on the south.
Quiet on the east.
All right, gentlemen, listen up.
This is the last load.
Keep your heads up
and your assholes puckered.
That son of a bitch is out there,
I want him.
JOHNNY:
Hey, sunshine. Whoa.
Give me a sec, I wanna talk to you.
This is a restricted area.
You're telling me. Let me ask you,
what the hell are you doing here?
-Excuse me?
-We're from the Local 129, sonny.
We heard you was loading a ship without
the assistance of bona fide union labor.
Say it ain't so.
-Sir, we have a situation here.
-You certainly do.
Stand by. We're coming to you.
-What the hell is going on here?
-Let me explain something to you, sonny.
Nothing moves off these docks
without it don't get loaded by the union.
And I don't see no union people
around here. Do you?
Gentlemen, this is a matter of national
security. Clear this area immediately.
-Are you threatening us?
-Absolutely.
[COCKS GUN]
-What the hell was that?
-We got gunfire at the warehouse!
Nobody screws with the union.
Perimeter, check in. If someone's there,
talk to me, goddamn it!
We have a security breach.
Well, check it out.
Get that crane on the move!
[WHISTLES]
I've got movement,
southwest corner of the warehouse.
It's nothing.
TONY:
There they are.
Commie bastards.
Actually, they're not
Communists anymore.
They're a federation
of independent, liberated states.
-Don't make me hurt you, Mikey.
JOHNNY: Quiet.
Keep your eyes
on those guys on that crane.
Think I can hit that guy from here?
Give it a rest, Sal. You're lucky
if you hit the floor if you fell on it.
-Got him. Thirty yards out.
-Fry the bastard.
Jesus Christ.
Fuck me.
DEGUERIN:
Okay.
-I think it's safe to say we got him.
-He's toast.
-I think we even got the roaches.
-Yeah. Royce, Somes, you're recon.
Bring me back the good news.
E.M. team, you cover them.
Roger.
JOHN:
Come on, goddamn it.
Nice shotgun, asshole.
No!
Royce?
Schiff! Calderon!
They missed.
-Johnny?
-I'll be right out.
Open fire!
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
It looks as if your friend has arrived.
I'll enjoy introducing him to you.
I doubt I'll have the pleasure.
He has forced me to hasten our departure.
And yours.
[MAN YELLING IN RUSSIAN]
John!
Goddamn it!
Now you are pissing me off!
Drop the guns.
Do it now.
Thanks.
-John!
-Shut up!
Take it up! Let's go, now!
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[SCREAMS]
JOHN:
Here. Grab the ladder.
Hold on.
Say goodbye, John.
Goodbye.
DEGUERIN:
John! John, buddy!
John! Don't let me go like this, man.
John, help me. John.
Son of a bitch!
MAN:
Drop the gun!
-All right, get him out of here!
-Yes, sir.
Thank you, John.
MAN 1: Ready? Let's go!
MAN 2: You got that end?
Come on!
John!
[CHATTERING]
MAN 1:
Mr. Undersecretary, Mr. Undersecretary.
MAN 2:
Mr. Undersecretary.
-How does it feel to be indicted for treason?
-We have nothing to say at this time.
Marshal DeGuerin.
Marshal DeGuerin, what about you?
-I'm proud of what I've done.
-You admit to treason?
I admit to patriotism.
Our actions stopped a secret alliance...
...that this administration has had
with some of our nation's worst enemies.
The public deserves to know the truth.
When we have our day in court, they will.
-That's all.
MAN 3: Yes, sir. What is your response--?
They could get away with this?
If Morehart takes the fall.
You did well in there.
I couldn't have done it
without you watching over me.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Pretty impressive speech.
You ought to learn to keep your
mouth shut in front of the press.
DEGUERIN:
It doesn't matter anyway.
This'll never go to trial
without her testimony.
-I'm not so convinced we should start again.
DEGUERIN: Why not?
With this bitch gone,
we can spin-doctor ourselves clean.
What about people she's been
in contact with, her friends, her family?
Fuck her family, fuck her friends.
I'll kill them one by one.
-By next year, she won't even be a memory.
-Robert, you never fail to amaze me.
Me? Thank you.
But you--
I gotta hand it to you, Danny boy.
That was a brilliant piece of work
you did back there.
-What are you talking about?
-The van.
It was beautiful.
I mean, it was clean, it was swift.
You got hundreds of witnesses
to say we were never near it.
I like your style.
You know, you remind me of me.
-Wait a minute, I thought you set that up.
-What? Didn't you--?
[TIRES SCREECH]
What the hell's going on up there?
-What the hell's going--?
-What is it?
Hey.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
It's for you.
-Yeah?
JOHN: You've just been erased.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
HARPER: Oh, my God!
DEGUERIN: Holy shit.
-Let me out of here! I don't wanna die!
-Break it!
Get the hell off of me!
What happened?
They caught a train.
[ENGLISH SDH]