[HONKS]
[BIRDS CHIRP]
[MONKEYS SCREECH]
[GASPS]
AAH! THIS PLACE GIVES ME
THE JUICEBUMPS.
[SQUEAKS]
MAYBE WE
SHOULD GO BACK.
VERY BACK!
Tommy: NO!
WE CAN'T GO BACK
NOW, YOU GUYS.
OKEY-DOKEY JONES
NEVER GOES BACK!
[SNARLING]
[GASPS]
HANG ON TO YOUR
DIAPIES, BABIES,
WE'RE GOIN' IN.
Chuckie: THAT'S TOMMY PICKLES.
[INDIANA JONES THEME PLAYS]
HE'S THE BRAVEST BABY
I EVER KNOWED.
AND THAT'S PHIL AND LIL,
UH, UH, WELL, THEY--THEY
LIKE WORMS,
AND I'M CHUCKIE. UH...
I'M NOT SO BRAVE.
BUT THAT'S OK,
'CAUSE I GOT TOMMY, AND
HE'S MY BESTEST FRIEND.
[GIGGLE]
[EXCITED CHATTER]
[STRAINING]
[STRAINS]
AAH!
WATCH OUT!
[SCREAMS]
IT'S RIGHT BEHIND US!
KEEP MOVING!
AAH!
[YELLS]
Chuckie: TOMMY!
HELP ME.
AAH!
COME ON, CHUCKIE!
[SCREAMS]
TOMMY!
YOU KIDS SHOULDN'T
BE PLAYING IN HERE.
[SCREAMS]
Chuckie: WE THOUGHT THE FUN
TIMES WOULD LAST FOREVER.
UNH.            UNH.
BUT WE WAS WRONG!
OH, MY.
[STRAINS]
UPSY-DAISY, DIDI.
THANKS.
THANK YOU INVITING ME
TO YOUR BABY SHOWER,
MRS. PICKLES.
GLAD YOU COULD
BE HERE, SUSIE.
WHAT A PRETTY PARTY DRESS,
ANGELICA.
THANK YOU.
MY MOMMY'S ASSISTANT
BOUGHT IT ESPECIALLY FOR
MY AUNT DIDI'S PARTY.
HEE HEE.
DON'T SAY A WORD.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT $20
ON 8 POUNDS, 6 OUNCES.
8 POUNDS, 6.
WHO'S GOT 8, 7?
12.
12 POUNDS?
WHAT ARE YOU, CRAZY?
GOSH, YOU CAN HARDLY TELL
SHE'S GAINED ANY WEIGHT.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
FROM BEHIND.
THERE YOU ARE, DIDALA.
[GERMAN ACCENT]
COME. LOOK WHAT WE GOT
FOR YOU.
BORIS, MOVE YOUR TUCKUS.
A GOAT?
[BLEATS]
OH, MOM, YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE.
NOTHING BETTER FOR
THE LITTLE BUBBALA
THAN GOAT'S MILK.
EXCEPT MAYBE YAK.
BUT YOU TRY FINDING
GOOD YAK THESE DAYS.
[BLEATS]
HE'S SAYING, "HELLO."
[LAUGHS]
THERE YOU GO,
KINDERWUND,
SOME CHOCOLATE COINS.
EVERYTHING, I--OOH!
AAH!
AREN'T YOU GONNA
EAT IT, TOMMY?
[LADY SCREAMS]
NOPE. I'M SAVIN' IT
FOR MY BABY SISTER.
OH, YOU MEAN,
SHE FINALLY CAME?
NOT YET, BUT THEY'RE
GIVING HER THIS BIG PARTY,
SO I'M PRETTY SURE
TODAY'S THE DAY.
DO YOU THINK SHE GOT LOSTED
ON HER WAY TO THE PARTY?
HMM, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE WE BETTER
GO LOOK FOR HER.
COME ON!
UH, BUT, TOMMY,
SHE COULD BE ANYWHERES.
WATCH IT, PUPS.
CAREFUL.
I'LL GET BACK
TO YOU, JONATHAN.
I'VE GOT TO SAY HI TO
THE LIFE OF THE PARTY.
HOW'S OUR LITTLE MAN?
I TOLD YOU, CHARLOTTE,
DR. LIPSCHITZ SAYS
IT'S A GIRL.
HA! THAT WINDBAG
THOUGHT PHIL AND LIL
WERE INTESTINAL GAS.
FACE IT, DOLLY.
RIDING HIGH, IT'S A GUY.
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY SAY,
"BORN UNDER VENUS,
LOOK FOR A--"
[RINGS]
HELLO?
NOW, NOW, DR. LIPSCHITZ
IS THE EXPERT.
I DON'T SEE ANY OF YOU
WITH A Ph.D. IN LATIN.
YEAH, PIG LATIN MAYBE.
WELL, LET'S JUST HOPE FOR
TOMMY'S SAKE IT'S A GIRL.
I'D HATE TO THINK HOW MUCH
MY PUPS WOULD BE SQUABBLING
IF THEY WERE BOTH BOYS.
UH-UH-UH.
LET'S NOT DO ANY
GENDER STEREOTYPING.
AFTER ALL, STU AND
DREW ARE BROTHERS,
AND THEY GET ALONG
JUST FINE.
PUSHY!
LAZY!
BOSSY!
INCONSIDERATE!
NOSY!
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING!
BUSY-BODY.
Stu and Drew:
WHY CAN'T YOU LISTEN TO ME?
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
A REAL JOB, STU,
WITH BENEFITS.
I'M NOT GOING
TO WASTE MY LIFE
AS A CLOCK-PUNCHING,
PAPER-PUSHING,
BEAN-COUNTING...
[GASPS]
OH, NO OFFENSE.
YOU CAN'T EVEN
MAKE ENDS MEET NOW.
YOU GOT NO INSURANCE,
NO SAVINGS,
AND ANOTHER KID ON THE WAY!
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, BRO,
I AM WORKING ON
SOMETHING RIGHT NOW
THAT IS GOING TO PUT THIS
BRANCH OF THE PICKLES FAMILY
ON EASY STREET.
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME,
HUH,
AN ELECTRIC SPONGE?
OF COURSE NOT!
THAT WAS LAST YEAR.
THIS, THIS IS
THE REPTAR WAGON!
THE ULTIMATE IN TODDLER
TRANSPORTATION.
THE PERFECT CHILDREN'S TOY!
IN MY DAY,
WE HAD PLENTY OF FUN
JUST THROWING ROCKS
AT EACH OTHER.
BIG BAG OF DIRT CLODS,
THAT'S WHAT THE KIDS
WANT.
THE REPTAR CORPORATION IS
HOLDING A TOY DESIGN CONTEST,
AND THE WINNER GETS $500!
OOH!
AND THERE'LL BE PLENTY
MORE IF THIS TOY'S A HIT,
AND I'LL BE FAMOUS!
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID
WHEN YOU BUILT
THAT STUPID THING.
MAYBE DUCKTAR
WAS A LITTLE COMPLEX,
BUT THIS...THIS...WATCH!
I AM REPTAR!
HEAR ME ROAR!
[IN LOUD ROBOTIC VOICE]
I AM REPTAR!
HEAR ME ROAR!
DANG-FLABBIT! CAN'T A MAN
WORK IN HIS OWN BASEMENT
WITHOUT GETTING BARBECUED?
OK, SO MAYBE REAL FIRE
ISN'T THE BEST IDEA
FOR A CHILDREN'S TOY.
[RUGRATS GASP]
Chuckie: TOMMY, SOMEBODY'S
BEEN COLORING YOUR ROOM.
YEP, IT'S FOR
MY NEW SISTER.
HOW ARE WE GONNA
FIND HER, TOMMY?
YEAH, WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT SHE LOOKS LIKE.
WELL, SHE'S A GIRL
LIKE ME,
SO WE KNOW
SHE'LL BE PRETTYFUL.
OH, BROTHER!
YOU DUMB BABIES
GOT A LOT TO LEARN
ABOUT THE FACTS
OF LIFE.
NOW, GET OUT
OF MY WAY.
I GOTTA GET BACK
TO THE DESSERT TABLE
BEFORE THE GROWNUPS
GET ALL THE GOOD STUFF.
ANGELICA, CAN YOU HELP US
FIND MY BABY SISTER?
I WOULDN'T BE
IN SUCH A BIG HURRY
IF I WAS YOU, TOMMY.
'CAUSE WHEN
THE NEW BABY GETS HERE,
SHE'S GONNA GET ALL
THE TOYS AND THE LOVE
AND THE ATTENTION.
AND YOUR MOMMY AND DADDY'LL
FORGET ALL ABOUT YOU.
IT'LL BE LIKE, "LOOK, DID...
THERE'S THAT LITTLE BALD KID
IN THE HOUSE AGAIN."
MY MOMMY AND DADDY
WON'T FORGET ME.
THAT'S WHAT SPIKE SAID
BEFORE YOU WERE BORN.
BACK WHEN HIS NAME
WAS PAUL.
Tommy: PAUL?
YEAH, BUT THEN YOU
CAME ALONG,
AND THEY PUT HIM OUT
IN THE RAIN,
AND HE TURNED INTO
A DOG.
THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN
TO ME, ANGELICA.
MY MOMMY AND DADDY WILL
LOVE ME NO MATTER WHAT!
♪ A BABY IS
REALLY NEAT ♪
A SPECIAL TREAT ♪
UGH! WHO DOES SUSIE
CARMICHAEL THINK SHE IS?
Susie: ♪ A BABY
HAS A FUNNY NOSE ♪
♪ A BABY IS
A LITTLE DICKENS ♪
A CUDDLY CHICKEN ♪
♪ A BABY IS LOTS OF JOY ♪
♪ A BABY WILL GET
ALL THE TOYS ♪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
♪ A BABY HAS A SMILEY FACE ♪
♪ A BABY IS FROM
OUTSIDE SPACE ♪
ANGELICA!
SUSIE!
♪ A BABY IS EXTRA FANCY ♪
♪ A BABY POOPS
IN HIS PANTSIES ♪
ANGIE, GET OUT!
NO!
♪ LIKE A BIRDIE ♪
♪ SINGING IN A TREE ♪
♪ MORE LIKE REPTAR ♪
♪ SCREAMING IN YOUR EAR ♪
Susie and Angelica:
♪ A BABY IS A GIFT ♪
♪ A GIFT FROM A BOB ♪
♪ FROM A BOB, BOB, BOB ♪
♪ A BABY IS A GIFT ♪
♪ A GIFT FROM A BOB ♪
DO YOU REALLY THINK BABIES
ARE A GIFT FROM A BOB?
I DON'T KNOW. WHY?
BECAUSE IF BOB
BRINGED A GIFT,
IT'S PROBABLY ONE OF THEM.
Susie: ♪ A BABY
IS VERY SPECIAL.
♪ A BABY IS, IS NOTTT! ♪
OH!
BETTY, IT'S TIME!
IT'S TIME? OH, BOY.
EVERYBODY TO YOUR STATIONS,
PEOPLE!
HOWARD, GET STU.
CHARLOTTE,
CALL THE HOSPITAL.
DIDI, START YOUR BREATHING.
COME ON, GOOD GIRL.
UP WE GO, SPROUT.
WE GOT A PICKLE
TO DELIVER.
Woman: WE'RE GOING
TO THE CAR, KIDS.
[BAAAA]
WILL SOMEBODY TURN
THAT SPRINKLER OFF?!
NOW, THAT'S WHAT
I CALL A BABY SHOWER!
WELCOME TO THE
WERNER P. LIPSCHITZ CENTER
FOR HOLISTIC BIRTHING,
OFFERING THE MODERN PARENT
THE STATE OF THE ART IN
PRIMITIVE BIRTH ALTERNATIVES.
[DIDI DOES
LAMAZE BREATHING]
OH, MRS. PICKLES!
YOU WEREN'T DUE TILL
NEXT WEEK, NOW, DEAR.
WELL, I GUESS
WE COULD TRY
AND SQUEEZE YOU IN
SOMEWHERE.
BUT DR. LIPSCHITZ
PROMISED US
THE ALL-NATURAL
ZEN EXPERIENCE
IN THE TIBETAN
TERRACE ROOM!
IN MY DAY, A WOMAN
JUST DROPPED HER BABY
IN THE POTATO FIELD
AND KEPT GOING.
AH, YES,
THE OLD COUNTRY ROOM.
Didi: DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
A LITTLE CLEANER?
WE COULD TRY THE AQUATIC
IMMERSION ROOM.
[DOES LAMAZE BREATHING]
SHE'S HAVING A BABY,
NOT A GEFILTE FISH.
[BELL RINGS]
OH! STU, DIDI, RANDY CALLED
TO SAY YOU WERE ON YOUR WAY.
[LAUGHS]
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE
BRINGING THE WHOLE PARTY!
HOW FAR APART
ARE THE PAINS, HON?
OH, THEY'RE...
PRETTY MUCH
CONSTANT.
OK, DIDI, LET'S GO
AND GET YOU
SETTLED IN, HUH?
HERE YOU GO, SPROUT.
[DIDI CONTINUES
LAMAZE BREATHING]
DON'T WORRY, SWEETIE,
MOMMY'S GOING TO BE OK.
[CONTINUES
LAMAZE BREATHING]
Chuckie: OH, GOSH, TOMMY,
YOUR MOMMY SURE SEEMS UPSET.
MAYBE YOUR BABY SISTER
REALLY IS LOSTED.
WHOA!
MAYBE WE CAN BUY HER
A NEW ONE.
WHERE'RE WE GONNA FIND A BABY
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
[BABIES CRYING]
YOU GOT ANY QUEENS?
GO FISH.
[BABIES CRYING]
P.A.: PLEASE REPORT
TO INTENSIVE CARE.
[RUGRATS GASP]
HEY, A BABY STORE.
NICE AND WIGGLY.
YOU GUYS, HELP ME PICK
ONE MY MOM WILL LIKE.
[CRYING]
♪ WHERE AM I? ♪
♪ HOW DID I GET HERE? ♪
♪ TODAY IS DIFFERENT
THAN YESTERDAY ♪
SO THIS IS THE WORLD?
I MISS MY OLD WOMB.
THIS WALLPAPER HERE
JUST AIN'T THE SAME.
THIS WORLD IS
SOMETHING STRANGE!
♪ I'M WET ♪
♪ I'M COLD ♪
♪ I NEED A CHANGE ♪
Babies: ♪ THIS WORLD
IS SOMETHING NEW TO ME ♪
Baby boy: OH, MY HEAD.
WHAT IS THIS?
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
ME, EITHER.
I'M HUNGRY.
I'M TIRED.
I'M IRRITATED.
I LOVE THE
EXTRA LEG ROOM.
MAN, THEY CUT MY CORD.
CONSIDER YOURSELF LUCKY!
♪ THIS WORLD
IS WAY TOO BIG ♪
♪ AND POPULATED
BY FUZZY PIGS ♪
♪ THIS WORLD IS SOMETHING
NEW TO ME ♪
THIS WORLD IS SUCH A GAS.
♪ P.U.,
WHERE'S YOUR CLASS? ♪
♪ THIS WORLD IS SOMETHING
NEW TO ME ♪
QUIET!
CAN'T A GUY
GET SOME SHUTEYE?
IT'S SO NOISY IN HERE!
I CAN BARELY
HEAR MYSELF SUCK!
FOOD HERE TASTES PRETTY GOOD.
MY COMPLIMENTS
TO THE CHEF.
♪ AND YOU GOTTA HOLLER
TO GET FED ♪
BUT I COULD
GET USED TO THAT.
[BABIES YELLING]
♪ THIS WORLD IS WAY
TOO BRIGHT ♪
♪ CAN SOMEBODY TURN
DOWN THE LIGHT? ♪
SO THAT'S WHAT THAT
THING LOOKS LIKE.
♪ ALL THINGS HERE
ARE MEANT FOR PLAY ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA BE
A REAL COOL DAY ♪
♪ THIS WORLD IS SOMETHING
NEW TO ME ♪
[SCREAM]
[BABIES HUM]
Baby boy: REAL COOL!
[GASPS]
[BABIES HUM]
♪ THIS WORLD IS
SOMETHING NEW TO ME ♪
THERE YOU ARE.
OY, GEVALT!
YOU KINDER GAVE MY
TICKER SUCH A SCARE.
[BEEPS]
[DIDI DOES
LAMAZE BREATHING]
ALL RIGHT, DIDI,
YOU CAN DO IT. PUSH!
HAVE WE GOT A GOOD
READING ON THE E.F.M.?
AAH!
HERE IT COMES.
GORGEOUS!
DIDI, SHE'S SO
BEAUTIFUL.
SHE'S--SHE'S A BOY!
[BABY CRIES]
HELLO, MY WONDERFUL,
SWEET BABY BOY.
Stu: WELL, I GUESS
WE WON'T BE NAMING HIM
AFTER MY MOTHER.
HE DOESN'T LOOK
MUCH LIKE A TRIXIE.
WHAT ABOUT MY COUSIN DILLON?
DILLON PRESCOTT
PICKLES.
DIL PICKLES.
YEAH, I LIKE IT.
HERE YOU GO, SPROUT.
TOMMY, I WANT YOU TO MEET
SOMEONE VERY SPECIAL.
THIS IS YOUR BROTHER
DILLON.
DIL, THIS IS TOMMY.
[GASPS]
BABY...
SEE, THEY ALREADY
LOVE EACH OTHER.
[HICCUP]
WAAH!
WELL, THAT'S A START.
[BABY CRYING]
[CRIES]
DIDI, WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
HE HASN'T STOPPED CRYING
SINCE WE BROUGHT HIM
HOME.
SOMEHOW IT'S NOT AS MUCH
FUN AROUND HERE ANYMORE.
YEAH! WHAT IS YOUR
BROTHER SO SAD ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW!
BUT WHATEVER IT IS...
IT MUST BE REALLY BAD.
MAYBE HE'S BROKED!
WHAT?
BROKED!
[BABY CRYING]
HE'S NOT BROKED. HE'S A...
JUST A LITTLE LOUD!
THAT BABY'S
GETTING ON MY NERVES.
[SNORES]
Announcer:
DIRECT FROM MOSCOW,
THE BANANA BROTHERS
MONKEY CIRCUS!
FEATURING THE MOST
AMAZING MONKEY
SINCE BREZHNEV!
THIS IS REAL
MONKEY BUSINESS,
SO TROTSKY ON DOWN.
THE BANANA BROTHERS
MONKEY CIRCUS!
GRANDPA! CAN WE GO
TO THE CIRCUS?
[BLEATS]
IT'S ENOUGH OF A CIRCUS
AROUND HERE ALREADY.
[CHUGGING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Station Master:
ARRIVING ON TRACK ONE.
SERGEI, YOU STAY HERE
AND WATCH MONKEYS,
I GET US COFFEE.
NO, IGOR, YOU STAY
AND WATCH MONKEYS,
AND I GET US COFFEE.
NYET! MONKEYS WATCH YOU,
I GET COFFEE.
[SLURPS]
I THINK COFFEE'S BETTER
IN ST. PETERSBURG.
NYET, IS BETTER IN KIEV.
NO, IT'S BETTER
IN ST. PETERSBURG.
NOTHING IS BETTER
[CRASH]
LOOK! THE TRAIN!
LET ME OUT!
[SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
STOP!
[SHRIEKING]
[BELL RINGS]
[SHRIEKS]
[WHIMPERS]
Didi: AND THEN
THE WIZARD LOOKED DOWN
AT THE LITTLE BOY AND SAID,
"YOUR WISH
HAS BEEN GRANTED."
AND THE LITTLE BOY LOOKED--
Stu: DIDI!
[CRIES]
HELP!
I'LL BE BACK, SWEETIE.
Stu: ALL I DID
WAS COUGH, DID.
I TRIED NOT TO,
BUT I HAD A FEELING
IN MY THROAT.
AND THEN I COUGHED!
AND NOW HE'S CRYING!
AND NOW HE'S GOT
THE HICCUPS!
[BAWLS]
OH, STU.
STU, WHY DON'T YOU SING
DIL A LULLABY?
I'M TOO TIRED TO SING.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL MAKE SOMETHING UP.
GOOD.
♪ BABY, PLEASE ♪
♪ REST YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ NOW IT IS
TIME FOR BED ♪
THAT'S GOOD.
THANKS.
♪ YOU'RE
CUTER THAN ♪
♪ UNCLE NED ♪
♪ OUR LITTLE ♪
UH...QUADRIPED?
OH, STU.
OH, YEAH.
Didi: IT DIDN'T WORK.
Stu: I KNOW.
HE'S STILL AWAKE.
I GOT ONE. I GOT ONE.
OK.
♪ TWINKLE, TWINKLE ♪
♪ HOW TIME FLIES ♪
♪ SLOWLY IN THE
STARRY SKIES ♪
♪ BABY, PLEASE ♪
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES ♪
♪ YOU'RE AS SWEET AS ♪
♪ APPLE PIES ♪
Didi: ♪ AS YOU GROW ♪
♪ AND LOVE AND PLAY ♪
Stu:
♪ IN OUR HEARTS ♪
♪ YOU'LL
ALWAYS STAY ♪
♪ SO SLEEP
AND DREAM THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AWAY ♪
AH, THAT WAS GOOD.
♪ BABY, PLEASE ♪
♪ REST YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ NOW IT IS ♪
♪ TIME FOR BED ♪
♪ PLEASE STOP ♪
♪ DON'T YOU SEE? ♪
♪ I WANT MOM AND DAD ♪
♪ FOR ME ♪
[HICCUP]
[HOWLS]
[BABY CRIES]
OH, DARN IT.
AH-CHOO!
HEY, SPROUTS,
CRATE'S NO PLACE
FOR YOU TO PLAY.
YOU WOULDN'T WANT
TO GET SHIPPED TO JAPAN
WITH REPTAR,
NOW WOULD YOU?
I BETTER PUT THIS
WHERE I CAN KEEP
AN EYE ON IT.
DIL,
THAT'S TOMMY'S
BLANKIE.
YEAH, IT USED
TO SLEEP WITH ME
BEFORE WE
EVEN GOT YOU!
[LAUGHS AND GURGLES]
[CRACK]
MY BLANKIE!
HE'S NOT VERY NICE.
OW!
Lil: THAT'S NOT
HOW YOU GET THINGS
FROM A BROTHER, TOMMY.
Tommy: IS NOT?
IT IS NOT. HERE, WATCH.
HEY, THAT'S MY REPTAR, LILY!
IS NOT, PHILLIP!
IS...TOO, LILLIAN.
IS NOT!
IS, TOO!
SEE, TOMMY,
NOW YOU TRY IT.
[SQUEALS]
Dil: TEDDY MINE!
MINE!
GOSH, TOMMY LEARNS FAST.
YEAH.
[STRAINS]
Stu: HURRY, POP,
THEY'LL BE HERE TO
PICK IT UP ANY MINUTE.
Angelica: DADDY, WHY CAN'T
I WATCH SHIRLEYLOCK HOLMES
AT OUR HOUSE?
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO HEAR
IT WITH THAT NEW BABY
SQUAWKING THE WHOLE TIME!
NOW, SWEETHEART,
DADDY'S GOT TO PUT IN
A LITTLE OVERTIME TODAY,
SO THAT MOMMY
WON'T BE SO ASHAMED
OF HIS QUARTERLY
EARNINGS.
HI, UNCLE STU.
SORRY TO HEAR YOUR PONY
IS SO SLOW.
UH, WE DON'T HAVE A PONY,
ANGELICA.
THEN HOW COME
YOU TOLD MOMMY
AUNT DIDI GOT SADDLED
WITH A LOSER.
[GASPS]
"LOSER"?
HE--HE...
EXCUSE ME, BRO.
MY TAX DEDUCTIONS
ARE CRYING!
YOU CAN'T DEDUCT THEM
IF YOU DON'T
HAVE ANY INCOME.
[BABIES STRAINING]
OHH.
TOMMY! DIL!
BOYS, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
OHH.
DIL...
WHAT SAY WE GIVE TOMMY
A LITTLE TURN
WITH THE BEAR, HUH?
WAAH!
OR NOT.
HEY, CHAMP,
WHY DON'T YOU COME
WITH ME FOR A MINUTE?
I GOT SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU
THAT'S EVEN BETTER
THAN YOUR OLD TEDDY BEAR.
[YAWNS]
WE WEREN'T GOING
TO GIVE YOU THIS
UNTIL YOU WERE
A LITTLE BIT OLDER,
BUT I THINK NOW'S
THE RIGHT TIME.
SHINY, HUH?
AND GRANDPA LOU
PUT YOUR PICTURE INSIDE.
[TICKS]
I KNOW IT'S HARD, TOMMY.
YOU HAVE
A LITTLE BROTHER NOW,
AND THAT'S A BIG CHANGE.
UH, DIL
CAN BE PRETTY TOUGH
TO GET ALONG WITH, HUH?
BUT SOMETIMES
LITTLE BROTHERS,
THEY AREN'T EVERYTHING
YOU'D HOPED THEY'D BE.
THAT'S WHY BIG BROTHERS
HAVE GOT TO HAVE FAITH.
AND ONE DAY,
YOU'LL SEE...
HE'LL CHANGE.
AFTER ALL,
YOU'VE GOT
RESPONSIBILITY NOW.
I KNOW I CAN TRUST THAT
YOU'LL STICK BY DIL'S SIDE
AND BE A SWELL BIG BROTHER.
[THINKS]
SPONSATILITY.
[BLEATS]
[RUGRATS GASP]
WHAT IS THAT, YOU GUYS?
Lil: REPTAR!
ON WHEELS!
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT'S FOR?
I DON'T KNOW.
I BET IT COULD TAKE
US TO THE BABY STORE.
GREAT IDEA, LILLIAN.
WE COULD TAKE DIL
TO THE HOPSICLE
AND GET TOMMY'S MONEY BACK.
YEAH, DO IT.
IT'S MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
GUYS!
GUYS, TOMMY'S NOT GONNA
BE HAPPY ABOUT THIS.
WELL, HE'S SURE NOT
HAPPY NOW.
WELL...
YOU WATCH.
ONCE DIL GOES BACK
TO THE BABY STORE,
TOMMY WILL BE HAPPY.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
[HUMMING]
[GASPS]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE, UH, ACTUALLY,
LILLIAN WAS, UH--
WE'RE TAKING DIL BACK
TO THE HOPSICLE, TOMMY.
WE'RE GONNA GET
YOUR MONEYS BACK.
WHAT? YOU CAN'T
DO THAT.
MY MOMMY AND DADDY
WANNA KEEP HIM.
SEE? SEE?
WHY? ALL HE DOES
IS CRY AND POOP.
SO DO YOU.
I DON'T CRY THAT MUCH.
WELL, YOU POOP
AN AWFUL LOT.
LOOK WHO'S TALKING,
MR. CHOCOLATE PANTS.
I AM NOT A POOPIE MONSTER!
TV: SHIRLEYLOCK HOLMES,
GIRL DETECTIVE,
RIGHT AFTER THESE MESSAGES.
TOMMY!
WELL, I'M NOT.
HEY, BABIES. KNOCK IT OFF!
CYNTHIA AND ME ARE TRYING
TO WATCH TV.
HUH?
HEY, HANDS OFF
THE MERCHANDISE, PINKIE.
PRETTY GOOD.
[GROWLING]
BE NICE, ANGELICA.
HE DIDN'T MEAN IT.
YOU WANNA RIDE
IN A WAGON?
I'LL GIVE YOU A RIDE
TO OUTSIDE SPACE!
OW!
MY SHOW!
NEXT COMMERCIAL, YOU BABIES
ARE IN BIG TROUBLE!
Lil: ALL ABOARD.
JUST WALK AWAY, CHUCKIE.
WALK AWAY.
OOH! WAIT FOR ME!
Phil: WHICH WAY
TO THE HOPSICLE?
Tommy: WE'RE NOT GOING
TO THE HOPSICLE!
Chuckie: WELL,
WE'RE GOING SOMEWHERES!
[SNORING]
UH, PARDON ME.
PICKUP FOR PICKLES
TO JAPAN?
TAKE IT AWAY,
TAKE IT AWAY.
[SNORING]
YEAH, HAVE
A GOOD DAY.
[BARKING]
PIPE DOWN, SPIKE!
ME AND CYNTHIA ARE WATCHING...
[GASPS]
CYNTHIA?!
NICE TRY, BABIES.
NOW GIVE ME BACK MY...
[GASPING]
CYNTHIA!
[CRASH]
THEY TOOK CYNTHIA. SPIKE!
COME ON!
YOU'RE GONNA
BE MY BUTTHOUND!
WE GOTTA SEARCH
EVERY DOGHOUSE,
PLAYHOUSE,
TREE HOUSE,
AND DOLLHOUSE!
I WANT THOSE
FOOGITIVES
BACK IN CUSTARDY.
[BARKING]
WHOAAH!
BAD DOG! BAD DOG!
STOP!
DID, JUST TO THE SPA
AND RELAX.
POP AND I ARE DOING FINE
TAKING CARE OF THE--
POP? W--WHERE'S THE CRATE?
OH, I GUESS
THE DELIVERY FOLKS
MUST HAVE COME.
WOW. THEY LOADED HER UP
AND EVERYTHING, HUH?
SURE, I'LL LET YOU TALK
TO TOMMY.
POP...UH...UH,
WHERE ARE THE KIDS?
THAT'S FUNNY.
THEY WERE HERE
A MINUTE AGO,
PLAYING IN THE...
Both: THE CRATE!
HONEY,
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO CALL YOU BACK.
[RAP SONG PLAYS]
WHOAA!
HOW COULD YOU
FALL ASLEEP
WHEN YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE
WATCHING THE KIDS?!
[SNORING]
WE'LL NEVER FIND
THE BABIES
WITH THIS JERK
IN FRONT OF US!
[HONKS HORN]
Phil: THIS IS MORE FUN
THAN PICKING NOSES!
OR MAKING BUBBLES
IN THE BATHTUB.
I DON'T KNOW IF
I SHOULD THROW UP
OR THROW DOWN!
PHEW!
I'VE TURNED THIS
PLANE UPSIDE DOWN,
AND I ASSURE YOU
THERE ARE
NO CHILDREN.
NO.
WE FOUND A KID,
BUT HE'S NOT THE ONE
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
Goat: BAAAA.
TOMMY!
SPROUT?
DIL!
ANGELICA?
WHERE CAN THEY BE?
WE GOTTA FIND THEM!
FIND WHAT?
[GASPS]
EINSTEIN HERE LOST THE KIDS.
I LOST THE KIDS?
SEE?
[RUGRATS EXCLAIM IN WONDER]
Chuckie:
WHERE ARE WE?
Tommy: I DON'T KNOW.
IT LOOKS KINDA LIKE
THE PARK.
Lil: ONLY BIGGERER.
BIGGERER? THIS
PLACE IS BIGGER
THAN THE PARK
AND THE BACKYARD
ALL PUT TOGETHER.
THIS IS BAD,
YOU GUYS.
THIS IS BAD.
OH, TOMMY, I THINK YOUR BROTHER
IS BROKED AGAIN.
OH, NO. DIL,
ARE YOU OK?
Phil: I THINK
HE'S GONNA EXPLODE.
POOPIE.
WHAT?!
[GROANING]
POOPIE!
All: EUW!
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL HAVE
TO CHANGE HIS DIAPIE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WE?
[POLICE SIRENS]
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LEFT THEM
WITH YOUR FATHER.
THE MAN SLEPT THROUGH
PEARL HARBOR, FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE.
I SOUNDED THE ALARM
AS SOON AS I COULD.
MRS. PICKLES, DID YOUR SON
HAVE ANY ENEMIES?
[GASPS]
UH-HUH. ANY UNDERWORLD
OR MOB CONNECTIONS?
HE IS A BABY!
[COUGHING]
THE POWDER GOES
ON HIS BOTTOM, TOMMY!
WELL, I'M DOING
THE BEST I CAN.
Dil: PEE-PEE.
LOOK OUT!
STOP IT, DIL.
GET OFF ME!
AAH! FROG, FROG!
YOUR BROTHER MADE
A FROG JUMP ON ME!
STOP IT.
YOU STOP IT!
HEY, GUYS, MAYBE WE SHOULD
STOP PLAYING AROUND
AND FIGURE OUT HOW
TO GET HOME.
BUT, TOMMY, WE DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHERE WE ARE.
I KNOW. I'VE GOT
MY SPONSATIVITY!
WHAT'S A SPONSATIVITY,
TOMMY?
SOUNDS YUCKY.
NO, IT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR BEING A BIG BROTHER.
IT'S JUST LIKE
OKEY-DOKEY JONES USES
WHEN HE HAS TO FIND
HIS WAY HOME.
I THOUGHT THAT'S
CALLED A CRUMPUS.
WELL, MY DAD GAVE IT TO ME,
AND HE CALLED IT
A SPONSATIVITY.
WHERE'S IT SAY
TO GO?
WELL, UM, UH, HMM.
THIS WAY.
UH...
[GASPING]
THAT'S THE WAY!
STRAIGHT UP THAT HILL!
AAH! BAD DOG, BAD DOG!
STOP!
[SNIFFING]
AAH!
[WHIMPERS]
YOU KNOW, NOT ALL
DOGS GO TO HEAVEN.
[WHIMPERS]
MR. PICKLES, IS IT TRUE
YOU SHIPPED
YOUR OWN CHILDREN TO TOKYO
IN A WOODEN BOX?
IS IT TRUE A DINGO
ATE YOUR BABY?
MR. PICKLES,
HOW MANY PECKS
OF PICKLED PEPPERS
DID YOU PICK?
CHILDHOOD, A TIME OF INNOCENCE,
A TIME OF JOY.
A TIME OF UNSPEAKABLE,
UNRELENTING TRAGEDY.
MRS. PICKLES, TELL
US HOW IT FEELS
TO KNOW YOU MAY
NEVER SEE
YOUR CHILDREN
AGAIN.
CRIMINY! CAN'T YOU PIT BULLS
SHOW SOME COMPASSION?
I'M SO SORRY.
FORGIVE ME.
PLEASE TELL US
HOW IT FEELS
TO KNOW YOU MAY NEVER SEE
YOUR CHILDREN AGAIN?
GET HIM!
LET ME AT HIM!
ALL RIGHT!
HOLD ON, JONATHAN.
THERE'S AN ALARMING CROWD
AT MY IN-LAW'S
INDICATING EITHER A YARD SALE
OR A FAMILY TRAGEDY.
LET ME GET BACK TO YOU.
HEY, MR. PICKLES,
HOW DOES IT FEEL
KNOWING YOUR
BROTHER LOST
YOUR ONLY DAUGHTER?
HE WHAT?!
SHARE YOUR PAIN.
YEOW!
YOU'RE BREAKING MY ARM!
ONLY 'CAUSE I CAN'T
REACH YOUR NECK!
AND THERE
YOU HAVE IT.
2 SOUR PICKLES
AND YOUNG TAMMY,
BABY DALE, THE TWINS
BILL AND JILL,
LITTLE CHUNKY,
AND POOR AMELIA,
ALL VANISHED WITHOUT A TRACE.
I'M REX PESTER,
AND I'LL BE BACK
WITH MORE BIG ACTION NEWS.
MR. SWENSON SAID HE SAW
ANGELICA AND SPIKE
RUN THROUGH HIS GARDEN
AND HEAD NORTH ON I-99!
Charlotte: MY BABY!
LET'S GO!
PRIVATE FIRST CLASS PICKLES
REPORTING FOR DUTY.
JUST GET IN.
COME ON.
GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
GOOD, DIL. NOW, PLAY NICE.
[BONK]
NOT MUCH FUN
BACK THERE, IS IT?
OH, WE'RE DOING OK.
THAT'S SOME GOOD
HITTIN' THERE, DILLY.
[BONK]
I'M HUNGRY.
RIGHT ABOUT NOW
MY DADDY'D
BE MAKING ME
A FRIED BOLOGNA
SANDWICH.
I CAN ALMOST SMELL
THAT BURNING.
OOH, IT TASTES
ALL CRUNCHY.
STOP IT, CHUCKIE.
YOU'RE MAKING ME HUNGRY.
[ALL GASP]
OH, NO!
WE CAN'T SEE OUR HOUSES
FROM HERE, TOMMY.
Phil: WE CAN'T SEE
ANY HOUSES FROM HERE.
WE'RE DOOMED!
DOOMED.
DOOMED, I TELL YOU!
[ANIMAL SNARLING]
MRS. PICKLES, I KNOW
THIS IS HARD FOR YOU,
BUT CAN YOU IDENTIFY
THIS BINKY?
[CRYING]
DIL'S FAULT,
THIS IS ALL
RIGHT, CHUCKIE?
UH-UH. THIS NEVER WOULD
HAVE HAPPENED
IF YOU HADN'T PUTTED HIM IN
THE WAGON IN THE FIRST PLACE,
RIGHT, CHUCKIE?
UH-UH.
IT'S NOT OUR FAULT
YOU GOT A BAD, NAUGHTY,
STINKY BABY FOR A BROTHER!
HE'S NOT NAUGHTY.
HE'S JUST A--
HE'S JUST A--A BABY!
HOW COULD YOU BE MAD JUST
BECAUSE YOU'RE, UM...
STANDING THERE ALL NAKIE?
I MEAN, I'M SURE HE'S
JUST TRYING TO HELP.
AND 'SIDES, IT'S HOT,
'SPLORING IN THE WOODS
ALL DAY.
AH! A LITTLE BREEZE
FEELS GOOD.
JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
OH, THANK YOU, DIL.
[HICCUPS]
THOSE HICCUPS ARE REALLY
STARTING TO BUG ME.
FACE IT, TOMMY.
HAVING A BABY BROTHER
JUST ISN'T WHAT
YOU EXPECTED.
HEY, YOU GUYS,
LOOK.
SOMEBODY'S HOUSE.
TOMMY WAS RIGHT.
WOW. MY SPONSATIVITY
DOES WORK.
YEAH, BUT WHO'D
HAVE A HOUSE
WAY OUT HERE
IN THE FOREST?
Tommy: MAYBE A LIZARD
LIVES THERE.
A LIZARD!
YOU KNOW, A--A BIG GUY
WITH A POINTY HAT
THAT GRANTS WISHES.
ALL'S WE GOTS TO DO
IS KNOCK ON THE DOOR
AND SAY WE WANNA GO HOME.
SEE? THEN EVERYTHING
WILL BE BACK TO NORMAN.
THANK BOB!
THANK YOU, BOB.
COME ON, GUYS!
WE'RE OFF TO SEE
THE LIZARD.
OH, TOMMY,
ARE YOU OK?
I'M FINE. I JUST TRIPPED
IN A LITTLE HOLE,
THAT'S ALL.
Chuckie: GOSH,
IT LOOKS KINDA
LIKE SPIKE'S FEET,
ONLY IF HE WAS
A GIANT.
I SAW FEETPRINTS LIKE THAT
IN OUR STORYBOOK.
A WOLF MADE THEM,
AND THEN HE ATE THAT
LITTLE RED RIDING GIRL.
THE WOLF ATE A GIRL?
THEY GOT HER OUT.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S A WOLF, CHUCKIE.
IF IT WAS, WE'D HEAR HIM SAY--
[ANIMAL HOWLING]
THAT WAS
PRETTY GOOD.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
[ANIMAL HOWLING]
All: AAH!
DO YOU SEE THE WOLF?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HE LOOKS LIKE.
TEETH!
TEETH AND FUR!
AND TEETH!
NO, DIL!
BAD DIL.
MARGARET?
THAT'S YOUR
NAME, ISN'T IT?
I'M SURE YOU'VE
RUN AFOUL
OF MANY A SCARY
PEDESTRIAN.
BUT OUT HERE,
WE HAVE
WHAT YOU MIGHT
CALL--
HMM, HOW SHOULD
I PUT IT?
ACTUAL DANGER.
DANGER?
GRIZZLIES
THAT'LL RIP
THE TOP OFF
YOUR CAR.
BOBCATS, WOLVES,
WOLVERINES,
WHICH ARE SOMETHING
ENTIRELY DIFFERENT.
AND DRAGONS. AAH!
TOMMY, I SAW
SOME GROWNUPS.
STOP! STOP!
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
WELL, I HOPE YOU
FIGURE IT OUT,
'CAUSE I DIDN'T BRING
NO BATHING SUIT!
AAH!
ANY FURTHER, AND I WOULD
HAVE NEEDED A FRESH DIAPIE.
DIL, NO!
AAH!
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Reptar: AQUA REPTAR ENGAGED.
Margaret:
I'M TELLING YOU,
I SAW A DRAGON.
MARGARET.
A BIG GREEN,
FIRE-BREATHING
DRAGON.
I'VE GOT TO CALL
HEADQUARTERS.
WHILE YOU'RE
AT IT,
YOU MIGHT ASK FOR
A NEW ASSIGNMENT,
SAY, A CITY PARK.
'CAUSE, YOU SEE, OUT
HERE IN THE COUNTRY,
YOU HAVE TO BE JUST
A LITTLE TOUGHER.
AAH! AAH!
THE DRAGON! I JUST SAW IT!
I SAW IT!
WHERE? WHERE?
HERE? WHERE?
Lou: BINGO.
LOOKIE HERE.
A WRAPPER FROM
A CYNTHIA
SWEET BAR.
MY ANGEL!
SHE'S BEEN HERE.
YEP, I FIGURE
SHE'S TRACKING
THE SPROUTS.
IT'S THE PICKLES'
BLOOD.
I MYSELF
SPENT 15 DAYS
TRACKING
SITTING BULL
THROUGH THE
NORTHWEST TERRITORY.
THE YEAR WAS 19--
OVER HERE!
WE FOUND SOME WHEEL TRACKS
AND BABY FOOTPRINTS
HEADING INTO THE WOODS.
ACTUALLY, HOWARD
FOUND THEM.
I SAW THEM.
THEY MUST BE
IN MY REPTAR WAGON.
IT'S THE PERFECT
CHILDREN'S TOY.
YOU AND YOUR STUPID
INVENTIONS!
MY STUPID
INVENTIONS?
THAT'S IT!
ALL RIGHT, THE PUPS
ARE IN THE WOODS.
YOU MEN FOLLOW
THOSE TRACKS.
WE'LL HEAD
TO THE RANGER'S STATION
AND START THE SEARCH
FROM THERE.
NOW, MOVE! HUT, HUT, HUT!
STU, WHERE
ARE YOU GOING?
TRUST ME, DID.
I HAVE A PLAN.
Tommy: SLOB THE POOP DECK,
MR. PHIL.
HOIST THE ANKLE, NUMBER ONE.
♪ A PIRATE'S LIFE
IS A LIFE FOR ME ♪
♪ YO HO HO
AND A BOTTLE OF YUM ♪
♪ I GET SEASICK
ON THE SEA ♪
♪ YO HO HO
AND A BOTTLE OF YUM ♪
♪ HOIST THE REPTAR
FLAG REAL HIGH ♪
♪ MY SWORD IS POINTED
TO THE SKY ♪
♪ YOU NEED A PATCH
ACROSS YOUR EYE ♪
♪ FROM ZANZIBAR ♪
♪ TO CANDY BAR ♪
♪ YO HO HO
AND A BOTTLE OF YUM ♪
♪ WE SEARCH FOR TREASURES
NEAR AND FAR ♪
♪ YO HO HO
AND A BOTTLE OF YUM ♪
♪ BEWARE YOUR SHIP
SHOULD CROSS OUR PATH ♪
♪ WE'LL SHOOT A CANNON
THROUGH YOUR MAST ♪
♪ REMOVE YOUR GOLD
BABOONS BY HALF ♪
OH OH OH!
♪ A PIRATE'S LIFE
IS THE LIFE FOR ME ♪
♪ YO HO HO
AND A BOTTLE OF YUM ♪
♪ ADVENTURE
ON THE OPEN SEA ♪
♪ YO HO HO
AND A BOTTLE OF YUM ♪
Tommy: DIL!
HELP ME, TOMMY!
FISH!
Phil: MAN OVERBOARD!
HANG ON, CHUCKIE.
AAH!
LOOK AT HIM GO.
TOMMY, WHY DIDN'T YOU
HELP ME?
I'M SORRY, CHUCKIE,
BUT DIL,
HE NEEDED ME,
AND HE'S JUST A--
Both: JUST A BABY!
UH-OH!
Tommy: HARD TO PORT SIDE.
TURN! TURN AROUND!
HELP ME, YOU GUYS!
HELP!
DIL, NO!
WHOAAA!
WOULD COME IN HANDY.
I KNEW MY DUCKTAR
POP, ARE YOU OK?
[SNORING]
OH, POP.
DO YOU THINK
WE'LL STILL BE ABLE
TO FIND THE LIZARD'S
HOUSE, TOMMY?
SURE, CHUCKIE.
LONG AS I GOT
MY SPONSATIVITY,
WE'LL NEVER BE LOSTED.
WHICH WAY ARE WE
APPOSED TO GO?
UM...UH...UM...
THAT WAY.
Chuckie: HEY, LOOKIE,
FOOTPRINTS.
MAYBE THERE'S OTHER BABIES
AROUND HERE.
THOSE ARE OUR
FEETPRINTS, CHUCKIE.
YOU'RE LEADING US AROUND
AND AROUND, TOMMY.
B-BUT IT WAS
WORKING BEFORE.
I DON'T THINK
IT EVER WORKED.
I THINK YOUR
SPONSATIVITY'S BROKE,
JUST LIKE
YOUR BROTHER.
Tommy: MY BROTHER
IS NOT BROKE!
HE PULLED
THE LEVER!
Phil: HE TRIED TO SEND US
INTO THE BIG JACUZZI.
WE COULD HAVE
BEEN DROWNDED.
HEY, YOU GUYS!
CLOW--CLOW!
WHAT IS IT,
CHUCKIE?
CLOWN!
WHAT'S A
TRAIN DOING
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE FOREST?
MAYBE SOME GIANT BABY
LOSTED HIS CHOO-CHOO.
EEE!
EEK!
OOH AHH AHH!
♪ TING, TANG,
WALLA WALLA BING BANG ♪
♪ OOH ♪             EEE ♪
♪ OOH AHH AHH ♪
♪ TING, TANG,
WALLA WALLA BING BANG ♪
♪ YOU WANT TO LEARN SOMETHING
THAT I CAN TEACH TO YOU ♪
♪ YOU WANT TO KNOW A SECRET
THAT I SWEAR IS TRUE ♪
♪ MONKEYS, WE HAVE MORE FUN
THAN HUMANS EVER DO ♪
♪ OOH, EEE, OOH AHH AHH ♪
♪ TING, TANG,
WALLA WALLA BING BANG ♪
♪ OOH, EEE, OOH AHH AHH ♪
♪ TING, TANG,
WALLA WALLA BING BANG ♪
♪ WE LEARN TO CLIMB
AND SWING ♪
♪ BEFORE WE LEARN TO RUN ♪
♪ WE LIKE TO PARTY,
AND THERE'S ROOM FOR EVERYONE ♪
♪ COME BY AND SEE US IF YOU
REALLY WANNA HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ OOH, EEE, OOH AHH AHH ♪
♪ TING, TANG,
WALLA WALLA BING BANG ♪
♪ OOH, EEE, OOH AHH AHH ♪
♪ TING, TANG,
WALLA WALLA BING BANG ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER SEE US TIRED ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE WAY
TOO SMART FOR WORKIN' ♪
♪ A MONKEY KNOWS A LOT MORE
THAN A MAN ♪
♪ WE LOVE SWINGING
IN THE TREES ♪
♪ AND EATING OUR BANANAS ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW WE NEVER
NEED A PLAN ♪
WHAT? WHAT DO YOU WANT?
HUNGRY, HUNGRY.
OH, BUT I
REALLY WANNA
GO PLAY WITH
THE MONKEYS.
[MONKEYS SNIFFING]
HUNGRY, HUNGRY.
WATCH MY BROTHER.
I GOTTA GET
THE DIAPIE BAG.
HEY, LEAVE HIM ALONE.
HE'S NOT A NANNER.
OH, NO!
HEY, GUYS, HELP!
THERE'S A MONKEY
WHO'S TRYING
TO TAKE
TOMMY'S BROTHER!
SO?
OH, JUST
HELP ME, OK?
HOLD ON!
LET GO!
OK!
OH, THIS IS JUST GREAT.
I TELL YOU, IT CAN'T GET
ANY WORSER THAN...
[GLASSES SHATTER]
THIS.
AT LEAST THE MONKEYS
ARE GONE.
YEAH.
AND THEY TOOK BABY
DIL WITH THEM.
HEY, SPIKE!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING,
YOU DUMB DOG?
HEY! MY ROLLY BLADE
IS CRACKED.
OH, CYNTHIA.
ARE THEY TAKING CARE
OF YOU?
WILL THEY KNOW
TO COMB YOUR HAIR,
OR CHANGE YOU
INTO YOUR SPORTS JUMPER
WITH MATCHING NECKERCHIEF
AT LUNCH TIME?
PEE-YEW, SPIKE!
DOG BREATH!
[GROWLS]            [WHIMPERS]
SPIKE?
DON'T WORRY. THIS TIME
SHE'LL FLY.
I'M FACING INTO THE WIND.
[ENGINE STARTS]
HE'S READY?
NO.                 GO?
NO!
ALL RIGHT, THEN!
WHOAA!
OH, THIS IS BAD!
BAD!
SHH!
HERE COMES TOMMY.
PUT THE BLANKIE ON HIM.
Tommy: OK, GUYS!
I GOT IT.
UM, I THINK IT'S
GONNA RAIN, TOMMY.
OH, YEAH.
UH, WE BETTER GO.
I GOTTA FINISH
FEEDING MY BROTHER.
I DON'T THINK
HE'S HUNGRY.
YEAH. BESIDES, HE'S, UM...
[GASPS]
A MONKEY?
Phil: WOW!
LOOK AT THAT!
MY BROTHER TURNED
INTO A MONKEY?!
[THUNDER]
COME ON, TOMMY.
WE GOTTA GET
OUTTA HERE.
I CAN'T GO HOME WITH MY
BROTHER BEING A MONKEY!
OH, BUT, TOMMY,
WE GOTTA GET
TO THE LIZARD'S HOUSE.
THAT'S IT!
I'LL GET THE LIZARD TO
WISH HIM BACK INTO A PEOPLE!
THE LIZARD'S ONLY GOING
TO GIVE US ONE WISH.
YEAH, AND IF YOU
USE IT UP ON DIL,
HOW ARE WE GONNA GET HOME?
HE'S MY BROTHER,
CHUCKIE!
I HAVE
TO WISH HIM BACK!
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
YES, I CAN!
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF PHIL TURNED
INTO A MONKEY?
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
I LIKE PHILLIP!
BESIDES, YOU'D BE WASTING
YOUR WISH ANYWAY,
'CAUSE THAT'S NOT
EVEN YOUR BROTHER.
[GASPS]
[BOTH GASP]
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT LILLIAN MEANS IS...
UM...
THE MONKEYS KIND OF TOOK
BABY DIL,
AND WE JUST--WE THOUGHT
YOU WOULDN'T MIND
A BABY MONKEY INSTEAD.
WHAT?
LOOKIT, TOMMY,
NOBODY LIKES HIM!
WE'RE GONNA FIND
THAT LIZARD, TOMMY.
YOU CAN FIND YOUR BROTHER
BY YOURSELF!
WILL YOU HELP ME,
CHUCKIE?
SORRY, TOMMY.
BUT--BUT YOU'RE
MY BESTEST FRIEND.
YEAH? WELL, IF--
IF I'M YOUR BESTEST FRIEND,
THEN HOW COME
WHEN I GOT THROWED UP ON,
YOU DIDN'T HELP ME?
HUH, HUH?
AND WHEN I FALLED
OVERBOARD,
YOU DIDN'T HELP ME.
AND THEN WHEN
THE MONKEY GRABBED ME,
YOU DIDN'T EVEN CARE
ABOUT MY BOO-BOO.
[CRYING]
FACE IT, TOMMY.
YOU DON'T GOT
A BESTEST FRIEND
NO MORE.
ALL YOU GOTS
IS A BROTHER.
OH, UM...
FINE.
I'LL GO FIND HIM
BY MYSELF.
[THUNDER]
[ALL GASP]
YOU DUMB BUTTHOUND!
[WHIMPERING]
FINE! I HOPE YOU
TURN INTO A FROG.
NYAH!
[WHINING]
I'LL FIND CYNTHIA MYSELF!
♪ ONE WAY OR ANOTHER ♪
♪ I'M GONNA FIND YOU ♪
♪ I'M GONNA GET YOU,
GET YOU, GET YOU, GET YOU ♪
♪ ONE WAY OR ANOTHER ♪
♪ I'M GONNA WIN YOU ♪
♪ I'M GONNA GET YOU,
GET YOU, GET YOU, GET YOU ♪
♪ CYNTHIA, OH, CYNTHIA ♪
♪ I NEED TO SEE YOU ♪
♪ I NEED TO SEE YOU,
SEE YOU, SEE YOU ♪
♪ FROM THAT KID
OR HIS BROTHER ♪
♪ I'M GONNA GET YOU ♪
♪ I'M GONNA GET YOU,
I'LL GET YOU ♪
♪ I'LL FIND
THE FULL DIAPER BAG ♪
♪ AND IF YOU'RE RIPPED
OR YOU'RE HURT ♪
♪ I'LL PUSH THEM IN DIRT ♪
YEAH!
[WOOF]
AAH! OOH!
OH!
STOP!
I SAID STOP!
CYNTHIA!
[GRUNTING]
[BABY CRIES]
HEY!
GIMME BACK MY BROTHER!
SHOO!
OH! GET OUTTA HERE,
YOU MONKEYS!
GO!
[CRYING]
[AWOO]
UGH!
COME ON.
LET'S GET OUTTA THIS RAIN.
[THUNDER]
I KNOW YOU ROOKIES
CAN GET EXCITED
AND LOSE YOUR HEADS,
BUT VETERANS LIKE ME
KNOW THE KEY IS
TO REMAIN CALM
AND COOL
AND COLLECTED.
[GASPS]
PLEASE, OUR KIDS
ARE LOST IN THE STORM.
YOU'VE GOT TO HELP US.
THERE'S DRAGONS
OUT THERE!
I'M A PARK RANGER,
NOT A KNIGHT
OF THE ROUND TABLE!
GO FIND SOMEBODY
WITH A LANCE!
NEVER MIND HIM.
COME WITH ME.
Ranger Frank:
WHAT DO YOU--COMING--I GOT--
THE DRAGON--I SAW IT.
[GRUNTING]
WE'LL JUST HAVE
A LITTLE BOTTLE
AND TAKE A NICE NAPPY,
AND EVERYTHING WILL BE OK.
MINE!
BUT I'M HUNGRY, TOO.
[WHINES]
STOP IT!
DIL, THAT'S ENOUGH!
UNH! OH!
[COUGHING]
YOU DIDN'T LEAVE
ANY FOR ME!
[BURPS]
ALL GONE.
[GIGGLING]
OH.
DIL.
DIL!
MY BLANKIE!
I NEED
SOME BLANKIE, TOO.
MINE!
MINE! MINE!
UNH!
UGH!
[GIGGLING]
YUCKY LOOKIE.
YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY?
PHIL AND LIL WAS RIGHT!
YOU'RE A BAD,
NAUGHTY BABY,
AND YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
GET ANY BETTER!
I'M THROUGH BEING
YOUR BIG BROTHER!
I DON'T WANT
MY SPONSATIVITY NO MORE!
[CHI CHI]
[HOO HOO HOO]
Dil: MONKEY!
MY MONKEY!
Dil: MINE.
YOU WANT MONKEYS?
OH, OK.
I'LL GIVE YOU MONKEYS.
YOU'LL HAVE A MONKEY MOMMY
AND A MONKEY DADDY
AND A MONKEY BROTHER!
I SHOULDA LET MY FRIENDS
TAKE YOU BACK
TO THE HOPSICLE,
BUT, NO, I SAID,
"HE DIDN'T MEAN IT,"
I SAID.
"HE WAS ONLY PLAYING."
WELL, I WAS WRONG!
NOW I DON'T EVEN
HAVE FRIENDS.
[GURGLING]
Tommy: DIL WANTS MONKEYS,
AND MONKEYS
WANT THE NANNERS.
SO EVERYBODY
GETS WHAT THEY WANT.
MY NANNA.
[THUNDER]
[CRYING]
TOTO--TOTO--TOTO.
I'M SORRY, DIL.
TOTO.
IT'S OK, DIL.
EVERYTHING IS
GONNA BE OK.
[TICKING]
[THUNDER]
[GASPS]
PHIL?
LIL?
AAH!
OHH! OH.
PHIL.
CHUCKIE?
HE ALWAYS LOVED
CLIMBING ON TREES.
NOW A TREE'S
CLIMBED ON HIM.
[CRYING] HE WAS
MY FAVORITEST BROTHER.
[CRYING]
SPEAK TO ME, PHIL.
YOU GUYS SEEN MY SHOES?
PHILLIP!
OH!
I DON'T LIKE THIS
ADVENTURE ANYMORE, PHILLIP.
GOSH, CHUCKIE, THIS TIME
WE REALLY ARE DOOMED.
DOOMED!
[CRYING]
SNAP OUT OF IT, LILLIAN!
WE GOTTA FIND THE LIZARD!
I DON'T KNOW, GUYS.
IF WE FIND THE LIZARD
AND TOMMY DOESN'T,
HOW'S HE EVER GONNA
GET HOME?
WHAT ARE YOU WORRIED
ABOUT HIM FOR?
HE'S THE ONE
WHO WAS GONNA LET YOU
GET EATED BY A FISH!
ALL HE CARES ABOUT NOW
IS BABY DIL.
YEAH, WELL, SOMEBODY HAS TO.
DON'T THEY?
[THUNDER]
[CRYING]
♪ BABY, PLEASE ♪
♪ REST YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ SOON WE WILL BE
HOME IN BED ♪
♪ UNTIL THEN ♪
♪ I'LL PROTECT YOU ♪
♪ LIKE NO OTHER ♪
♪ YOU'RE OK ♪
♪ FOR A LITTLE BROTHER ♪
MY TOMMY.
MY DIL.
[HICCUPS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CRYING]
OH, WE'LL NEVER FIND THEM.
CAN'T YOU DO SOMETHING?
COME ON, BABY.
COME ON!
Radio: SKY PICKLE
TO GROUND PICKLE.
STU, STU,
IS THAT YOU?
ROGER THAT, DID.
WE HAVE AERIAL SEARCH!
[QUACKING]
OOH!
UGH!
[QUACKING]
AAH!
OH, NO.
Tommy: N-NICE MONKEYS.
OHH.
NOT SO FAST,
YOU MONKEYS!
[SCREECHING]
LIL!
PHIL!
YOU CAME BACK!
OH, BUT--BUT WHERE'S--
Reptar: GRRR!
I AM REPTAR,
THE PERFECT CHILDREN'S TOY.
Tommy: CHUCKIE!
HI, TOMMY!
HEY, MONKEYS!
YOU WANT NANNERS?
WELL, COME AND GET 'EM!
[SCREECHING]
GOSH, I NEVER KNOWED
HE WAS SO BRAVE.
YEAH. WE'RE
GONNA MISS HIM.
WELL, WE BETTER
GET IN THE WAGON
AND GET OUTTA HERE.
NO!
YOU GUYS TAKE DIL
AND GO LOOK
FOR THE LIZARD.
I GOTTA GO HELP
MY BESTEST FRIEND.
[TICKING]
[WOOF WOOF]
OHH!
AAH!
OOH! DUMB DOG.
THERE'S NO BABIES
AROUND HERE.
AAH!
THERE YOU ARE!
HAND OVER
MY CYNTHIA, FINSTER.
RUN, ANGELICA!
THE MONKEYS IS COMING!
WHO?
THE MONKEYS
IS COMING!
CYNTHIA!
HEY!
OHH!
STOP!
[WOOF]
SPIKE!
YOU FOUND ME!
AAH! UGH!
OHH.
[GRRR]
UGH!
[SNIFFING]
OH!
OHH!
NICE MONKEYS.
I WAS ONLY KIDDING.
DON'T BE MAD AT ME.
PLEASE?
[GIGGLING]
OK.
HELP.
[WOOF WOOF]
TOMMY!
THANK GOODNESS!
HA HA HA!
COME ON, CHUCKIE!
[SCREECHING]
CHUCKIE!
THE LIZARD'S HOUSE!
LET'S FIND THE OTHERS!
WE GOTS A LIZARD TO SEE!
Chuckie: OH,
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
OHH! OHH!
SPIKE! I CAN'T LOOK!
I CAN'T LOOK!
OOH!
SPIKE!
MY BALL!
[GIGGLING]
DON'T LET THEM
TAKE ME, TOMMY!
I DON'T WANNA BE
MONKEY BOY!
AAH!
Reptar: HANG
ONTO YOUR DIAPIES, BABIES.
AAH!
Phil: GOOD ONE, DIL.
Tommy and Lil:
THANKS, DILLY.
THANKS, DIL.
DILLY, YOU'RE MY HERO!
MMM-WAH--WAH!
BYE-BYE, MONKEYS!
[ALL GIGGLING]
AAH! OH!
STOP IT!
[SCREAMING]
CYNTHIA!
HEY, YOU STUPID DIAPER BAG!
WAIT FOR ME!
DUMB MONKEYS!
All: AAH!
AFTER ALL I'VE DONE
FOR YOU BABIES,
YOU WERE GONNA LEAVE ME
AND CYNTHIA BEH--
I-I-I-I!
I DIDN'T KNOW
SHE COULD FLY.
I THINK IT'S 'CAUSE
SHE'S A WITCH.
[RIP]
OHH!
Tommy: HANG ON, ANGELICA!
[HELICOPTER WHIRS]
A TRUCKLOAD OF BABIES
AND THEIR PET HORSE
LOST IN THE WOODS.
OUR HEARTS GO OUT
TO THEIR GRIEF-STRICKEN
FAMILIES.
AAH!
AAH! AAH! AAH!
LOOK OUT, PICKLES!
NOW LOOK
WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
UGH! UGH!
ARE YOU
OUT OF YOUR MIND?
GET OUT!
WHOA!
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Rex: AND I NEVER
WON AN EMMY!
BOO-HOO!
OOPS.
I'M COMING, TOMMY.
I'M COMING, DIL.
OOPS!
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
UGH!
HURRY UP, BABIES!
[SCREECHING]
DON'T LET THEM TAKE ME!
DON'T LET THEM
TAKE CYNTHIA!
I DON'T THINK THEY'RE
GOING TO TAKE ANYONE.
LOOK!
[SCREECHING]
All: YAY!
YEAH! GO HOME, MONKEYS!
HOORAY! DUMB-DUMB MONKEYS!
[GRRR]
[ALL GASP]
WE WANNA GO HOME.
[GRRR]
AAH!
YUCKIES.
[WOOF WOOF]
YAY!
YAY, SPIKE!
SPIKE, SPIKE!
OH, NO, SPIKE!
SPIKE!
Phil: YOU GOTTA GET
OUTTA THERE, SPIKEY!
Angelica: YO, DUMB WOLF!
[RASPBERRY]
[AWOO]
[WHIMPERING]
All: SPIKE!
[SPLASH]
OHH!
SPIKE?
OH, SPIKE.
[CRYING]
DUMB DOG!
WHY'D YOU HAVE
TO GO AND--
[CRYING]
OHH!
[GASPS]
DID, I FOUND THEM!
THEY'RE OVER
BY THE RANGER STATION!
I'M GOING IN-N-N-N!
[ALSO SPRACH ZARATHUSTRA
PLAYS]
AHH!
All: THE LIZARD!
AHH! AHH!
AHH!
OHH!
HMM.
PLEASE, MR. LIZARD,
WE WISH WE COULD GO--
AHH-HH.
NO.
WE WISH WE HAD
OUR DOGGIE BACK.
AHHH.
[WOOF WOOF WOOF WOOF]
[WOOF WOOF WOOF]
SPIKE!
HE'S ALIVE!
[WOOF WOOF]
THANK YOU,
MR. LIZARD!
[TIRES SCREECH]
MY BABIES! MY BABIES!
OH, DIL!
MY DARLING!
OOH!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
WE'RE HERE! BETTY--
BETTY AND DADDY ARE HERE!
YOU RASCALS!
OH!
DADDY'S HERE.
ANGELICA, SWEETHEART,
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE OK!
OH, MOMMY, OH, DADDY!
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
DID YOU MISS ME?
YOU OK?
[RING]
[SPLASH]
YOU'VE GOT
THE PICKLE SPIRIT, SON.
MAYBE NOT THE BRAINS,
BUT THE SPIRIT.
OH, STU, YOU DID IT!
YOU FOUND OUR BOYS.
Dil: OH.
OH.
YEAH, I GUESS I DID.
[SIREN]
AHA!
MY LITTLE
FURRY COMRADES!
SPLENDID MONKEYS,
COME TO PAPA.
WHO'S YOUR DADDY?
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
BABIES AND MONKEYS,
BOTH LOST.
NOW BOTH FOUND.
THIS IS MY STORY, PAL.
AAH!
I'M REX PESTER.
STAY TUNED.
AAH!
NO, NOT MY TOUPEE!
NO!
GO GET HIM,
YOU LITTLE SIMIANS!
HEY, REX, TIME
FOR YOUR CLOSEUP!
OH, DEAR, TOO BAD.
AH.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT ALL THIS, DREW.
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
LITTLE BROTHER.
FOR A NINCOMPOOP,
YOU'RE NOT HALF BAD.
Angelica: NOW THE WHOLE
FAMILY'S TOGETHER AGAIN.
Stu: REMEMBER
THERE WAS SWAMPTAR?
Drew: OH, YEAH,
I REMEMBER THAT.
Chuckie: SO THAT
WAS OUR BIG ADVENTURE!
THE MONKEYS FOUNDED
THEIR DADDIES,
AND WE ALL GOTS
TO GO HOME
AND HAVE FRIED BOLOGNA
SANDWICHES,
EXCEPT DIL,
'CAUSE HE GOTS NO TEETH.
Chuckie:
BUT IF YOU THINK THINGS
WENT BACK TO THE WAY
THEY WAS BEFORE,
YOU'RE WRONG, 'CAUSE NOW,
THANKS TO BABY DIL,
THEY WAS EVEN BETTER.
HA HA HA!
AAH!
All: WAY TO GO, DILLY!
[GIGGLING]
♪ R-R U-U ♪
♪ G-G-G ♪
♪ R-R ♪
♪ A-A-A-A ♪
♪ T-T-T-T ♪
♪ S-S-S-S-S-S ♪
♪ TAKE ME THERE ♪
♪ I WANNA GO THERE ♪
♪ LET'S GO THERE ♪
♪ TAKE ME TO THAT
GREAT PLACE ♪
♪ WITH WONDERS
AND WISHES ♪
♪ SITTIN' HERE THINKIN'
ABOUT YESTERDAY ♪
♪ ALL ABOUT WHAT WE DID
AND HOW WE USED TO PLAY ♪
♪ JUST THE THOUGHT OF YOU
BRINGS A SMILE UPON MY FACE ♪
♪ SO I'LL MAKE IT HERE
TO SEE YOU EVERY DAY ♪
♪ OH OH OH ♪
♪ NOBODY KNOWS ♪
♪ AND WHAT WE DO
IS BETWEEN ME AND YOU ♪
♪ COME ON
AND TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ TO THAT SPECIAL PLACE ♪
♪ OUR SOULS COME TO LIFE
AND DREAMS COME TRUE ♪
♪ OOH OOH OOH OOH ♪
♪ TAKE ME THERE ♪
♪ I WANNA GO THERE ♪
♪ LET'S GO THERE ♪
♪ JUST TAKE ME
TO THAT PLACE, YEAH ♪
♪ WITH WONDERS
AND WISHES ♪
♪ TAKE ME THERE ♪
♪ I WANNA GO THERE ♪
♪ OH, OH, YEAH ♪
♪ TAKE ME THERE ♪
♪ WITH WONDERS
AND WISHES ♪
[NEW TUNE]
CALLING--CALLING--
CALLING--
CALLING ALL RUGRATS.
PLEASE COME IN, RUGRATS.
♪ TAKE IT TO THE MAXIMUM ♪
♪ TAKE IT TO THE MAX ♪
♪ TAKE IT--TAKE IT--TAKE IT--
TAKE IT--TAKE IT ♪
♪ TAKE IT TO THE MAXIMUM ♪
♪ THE TRAIN HAS BEEN
HIJACKED, ON TRACK ♪
♪ IT NEVER COMIN' BACK ♪
♪ THE EXPRESS,
THE LAST STOP ♪
♪ IS WHERE THE FUN'S AT ♪
♪ GOT MY FRIENDS,
A CAR FULL OF HOSTAGES ♪
♪ TO THE DESTINATION,
THERE'LL BE LOTS OF KIDS ♪
♪ ENOUGH SAID ♪
♪ TAKE IT
FULL STEAM AHEAD ♪
♪ I GIVE EXTREME DOWN PATCHING
TO THE TEAM OF FRED ♪
♪ WE AIN'T ACQUIESCED ♪
♪ WHEN WE HIT TOP SPEED,
THEY'RE GONNA PANIC ♪
♪ FOR THERE ARE
SEVERAL DYNAMICS ♪
♪ SCREAM ACROSS THE PLANET ♪
♪ ANGELS GO AGAINST
THE GALE FORCE WIND ♪
♪ ADRENALINE MAKES SURE
THE TRAIL OF FORCE WON'T END ♪
♪ IF THE THIRD RAIL FAILS,
WE'LL HAVE A TEND TO SPIN ♪
♪ THE NEXT QUESTION IS
WHEN WILL THE FUN BEGIN? ♪
♪ BEFORE WE CAN GET THERE ♪
♪ DOUBLE THE KICKS ♪
♪ HURRY UP 'CAUSE WE CAN
GET IN TROUBLE FOR THIS ♪
♪ SPEEDING EVEN
WITH THE RUGRATS AND ALL ♪
♪ WE HAVE TO CALL,
TAKE IT TO THE MAXIMUM ♪
♪ ALL TOGETHER,
LET'S MAKE THE GAME ♪
♪ WE CAN ALL WIN
IF WE PLAY THE SAME ♪
♪ WHOEVER GET CAUGHT
GOT TO TAKE THE BLAME ♪
♪ WE GONNA TAKE THE TRAIN ♪
♪ TAKE THE TRAIN ♪
♪ TAKE IT TO THE-- ♪
♪ TAKE IT TO THE MAXIMUM ♪
[NEW TUNE]
♪ I'VE GOT NO TIME
FOR FAIRY STORIES ♪
♪ I'M NOT A LITTLE GIRL ♪
♪ SO YOU CAN LEAVE ME
ALL ALONE ♪
♪ AND TURN OFF THE LIGHTS
AS WELL ♪
♪ IF YOU ARE FRIGHTENED ♪
♪ THEN LISTEN, WELL,
I DON'T THINK YOU'D LIKE IT ♪
♪ SUCH A NICE KID ♪
♪ NOBODY'S LOOKIN' NOW ♪
♪ I'LL THROW
MY TOYS AROUND ♪
♪ SOMEBODY'S
BEING VERY BAD ♪
♪ I WONDER WHO
IT CAN BE ♪
♪ SOMEBODY'S GOING
TO GET IN TROUBLE ♪
♪ I KNOW IT ISN'T ME ♪
♪ I'M JUST A LITTLE ANGEL ♪
♪ BET YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'VE DONE ♪
♪ WHEN YOUR BACK'S TURNED ♪
♪ NOBODY'S LOOKIN' NOW ♪
♪ I'LL THROW
MY TOYS AROUND ♪
♪ PICK UP THOSE
BUILDING BLOCKS ♪
♪ CHOP OFF
THE BABY'S LOCKS ♪
♪ SWING DOLLY
BY THE HAIR ♪
♪ PUT DOWN THAT TEDDY BEAR ♪
♪ SLAM DOWN
THE HAPPY CLOWN ♪
♪ I'LL THROW MY TOYS AROUND ♪
♪ I'LL THROW MY TOYS
AROUND ♪
♪ I'LL THROW MY TOYS AROUND ♪
♪ I'LL THROW MY TOYS
AROUND ♪
[SNORING]
[BAA]
♪ I AM REPTAR, HEAR ME ROAR ♪
♪ I AM REPTAR,
KING OF DINOSAURS ♪
[BAA]