Improved By: FidelPerez
Subtitle By: explosiveskull
Sub Upload Date: November 7, 2018
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
ANIMALS: (SINGING)
♪ On my merry way ♪
♪ I'll always think of you ♪
♪ On land or sand or gravel ♪
- (LAUGHING)
- (SINGING CONTINUES)
Focus, everyone, focus!
Listen to each other!
♪ It's more fun with two
It's always me and you ♪
♪ And together we will stay ♪
♪ Through warm
or stormy weather ♪
♪ We'll always be together ♪
RABBIT: Concentrate!
♪ Forever ♪
♪ For within my heart
If we should ever part ♪
♪ We'll be never far away
from each other ♪
♪ We'll be never far away ♪
Oh! What's he doing?
- Big finish!
- That'll do! That'll do!
Please!
- (CLANGING)
- I sounded incredible!
Tiggers are excellent singers.
It's lovely having you
all here.
Always very moving,
that number.
Now, um, we all know
why we're here.
- (FLY BUZZING)
- It's a sad day.
But I have asked
my friend, Eeyore...
- That's me.
- (RABBIT CLEARS THROAT)
I have asked him
to propose a rissolution.
- Uh, it's "resolution."
- Yes, that's what I said.
What's a "rissolution?"
After the poem, dear.
(EEYORE CLEARS THROAT)
"Christopher Robin is going.
"At least I think he is.
"Where? Nobody knows.
"But he is going."
I mean, he goes.
"Do we care?
We do. Very much.
"Anyhow, we send our love.
"End."
If anyone wants to clap,
now is the time to do it.
- PIGLET: Yay!
- KANGA: Wonderful!
- (ALL APPLAUDING)
- POOH: Christopher.
RABBIT:
There he is! He's here!
That was a lovely poem,
Eeyore.
EEYORE: It was nothing.
Oh, sorry.
POOH: It's just too bad
it's over.
I would've liked it to go on
for a while longer.
RABBIT: Now, now, let's not
get carried away there,
Pooh Bear.
That was plenty long enough.
For let's all remember,
I commissioned it.
Based on an original idea
by me.
Which I suggested.
OWL: After I thought of it.
RABBIT: Let's not do this
in public, shall we?
You wide-eyed
nincompoop.
Christopher Robin,
I made you this
sack of Hundred
Acre Wood haycorns.
They're my very
favorite snack.
Wherever you may go,
they'll remind you
of the Hundred Acre Wood.
CHRISTOPHER:
Thank you, Piglet.
I don't think
I'll need any help
remembering the Wood...
but I shall treasure them.
I'm gonna miss you, I am!
I'm gonna miss you too,
Tigger.
Now, don't you go
and get all growned up on us!
Uh, we shall all
miss the lad.
As my Grandowl Osgood
- used to say...
- EEYORE: Wow!
What did he used to say?
- I call the cherries.
- Extra cream for me, please.
OWL: No, it wasn't that.
Is it a carrot cake?
Mmm. Larger.
Cake is what
Tiggers like best!
I'm gonna
go for it.
(EXCITED CHATTERING)
TIGGER: What is this again?
(ALL MUNCHING)
RABBIT: Cake, cake, cake.
Will you never learn?
I would prefer a lovely,
crunchy carrot.
What's wrong with
something healthy?
- Good for your teeth.
- Sweets go right to my feets!
- You won't be able to stop me!
- Careful, Tigger.
Bounce
and bounce!
Come on, Roo!
And I'll bounce!
And I'll...
(SNORING)
(ALL SNORING)
Come on, Pooh.
(POOH SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Where are we going,
Christopher Robin?
Nowhere.
Oh.
One of my favorite places.
EEYORE: Saddle's too tight.
(SNORING CONTINUES)
CHRISTOPHER:
What do you like to do best
in the world, Pooh?
POOH: Hmm.
Well...
What I like best...
is me and Piglet...
going to see you...
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
and you say, "What about
a little something?"
And I say...
"Well, I shouldn't mind
a little something."
And it being a hummy
sort of a day outside.
CHRISTOPHER: I like that too.
But what I like doing best
is nothing.
How do you do nothing?
CHRISTOPHER:
It's when people call out...
"What are you going to do,
Christopher Robin?"
And you say, "Oh, nothing."
And then you go ahead
and do it.
Ah, yes.
Doing nothing often leads
to the very best something.
CHRISTOPHER: Pooh.
I'm not going to do
nothing anymore.
POOH: Oh.
Never again?
Well, they don't let you
at the boarding school.
Pooh...
When I'm off
not doing nothing,
will you come up here
sometimes?
Just me?
Where will you be?
I'll be right here.
But what should happen
if you forget about me?
I won't ever forget
about you, Pooh. I promise.
Not even when
I'm a hundred.
How old will I be then?
(SIGHS) 99.
Silly old bear.
POOH: Hmm.
99...
Christopher, come on now.
CHRISTOPHER'S MOTHER:
Do hurry up, darling.
CHRISTOPHER'S FATHER:
Christopher!
Christopher Robin,
your mother is in the car!
You take care.
CHRISTOPHER'S FATHER:
Off you go, young man.
Christopher Robin!
Now concentrate!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
WOMAN: You're the man
of the house now, dear.
(GASPS)
Would you like to sit down?
Oh, um...
Thank you.
- Cheeky blighter.
- Mmm-hmm.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
(EVELYN LAUGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
EVELYN: Will you write?
Of course, every day.
(MAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
ANNOUNCER: (ON RADIO)
It's February 11th, 1944.
Soon the nightly battle
of London will be on.
This has been
a quiet day for us,
but it won't be a quiet night.
They'll destroy
a few buildings,
and kill a few people.
Probably some
of the people you...
(RADIO TURNS OFF)
EVELYN: (SINGING)
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday,
dear Madeline ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- (BLOWS AIR)
- (EXPLOSIONS)
- This is Zebra-One-Charlie!
- (GUNS FIRING)
This is Zebra-One-Charlie.
Where are my reinforcements?
Ah, well done.
MADELINE: Mummy,
when is Daddy coming home?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(EVELYN CHUCKLES)
EVELYN: This is your daddy.
(LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Good morning.
KATHERINE:
Good morning, Mr. Robin.
- Good morning, Ms. Dane.
- Did you have a pleasant...
I'd like them to reconsider...
the brass fittings
on the chestnut wardrobes
for nickel-plated ones.
KATHERINE:
I'll make a note of that.
CHRISTOPHER:
Now, what's the holdup from Glasgow?
- Tanners union dispute, sir.
- What about Manchester?
Waiting on fabric, sir.
And what's
Birmingham's excuse?
It's just Birmingham, sir.
They're always late.
CHRISTOPHER:
I don't need to remind you,
we're under increasing
pressure to cut costs!
- MATTHEW: Mr. Robin?
- Yes.
If we replace
the second inner bevel
with beechwood...
we can increase buoyancy
by four percent.
JOAN: And decrease weight
by point-two percent.
And cost?
Oh, well, it might save
a few pennies.
Oh, keep plugging away,
everyone.
GILES: Bravo!
That's what we like to hear.
CHRISTOPHER:
Oh, Mr. Winslow, I could easily
have come up to your office.
No, no. I love
to come down here,
get my hands dirty
once in a while.
Oh sir, that sample is,
in fact, still wet.
Yes. (CLEARS THROAT)
The, uh, smell of the leather.
The smell of hard work.
Much rather be here
than in my stuffy office
where the boring stuff happens.
(CHUCKLES)
Yawn.
(LAUGHS LOUDLY)
This is where I belong.
Down here with the real men.
And women.
Sorry, always forget
about them.
Yes, I hate offices.
Give me some manual labor
any day of the...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Let's, uh, go into your office.
Yes, Mr. Winslow. Uh...
(CLEARS THROAT)
- After you, sir.
- Oh, no, please.
(CLATTERING)
Carry on.
Ah. (CLEARS THROAT)
- I spent all morning on that.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
GILES: Of all my father's
businesses, Winslow Luggage
is the worst.
Embarrassing for me,
of course,
but hardly surprising.
There's been a war.
Who has the time or the money
to go on holiday these days?
In short, we need
to cut some costs.
That's all I've been
working on, sir.
We've made some progress.
Three percent, or thereabouts.
We need to cut deeper
than three percent, Robin.
- We're stuffed.
- What did they say?
- (WHISPERS) I can't hear.
- JOAN: Don't worry.
I can lip read.
How much deeper, sir?
- Twenty.
- Twenty!
(MUFFLED)
Twenty percent, that's impossible.
He's saying, "Windy tent.
That's an apple."
What are they talking about?
Perhaps it's a lunch order.
Sir, your father promised
these people
good jobs to come home to
after the war.
Well, they'd do anything
for this company.
I'd do anything
My father has called an
emergency meeting on Monday.
We need to produce
the cuts by then.
It's sink or swim.
I promised my wife
and daughter
I'd take them away
this weekend, sir.
I thought you'd do anything
for this company.
Do you have dreams, Robin?
I beg your pardon, sir?
Well, I'll let you
into a little secret.
Dreams don't come
for free, Robin.
Nothing comes from nothing.
And if this ship goes down,
you need to ask yourself
the question...
"Am I a swimmer,
or am I a sinker?"
Well, which one
are you, Robin?
Well, obviously
I'd like to reply
that I'm a swimmer, sir.
- (PATS BACK)
- Right answer! Me too.
That's why I shall be working
this weekend, also.
All hands on deck
and all that.
This may help,
a list here of names.
People who can walk the plank
if you, um...
if we don't come up
with something.
It's all on you, Robin.
Oh, good heavens.
GILES:
Keep up the good work.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
Ah, Christopher.
- All work and no play, eh?
- Ah, Cecil.
Um, speaking of play, the wife
and I were just talking...
and hate to be
a persistent Peter...
but we're still waiting
for that gin rummy game.
Oh, yes, yes!
Well, one of these days,
eventually.
Eager to finally see
how good you are.
(CHUCKLES)
EVELYN: Madeline wanted
to wait for you but it got so late.
Yes, I'm sorry,
I got held up at work.
I know. Katherine rang
to let me know.
She also said you'd
be working this weekend.
I suppose you won't
be coming to the cottage.
(CHRISTOPHER STAMMERS)
Well, it can't be helped.
It never can.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hello.
What've you got there?
Oh, uh... It's yours.
I found it in the attic.
It has loads of things
from when you were my age.
Haycorns.
I mean, acorns.
Nothing of any great
importance.
Don't you think
you should be doing something
more useful with your time?
Reading perhaps?
I've already finished
the book list
that Grayford Prep sent.
I'm way ahead.
I've been very efficient.
Oh, good. That's good.
Yes, so there's no work
to do this weekend.
We can do whatever we want.
We'll go back to your cottage.
Play where you played.
We can do puzzles,
board games.
Right. Um...
I wanted to talk to you
about that.
I can't come this weekend.
But summer will be over soon.
I have to stay for work.
You and your mother will go.
I never see you.
Well, I wished I didn't
have to stay for work...
but dreams don't come
for free, Madeline.
You have to work for them.
Nothing comes from nothing.
Do you understand?
(SIGHS)
I understand.
I suppose you can keep
these here then.
Yes.
Do you think you could
read to me for a minute?
Of course.
Yes.
"The Victorian Era signified
"the height of
the Industrial Revolution...
"and was viewed as the apex
of the British Empire."
Oh, we've got
a real good one here.
"It followed
the Georgian period...
"and preceded
the Edwardian period."
Actually...
Father.
Yes?
I'm a bit tired.
Right.
Yes. Um...
You sure?
Hmm. Of course.
Well...
Good night.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
CHRISTOPHER:
I've been thinking.
You two don't have to go
to the country tomorrow.
We've been over this. She
needs to play, Christopher.
Not spend
all of her time studying.
Grayford Prep is the best!
She told me she's done
all the reading.
Because she would
do anything to please you.
But there are perfectly good
schools here in London...
that don't require us
to send her away.
And come on, Christopher.
You know
she doesn't want to go.
I went away
when I was her age.
It'll prepare her
for the real world.
Set her up for a career.
Well, isn't that
our responsibility to her?
What?
Do you even like your job?
What's that got to do
with anything?
You're going
to hit your limit.
One day you're going to crack.
Evelyn.
Look, if I work really hard
now, then in the future...
our life will be...
Will be what?
Will be better? Worse?
We don't care, we want you.
This is life, Christopher.
This weekend is your life.
Your life is happening now.
Right in front of you.
Look. Hello!
Yahoo. Remember me?
I'm your wife. (GIGGLES)
And that's another thing.
I haven't seen you laugh
in years.
Evelyn.
I want to see you
have fun, sometimes.
Be silly.
I didn't fall for you
because you had
your career set up.
- Was it my dancing?
- (CHUCKLES)
Actually, yes, it was...
It was dancing with you.
Being held by you.
Look, don't make this
harder on me.
I am sorry.
I'll take
my suitcase upstairs.
Where is my suitcase?
I didn't bother
packing it.
CHRISTOPHER: Have a nice time.
Goodbye.
- Take care.
- Hmm.
CHRISTOPHER: See you soon.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(SIGHS)
CECIL: We can have that game
of gin rummy
now that you're
a Tommy-time-on-his-hands.
Ah.
MADELINE: Dear Father...
I never knew
you could draw so well.
Maybe you could hang
this one next to mine.
Love, Madeline.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(SNORING)
POOH: Honey.
(MUMBLING)
(CONTINUES SNORING)
Honey!
Where am I?
I can't see anything.
Oh, that's right. (CHUCKLES)
Oh.
Good morning, house.
How are you today?
Time to make myself hungry
with my stoutness exercise.
(SINGING) ♪ When I up,
down, touch the ground ♪
♪ It puts me in the mood ♪
♪ When I up, down,
turn around ♪
♪ In the mood for food ♪
♪ And I'm off,
ready for my morning honey ♪
(YELPING)
Ouch.
Oh, some honey
will make me feel better.
Oh, bother.
Somebody seems to have eaten
all the honey.
Oh. (GROANS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Hmm.
Oh, my.
Foggy today.
If I know anything
about anything...
it's easy to lose your way
on a foggy day.
And rather hard to find
the way back.
Piglet always has
a little smackerel
of something hidden away.
Piglet?
It's Pooh.
Are you home?
It would appear not.
(ECHOING) Rabbit!
Are you home?
It's Bear speaking.
Eeyore!
Where is everybody?
How gloomy and sad.
If only Eeyore
were here to enjoy it.
Hello?
Anybody here?
Can anybody hear me?
(ECHOING) Hello?
What has happened
to my friends?
(WHINES)
Oh, dear.
I appear to have
reached the end...
of my thoughts.
(WIND HOWLING)
Oh.
Hmm.
(SIGHS)
YOUNG CHRISTOPHER:
Come on, Pooh.
(POOH GASPS)
Christopher?
Are you there?
It's me.
Winnie the Pooh.
Are you finally home?
Think, think, think.
It would seem
I must go forward...
where I have never been...
rather than backwards...
where I have.
Christopher Robin
must help me find everybody.
Or help everybody find me.
That will be the order
of looking for things.
Christopher?
Are you here?
It's Pooh.
(CLOCK TICKING)
Hello.
It's Pooh.
Are you hiding?
(BELL TOLLING IN DISTANCE)
(YAWNING)
Oh, I'm getting very sleepy.
Oh.
And that looks like a bed.
(BELL DINGS)
Where, oh, where
is Christopher Robin?
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(POOH SNORING)
(CHRISTOPHER EXHALES)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SIGHS)
What to do, what to do,
what to do?
POOH: What to do, indeed.
Pooh?
- Christopher Robin!
- No!
No, no, no, no, no!
(STAMMERS) You can't be here.
Hmm.
This can't be happening.
- It's stress.
- POOH: It's not stress.
My God, I'm stressed.
- It's Pooh.
- I'm so exhausted.
Evelyn warned me.
I like to be warmed.
Warmed and cozy.
I've cracked.
- Oh.
- I've totally cracked.
I don't see any cracks.
A few wrinkles maybe.
Pooh!
You're here!
How are you here, Pooh?
Oh. Well, I went
through the door
through which Christopher
Robin is known to appear.
And now, I'm here!
CHRISTOPHER:
But the tree I remember
was behind the cottage
in Sussex...
not here in London.
I suppose it's where
it needs to be.
CHRISTOPHER:
There's no opening.
There's no door
on the other side.
Oh. We must not
need it anymore.
That's a silly explanation.
Why, thank you.
Are you glad to see me,
Christopher Robin?
CECIL: Well, hello there!
Ooh, what have you got there,
secret Susan?
CHRISTOPHER: Uh, um...
Well, it's a, it's a... a cat.
Yes, definitely.
Just a cat.
Ooh, I love cats.
May I? Can I?
Well, not this one,
because it's a diseased cat.
It's ferocious.
Ooh, it's a biter.
I was about to take it in,
give it some milk.
You know, rehabilitate it.
POOH: (MUFFLED)
You're squishing me.
What on earth?
- Did you hear my voice there?
- CECIL: Yeah.
I do that funny voice,
"You're squashing me...
"with your demands to play gin rummy."
(CHUCKLES)
I was like a ventriloquist
when I was younger.
- Very good. Very good.
- (LAUGHS)
We've got all weekend.
For?
Gin rummy.
We should probably try
and play cards tomorrow then.
I'd love that.
- Yes!
- Tomorrow?
Well, yes, good evening!
- Good night!
- Have a nice...
CECIL: See you tomorrow.
CHRISTOPHER: Stop wriggling,
he's gonna see you moving.
Good evening.
Stop it.
Meow! You see?
CECIL: Ha! Yeah.
(POOH SLURPING)
(MUSIC PLAYING
OVER RECORD PLAYER)
(POOH CHUCKLING)
POOH: Mmm.
Oh, it really is very good.
Are you sure you wouldn't
like some, Christopher Robin?
(STAMMERS) Yes, yes, I'm sure.
Pooh, how ever
did you recognize me?
After all these years.
Well...
You haven't changed a bit.
But I've changed tremendously.
Not right here.
(SIGHS)
It's still you looking out.
I'm covered in honey now.
Oh. Oh, yes, I see.
(GRUNTING)
CHRISTOPHER: Sticky mess.
POOH:
Your floor is very sticky.
Pooh. Oh...
Oh, this place is very big.
Do you live here all alone?
CHRISTOPHER:
Just now, yes. But usually, no.
My wife and daughter
are in the countryside
for the weekend.
Well, why aren't you
with them?
- Well...
- (POOH STRAINING)
CHRISTOPHER: Oh.
Sticky business.
I had to stay for work.
Why are you here and not in
the forest with your friends?
That's the question, Pooh.
Well, I couldn't
find anybody.
And, I couldn't find
anyone either.
And I looked for them both.
- (MUSIC STOPS PLAYING)
- (MUFFLED) Hello?
(SIGHS)
POOH:
Piglet? Eeyore? Tigger?
Where is everybody?
Exactly! Where is Tigger,
or Kanga, or Roo?
POOH: That's why I'm here.
I'm sure I don't know
where they are.
I've scarcely thought
about them in 30 years.
(GRUNTS)
Well, we think
about you every day.
Well, that's very kind.
And I'm sorry, Pooh.
But it's getting late,
and I'm very busy.
I haven't got time to help
you look. I'm on a deadline.
So, do you think
you might just...
(POOH SNORING)
Oh, you silly old bear.
(SNORING CONTINUES)
(SOFTLY)
Good night, Winnie the Pooh.
(CRASHING)
(GROANS) What on earth!
- Pooh!
- POOH: Oh, dear.
(POOH GROANS)
What luck.
Pooh!
Your ladder is broken.
That's not a ladder.
That was a shelf.
That explains why it's no good
for climbing.
(SIGHS)
I haven't got time
to muck about.
I should be working.
Trying to find a solution.
Even though I think
it may be impossible.
People say nothing is impossible.
(CHUCKLES)
But I do nothing every day.
No, Pooh, that's not the...
(SIGHS) Never mind.
Look, I can't be distracted.
Which is why you need
to go home.
But how?
(CRASHING)
Sussex.
We go to Sussex.
And we get you back
in your own home. Now!
(HORNS HONKING)
It's very loud and not
in a hummy sort of way.
Well, welcome
to London.
(DOG BARKS)
Well, hello there. Are you
on an expotition, too?
- Oh, bother!
- Pooh!
What did you do?
POOH:
Do you think he's all right?
CHRISTOPHER:
Come here. Come in here.
Look.
You can't just keep saying
hello to people.
People can't see you
moving and talking.
But why?
Because, because...
You're different.
And people don't like things
that are different.
So I shouldn't be me.
(STAMMERS) No! No, you should
always be yourself.
Oh, this is very confusing.
It may be the hunger.
- You've just eaten!
- Oh, that's right.
Maybe I didn't eat enough.
Look, never mind about that.
For now, just try and be
a less exuberant you.
- Ex-Pooh-berant.
- Flop.
Sag.
Go limp.
- POOH: Flop. Sag.
- Yes!
POOH: Go limp.
I know, I've got it!
How about, play "Naptime."
- I love play!
- Well, let's see it.
Like this?
Well done! Now, just keep
absolutely still.
That's it.
Come on.
POOH: Christopher!
There's a rumbly in my tumbly.
Let's stop for a snack.
CHRISTOPHER:
There's no time for snacks.
- POOH: What about a smackerel?
- Play "Naptime!"
Balloons!
Come and get them.
- May I have a travel balloon?
- You don't need a balloon.
Well, I know
I don't need one...
but I would like one
very, very much, please.
Please. Please!
VENDOR: We've got all your
favorite colors!
I'd like a balloon,
please.
What color?
Red.
Uh, red will be fine, yes.
Thank you very much.
POOH:
Thank you ever so much.
Balloons!
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON P.A.)
(MAN BLOWS WHISTLE)
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ATTENDANT:
Here is your ticket.
Thank you very much.
ATTENDANT: Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
- POOH: Why is he in a cage?
I'd like a return ticket,
please?
To Hartfield in Sussex.
Thank you.
ATTENDANT: Certainly, sir.
CHRISTOPHER: Could you give me
some space, please?
ATTENDANT: Your ticket.
(COINS CLATTERING)
Here we are.
And, uh, still two minutes
to spare. So, good, yes?
- On the dot, sir.
- Good, thank you.
(ATTENDANT CLEARS THROAT)
The balloon
went that way, sir.
Thank you.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
Excuse me.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
I'm terribly sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
There he is!
Right.
Excuse me.
You're not a Woozle,
are you?
Oh, Christopher Robin!
Thank goodness.
- Give me that!
- That's mine. Give it back.
Well, he was mine first,
you know?
That is true.
Oh, for heaven's sake!
You can't just take a teddy
bear from a grown man.
POOH: Christopher,
could you turn the world
right side up again, please?
Did that say honey?
Can we go back?
Ooh!
- CHRISTOPHER: Excuse me.
- POOH: (SIGHS) Much better.
I thought you
were playing "Naptime."
It was one
of my briefer naps.
But, Christopher, my balloon.
Well, it's gone now. You don't
need it anymore anyway.
But it did
make me very happy.
Did it not make you happy?
Not really.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
(CHRISTOPHER MUMBLING)
Do you always have
that case with you?
What? A case?
(STUTTERS) My briefcase?
Yes, usually. Why?
Is it more important than...
a balloon?
Yes, it's more important
than a balloon.
I see.
More like... a blanket.
Yes.
More like a blanket.
What does it do?
What?
It's for keeping very
important things in.
Pooh, do you think
you might be able to
amuse yourself for a while?
I have got some rather
pressing work to do.
House.
Clouds.
Tree.
Bush. A man.
- Dog.
- Pooh.
- What're you doing?
- Oh, I'm playing a game.
It's called
"Say What You See."
Could you "Say What You See"
a little more quietly?
(SOFTLY) House.
Grass.
Trees.
Pond.
I don't know
what that is.
- Pooh.
- Well, that's a man.
Pooh.
Little bit more quietly.
Please?
Oh, I'm sorry, this
compartment is rather full.
It's his naptime.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Hmm.
(CHRISTOPHER MUMBLING)
CHRISTOPHER: We'll save
at least 322 pounds a month.
Well, that's not nothing.
Which brings us to 14%.
Still not enough.
Someone's gonna have
to walk the plank.
They'll never forgive me
for this.
Sorry, Gary.
CONDUCTOR:
Now arriving at Hartfield Station.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
(BELL DINGING)
Hartfield! Hartfield Station!
- Look. My balloon!
- Oh.
Now come on, Pooh.
We've got to hurry.
POOH: Yes.
We need to find our friends.
CHRISTOPHER:
No, Pooh. I meant,
- I have to get back for work.
- Oh.
- POOH: Are we going in?
- No, no, Pooh.
We must keep very quiet.
Not let them see us.
Come on.
Stay low.
POOH: (WHISPERS) Oh.
- Who is that?
- Pooh!
POOH: She can't be Pooh.
I'm Pooh.
CHRISTOPHER: (WHISPERS)
No, that's Evelyn. My wife.
POOH: Oh.
She looks very kind.
She is very kind.
And who is that?
That's Madeline.
My daughter.
POOH: Can she come
and play with us?
No, she can't come.
Does she not like to play?
No, no, it's just...
Well, look, she's working.
POOH: Oh, I see.
Does she have a briefcase
like you?
No.
Come on, Pooh.
POOH: Do you think
she'd like my red balloon?
It might make her happy.
What is it with you
and the balloon?
There's more to happiness
than just balloons, Pooh.
Look, Madeline is happy and
I'm happy that she's happy.
Well, let's go.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
CHRISTOPHER: There, Pooh.
I got you home.
Aren't you coming with me?
CHRISTOPHER: I can't.
I've gotta go back to London.
But I need your help.
I've lost all of my friends.
Perhaps they're back now...
and you can tell them
all about your adventures.
I would like to do that.
Off you go then.
Goodbye, Christopher.
Goodbye, Pooh.
What're you doing, Pooh?
Sometimes when I'm going
somewhere and I wait...
a somewhere comes to me.
Right.
Well...
Good luck with everything.
I should need good luck.
For I am a bear
of very little brain.
Right. Well, goodbye.
POOH: Goodbye.
(SIGHS)
Look out, Pooh. Here I come.
(GRUNTING) Pooh?
Pooh!
(GRUNTING)
(WOOD CREAKING)
Oh.
(GRUNTS) So this is what
this feels like.
Are you stuck?
Yes, it would appear
that I am stuck.
Happens to me all the time.
Have you just eaten honey?
No, Pooh, I have not
just eaten honey. (GRUNTS)
Oh, it's still here.
Hundred Acre Wood.
Well, I didn't expect
to be here this morning.
Was it always this gloomy?
POOH: I don't believe so.
I wonder where
they all could be.
Well, I was hoping
you would know.
Pooh, I haven't been here
in years. How would I know?
But you're Christopher Robin.
Ah, right. Yes.
Well, the thing is
to do this systematically.
Oh, follow
the simple honey bee.
No, Pooh.
The key is to head
in just one direction
to avoid getting lost.
Especially in all this fog.
I always get to
where I'm going...
by walking away
from where I have been.
CHRISTOPHER: Do you?
POOH:
That's the way I do it.
I'm hungry.
CHRISTOPHER: Come on, Pooh.
We'll never get anywhere
at this rate.
(WIND HOWLING)
(POOH HUMMING)
CHRISTOPHER:
Is anything familiar?
- POOH: The fog.
- Well, besides the fog.
POOH: (GASPS) Oh, bother.
CHRISTOPHER:
What's the matter?
Oh, Pooh.
You can't be serious.
There's no such thing
as Heffalumps and Woozles.
Of course there are.
Didn't you see the sign?
Pooh, terrifying elephant
and weasel-like beasts...
who wander the world preying
on happiness aren't real.
Now, come on.
Christopher?
What do you do?
I'm the Efficiency Manager
at a luggage company.
You must have
many friends there.
There's lots of people
who rely on me.
So, yes.
No, I don't think
of them as friends.
That makes it harder
if I have to let them go.
Where will they go?
I don't know, Pooh.
(STAMMERS) I don't know.
Did you let me go?
I suppose I did.
Come on, Pooh.
Oh. What is that?
It's a compass, from the war.
I still keep it with me.
May I see the compass?
Yes, I suppose so.
Oh.
Shall we follow this
very handy arrow?
Well, that's
a very good idea.
No, wait, Pooh.
Keep us headed north.
North.
Oh, north.
Yes, there's an "N"
in front of it, for "north."
POOH:
That's what that means.
(POOH HUMMING)
CHRISTOPHER:
Isn't this the same sign?
Pooh, are you sure
we're still heading north?
Let me look.
You haven't been looking?
Not since I started following
these footsteps.
Pooh, they're our footsteps!
Oh, we've just been going
around in a great, big circle.
What's the matter with you?
All you had to do
was follow the compass!
But it led us to the
Heffalumps and the Woozles.
There are no Heffalumps
and Woozles, do you hear?
Oh, I should never
have trusted you with it!
I'm sorry.
I'll put it back in the holder
of important things.
Oh, my papers!
They're irreplaceable!
I shall never remember
all this!
Pooh, you're right.
You are a bear
of very little brain.
Do you know what'll happen
if I lose
one single sheet of this?
Winslow will eat me
for breakfast.
A Woozle will eat you
for breakfast?
Yes, a great big Woozle
will gobble me up.
That doesn't sound like fun.
That's the real world for you.
Oh, Pooh, there's more to life
than just balloons and honey.
Are you sure?
Silly bear.
I don't know
why you came back.
I'm not a child anymore.
I'm an adult,
with adult responsibilities.
But you're Christopher Robin.
No.
I'm not how you remember me.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
You should let me go...
for a fish in the sea.
"A fish in the sea?"
No, "efficiency!"
- Pooh?
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
Pooh?
Winnie the Pooh?
I haven't got time for this.
Pooh!
Pooh, where are you?
Oh, where have you gone,
you silly bear?
I didn't mean
to frighten you. Pooh!
Tigger, Eeyore, anyone?
- (ECHOING)
- (DISTANT TRUMPETING)
There's no such things as
Heffalumps and Woozles.
Oh, not real,
not real, not real.
(TRUMPETING CONTINUES)
(ECHOING) Not real.
Not real, not real, not real.
(YELPS)
(GROANING)
Oh, no! No,
I'm not a Heffalump!
They're up there!
And I'm down here.
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- Pooh!
Somebody help!
Oh, perfect!
(GRUNTING)
WOMAN: You're the man
of the house now.
EVELYN: I haven't seen you
laugh in years.
CHRISTOPHER:
Dreams don't come for free.
EVELYN: One day
you're going to crack.
CHRISTOPHER:
Nothing comes from nothing.
GILES: You need
to ask yourself the question,
"Am I a swimmer,
or am I a sinker?"
(ECHOING)
Sometimes the thing to do
is nothing.
Ooh.
Oh, no! Christopher.
(SCREAMING)
No!
Come back to us!
CHRISTOPHER:
Just do nothing! Just do nothing!
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(EXHALES)
Pooh!
Anyone?
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Just my luck.
A Heffalump.
Leering at his lunch.
Eeyore, I'm not a Heffalump!
Doesn't matter anyway.
Headed for the waterfall.
I'll be gone soon.
CHRISTOPHER:
Oh, no, not the waterfall.
Swim!
Not that anyone will notice.
Swim, swim, swim!
Just have to go with the...
(GRUNTS) Ow. Flow.
- CHRISTOPHER: Don't worry.
- I'm not.
Can't change the inevitable.
You mustn't give up, Eeyore!
I'll save you.
We'll see.
Oh, yes, of course.
I've grown up, haven't I?
(LAUGHING)
Oh! Eeyore!
Laughing at my misfortune.
Just like a Heffalump.
Hello, Eeyore.
Hello, Heffalump.
I'm not a Heffalump.
I'm Christopher Robin.
Do you remember, I used
to try and cheer you up?
I don't remember being cheery.
What were you doing
in the water?
Just an average
Windsday morning for me.
Woke up. Windy.
Wind blew me
into the river.
It must know I can't swim.
- (DISTANT TRUMPETING)
- There's that sound again.
It's your fellow Heffalumps,
calling you home.
Come on, Eeyore. Let's get
to the bottom of this.
I'm already at the bottom.
It's kind of you to kidnap me.
CHRISTOPHER:
Now we're getting somewhere.
EEYORE:
Not exactly what I had in mind.
CHRISTOPHER: Oh, look,
Owl's house has fallen out
- of the tree again.
- (DISTANT TRUMPETING)
And there's that
terrible noise.
EEYORE:
I think it's behind the house.
CHRISTOPHER:
Well, I think we should investigate.
EEYORE: I wouldn't go in there
if I was us.
(TRUMPETING CONTINUES)
CHRISTOPHER:
There's no such thing as Heffalumps.
There's no such thing
as Heffalumps.
(LOUD TRUMPETING)
- There's no such...
- (CREAKING)
Look.
It's just the old
weather vane.
Great. Now it has a weapon.
No sign of Owl though,
either.
Wonder what happened.
EEYORE:
If only Christopher Robin were here.
I am Christopher Robin.
You should be able
to tell us then.
- (WOOD CREAKING)
- (GRUNTS)
Let's see.
Looks like they were all here.
Rabbit...
Oh, someone was bouncing.
- Tigger.
- Looks like a disaster.
Why wasn't I invited?
So I think what happened is...
the weather vane broke off
when the house
fell out of the tree...
and started making
that noise...
and they all thought it was
a Heffalump and panicked.
- And then they all...
- (CLATTERING)
flew out of the door.
Oh.
Look, haycorn shells.
A whole trail of them.
Follow them
and we'll find Piglet.
Now that is...
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
I'm sorry, old bean.
Come on.
EEYORE:
I was just getting comfortable.
CHRISTOPHER: Let's go and see
if we can't find Piglet.
EEYORE: Goodbye, Bucket.
There's one.
And here.
Another one.
EEYORE:
You don't have to tell me
every time you pick one up.
And another...
(LOUD MUNCHING)
(PIGLET GASPS)
Who is it?
Who's there?
EEYORE: It's nobody.
Oh, Eeyore.
Thank goodness it's you.
Oh. And a Heffalump.
(GASPS)
Piglet, it's just me.
Christopher Robin.
Don't move.
Don't move, Eeyore.
Maybe it won't eat us.
Oh, Piglet.
Would a Heffalump
offer you a haycorn?
It would if it was trying
to trick me!
Oh. (GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
- PIGLET: His legs are so long!
- CHRISTOPHER: Piglet!
I didn't mean to frighten you.
Come on.
I'm not frightened.
(WHIMPERS) I'm terrified.
Got to go quicker.
These haycorns are weighing
me down, but I can't let go.
He's coming! It's coming!
RABBIT: Piglet,
you have a head full of fluff.
You've led it right to us!
Now we're stuffed!
TIGGER:
What's the point of hiding
if you're going
to bring him to us?
- Hello, everyone.
- RABBIT: Nobody move.
Heffalumps can't see you
if you don't move.
I can clearly see you.
TIGGER:
Well, you didn't see this.
I'll pounce ya. I'll pound ya.
Tigger!
It's Christopher Robin.
- Huh?
- Oh, Tigger, just look.
Look closely.
He's giant. Huge!
He's a massive beast.
And he smells a little funny.
OWL: Don't look him
in the eye.
(GASPS)
He has hair everywhere!
Even in his ears.
KANGA: Such troubled eyes.
- ROO: His nose is huge!
- KANGA: He's hideous.
Well, that's a bit harsh.
- He's clearly a Heffalump.
- KANGA: Don't stare.
No, the Heffalump was just
your old weather vane, Owl.
(STAMMERS)
Have you eaten Winnie the Pooh?
ROO: Did they take him?
Do the monsters have Pooh?
Look, there's no such thing
as monsters.
- PIGLET: He's tricking us.
- Of course there are!
He lies!
How dare you pretend
to be Christopher Robin.
He'd never say such a thing.
I am Christopher Robin.
Help me.
ROO: Then prove it.
Christopher Robin would know
how to stop the Heffalumps.
You're right, Roo.
And I'm not
gonna let you down.
We have got a scary
Heffalump here...
and it's about time I,
Christopher Robin,
defeated it.
So... There!
- (GASPS)
- There it is!
Stop, Heffalump!
Come on, Eeyore.
You'll be my witness.
Oh, sure.
Sacrifice the donkey.
- RABBIT: Let me stand on your back.
- No!
- Your foot is on my shoulder!
- Push me up.
Up, up, I'm up now.
I can hear him.
(GROANS)
He's headed to a clearing.
Sure, I'll just sit here
while we wait for them
to show up.
OWL: (GASPS)
He's drawn his sword.
RABBIT: What's happening?
OWL: He's just drawn
his sword.
CHRISTOPHER: You there!
Heffalump!
He's seen it!
RABBIT: It sounds agitated!
Don't agitate it!
I'll teach you to scare
my friends!
(YELLING)
But there's nothing there.
Something is clearly there.
Do you hear that?
- Where's he gone?
- He's gone behind the tree!
- (YELLING)
- Huh?
Take that, Heffalump!
(SCREAMS) He's got me!
OWL: I think the Heffalump's
got him by the foot.
RABBIT: It's the Heffalump
that's screaming!
Oh, no!
He's attacking me!
(GRUNTS)
- Huh?
- CHRISTOPHER: Oh, no!
Oh, goodness gripes!
EEYORE: Hmm...
(GRUNTS)
- Christopher Robin.
- They're attacking me!
- It's you.
- Take that, you Heffalump!
Playing again.
Do you see it, Eeyore?
EEYORE:
I think it's a whole herd.
They've got us surrounded.
What do they sound like,
Eeyore?
Uh, like this.
(ROARING)
RABBIT:
That sound is terrifying!
- Louder, Eeyore, louder!
- (ROARING LOUDLY)
It chills my heart.
That Heffalump's lucky
I'm needed here.
I'd be bouncing all over it!
- (ROARING)
- (YELLING)
Attack!
(GRUNTS) Well done, Eeyore.
Keep up the good work.
Finally good at something.
(CHUCKLES)
And there goes the tail.
He's winning, Mum.
I think you're right, Roo.
Then it must be
Christopher Robin!
RABBIT: I can't see
what the Heffalump's doing,
but it sounds very nasty.
It all sounds very,
very nasty!
I'm not afraid of you!
You rotten,
stinking Heffalump.
RABBIT: Go on, Christopher!
PIGLET:
I think he's gonna do it!
- (YELLING)
- (ALL GASPS)
RABBIT: There is silence.
I do not know
which one is standing.
OWL: It's not entirely clear.
RABBIT: Something is moving
towards us.
Please, please make it,
Christopher Robin.
Did he win? Mummy,
tell me what's going on.
Something's coming.
- RABBIT: Can you see him?
- Yes, I can see him.
How does he look?
Smaller, getting larger.
- ROO: Christopher Robin!
- OWL: It's Christopher Robin!
- He's won!
- ROO: He did it!
CHRISTOPHER:
I have vanquished the Heffalump.
RABBIT: Well, of course,
we all knew really!
We knew you'd dump that lump.
PIGLET: Only Christopher Robin
can beat a Heffalump!
OWL: I never lost hope.
- ROO: We missed you!
- I've missed you, too.
All of you.
Very much.
Oh, you've grown up well.
So glad we're all back
together again.
But where's Pooh?
Oh, yes, of course, Piglet.
Well, Pooh...
I lost him.
- He's lost him?
- KANGA: Oh, dear.
Where exactly
did you lose him?
Concentrate. Let's all
work together, please.
I'll get searching. Tiggers
are the best searchers.
You're Christopher Robin.
You'll find him.
Somewhere.
Well, that's it, Roo.
Pooh's waiting for Somewhere
to find him.
And I think I know just
where Somewhere is.
(POOH SIGHS)
KANGA: There he is.
Waiting for you.
(CHRISTOPHER SIGHS)
Hello, Pooh.
Hello,
Christopher Robin.
I'm so sorry, Pooh.
I'm so terribly sorry.
I should never have
shouted at you.
Well, I am a bear
of very little brain.
CHRISTOPHER: No, Pooh.
You are, I think,
a bear of very big heart.
POOH: Hmm.
You'll be happy to hear that
everyone's safe and sound.
I saved them from a Heffalump
which was, in fact, well, me.
And Owl's weather vane.
POOH:
I'm sorry I wasn't there.
But I am rather glad
that I was here.
Waiting for you.
Thank you
for waiting for me, Pooh.
It's always a sunny day...
when Christopher Robin
comes to play.
CHRISTOPHER: Hmm.
Not so sure about that.
I'm not
who I used to be.
POOH: Of course you are.
You're our friend.
Look at how you saved
everybody today.
You are our hero.
I'm not a hero, Pooh.
I'm lost.
But I found you.
Didn't I?
(MUFFLED)
You're squashing me again.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
May we wake them?
(SNORING)
(WHISPERS) Pooh. Pooh!
It's me, Piglet.
- Wakey, wakey.
- POOH: Good morning, Piglet.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- POOH: What is it?
- It's tomorrow!
POOH: It's usually today.
Well, yes,
of course it's today.
But that means I slept here,
and I'm meant to be
in the office in...
Oh, blast!
How did I let this happen?
- RABBIT: He's overslept!
- Where's my briefcase?
Owl, you've been up all night.
- You should've squawked!
- OWL: Don't you worry.
As my old Uncle Orville
used to say...
"Worry is the way to concern."
Or is it, "Concern is
the way to confusion?"
RABBIT:
You're the way to confusion.
We've got all your belongings
all nice and dried out.
Tigger helped me
get you all sorted.
I sure did. (LAUGHS)
- Here you go.
- CHRISTOPHER: Oh, thanks.
I could never have forgotten
my case of important things.
I'm sorry
I have to go,
but I've already
stayed far too long.
Oh, Pooh,
you should keep this.
That way, if you lose someone,
you'll be able
to find them again.
Thank you, Christopher Robin.
Oh, and you should take this.
For Madeline.
ROO: What's a Madeline?
Is it more important than your
case of important things?
Madeline's my daughter,
so, yes, of course.
Absolutely.
She means the world to me.
Then why isn't she with you?
POOH: Well, uh...
She has work to do, Roo.
- Oh, the poor dear.
- CHRISTOPHER: No, no.
She likes work.
Uh...
Look, I've got to hurry.
Goodbye, everyone.
It's so nice
to see you all again.
Goodbye, Christopher.
CHRISTOPHER: Goodbye!
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GRUNTING)
Father?
Father, is that you?
Yes.
What are you doing here?
Well, uh...
(STAMMERS) I was, uh...
Were you in the woods?
Yes, I was.
- But I'm terribly sorry...
- (DOOR OPENS)
Hello.
I've really
got to go.
You can't stay?
I can't, darling.
There's an 11:00 meeting
I'm terribly late for.
I'm so sorry.
Madeline?
(SOFTLY) Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry, darling. I never
meant for her to see me.
I've really got to make
the next train.
Well, you better go then.
There's a good explanation
for all of this.
I'd love to hear it.
Well, I was...
Well,
it's a little complicated.
I suppose I can't right now.
I was thinking that Madeline
and I should stay longer.
Do you think that's really
for the best?
I do.
- For how long?
- I don't know, Christopher.
Evelyn!
You're going
to miss your train.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GRUNTS)
(CLATTERING)
How's it going
in here?
Fine. Wonderful.
Everything's just perfect!
Yeah, I can see that.
It's hard to imagine your
father as a child, isn't it?
Are you sure he ever was one?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Well, I'm pretty sure.
I'm sorry he couldn't stay.
Your father...
He's having
a bit of a hard time of it.
Then he should have come
and spent the weekend with us.
We would've made him
feel better.
It's not always that simple.
He will come back
to us, though.
I know it.
Boarding school starts soon.
There's not
a lot of time left.
That's why you should
go and play.
- Play?
- Yes.
Dirty, mucky play.
I expect you
to come back filthy.
(OPENS DOOR)
Yes. I'm going to play
better and harder
than any child
has ever played before.
Or, you know, have fun.
Right. Fun.
How exactly do I do that?
Go explore.
I'm sure your father found
loads of things
to play with around here...
when he was your age.
I don't feel
much like Pooh today.
There, there, I'll bring you
tea and honey until you do.
Hmm, that's an idea, Piglet.
TIGGER: One Tigger-knot
coming right up.
This is the crucial part.
EEYORE: It's too tight.
POOH: Eeyore, you've got a,
um, a something...
on your back.
Rain protection.
(CHUCKLES)
- What do you think?
- EEYORE: I know what I think.
But those are Christopher
Robin's important papers.
Oh, Tigger,
what have you done now?
Well, I needed to make room
in his briefcase
for the real important stuff.
You know,
things to remember us by.
Not the flippity-flop papers.
But without them, the Woozles
will eat him for breakfast.
- (GASPS)
- Oh, no!
Pooh, what do we do?
Tree.
Sheep.
Cow.
Woman with dog.
(MAN CLEARS THROAT)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Tree.
Sheep.
Cow.
Bridge.
Is it all tied up
nice and tight?
Well, of course!
I used a Tigger-knot.
The strongest knot known.
Does this make me look husky?
You look like a sad house.
Pooh, are you sure
we need to go to Lon Don?
POOH: Oh, yes, Piglet.
Christopher Robin
always comes to save us.
Now, it's our turn
to save him.
We're probably too late.
I'd say
they've eaten him already.
Come on, then!
Bounce faster, Eeyore.
We've gotta get this
to Christopher Robin.
EEYORE:
I've only got one speed.
We're right
behind you, Tigger.
(STUTTERS)
I'm not sure I'm going to go.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
No, I think I might stay.
I'm actually going
to definitely stay.
POOH: There, there, Piglet.
Come on. Here.
- PIGLET: Oh.
- We need you.
PIGLET: You need me?
Um...
Well, if you need me...
We always
need you, Piglet.
PIGLET: Thank you, Pooh.
POOH: And wait
till you see London.
So many balloons.
It's Madeline Robin serving
for the Wimbledon title.
(GRUNTS) And it's an ace!
She's won!
The crowd goes wild!
- (WHOOPING)
- PIGLET: Hip hip hooray!
- Hip hip hooray!
- TIGGER: The crowd goes wild!
Which way is Wimbledon?
EEYORE: Shh! Be quiet.
TIGGER:
What do you mean, "shh?"
MADELINE: Hello?
- POOH: That's a Madeline.
- TIGGER: Oh.
EEYORE:
You're crushing the papers.
- Hello?
- POOH: Uh-oh.
PIGLET: She doesn't know
we're here.
POOH: Quiet, Piglet.
- EEYORE: Ow.
- PIGLET: Oh, she's very good.
- Who's in there?
- TIGGER: Throw it back.
POOH:
No pushing. We might fall...
TIGGER: Okay, easy. Tail...
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, hello!
Congratulations
on Wimbledon.
You must be
a Madeline.
- (SCREAMS)
- EEYORE: Oh! Danger!
POOH: I'm ever so sorry.
We're sorry. We didn't mean
to interrupt your games.
(STUTTERS)
You're talking.
Me? No, I'm not talking.
Oh, well, I am now, I suppose.
Wait. I recognize you.
You're the bear
in my father's drawings.
Winnie the Pooh.
Pooh for short.
This is Piglet.
- Eeyore...
- TIGGER: Wait for me!
(GRUNTING)
EEYORE: Oh, dear.
And I'm Tigger,
T-I-double G-UHR!
What's a Tigger?
TIGGER: I'm glad you asked.
(LAUGHING)
Please, not the song.
(SINGING) ♪ The wonderful thing
about Tiggers ♪
♪ Is Tiggers
are wonderful things ♪
♪ Their tops
are made outta rubber ♪
♪ Their bottoms are made
outta springs ♪
♪ They're bouncy,
flouncy, trouncy, pouncy ♪
♪ Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun ♪
♪ But the most wonderful thing
about Tiggers is ♪
♪ I'm the only one ♪
He does that a lot.
(WHISPERS) I'm the only one.
MADELINE:
Well, hello, everyone.
Did the red balloon
make you happy?
Balloons make me very happy.
- That was from you?
- POOH: No.
It was from Christopher Robin.
My father was with you?
POOH: Oh, yes.
He was helping me
to find my friends.
And he saved us
from the Heffalump.
MADELINE: A Heffa-what?
But he left
his important papers...
which might have been
a smidge my fault.
It was your fault.
So we're going on
an expotition to Lon Don.
Oh. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
If we don't get
the papers to him...
a Woozle is going to eat him
for breakfast.
A Woozle...
You must mean a Winslow.
Exactly. A Woozle.
He's going to be awfully glad
to get them back.
(TIGGER LAUGHS)
Come on, let's bounce!
We haven't got
a moment to lose.
PIGLET: Which way do we go?
Christopher Robin said
we should head north.
London's northwest actually.
The train station is south.
I don't know south.
Don't worry, I do.
On an expotition
to father's work,
got his papers. Be back soon.
(TIGGER LAUGHS)
EEYORE:
I'm going to close my eyes.
TIGGER: Pretty quickity-quick.
POOH: This is faster
than most expotitions.
Nice to feel
the wind in your fur.
Come on, Madeline.
Let's see what this thing
can do. (LAUGHS)
Maddy!
Maddy, would you like
some lemonade?
POOH: Remember "Naptime."
TIGGER:
Tiggers make the best nappers.
MADELINE:
One ticket to London, please.
Five shillings, please.
(GRUNTS) Oh.
Right where I belong.
Grand.
- MADELINE: Thank you!
- Thank you!
EEYORE: Thank you.
- (BELL DINGING)
- (TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
(BRAKES SCREECH)
(PANTING)
MAN: Stand clear
for the departing train.
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERING) Does this world
ever slow down?
Play "Naptime."
- Hello, Miss.
- Hello.
Can I get you anything
from the trolley?
Um, I'd like
five cups of tea, please.
Of course! (CHUCKLES)
And some milk, and sugar...
POOH: (SOFTLY) And honey.
Honey, please.
Lots of honey.
POOH: And the game is called,
"Say What You See."
You first, Piglet.
(PANTING) Panic. Worry.
Catastrophe.
Speed! Danger!
Recklessness! (CHUCKLES)
- Disgrace. Shame. Humiliation.
- TIGGER: Oh. Ooh.
Well, that's one way
to play it.
There's going to be no fun
like this
at boarding school, Pooh.
Oh. Why not just not go
to boring school?
If I can get these papers
to Father...
then maybe he'll be so happy
that he won't make me go.
Dreams don't come
for free, Pooh.
You've got to fight for them.
Nothing comes from nothing.
Oh, yes.
Doing nothing often leads
to the very best something.
What?
Who told you that?
Christopher Robin.
That doesn't sound
like Father.
He also said
that your happiness
means the world to him.
TIGGER: He sure did.
That's right.
- He said that.
- TIGGER: Mmm-hmm.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
CHRISTOPHER:
Hold the lift, please.
PORTER: Yes, sir.
CHRISTOPHER: Ah, thank you.
Ah, ready for
the presentation, Robin?
CHRISTOPHER: Ah, yes.
It's all in here, sir.
GILES: Hmm.
(GILES CLEARS THROAT)
Well, see you
on the dance floor.
We're all counting on you.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(PANTING)
EEYORE: Who are these people?
PIGLET: Oh, it's so loud!
POOH: Welcome to Lon Don.
TIGGER:
How come nobody's bouncing?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Winslow Luggage, please.
On Torrington Street.
Whatever you say, guv'nah.
Where are you, Maddy?
(PANTING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (HORNS BLARING)
Come on, mate.
I haven't got all day.
MAN: I'm not doing this
for fun, you know?
Hey, what the...? (GASPS)
There's a Tigger
looking right at me.
But I'm the only one!
- (SOFTLY) What are you doing?
- Tigger, be quiet.
I just saw the most
preposterous imposterator.
- (WHISPERS) Tigger.
- DRIVER: What's that, love?
Oh. Nothing.
I'm just talking
to my teddies.
There's another one!
Look at him.
His eyes
are too close together.
Look at his big, silly nose,
and his flippy-floppy ears.
That's not very nappy.
Look at that silly stripe.
Imposterator!
EEYORE: Calm down.
Now is not the time
for napping, Madeline.
I wanna look him
straight in the eye.
PIGLET: Oh, he's not stopping!
EEYORE: No, he won't.
My kinda speed!
Follow that Tigger!
- (LAUGHS)
- (SCREAMS)
You're losing him!
(HORN BLARING)
(ALL GASPS)
(TYRES SCREECHING)
TIGGER:
Perfect! You exploded him!
Good morning.
- (SCREAMS)
- Thank you for the ride.
- Is everyone all right?
- TIGGER: Cheese and crackers.
My neck, my back!
I can't feel my toes.
That was so much fun!
Let's do it again!
Marvelous, mate.
Oh, thank you
very much indeed.
That's fantastic.
This is my livelihood!
What in the blue blazes
is going on here?
Officer, thank goodness
you're here.
I don't think we played
"Naptime" very well.
DRIVER: You need
to arrest this lot here.
Immediately.
What? This little girl
with her stuffed animals
is givin' you
the fear, is she?
No, no, there's something
strange going on with them.
Something spooky.
Are you on the lemonade, mate?
(WHISPERS)
Madeline, look!
Doesn't that say "Woozle?"
DRIVER:
What are you incinerating?
POLICEMAN: Incinerating?
DRIVER: Yeah, what are you
incinerating about me?
POLICEMAN: No, no, I think
you've got the wrong word.
Excuse me. Officer?
Yes, my darling?
That's my father there.
Okay, well, off you pop.
And be careful.
I will.
Thank you, Officer.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, orifice.
What a nice man.
Here's me cabbie license.
You don't believe me?
That is a certificate
of excellent...
There's that face.
I did that face.
You seen him.
You saw, didn't you?
You saw.
You have witnessed
the peculiarity, haven't ya?
What did we see?
- The bear talking.
- Little teddy bear.
No, you didn't.
You saw no such thing.
- Talking.
- POLICEMAN: No, it was not.
- SALESMAN: It was.
- That's right, write it down.
- It wasn't. We misheard it.
- There was a pig as well.
- There was a pig.
- It was a talking pig.
OLD MAN WINSLOW:
As you were.
Right, we all know
why we're here.
No one wants to see the
Winslow Luggage ship sink...
so hard decisions
must be made.
Now, Robin and I
worked tirelessly
the whole weekend on this.
But I don't want
to take all the credit...
so I'll let Robin
present our solutions.
TIGGER: We're never gonna
find Christopher Robin
inside this box.
Can you see any of the others?
MADELINE: Hello? How are you
getting on in there?
EEYORE: Dark. Gloomy.
You should just leave me here.
(WHIMPERS) Don't leave us.
Tigger! Lift it, lift it!
I got you, Piglet.
Don't worry.
Ain't too heavy for Tigger.
- Thank goodness.
- Tiggers are strong!
Sit tight,
and we'll be there soon.
Sit tight?
What does that mean?
It means stay right here
in this very, very safe box.
Tiggers don't
sit tight.
Tiggers barely sit at all.
I gotta tell her.
Madeline!
(YELPS) My tail is trapped!
Pooh?
Did you hear that?
It's hard to hear anything
above my tummy rumbling.
Okay. Don't worry,
I'll get us outta this mess!
PIGLET:
Madeline said to sit tight
and she's
the Wimbledon Champion!
The good news is
that I've found some cuts.
But it's not going to be easy.
We'll have to
reduce overheads...
and find cheaper suppliers.
Well, there'll be sacrifices
to be made
in terms of our workforce.
He's talking about me.
- Yes, I think he probably is.
- Oh, dear.
Sacrifices are fine, Robin.
Just show us the proposals.
Right, um...
It's all here. In my papers.
Um...
They are a tad rushed...
so, um, I'd bear with me.
Um, hold on.
GILES: Robin.
Oh, no!
OLD MAN WINSLOW: Robin!
If we don't
solve the issue,
we'll have no choice
but to shut down!
What have you got?
CHRISTOPHER:
Uh... Well, sir...
I think what's happened is...
(WHISPERS)
I'm so sorry, Mr. Robin.
There's an emergency.
Your wife is outside.
She can't find Madeline.
Oh, ladies and gentlemen,
I have to step outside.
Please excuse me.
GILES: What the devil
are you doing?
TIGGER: My tail!
You're gonna pull it off!
EEYORE: No tail lasts forever.
TIGGER: Bounce with me!
Bounce, bounce, bounce!
Everybody bounce!
Careful, Tigger.
Things might get worse!
Nonsense! Nothing ever
bad came from bouncing.
(ALL GRUNTING)
EEYORE: It's getting worse.
(ALL YELPING)
EVELYN: This way. Up here.
CHRISTOPHER: (STAMMERS)
Where is she?
I don't know. Somewhere
between here and the station.
She's all alone.
CHRISTOPHER: "Expotition?"
- No, she's not alone.
- Who's she with?
EEYORE: I wanna go home.
TIGGER: We'll be fine.
We won't hit anything else.
(ALL SCREAM)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Robin was
a reasonably good man.
Shame he went mad.
Oh, dear.
CHRISTOPHER: The wonderful thing
about Tiggers is...
their tops are made
out of rubber,
their bottoms are made
out of springs.
(TIGGER LAUGHING)
Tail, you're back!
Tastes like milk.
I was pretending
that there was a Heffalump.
But of course, there wasn't
really a Heffalump.
Are you hearing yourself?
You need to quit.
I think that decision's
about to be made for me.
Stick with me, Piglet.
I'll fix this!
You worry too much.
Oh, we'll never get
to Christopher now!
CHRISTOPHER: Maybe we should ask
if anyone's seen a bear
or a Tigger
or a very small donkey.
Darling, these creatures
aren't real.
TIGGER: Don't worry.
This is part of the plan.
PIGLET: Careful!
We don't want to fly out!
TIGGER: We just need
a leap of faith!
EVELYN: Listen, I will call
Dr. Cunningham on Monday.
I think with
the right amount of rest...
- (EVELYN GASPS)
- (EEYORE GROANS)
- TIGGER: Christopher!
- Tigger! Eeyore!
(PIGLET SCREAMING)
- Piglet!
- Ah.
My plan worked.
I don't know how I do it.
PIGLET: You must be
Christopher Robin's wife.
Ha. How do you do?
EEYORE: My bum hurts.
- And now this.
- Oh.
What have we here?
Some sort of medal?
Voodoo emblem, do you think?
GILES:
Madness takes many forms, Father.
OLD MAN WINSLOW: It does.
I thought you were
working on this, too.
Don't you have a copy?
Um...
I have
an alternative solution.
Ah. I'm listening.
We fire the entire efficiency
department for a start.
CHRISTOPHER:
Let's get going.
Where's Madeline?
She's in a truck.
Headed Woozlewards!
Woozlewards?
- Winslow's!
Drive to Winslow's.
That's where Madeline will be.
We're going to Winslow's, yes.
- (POOH GRUNTS)
- MADELINE: Where are the others?
POOH: They must've gone off
on their own expotition.
At least they left us
the important papers.
MADELINE: We need to get these
to Father right away.
Come on, Pooh!
- Christopher?
- Yes, hon?
- Is that a talking donkey?
- It's Eeyore.
Eeyore, this is Evelyn,
my wife.
EEYORE: Hello, Evelyn my wife.
Hello, talking donkey,
how are you doing today?
EEYORE: Don't get me started.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
We did it, Pooh!
POOH: Oh, yes!
(GRUNTING)
POOH: Oh, no!
(GRUNTS)
- Oh.
- Oh, Pooh.
- (SIGHS)
- Poor Christopher.
- I'm so sorry, Madeline.
- (SIGHS)
- CHRISTOPHER: Madeline!
- POOH: Christopher Robin!
Daddy!
Thank God we found you.
Are you all right?
(SIGHS)
I lost your papers.
I'm so sorry.
Madeline!
Darling, that doesn't matter.
You're safe.
That's all that's important.
Not my papers.
But your work is so important.
I thought that maybe if
I brought you your papers...
that you wouldn't
send me away,
and then we could
all be together.
I saved a little bit.
Sweetheart.
I was wrong about work.
I was wrong
about everything...
and I'm so sorry.
I've been a father
of very little brain.
I lost myself, Maddy.
And I almost lost you.
My most precious love.
And I don't
want you to go away.
You don't have to go
to boarding school.
You can stay here with us,
and I'll never let you go.
(SNIFFLING)
CHRISTOPHER: And I'll read you
a bedtime story every night.
I'd like that.
Though maybe I'll choose
from now on.
(LAUGHS) All right.
EVELYN: Oh, you gave us
a real fright.
Well, another
disastrous expotition.
I don't know
about that, Eeyore.
It all depends
on how you look at things.
(EVELYN SIGHS)
MADELINE: Mom, did you know
that we went to the train
and had a tea party?
Darling, you're a genius!
Oh.
Come on!
Oh. Off we go again.
Righto.
CHRISTOPHER:
Come on, it's not too late.
EVELYN: Oh. Wait for me!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
HAL: Mr. Robin?
Come on!
Ooh, that floor would be
good for bouncing! Whoo-hoo!
Oh, you're back!
Thank goodness.
Stop!
I have the answer.
This better be
worth the wait.
Oh, it is, sir.
Because the answer
to all your problems...
is nothing.
Nothing?
Nothing comes
from nothing, Robin.
Oh, that's where you're wrong.
Doing nothing leads to
the very best something.
(WHISPERS)
I told you, he's gone crackers.
What happens when people
have time off work?
Nothing to do.
They go on holiday.
And what do people need
to go on holiday?
Luggage, Mr. Winslow!
You employ thousands of people
all across your companies...
and if you were to give them
all paid holidays...
Paid holidays?
CHRISTOPHER: At the moment...
you supply the wealthy.
And no one else.
Do you see?
But now look.
If we all could afford
to go on holiday...
up here...
there would be hundreds
and thousands
of ordinary people...
going to the countryside,
to the lakes, and beaches...
all with their
Winslow Luggage.
And if we made
the prices cheaper...
then everybody could afford
to buy them.
Oh, great.
Our lovely beaches rammed
with hoi polloi...
with their gramophones
and bottles of cider.
Now, now, hold on, Giles.
Father, please.
This is clearly codswallop!
Well, you would say that,
wouldn't you, Giles?
And why is that?
Because you're a Woozle.
(WHISPERS) So that's what
- a Woozle looks like.
- Shh.
What the devil is a Woozle?
A Woozle is a slinking,
little monster...
who gets everyone else
to do his work for him...
and hopes that we forget
what's important in our lives.
Our families.
Our dear friends.
The people who love us.
The people whom we love.
We're here to tell you...
I'm here to tell you...
that we're not afraid
of Heffalumps
and Woozles anymore. Are we?
Dear Lord,
he has lost his marbles.
Has he?
Let's address the Heffalump
in the room, shall we?
What were you doing
this weekend, Giles?
GILES: What?
Me?
(GILES STAMMERS)
I told you I was working.
- (CLATTERS)
- OLD MAN WINSLOW: Oh.
Now, I've not heard
of a Woozle before, son.
But by the sound of it,
you are one.
Me? A Woozle?
Now sit down, Giles.
- (CHAIR CREAKS)
- (YELPS)
(CHUCKLES)
OLD MAN WINSLOW:
Congratulations, Robin.
I'd like you to start
on this immediately.
Thank you very much, sir.
I look forward to it.
But first...
I'm going to be doing nothing
for a while with my family.
Because when you do nothing...
it leads to the very best
of a something.
Did I get that right?
- Close enough, sir.
- OLD MAN WINSLOW: Ah.
Are you ready?
Oh, Eeyore.
Here.
Ah.
Now we're ready.
Come on.
We're going on holiday. Yes.
That donkey was staring at me.
A donkey staring at you?
Clearly, it's you
who've lost your marbles.
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Oh, boy.
It is good to be home.
- (SNIFFING)
- Oh, I suppose so.
Weather's too nice.
Oh! Home sweet home!
Where have you all been?
I was about to mount
a search party.
(ROO GIGGLES)
RABBIT: Hello.
ROO: Who's that, Mum?
KANGA: That's a little girl.
I believe that's a Madeline.
Ah! Christopher Robin!
You've brought guests.
Welcome to Hundred Acre Wood.
OWL: Right, Rabbit.
Fetch tea.
RABBIT: I beg your pardon?
You don't get this in Lon Don.
CHRISTOPHER:
Go this way, come on.
(TIGGER LAUGHS)
Keep north, Christopher.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
EVELYN: Now everyone is happy.
Owl, would you like some tea?
- OWL: Is it the way I like it?
- RABBIT: Just say yes or no.
I'll take this to Pooh.
TIGGER: Come on, Madeline!
I'm gonna show you
how to bounce. (LAUGHS)
You're gonna jump real high.
- That's right.
- (MADELINE GIGGLES)
You're almost
as good as I am.
And Tiggers are the best
springers in the world!
You're a natural, kid.
Tigger, just not too high.
ROO: Please, may I have
the last jam tart?
EEYORE:
Thank you, Evelyn my wife.
TIGGER: Look at that! Amazing!
Ooh. (CHUCKLES)
How did you know?
Mmm.
(SLURPING)
Christopher Robin.
What day is it?
It's today.
Oh.
My favorite day.
Mine too, Pooh.
Mine, too.
Yesterday,
when it was tomorrow...
it was
too much day for me.
Silly old bear.
(JOLLY MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING) ♪ I'm busy,
busy, busy doing nothing ♪
♪ Doing nothing,
that's the life for me ♪
♪ For when I'm doing nothing,
I'm busy doing something ♪
♪ Something that suits me
to a "t" ♪
♪ Because I'm busy,
busy doing nothing ♪
♪ I find I never find
the time to rest ♪
♪ Being busy doing nothing,
I'm busy doing something ♪
♪ Doing nothing is
the something I do best ♪
♪ I'm busy, busy,
busy doing nothing ♪
♪ Doing nothing,
that's the life for me ♪
♪ For when I'm doing nothing,
I'm busy doing something ♪
♪ Something that suits me
to a "t" ♪
♪ Because I'm busy,
busy doing nothing ♪
♪ I find I never find
the time to rest ♪
♪ Being busy doing nothing,
I'm busy doing something ♪
♪ Doing nothing is
the something I do best ♪
I think things are changing.
And not for the worse.
Thank ya for noticing me.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)