♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
(steam hissing)
♪ ♪
- (whistle blows)
- CONDUCTOR: All aboard!
All aboard!
(whistle blows)
♪ ♪
(train whistle blowing)
(whistle blowing)
♪ ♪
(bell jingles)
(jingling)
- Morning.
- Special one today.
Blimey.
What have you got there?
- Wouldn't you like to know.
- (scoffs)
♪ ♪
Just arrived, milord.
There's one
from Buckingham Palace.
Heavens.
- (Robert speaks indistinctly)
- MARY: But we really need
to cut back until the farms
repay the investment.
And we must make a plan
for the roof.
Well, this won't help us
to economize.
What is it?
The king and queen
are coming to stay.
What?
During their Yorkshire tour?
That's it.
Just for a night.
They'll spend one night
at Downton
and then go on to Harewood
for a ball.
While they're here,
there's to be a parade
of the Yorkshire Hussars
in the village.
Is there any chance
Henry might be back?
Well, I doubt it.
I'll send a telegram.
But there's a motor show
in Chicago
that I know he cannot chuck.
Tom, you're keeping
your enthusiasm under control.
Is this the Irish patriot
making a reappearance?
I know you find my opinions
highly entertaining.
I suppose they'll send people
to check that Mrs. Patmore
- isn't a Russian spy.
- MARY: Mm.
Will you tell them
downstairs, Barrow?
- I'll see to Her Ladyship.
- Yes, milord.
A royal luncheon,
a parade and a dinner?
I'm going to have to sit down.
- Oh, what about Mr. Branson?
- What about him?
Well, he's a republican,
isn't he?
Should Mr. Carson look in,
no one is to say that word
in front of him.
I agree with Mr. Branson.
I don't like kings, either.
I suppose that makes me
a republican, too.
Are the English allowed to be?
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
EDITH:
Two weeks to get ready? Golly.
It's quite an honor.
CORA (over phone):
It is. But if I know
anything about royal visits,
we will never stop
changing our clothes.
(laughs) I've just been
on a buying spree,
which is good.
Madame Handley-Seymour
is making me a ball dress.
- I'll get her to hurry it up.
- Have her send it here.
- How are things otherwise?
- Oh, you know.
I've got a luncheon for 30
today in aid of the lifeboats.
Or is that tomorrow?
Anyway,
it's in aid of something.
Sounds like business as usual.
I'll see you soon, darling.
(birds chirping)
You know I can bring back
as many vegetables
as we could eat.
- Yeah, I like to keep busy.
- (softly): Yeah.
How have they taken the news
up at the house?
Daisy's singing
"The Marseillaise."
(chuckles)
So no surprises there.
- (sighs)
- Oh, what's the matter?
I thought you'd be pleased.
I am pleased.
The visit is a great honor.
But members of the royal
and imperial household
are coming to Downton
who will have visited
the greatest houses in the land.
Blenheim, Chatsworth, Arundel.
Does Mr. Barrow know
what he's taking on?
Why should it affect you?
You're not in charge anymore.
Now, come in for your lunch
and let me get back.
♪ ♪
All right, sir, here we are.
This will do very well.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
(door opens)
FOOTMAN:
The Lady Bagshaw, Your Majesty.
QUEEN MARY:
Good.
We'll go to the 1844 Room
as soon as they're here.
Do sit down.
I've just received the plan for
the tour of Yorkshire, ma'am.
Yes. It's just been finalized.
I think we'll enjoy it.
I didn't realize we would be
staying at Downton Abbey.
Only for a night.
There's to be a parade
and a dinner,
and then we go on
to Princess Mary at Harewood.
I just wondered
if I might, perhaps,
go straight to Harewood.
Lord Grantham is my cousin,
and the two families have...
fallen out.
Or at least we might
if I were there in person.
And what would cause
this quarrel?
Lord Grantham's mother believes
her son should be my heir.
Old Lady Grantham can be
very hard to resist,
as I am well aware.
Exactly, ma'am.
But, surely, they need to know
if their hopes
are to be disappointed.
(sighs softly)
I wish I knew if they like
simple food or fancy.
I can't think
they'll want simple food.
With that sort,
don't they like sauces
and everything velouté and
frappé and smothered in cream?
"That sort"?
He's the King of England.
There's only one of them
in the world.
"That sort," indeed.
Don't plan too much.
Not until we know
what's expected.
Well, I know what's
expected of me... food.
You, too, Daisy. So less
philosophy, more elbow grease.
- Is the pudding ready?
- It is.
Oh, Daisy, take the soufflés
out of the oven
while I find me specs.
DAISY:
This country needs a shake-up.
- Ah, you should run for parliament.
- (scoffs)
Why not?
Lady Astor's done it.
And so an under-cook
from Yorkshire
is bound to follow her.
Well, you've got to have
big dreams.
But do you have
big dreams, Andy?
I've not offended you, have I?
- Why do you say that?
- Well, for a start,
you never talk
about the wedding anymore.
We'll get wed when we're
good and ready and not before.
But, you see, I am ready.
Take those up
before they collapse.
Maud Bagshaw is coming
to Downton?
Yes, as the queen's
lady-in-waiting.
Oh, my goodness.
Why so surprised?
Who is she?
Well, she's a cousin
of your father's.
(chuckles):
We'll-we'll discuss it later.
You're not
to make things awkward.
How's it all going?
Well, Mary's got it
under control.
Hardly. There's so much to do.
Who were those men measuring
on the green as we came past?
They're building the dais
for the queen at the parade.
- LORD MERTON: Oh, how exciting.
- Seems rather a waste of money.
Oh, here we go.
Isn't that what
the monarchy's for?
To brighten the lives
of the nation
with stateliness and glamour?
To quote Tennyson, "Kind hearts
are more than coronets,
And simple faith
than Norman blood."
Will you have enough clichés
to get you through the visit?
If not, I'll come to you.
(quiet chatter)
- ROBERT: Thank you, Barrow.
- (door closes)
And, now, you were gonna
tell us about Lady Bagshaw.
Is she a very distant cousin?
No. Her father was
my great uncle.
Then why have I
never heard of her?
Because she chose to cut
herself off from the family.
- Do you know the reason?
- Maybe.
See, I believe she means
to cheat your father
of his rightful inheritance.
She has no children.
Your father is
her nearest relation.
I won't have her put
on the spot.
ISOBEL:
You're plotting something.
I see a Machiavellian look
in your eye.
Machiavelli is
frequently underrated.
He had many qualities.
So did Caligula,
not all of them charming.
What are you up to, Granny?
Well, ideally, I would like
Maud to see your father
as the son she never had.
Will she be the mother
I never had?
Sarcasm is
the lowest form of wit.
- (piano playing)
- (panting)
- WOMAN: Oh. Hello.
- BATES: Mr. Molesley.
It's very late for you
to be out.
(panting):
Is it true?
Is what true, Mr. Molesley?
Mr. Bakewell said
that you'd warned him
that there was to be
a royal visit.
Well, now I know who not
to trust with a secret.
That we should deserve
such honor.
Not you, too.
I am disappointed.
- Ignore her.
- MOLESLEY: I wonder, do you think
I might be allowed
to slip on my livery again?
Would the school let you?
Oh, they'll give me time
for this, I promise.
Let's wait
till we know our orders.
What about it, Mr. Barrow?
Will you let me wait upon
my king and queen?
Uh, well...
- (bell rings)
- That's us.
Good night, Mr. Molesley.
BATES: When we're done,
shall I fetch Johnny
- or will you?
- I can fetch him.
(chuckling):
How exciting.
- Thank you.
- DAISY: They're all mental.
All this fuss for a man
and woman we don't even know.
No, never mind that.
I wanted to tell you.
I've had some ideas about what
to serve at your wedding.
Stop going on about my wedding.
♪ ♪
HUGHES:
We've only a few days left,
so I spoke to Her Ladyship,
and she's agreed
our normal rules
should be suspended.
We won't clean a room
if a family member is using it,
but, otherwise,
all restrictions are lifted.
No detail should be left
undone, however small.
I want every surface
in this house
to gleam and sparkle
by Thursday.
- (exhales) Blimey.
- (murmuring)
Can I have your attention,
please?
Uh, for this afternoon,
Their Majesties' butler,
Mr. Wilson,
will be coming over
from Raby Castle
with a lady's maid and a valet.
To give us our instructions?
With the royal servants,
are we to wait on them?
That is what
will be made clear.
I won't be waiting
on any valets and lady's maids,
thank you very much.
Before we get hot under the
collar, let's just wait and see
- what they have to say.
- BATES: Amen.
(indistinct chatter)
(trolley bell rings)
Mr. Branson.
(bell jingling)
(trolley bell rings)
(keys jangle)
Can I help you, sir?
It's really you I came to see.
- Oh. Well, how can I help you, Mister...?
- Chetwode.
Major Chetwode.
Am I right you're Mr. Branson,
Lord Grantham's son-in-law?
- I am.
- (chuckling): Oh.
The, uh... the papers tell me
the king and queen
will be staying at Downton Abbey
during their tour of Yorkshire.
Well, if it's in the papers,
it must be true.
Yes. Great honor.
Although, as an Irishman,
you may feel differently.
I know when my parents-in-law
have been paid a compliment.
Well, there's to be
a military parade, I gather.
How do you...
how do you feel about that?
What do you mean, how do I feel?
Only you didn't say
whether you support them,
the... king and queen.
I support Lord Grantham.
Very neat.
Until we meet again,
Mr. Branson.
Ah, Barrow.
They said you'd be in here.
Heavens. We can still
put on quite a show
when we need to,
I'm glad to see.
Has it all been cleaned?
More or less everything's been
done to a basic level, milady.
But we haven't done
the final buffing-up.
Why not?
I was waiting
for Their Majesties' butler.
I thought I'd ask his advice
on what to use on the table.
Really?
Can't we decide what we lay
on our own dining table?
(door opens)
Front doorbell, Mr. Barrow.
Please, go.
Milady.
♪ ♪
Greetings, Mr. Wilson.
Welcome to Downton Abbey.
(exhales)
(grunts)
Uh, this way, Mr. Wilson.
The royal butler's
terribly scary.
Barrow looked like a rabbit
in front of a cobra.
Oh, dear.
Should I go down?
They know what they're doing.
Do they?
They're hideously behind.
There's a mark on the Blue Room
carpet we can't shift.
I have no chairs for the parade.
And we haven't even decided
on the footmen.
I'm going to have another cup,
if no one's coming up to serve.
This is nice.
Princess Mary wants us
for tea tomorrow at Harewood.
Ugh, I've got so much to do.
I wonder if that means
the young couple
have taken over the big house.
They're hardly
"the young couple."
Well, he isn't, anyway.
She always seems
quite shy to me.
A shy royal?
Is that an oxymoron?
Anyway, we're going.
(quietly):
Right.
I will return to Raby Castle
and come back to Downton
in advance of Their Majesties
on Thursday.
But His Majesty's valet,
Mr. Ellis,
and Her Majesty's dresser,
Miss Lawton,
will stay on,
if that is convenient.
Or they can put up
in the village.
No, we'll find them rooms.
Then Monsieur Courbet,
the chef...
PATMORE:
E-Excuse me.
- Mr. Courbet, the chef?
- That's right.
We'd be very grateful if you
could make the kitchens ready.
So, what should I order?
Nothing.
He will bring it all.
And we don't cook any
of the food?
Um, cook for the servants.
Monsieur Courbet
won't have time for that.
Oh, I see.
That is something
to look forward to.
Calm yourself, Mrs. Patmore.
If it's the way
these things are done...
WILSON: Mrs. Webb
and four footmen will arrive
with Monsieur Courbet
the day before.
HUGHES:
Who is this...
Mrs. Webb, is it?
She is the housekeeper.
She will also bring two maids
with her.
The housekeeper?
WILSON:
While Their Majesties are here.
HUGHES:
And the maids?
They will make the beds,
clean the bathrooms...
that sort of thing.
I see.
So, my maids and I will not be
involved in the preparations?
You mean, during the stay,
you'll be the butler, and...
Excuse me.
I am not a butler.
I am the king's
Page of the Backstairs.
(soft chuckling, snorting)
So, our staff has nothing to do?
I'm sure they can be useful.
But how can they eat
and get dressed at Raby Castle
if the chef and the valet
and the maid are all here?
We have two of each.
The principal valet
and the principal dresser
will arrive in advance
of Their Majesties,
who bring an equerry,
a lady-in-waiting,
two detectives
and two chauffeurs.
The other chef goes from Raby
to Harewood.
Four footmen go with him,
and the other four come here.
Do you all understand me?
You can hardly heckle
Lady Bagshaw
in front of the queen.
Well, I'm just trying
to prevent a crime.
- Who says it's a crime?
- I do.
Oh, and you're an expert
in the matter?
I am an expert in every matter.
You must have some idea
why she doesn't want Robert
as her heir.
I have none.
He is her closest relative.
The family have held Brompton
for three centuries.
But she wants to give it to who?
Charity?
The dogs' home?
- (chuckles)
- Well, I would have thought
the family had enough
to worry about.
That's not the point.
Well, very well.
We must try
and discover her reasons.
Well, what possible reasons
can there be?
Well, that's what I intend
to find out.
- ♪ ♪
- (birds chirping)
- Carson.
- Oh, milady.
Please come in.
This is an honor.
I don't want to be a nuisance,
but I need your help, Carson.
Barrow just isn't up
to the task.
- Milady?
- He won't clean the silver.
- Or he won't let Andrew clean it.
- What?
He says the page of the...
thingummy
- will choose which pieces to use.
- I see.
The truth is,
he's in a sort of trance.
Won't you help me?
I feel I'm pushing
a rock uphill.
I'll be there in the morning,
milady. Don't you worry.
You're a treasure, Carson.
That's all there is to say.
I'll see myself out.
(door closes)
- You could never refuse her anything.
- Mm.
And what about Mr. Barrow?
Mr. Barrow can like it
or lump it.
Then I'm afraid he'll lump it.
We have supper
after the upstairs dinner,
so you've plenty of time.
Thanks.
How does it work
with two valets?
Well, I prepare
His Majesty's clothes
and uniforms for Downton.
Then, when Mr. Miller arrives,
I get the stuff
for Harewood ready.
Then I head back to London
and prepare for their return.
- It all overlaps.
- So, Mr. Miller's the one
who actually dresses the king?
Unless he's ill. Then it's me.
Is he often ill?
No. (chuckles)
I think it's rubbish.
They impose, they demand,
and now we're to be made
nothing in our own house.
It's very disappointing,
I won't deny it.
This water's not too hot.
Have they all been having baths?
How should I know?
Mr. Barrow, don't you think you
should speak to His Lordship?
- About what?
- Well, it's not right, surely,
for us to be humiliated
in this way.
Well, what could he do about it?
Is the staff
always ridden over roughshod
whenever royalty come to stay?
Why do they bring
so many servants with them?
Maybe it's because they go
from house to house
around the county
and they need to know
things are done
the way they like.
- As if we couldn't manage that.
- We're not footballs,
Mr. Bates,
and we don't deserve a kicking.
♪ ♪
ROBERT:
But what are we
to say to Barrow? After all,
he's done nothing wrong.
He's done nothing at all.
That's the problem.
But it feels very unfair.
Oh, I see.
- So it's now.
- CARSON: I've sent down
for Mr. Barrow to join us,
milord.
(door opens)
THOMAS:
You wanted to see me, milord?
Mr. Carson!
What brings you here?
Well, this is the thing.
Carson is going to move
back into the house
for the royal visit.
What?
You are coming back here
as butler
when I am the butler here?
Yes, uh, that is...
Can I ask how long
this has been planned, milord?
Well, I wouldn't say
it's been exactly planned.
THOMAS:
Because I don't quite understand
where it leaves me.
- Well, you can be a sort of...
- With your permission,
I'd prefer not to be
a "sort of" anything, milord.
I will surrender my position
for the duration of the visit,
if I must,
and serve you again
when Their Majesties
have gone, if you so wish.
- Please don't think that...
- By the way,
the boiler's playing up,
and there's no hot water.
- God, that's all we need.
- (door opens)
ROBERT:
Now, Barrow...
(sighs)
Not to worry. The plumber
will soon have it mended,
milady,
and we'll bring water jugs
up to the bedrooms tonight
and in the morning.
(chuckling):
It can't be that hard.
We did it for 300 years.
(sighs)
Thank you, Carson.
Well, that went well.
Will you sack him?
No. As a matter of fact,
I was quite interested.
I never thought of him
as a man of principle before.
♪ ♪
(groans)
I'll have to tell him
I'm only ordering
for the servants' hall.
I'm afraid
I've got his hopes up.
- (bell jingles)
- Aha!
BAKEWELL:
Oh, speak of the devil.
Come in, come in. I was
just saying you'll be wanting
- to finalize the order.
- Were you, indeed?
MOLESLEY:
Honestly, no one in the village
- can talk about anything else.
- Of course.
Oh, now, I know it's
a bit of a liberty,
but I've made a list
of all the ingredients
of your favorite dishes.
I know them well enough
after all these years.
But some things
will have to be brought in,
so we should really
get on with it.
Oh, well, I appreciate
everything you've done,
Mr. Bakewell...
(Bakewell and Molesley chuckle)
My heart is fit to burst,
I don't mind telling you.
I shall have fed
the king-emperor
from my own shop.
If only my father were alive.
He'd be so proud of me.
He would.
Well, I-I'm sure he'd be proud
of you anyway, Mr. Bakewell.
Oh, no, no, not like this, no.
This is the peak of my career.
Well, the peak
of my life, really.
Everyone's so jealous.
Oh, now, I've put ticks
next to the ones
I think you'll go for.
- Now, the thing is...
- I'm guessing the luncheon
will be for around a dozen.
Of course,
the dinner will be larger.
Let's say 30 or thereabouts?
- (Molesley chuckles)
- You'll correct me if I'm wrong.
- Well, you see...
- You're not wrong, Mr. Bakewell.
But we'll say
if the numbers change.
The pavlova's not realistic.
We'd be safer
with a charlotte russe.
We can do most
of the work before.
MOLESLEY:
And I shall be serving!
Think of that!
(chuckles)
♪ I've danced with a man
who's danced with a girl ♪
♪ Who's danced
with the Prince of Wales ♪
- ♪ I'm crazy with excitement ♪
- No. Stop it, Mr. Molesley.
♪ Completely off the rails. ♪
(laughs)
All of my suppliers
are so excited.
Oh, Mrs. Patmore,
I shall never be able
to thank you enough,
not if I live to be 100.
- (chuckles)
- (door opens, bell jingles)
- I feel like a liar.
- (door closes)
I should go back.
And lower yourself
to a kitchen skivvy
in the eyes of the village?
Never mind ruining
Mr. Bakewell's year.
You'll do no such thing.
♪ ♪
(horn honks)
No maid. No valet.
No nanny, even.
- It's 1927.
- (Robert chuckles)
We're modern folk.
Nanny will take care
of Marigold.
And Anna can look after you.
Really? Can she?
CORA:
Of course.
Just like the old days.
Granny's here, and Isobel,
and we're paying a call this
afternoon on Princess Mary.
Oh. Has my new ball dress
arrived?
Not yet, but it will.
(sighs) Hello, Mary.
How are you?
How long have you worked
for Her Majesty, Miss Lawton?
- Six years.
- How interesting.
I expect you're a skilled
needlewoman for that job.
Well, I've had no complaints.
I trained under Madame Lucile.
Her Majesty wanted
a professional dressmaker.
And they found you?
My reputation found me.
- (clock chiming)
- (quiet chatter)
Oh.
Come on, you two.
It's nearly 3:00.
We ought to get ready.
- Will the princess be at the parade?
- Thank you.
- They both will.
- What time are they expecting us?
I always find her rather sad,
Princess Mary.
Well, she is royal.
Royal women are not meant
to grin like Cheshire cats.
Well, they don't have
to look miserable.
Well, to you,
she looks miserable.
To me, she looks dignified.
Doesn't that say it all?
How comforting
to see you here, Carson.
What prompted you to take up
the flaming sword again?
I felt I should go where I
could do the most good, milady.
Wise words for all of us.
♪ ♪
Her Royal Highness is here.
(door opens)
The Marchioness of Hexham,
the Countess of Grantham,
the Lady Mary Talbot.
Your Royal Highness.
Please, sit down, Lady Grantham.
I suppose you're in turmoil
because of my parents' visit.
I do sympathize.
We don't need
to explain it to you.
- Just don't paint anything.
- (Cora chuckles)
They're sick
of the smell of new paint.
- (chuckling)
- I hope it's not too late.
EDITH:
Are you living here now, ma'am?
No. No, we're still
at Goldsborough.
But Lord Harewood's
not well, so...
- we've come to run the visit and the ball.
- (door opens)
(boys chatting indistinctly
in other room)
- (chuckles): Oh, hello.
- (door closes)
Hello, my darlings.
How have you been?
(grunts)
Have you been having
a lovely day? Hmm?
(boys speaking indistinctly)
(door closes)
Yes?
This is your lucky day.
I'm the new plumber,
Tony Sellick.
Oh, yes. Right.
Well, I'd better show you
where the boiler is.
Where are you off to?
This is Mr. Sellick,
the plumber.
I'm taking him
to the boiler house.
- I'll do it.
- DAISY: No, you're all right.
Just tell Mrs. Patmore
where I am.
(clicks tongue)
- (door opens)
- Please bring the boys on Thursday.
Oh, how lovely.
Why are the children in here?
We just got back,
and they wanted to...
They're not allowed in
the drawing room before 6:00.
- I know, milord. But they...
- Take them upstairs.
And don't bring them
down again tonight.
- NANNY: Yes, milord.
- But they were only...
Thank you, Nanny.
- BOY: Please, Nanny?
- NANNY: No, we're going.
(Nanny and boys
speaking indistinctly)
(door opens)
You remember Lady Grantham
and her daughters?
Lady Grantham.
They want us to bring the boys
to the parade.
No. They'd only cause a ruckus.
We were hoping
you would both stay
for dinner that night,
Lord Lascelles.
No, I'm afraid not.
Well...
I'll leave you to it.
♪ ♪
(door closes)
Well, I suppose
I better let you get started,
- so I'll be on me way.
- Aren't you gonna wish me luck?
You don't look as if you need me
to wish you luck, Mr. Sellick.
Or anyone else, for that matter.
You don't know what I need.
And I don't intend to find out.
♪ ♪
BERTIE: Do we need
to cut the grass again?
They're doing it
tomorrow morning.
CHETWODE:
Hello, Mr. Branson. Ah.
Getting ready
for Their Majesties, I see.
- That's right. This is Lord Hexham.
- Ah.
May I present Major Chetwode.
- Are you here for the parade?
- I am. I'm staying at the pub.
- MAN: Milord?
- Excuse me.
Or are you here
to keep an eye on me?
I was rather hoping you'd be
my guide for the ceremony.
Would you like a drink?
I'll join you in a minute.
BERTIE:
Well, well done.
- Who's he?
- (sighs) I don't really know.
Army, perhaps.
Or maybe a civil servant.
But I'll drink with him
and try and put his mind
at rest.
What does he want?
Maybe to make sure I'm a leopard
who has changed his spots.
♪ ♪
ANNA:
What about you, milady?
- Is everything ready?
- No.
And my heart is pounding.
ANNA: By the way,
have you seen the silver box
from the table by the fire
in the drawing room?
My grandmother used to keep
playing cards in it.
I know the one.
- Is it missing?
- Yes.
And so is the little cupid
from the mantelshelf.
Oh, they must have been taken
downstairs for cleaning.
I was just coming to you,
milady.
Oh, don't worry. I'm fine.
- If that's all, milady?
- I suppose.
Can you manage the jug
and basin?
Or are they too heavy?
No, no, I can do it.
Oh, how's the boiler?
I'm sure they'll fix it soon.
(door closes)
Bertie was with Tom earlier.
You don't think Tom
would ever try to make trouble?
Why do you say that?
Well, Bertie says
there's some army type
who has him under surveillance.
Tom likes to shock, that's all.
He'd never be disloyal
to this family. Never.
Shall we go down?
Yes, let's.
SELLICK:
So, I said to her,
"Listen, lady,
there's a little one here
- who still needs turning."
- PATMORE: Oh!
(chuckles):
Careful. Mr. Sellick,
you'll make Daisy blush.
Takes more than that
to make me blush.
- Now, get that down you.
- You deserve that.
- It's very late.
- Well, I've got to get it done.
And I don't mind long hours.
I, uh, mean to build
me own business,
and you can't do that
working 9:00 to 5:00.
These water jugs
nearly killed me.
How did we manage
in the old days?
Well, maybe people
were tougher then.
Maybe they expected less
from life.
Well, I expect a lot from life.
So do I.
And I mean to have it, too.
- (laughs)
- (chuckles) Are you still here?
Mr. Sellick's been working hard
for hours
for our benefit, Andy.
Then it's time he went home.
Is the savory ready?
Take this.
♪ ♪
Mmm.
He's right. The new pump
should arrive around 9:00.
- I'll be here.
- So will we.
Ta-ra.
♪ ♪
That was Mama. She's in London.
- She's staying with Rosamund.
- She can't be.
She was here for lunch.
She didn't say anything.
She went up this afternoon.
She'll be back tomorrow,
so I've asked her
to come for tea.
You must persuade her
to leave Maud Bagshaw alone.
(chuckles)
I don't believe even Mama
will pick a quarrel
in front of the king.
I wonder if he can come early.
(chuckles)
Are you excited?
I am a bit. Are you?
Would it be common to admit it?
Not to an American.
(Robert chuckles)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
(clock winding)
Here we go, Mr. Carson.
Leave this to me.
I am Monsieur Courbet.
And this is Mrs. Webb,
the housekeeper.
Ah. Follow that path,
and it'll take you
into the kitchen courtyard.
I said, I am Monsieur Courbet,
chef to Their Majesties.
Well done, Charlie.
Always start
as you mean to go on.
This way, gentlemen.
- Miss Lawton?
- I was just looking round.
It's a beautiful house.
You've seen many that are finer.
That's what I came for.
But we shouldn't be in here,
really.
♪ ♪
COURBET: Prepare for your
battle with the barbarians.
PATMORE:
Oh!
(sighs)
You. Uh, where can I put this?
Don't tempt me.
We've cleared some space
in the scullery.
And that cupboard.
What a lot of fuss over nothing.
Well, where's our order
from Mr. Bakewell?
Follow me.
♪ ♪
(Patmore chuckles)
Well, how did you manage it?
A gardener helped me carry
everything in, so no one saw.
PATMORE:
I suppose you could sell the lot
and use the money
to pay Mr. Bakewell.
Don't worry.
They can eat it gradual
when the visit's over.
(indistinct chatter)
Ah! It's done, Mrs. Patmore.
The new pump's installed.
Hail the conquering hero.
It's Mrs. Hughes
you should be telling.
Or Mr. Carson. Not them.
It's all right, Mr. Sellick.
We'll see the news
gets through. Thanks.
COURBET:
I would not feed it to my dog!
WEBB: But I don't need
your help, Mrs. Hughes.
I just want to know where
Their Majesties are sleeping
so Miss Stinson
can prepare the rooms.
Then I will show you, Mrs. Webb,
because, without my help,
you will not find them.
Is it always like this?
A royal visit is like a swan
on a lake.
Grace and serenity above,
demented kicking down below.
I wish I could get away.
I've got tomorrow night off
when Mr. Miller arrives.
Told my mum I'd look in.
Why don't you come to York
with me?
- We could have a drink.
- You should go.
- You're not on duty.
- That settles it, then.
I'll come find you
when I'm released.
We can borrow a car.
HUGHES: Mrs. Webb,
I am the housekeeper here.
WEBB: You are not housekeeper
so long as
His Majesty is under this roof.
Yes, but he's not here yet,
is he?
♪ ♪
It's like living in a factory.
It reminds me of our days
as a convalescent home
during the war.
I enjoyed that, although
I always feel guilty saying so.
- (Mary chuckles)
- Where's Tom?
- Daddy's in the village.
- ROBERT: Again?
- What's he playing at?
- Oh, I saw Tom
looking very stern
as I came up the drive.
ROBERT:
I hope he's not building a bomb.
Many a true word
is spoken in jest.
We think he's being tailed
by Special Branch.
ROBERT:
Nonsense.
- Mama, how was London?
- Oh, fine. Fine.
EDITH:
What were you there for?
- Oh, various things.
- But you hate London.
(chuckles):
Whoever told you that?
Now, when do you want me
tomorrow?
12:00 at the latest.
They arrive at half past.
But, Mama, you must promise
not to attack Maud Bagshaw.
Well, I can't ignore her.
- She is my cousin.
- Exactly.
Greet her as a cousin,
and leave it at that.
- I'll think about it.
- EDITH: But even if she has
left everything to an outsider,
what could we do?
Challenge the will.
On what basis?
Undue influence.
But how could you know that?
And how would you prove it?
We'd find a friendly judge.
ROBERT:
Friendly or corrupt?
Whichever does the trick.
- (Edith chuckles softly)
- ROBERT: Are you here
for dinner, Mama?
It's a buffet.
- Well, I'm not changed.
- EDITH: We won't change,
either, so you just need
to take off your hat.
You talk as if that were easy.
- (chuckles)
- ROBERT: Where's the paper knife,
the silver one
with my regimental crest?
They won't help tonight,
apparently.
They won't lift a finger.
(scoffs)
But then, my food
is only fit for servants.
Well, at least your young hero
seems to have sorted out
the water.
(chuckling):
He's not my hero.
Yes.
Why did you call him that?
Oh, it was just a joke.
- But why's it funny?
- DAISY: Oh, Andy, leave it.
(door opens, slams shut)
♪ ♪
- But this is a rabbit hutch.
- Don't look at me,
Mr. Courbet. You couldn't
swing a cat in my room.
Gentlemen, please.
I'm sure you'll find...
Out of my way.
I will have a bath,
and then I will decide.
Perhaps I will find a hotel.
Where can we eat?
Somewhere apart?
Uh, why not
in the servants' hall?
We never eat
with the resident staff.
- Excuse me.
- COURBET: The water's cold.
What's happening?
Th-This is impossible.
We can't stay here
with no hot water.
- Are you crazy?
- But the boiler was fixed today.
It was hot an hour ago.
Well, it's cold now.
THOMAS: Why are you
here again, Mr. Carson?
So you could keep control
when I would fail?
Was that it? I-I forget.
You... Mr. Barrow,
would you mind?
I'm not on duty, Mr. Carson.
You are.
Sorry, sir.
(thunder rumbling)
What do you want?
Since you are in my room,
sitting at my desk,
it is for me to ask
what you want.
Nothing from you.
I would remind you that I have
been in charge of Downton
for many years.
Mr. Carson,
you are a retired servant
in a minor provincial house,
serving an
undistinguished family.
Your history
is of no interest to me.
Now, if you will excuse me.
So, what would you
like me to do?
I would like you to find
a good book
and read it until we leave.
Mr. Carson, you'd better come
and see this.
SELLICK:
It's well and truly damaged.
- DAISY: Can you mend it in time?
- SELLICK: Oh, yeah.
But somebody should tell them
someone wanted to wreck
the royal visit.
They ought to know.
- CORA: Has the dress arrived?
- Not yet.
- What am I going to wear?
- MARY: Carson, what is it?
Uh, some folding chairs...
well, a great many chairs
have been delivered, milady.
They're at the back door.
Anna thought
you should be told at once.
She's right.
They're for the parade,
and we'll have
to set them out tonight.
There'll be no time tomorrow.
The villagers will start
arriving from 9:00 onwards.
I'm not sure fate
is on our side.
ROBERT:
Poor little Mary.
Have we let her
take on too much?
Yes, you're right.
Come on.
We should lend her a hand.
Well, you can't go out in this.
Of course we can.
Good night, Mama.
Remember to pray for us,
mainly for better weather.
I'll put in a word.
Of course, little Mary could
hammer in a tent peg
with her teeth.
I wonder who she got that from.
You know, I'm always surprised
when you praise me.
I'm surprised to hear
that I have.
(thunder rumbling,
rain pattering)
As if things aren't bad enough
without a thunderstorm.
We'll manage.
I've roped in Mr. Molesley,
and Andy's gone for the truck.
But, well, Mr. Bates can't help.
And Mr. Barrow has vanished.
Ditto. Lord Hexham's
out looking for Mr. Branson.
We'll have to do our best
without them.
You're not going yourself?
Well, how else will they know
what to do?
Then I'll fetch our coats.
Well, you don't have to come.
Of course I do.
I'll just tell Mr. Bates
where I've gone.
You're a good friend
to me, Anna.
I hope we're good friends
to each other, milady.
♪ ♪
- This should be the last of them.
- Great.
Okay, give me that,
Mr. Molesley.
- Can you chuck us the rope?
- Here you go.
- Tie it down, make sure it's tight.
- ROBERT: Here we are.
- All set and ready.
- MARY: Oh, Papa,
Dickie, you're so kind.
But are you sure?
You'll be soaked to the skin
and filthy.
Well, what's that to us?
We're hunting men.
- Come on.
- You don't need to come, my dear.
We can manage it between us.
Of course I'm coming.
Come along.
Cheer up, Molesley.
BRANSON:
The villagers and guests
will watch from both sides
of the dais.
And there'll be seats at
the front kept for the family.
- I'll join you there.
- I suppose so.
We'll meet in the high street
where we planned.
Don't bring anyone.
Come on your own.
It's all ridiculous, of course.
It's a lot of fuss over nothing.
What? I thought you
were here to check
I didn't do anything foolish
and spoil things.
- In what way?
- I don't know.
Throw eggs or wave a banner
or shout.
Will you?
No.
But I'm starting
to wonder about you.
I don't throw eggs.
- Have another?
- Yes.
- CHETWODE: Same again, please.
- Right you are, sir.
ROBERT:
We'll bring a special chair up
for the queen
after breakfast when,
hopefully,
it will have stopped raining.
I shall carry it myself, milord.
- Well, what about the king?
- Well, he'll be on his horse.
But suppose it's still raining?
God will make it stop.
Is that Tom?
Has he been in the pub
the whole evening?
(scoffs)
♪ ♪
MARY: Well, the day has dawned,
and the weather proves
conclusively
that God is a monarchist.
Who could doubt it, milady?
♪ ♪
CORA:
Here they come now.
♪ ♪
(Molesley shuddering)
Mr. Molesley?
I'm all right.
(stammers)
Just need a minute
to catch my breath.
CORA:
Your Majesties,
welcome to Downton Abbey.
We're glad to be here,
Lady Grantham.
Grantham.
You remember
Lord Grantham's mother.
- Hello, Lady Grantham.
- (chuckling): Oh.
- (whimpers)
- Oh, can I help you?
Someone must, sir, or I...
I may never rise again.
(both chuckle)
Thank you.
- My daughter, Lady Mary Talbot.
- Hmm.
The Marquess and Marchioness
of Hexham.
Mr. Tom Branson.
Lord and Lady Merton.
QUEEN MARY:
This is kind of you,
- Lord Grantham.
- Oh, not at all.
It is a great honor.
I'm sure you know,
but Princess Mary
and Lord Lascelles
will be joining us
for luncheon and the parade.
They're both coming?
As far as I'm aware.
What a relief.
Please forget I said that.
Said what, ma'am?
- Cousin Maud.
- Violet.
Are we going to kiss?
I'm glad you want to kiss me.
It wasn't quite what you said
when I last heard from you.
Wasn't quite how I felt
when I wrote. (chuckles)
Can I help you at all?
Thanks.
The others all shot off,
and I'm not sure
if this is the right way.
Just come with me.
What's your part in this circus?
I'm Lady Bagshaw's maid.
Oh, well, then it's this door.
You just ask for Mrs. Hughes.
- She'll look after you.
- Thank you.
COURBET:
Oh, have you tasted the water?
Only for body.
Never for drinking.
Ah, this has just arrived
for Lady Edith.
Lady Hexham these days,
Mr. Bates, but...
Thank you, Albert.
It's a relief.
COURBET:
I want the milk now.
I want the egg yolks now.
I want the olive oil now.
And I want
the vanilla pod now.
He wants a clip
around the ear... now.
Careful, Mrs. Patmore.
Uh, right. Who's taking
this up? Mr. Molesley?
Uh, there's no need for you
to meddle, Mrs. Hughes.
- We will see to it.
- Meddle?
I don't believe I'm meddling
in my own house, thank you.
Andrew, yes.
- You take that one.
- But it's not your house, is it?
So, would you like to go
and sit down?
- Now, just a minute.
- Uh, you leave those.
Put them down.
For heaven's sake,
go after them.
I really must protest.
My staff are...
Keep them down here, Mr. Carson.
That goes for you, too.
Stay out of our way.
You've seen Their Majesties.
Let it be enough.
- Excuse me.
- Wait a minute.
What-what are you playing at?
Hang on.
- What...?
- (scoffs)
(indistinct chatter)
Things seem calmer in the north.
You mean after the strike, sir?
Yes, if calmer means
more resigned.
I'm not sure
what the future holds.
Hmm.
And you, Lady Grantham.
Were you affected
by the general strike?
Well, my maid was rather curt
with me while it was on, sir.
But, you know,
she is a communist at heart.
(chuckling): So I suppose
it was only to be expected.
Wasn't the princess joining us?
Uh, they telephoned.
Lord Lacelles has been
held up by something.
Uh, but they are planning
to come for the parade.
MAUD:
I imagine the servants' bedrooms
are quite pleasant here.
Why? Are you worried
for your maid?
How clever of you.
Lucy is more of a companion
than a maid.
I'd hate for her
to be uncomfortable.
Of course.
I really have to go.
You can't embarrass Mama.
I'm sorry, but you must wait
until we stand.
KING GEORGE: Lord Hexham,
how is Northumberland?
As beautiful as ever, sir.
Can it spare you, do you think?
Well, that was humiliating.
(scoffs) Go on.
Oh! Well, we might as well
all go for a walk.
We cannot challenge the way
a royal visit is conducted,
Mrs. Patmore.
- I'm not so sure.
- Why don't we all meet
- back here after the parade?
- CARSON: Anna, Mr. Bates,
there must be no trouble or
disloyal tomfoolery of any kind.
Do you hear me?
We'll meet in the wine cellar.
Tell the others.
Now, I'm walking
to Mr. Bakewell's,
- if you've any errands.
- (sighs) No.
- (indistinct chatter)
- KING GEORGE: Well, then,
- we should get moving.
- Ah. - Of course, sir.
- ISOBEL: Yes.
- MARY: Here we go.
Ma'am.
ISOBEL:
I'm so looking forward to this.
- CORA: Okay.
- MERTON: Good lunch, I thought.
What was the king saying
earlier? I couldn't hear.
He's planning a tour for the
Prince of Wales next March.
It'll take in most
of the African colonies
- and finish in Cape Town.
- And he wants you to go?
(chuckles) He thinks
I'm a steadying influence.
How long would you be away?
About three months.
I can't believe my luck.
Can you?
(both chuckle)
(indistinct chatter)
I think we're parked
around the back.
- (band playing upbeat music)
- (crowd cheering)
(children chattering playfully)
♪ ♪
(music continues outside)
Tom.
What on earth
are you doing here?
I might ask you
the same question.
Go back, or you'll ruin things.
Isn't that what you're doing?
You don't know what I'm doing.
- Who's this?
- This is my sister-in-law,
Lady Mary Talbot.
I told you to come alone.
Leave this to me.
♪ ♪
(horse neighing)
(quiet chatter)
(both grunting)
- MARY: Tom!
- BRANSON: Get the gun!
(Chetwode screams)
There he is.
(grunting)
- Hold still.
- Got him?
Calm down.
You're not going anywhere.
(sighs, chuckles)
- OFFICER: Hold still.
- Are you all right, sir?
- High treason, that is.
- Your Ladyship?
Why are you even here?
I didn't suspect him myself
until last night.
How was I to know you'd
given up on a free Ireland?
Isn't it free now?
Not with the bloody Crown
around its neck!
Get in.
- Take him away.
- All right, sir.
I'm not impressed
you all decided
I was a royal assassin.
I didn't.
It was really the others.
If you'll follow us
to the station.
Why didn't you tell us?
I thought he'd come
to check up on me
and didn't want
to drag you into it.
I assumed he'd back off
if I answered his questions
and met him for a drink.
But last night at the pub,
I realized he wanted to use me
to get close to the king.
♪ ♪
COMMANDING OFFICER:
Royal salute!
Carry... swords!
("God Save the Queen" plays)
ANNA:
Sorry.
Excuse me.
We thought you'd miss it.
I was just in time.
I don't know why I bothered.
- Shh!
- Oh, quiet.
♪ ♪
COMMANDING OFFICER:
Your Majesty,
the Yorkshire Hussars
are formed up,
ready and awaiting
your inspection.
(band playing lively tune)
Where is he?
He's not feeling well.
Wasn't he out shooting
yesterday?
- What do you want me to say?
- Nothing.
You have to let me leave him.
We will not talk about it now.
♪ ♪
Is that your maid?
That's right. Lucy.
Don't you call her
by her surname?
She's been with me so long.
♪ ♪
It's so strange.
- He seemed so English.
- And so he was.
A pillar of the establishment,
until the notion
of Irish independence
took him over to the other side.
That's where I came in.
He'd heard my sympathies lay
with Ireland and the republic.
Don't they?
Not at any cost.
I'm a law-and-order man
these days.
That's what you lot
have done to me.
(Mary chuckles)
So, will there be a great splash
all over the newspapers?
Poor Papa.
Oh, no. You'll find
there isn't a whisper
about this anywhere.
An establishment cover-up.
I don't believe
in conspiracy theories.
(indistinct chatter,
birds chirping)
WOMAN (chuckles):
Yes.
- Do you... do you write?
- I try.
BRANSON: Ah, Miss Smith.
Did Mrs. Hughes sort you out?
She did.
And have you enjoyed the parade?
(both laugh)
Do you work at the house?
Not exactly.
I sell cars,
and I help with the estate.
Lord Grantham
is my father-in-law.
Oh, I do beg your pardon, sir.
Oh, no, please, let me explain.
I started here as a chauffeur.
You must be
Lady Sybil's husband.
I am.
Lady Bagshaw and I
followed the story.
We were so sad when she died.
How long ago was it?
Seven years, or nearly.
- My God.
- I'm sorry.
- It's still painful.
- Not in that way.
It doesn't hurt anymore,
but it's still there.
- Can I ask you something?
- Of course.
Was it hard,
coming up like that?
Joining the family.
Very hard.
Between my old world
and the new one,
sometimes I didn't know
who I was.
But you do now?
I think so, yes.
I came to terms with it.
Why?
I'm just curious.
♪ ♪
BATES:
Quickly, everyone. Quick.
ANNA:
Come on. Quickly, Mr. Barrow.
BARROW: Can somebody tell me
what's going on? Anna?
- ANNA: Shh!
- THOMAS: What's going on?
BAXTER: What are we all
doing down here?
ANNA: Shh. Go inside.
They can't hear us in there.
This is most improper.
Yes, why-why have you
got us all here?
- Yeah.
- I will tell you.
Mr. Bates and I...
we want to defend
Downton's honor.
In what way?
Would you like a repeat
of how you were all
- treated at luncheon?
- (others murmuring, scoffing)
No, I bloody well would not.
Andrew,
there are ladies present.
We think we should fight back.
I don't like the sound of this.
I do not like this at all.
Anna, tell them.
We are going to clear the way
so you cook and serve dinner
for the king and queen
at Downton Abbey.
- (murmuring, laughing)
- As you should.
Well, oh, my God,
is this a revolution?
Shall I fetch the pitchforks?
(laughs)
BATES:
No, we're serious, Mr. Moseley.
BAXTER: But do you know
what Mr. Courbet's
brought in for tonight?
Mm, never mind that.
We've got our own supplies.
And you can leave
Mr. Courbet to me.
What do you want us to do?
Don't bother with the maids
and valets.
We've no quarrel with them.
But we need to get rid
of the royal butler
- for the night.
- The Page of the Backstairs,
- if you don't mind, Mr. Bates.
- (laughter)
And the footmen need to be
out of commission
from 7:00 until you finish
serving them.
This is treason.
Well, what can we do about 'em?
Well, we could lock them
in the attic.
(groans)
Any more talk like that,
and we'll all end up
in Botany Bay.
HUGHES:
And did you enjoy
being pushed around
and passed over
and told to stay down here
by Mr. Wilson?
I will play
no active part in this.
Well, suppose His Majesty sees
what's going on
and is displeased.
PATMORE:
Why? Do you think
I'm not capable of cooking
a decent dinner?
Oh, no, of course not.
But-but I...
I'll see to the footmen.
What are you going to do?
You'll find out.
So, does this mean
we're back on duty after all?
- Me and Mr. Moseley?
- ANNA: And Albert as well.
You know where to find
the state liveries.
ANDY:
Right. (chuckles)
- Well, come on, Daisy.
- Will I pour wine
for the queen's sweet lips?
Any more of that,
and we'll lock you in the attic.
I don't know why
you're bothering.
What about that Mrs. Webb
who keeps telling us
she's the housekeeper?
Don't you worry about Mrs. Webb.
I am more than a match
for Mrs. Webb.
♪ ♪
- (inhales deeply)
- ANDY: I still don't know
how you're going to manage
Mr. Courbet.
- Well, there's, um...
- (yawning)
I'm just going upstairs
to lie down.
Can you get things ready
for when I come back?
When will that be, O Mighty One?
Wake me in half an hour
if I'm not already
in the kitchen.
(yawns)
Trust us.
♪ ♪
VIOLET:
Tell us about your maid.
Lucy is the daughter of...
David's army servant,
Jack Smith.
And, like my husband,
he died in the Boer Wars.
So you looked after his child?
Lucy had no mother, you see.
So I gave her a home.
That's very generous.
Generosity that has been amply
returned, I can assure you.
I'm glad.
You don't sound very glad.
♪ ♪
- (birds chirping)
- (children chattering)
(crying nearby)
(sighs)
(Branson clears throat)
Oh, goodness.
(clears throat)
I thought everyone
was in the drawing room.
I've been dodging it,
I'm afraid.
I suppose I ought to get back.
Can I get someone for you?
No, thank you.
You're the widower of the
youngest daughter, aren't you?
I've heard of you, Mister...
Branson.
Tom Branson.
And who are you?
Ah, I should know,
but I'm no good
at that sort of thing.
(chuckles)
Well, I suppose you can't
be expected to know everyone.
BRANSON:
Mm.
Did you enjoy the parade?
I'm afraid
I missed it completely.
I got distracted.
- What a shame.
- Well, to be honest,
I'm not much of a royalist.
Although I probably
shouldn't say that out loud.
Certainly not to a stranger.
That seems odd, as the Crawleys
would die for the Crown
if they had to.
You can love people
you disagree with.
And you love them?
They're decent at the core.
People can be decent at the core
but very difficult to live with.
True enough.
And they're silly, too,
and snobbish at times.
And I wouldn't give tuppence
for their politics.
But I've learned to be happy
with all of that.
And besides...
they're my daughter's family.
(chattering indistinctly)
PRINCESS MARY:
And she lives here?
I nearly took her away once.
But she belongs here now.
I spent so much of my life
not belonging anywhere.
That's important to me.
I suppose, in the end,
it's deciding
what's important, isn't it?
You've given me a great deal
to think about, Mr. Branson.
Good things, I hope.
That may be so, but...
now we must go in.
(quiet chatter)
We must change.
And you leave in the morning.
I wonder if we might have
a talk later.
We'll find a cozy spot.
And Robert can join us.
I won't be interrogated, Violet.
Please, don't miss the chance
to settle things between you.
Very well.
But now I must go.
♪ ♪
That was helpful.
Thank you.
Well, I told you
I wanted to help.
Well, thanks to you,
we have her cornered.
Mr. Wilson.
There's a telephone call
for you.
For me?
But, Sir Harry, they wouldn't
get to London until 9:00.
(over phone):
It doesn't matter.
The ball at Clarence House
won't start till 10:00.
What ball at Clarence House?
The Duke of Connaught's.
What are you playing at, Wilson?
I'm not questioning you, sir,
not if it's what
the Duke of Connaught wishes.
But how do I manage here?
Don't they have footmen
at Downton?
Yes, there are footmen.
But won't His Majesty...
His Majesty won't give
a tinker's cuss!
- Now, do as I say.
- Of course, Sir Harry. At once.
(snickering)
Everything all right,
Mr. Wilson?
I need to see my footmen
and the house footmen
and the hall boy.
Uh, when is the next train
to London?
I hope it's not bad news.
Not bad, exactly.
But irregular.
Very irregular, indeed.
(laughter)
I'll get drummed out of the
regiment if they ever find out.
Well, you sounded
convincing to me.
Oh, I'm very good
at doing Sir Harry Barnston,
- I can assure you.
- What if Mr. Wilson rings back?
No one queries
Sir Harry's orders.
But if he did?
Well, then they'd
uncover the trick.
But they couldn't
trace it back to me.
Right. Shall we go into York?
Sorry to miss out
on the fun, in a way.
Where shall I wait for you
when you're with your parents?
We'll find a pub.
(sighs)
(door opens)
Did you manage
to speak to someone?
I got hold
of Madame Seymour's assistant.
They've sent you the wrong one.
It's similar in style
but not, as you can see,
- in size.
- Well, where's my dress now?
On its way to New York.
Well, that's that, then.
(sighs) Wonderful.
Everything's going wrong
for me today.
- Milady?
- Oh. Never mind.
How are things downstairs?
Any better?
A bit better, yes, milady.
In fact,
I ought to be getting back.
Of course.
Oh, one thing.
The painted glass
that used to sit by my bed,
was it broken while I was away?
Leave it with me, milady.
And the dress.
You wouldn't mind a fitting
later tonight, would you?
I don't understand.
Who with?
I just had an idea.
(door opens)
LUCY:
I shouldn't think so,
not if she knows
what's good for her.
- (chuckles)
- Oh, I...
I'm sorry to interrupt.
How clever of you to find me.
Well, not really.
I lived here 40 years.
I assume this is your maid?
- Yes, this is Lucy Smith.
- Oh.
Good evening, Smith.
Good evening, milady.
- Shall I go?
- No, not for me.
Not for me.
I'm delighted to meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
Is there something you want?
Hmm?
Oh, just-just to see
you're comfortable
and to confirm
our little chat for later.
I live my own life now, Violet.
I'm not what I was.
My father is gone.
My husband is gone.
I see no reason
not to do what I want.
Well, that doesn't mean
there is no reason,
merely that you cannot see it.
I think Lady Merton is right.
We'll have it out,
once and for all.
But now I must go
to Her Majesty.
Hmm.
WILSON: You're not to speak.
You're not to think.
Just follow my lead.
Their Majesties must not know
they're being served
by anyone different.
Do you hear me?
I don't want them
to even notice.
We will do our best, Mr. Wilson.
I don't want your best.
I want far better
than your best.
Is everything under control
here, Mr. Wilson?
I gather the others
caught the train.
And this is
what we're left with.
Mind you don't disgrace
the state livery, Albert.
Of course, Mr. Carson.
Where is Monsieur Courbet?
- I came in here to see him.
- PATMORE: Uh, he went out.
So I thought I'd better get on
with dinner. Wasn't I right?
- No, you were not right. You were entirely wrong!
- Oh!
(gasping)
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know h-how
that happened.
WILSON: Well, I shall
have to go and change.
We'll sort this out
when I return.
(whispers):
Andy.
BERTIE: If you don't
want me to, I won't.
But you've already said
that you will.
Because it's a fantastic chance.
It didn't occur to me
you'd mind.
I don't, exactly.
Not in that way.
Then in what way?
I wasn't going to tell you.
I wasn't going
to tell anyone, but...
I might be pregnant.
(both chuckle softly)
Oh, darling.
- How marvelous.
- (both chuckle)
How fabulous.
My heart is bursting.
Oh, well, that's
exactly what I don't want.
- It could easily go wrong.
- Oh, but-but if it doesn't...
Then I'll give birth
just as you set off on
your three-month colonial tour.
(sighs)
Why didn't you say this
when I first mentioned it?
You'd agreed
before I had the chance.
Secrets always muddle things.
Oh, yes, that's right,
let's make it my fault.
Well, I'll tell the king
I can't go.
And he'll accept that, will he?
♪ ♪
(snoring)
Hello.
It's Miss Smith, isn't it?
We were talking about you
earlier. Weren't we?
Oh, Tom.
What luck.
You know Miss Smith, don't you?
Come along, Mary.
(Mary and Edith
conversing indistinctly)
Are you all right?
Has something happened?
Old Lady Grantham came in
while we were dressing.
I think the stage is set
for a fight later, about me.
She thinks Lady Bagshaw
means to favor me,
- and she doesn't approve.
- What business is it of hers?
Lady Bagshaw
must have her reasons,
and that's good enough for me.
Going down, Tom?
Good night.
Ah, there you are, Miss Lawton.
I hope you're having
a well-earned rest.
Well, there's
always less for me to do
when Miss Aplin arrives.
But we must be ready
for the ball tomorrow.
That's what I want
to talk about.
Later this evening, when I
go up to help Lady Hexham,
I want you to come with me,
fit a new ball dress
and sew it overnight
so it's done before you leave
in the morning.
Why on earth would I do that?
The box and cupid
from the drawing room.
The library paper knife.
Lady Hexham's painted glass.
(softly):
Never took the glass.
Then it must have been broken,
like she said.
But you took something
from that room.
What was it?
A patch box
from the dressing table.
I'd like them all back, please.
I can't sew a dress in a night.
When would I sleep?
When you get to Harewood
tomorrow.
And don't think I won't tell.
"Queen's dresser a thief."
That'll make headlines
from here to Peru.
♪ ♪
CARSON: The Marquess
and Marchioness of Granby.
(quiet chatter)
♪ ♪
CARSON:
Sir William and Lady Ingleby.
Where are the royal footmen?
They've had to go back
to London.
All of them?
Wasn't that rather unlucky?
Unlucky for some, milady.
CARSON: The Earl and Countess
of Scarborough.
♪ ♪
(children giggling)
Ah.
(rattling door)
For goodness' sake!
- (pounding on door)
- WILSON: Help me!
Will someone help me?
(quiet chatter)
(chuckles softly)
I'm going on to Turton's
in a minute.
Do you know it?
Uh...
I'm Chris Webster, by the way.
I'm waiting for someone.
- For a very long time.
- (chuckles)
Perhaps he's found
better things to do.
And?
Why don't you come with me?
You know you want to.
Excuse me, sir.
My name's Barrow.
If someone comes looking for me,
could you tell him I've gone?
- Shall I say where to?
- Never mind that. - Turton's.
(door opens)
I just cannot understand
where Mr. Wilson has got to.
Never mind him.
What about you?
Surely, you can't really mean
to leave His Majesty unattended.
But is it for me to attend him?
Well, you've got
your breeches on.
- Well, I have, but...
- Mr. Carson,
this is your destiny.
You know as much, and so do I.
Now, accept it proudly.
And walk into that room
with your head held high.
You can do it, Mr. Carson.
(grunts softly)
Please tell me what is going on.
Mr. Courbet is missing,
ditto Mr. Wilson,
and your footmen are
on their way up to London.
I am still in charge here.
No, Mrs. Webb.
These are my people now.
So please, uh, go back to the
servants' hall and sit down.
Or would you rather
ruin the evening?
ANDY:
That's telling her.
(laughter)
Mrs. Patmore forgot
to send up the sauce.
- And I've got the chopped egg.
- Oh, that's kind
- when it's not your job.
- ANNA: Nonsense.
We must all pull our weight
tonight for Downton's glory.
Now, are you ready, boys?
Ready as we'll ever be.
ANDY:
We'll be fine, Mrs. Hughes.
What about you, Mr. Molesley?
I know I'm
gonna forget my lines.
You haven't got any lines.
- You're on.
- Oh. Right.
ANNA:
And, Mr. Molesley?
Remember to breathe.
Breathe, yeah.
Gentlemen.
♪ ♪
(chuckling)
(indistinct chatter)
I'm glad you're here,
Mr. Carson.
I must go
where my king needs me.
- Hello.
- All right.
(jazz music playing inside)
♪ ♪
Oh, hello.
(indistinct chatter)
MAN: Looks like we've got
some new blood here.
Hello.
You're a very charming
young man.
MAN 2:
Hey!
Stay with me!
Stay with me, Michael!
THOMAS:
I can't believe this.
I've never seen
anything like it.
There's a first time
for everything.
I know, but...
(sighs)
Here. Come dance with me.
♪ ♪
- MAN 3: What'd you say?
- MAN 4: I said, "There's your friend."
MAN 3:
No, my friend's over there.
(quiet chatter)
I wish I could tell them how
grateful they should be to you.
You were every bit as brave
as I was.
VIOLET:
Mary,
you're talking
in the wrong direction.
Don't worry about Granny.
She's getting ready
to give Cousin Maud a grilling.
Mainly, I suspect,
about her maid.
I think Lady Bagshaw sees her
as more than just her maid.
Oh, I'm sure she does.
And that's what
Granny's afraid of.
I might as well admit...
I like her.
Good.
- Don't let them put you off.
- (Branson chuckles)
VIOLET: Tom, you're looking
pleased with yourself.
EDITH:
He was just praising
Lady Bagshaw's maid.
Well, uh, how did she contrive
to make your acquaintance?
She didn't contrive anything.
We met by chance.
(sighs)
What simpletons men are.
KING GEORGE:
This is good.
And I thought
something else was planned.
But it is excellent.
So, a well-done to old Courbet.
- Oh, yes.
- Yes, very delicious.
This wasn't Monsieur Courbet,
Your Majesty.
Mrs. Patmore cooked it.
In fact, it is
the Downton Abbey staff
who are serving you
this evening.
Oh.
(shuddering):
I do beg your pardon,
Your Majesty.
That's quite enough, Molesley.
You must give our compliments
to Mrs. Patmore
and all the staff.
- CORA: Molesley.
- Huh?
Her Majesty is speaking to you.
With pleasure, Your Majesty.
CORA:
That was kind of you, ma'am.
I suppose he's excited
that they've had to take over
from our people.
I wonder what's happened.
Whatever may have happened
does not excuse his behavior.
QUEEN MARY: I can assure you,
Lady Grantham,
we are quite used
to people behaving strangely
when we are near.
(light laughter, quiet chatter)
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
(both laugh)
- Whoa! (laughs)
- That's it. I've got you.
- (whistle blowing)
- MAN: The peelers are here!
MAN 2:
It's the police!
OFFICER: Make sure no one
scarpers. Block all the exits.
- What's going on?
- All right, gentlemen,
that's the end of your evening.
Shut that music up now!
- Right!
- (music stops playing)
You are all coming
to the station with us.
(murmuring)
We're just having a bit of fun,
Officer.
No one's making any trouble.
OFFICER:
That's for the judge to decide.
- Judge?
- OFFICER: What did you think?
We're gonna slap your wrists
and send you home?
I've never been here before.
You're here now. Right!
Gather your things!
You're coming with us,
you dirty perverts. Out.
- Get out! Move it!
- Come on, you filthy sods.
(all clamoring)
♪ ♪
- Come on, you lot.
- Pack it in. Get in the van.
- (murmuring)
- Sort it out.
(clamoring continues)
(breathing heavily)
- (doors lock)
- (sighs)
- There we are, my dear.
- Oh, thank you.
Yes, darling.
Thank you.
(indistinct chatter)
There might be a moment.
I met the maid.
She has Maud wound
around her little finger.
- Then we need to know why.
- Mm.
KING GEORGE: Well, I'll
look forward to it, gentlemen.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Milord.
What is it, Hexham?
Well, Your Majesty, it's this.
I've just learned
that Lady Hexham
is expecting our first child.
But that's wonderful news.
We're not telling anyone
quite yet,
but I thought
you'd be interested.
And so I am. Congratulations.
The-the thing is, sir,
it's due to be born
around the time
the prince and I
will be setting off on tour.
Excellent.
Please make it register
with him.
Help the prince
to understand what it means
to have a real family life.
You can be such an example
to him.
I know it.
Very well.
Let's get to the point.
Robert is my nearest relation
on my father's side.
He is.
But he will not be my heir.
And there we have it.
Who will be? Can you tell us?
Lucy Smith, my maid.
What? Are you out of your mind?
No. And I know what I'm doing.
On the contrary,
you're-you're clearly insane.
You should be in an asylum.
How like you.
A word of resistance,
and you slash with your saber.
It is lucky for Miss Smith
that I do not own a saber.
So, this is truly your choice?
Lucy has taken care of me
for many years.
I wish to show my gratitude.
With the family house?
With the family estate?
You belong in a straitjacket.
To treat your maid
as a blood relation
is to unpick every fiber
of the English way of life.
What piffle you talk.
- Oh!
- Please, there is no need to argue.
I never argue.
- I explain.
- (Maud sighs)
Face it, Violet,
I'll outlive you anyway,
so it need trouble you
no further.
And now...
I must attend Her Majesty.
Game, set and match
to Lady Bagshaw.
Not while I'm the umpire.
♪ ♪
We had a few drinks,
and Mr. Barrow thought
it'd be fun to play a trick
on the queers, that's all.
He was only in there
for five minutes.
Dancing the tango
with another man.
Come on, Sergeant,
it was a joke.
Turns your stomach, though.
- Relieved to hear it.
- Yeah, I'd rather be dead
if I thought I was one of them.
(Ellis sighs)
But what can I say to the earl?
What earl?
The Earl of Grantham.
Mr. Barrow is his butler.
Of course,
you'll want to see proof
of my identity.
(clears throat)
(sighs)
- Was it you who got me out?
- No.
The good fairy came down
on a moonbeam.
How did you know where I'd gone?
The landlord told me.
Waited outside,
followed you here.
Then I showed the sergeant
my card,
and that seemed
to settle things.
"The royal household."
He must have loved that.
(sighs)
I'm a...
I'm afraid
I've been a silly boy.
You just need to be
a bit more circumspect
in future, Mr. Barrow.
♪ ♪
Could you please remove it,
milady,
leaving the pins in place?
Can you really get it done
before you go?
- I don't see how.
- She'll finish it.
- Won't you?
- I'll do my best.
I'm sure you'll manage.
By the way, I think I know
what happened to the cupid
from the drawing room, milady.
EDITH:
Really? Was it missing?
Your dress will be ready
in the morning, milady.
Thank you.
(chuckles): I don't know how
you persuaded her.
She's nice, really.
When you get to know her.
- (chuckles)
- (door opens)
Is there anything else?
Only to say
that you're a genius.
- Good night.
I'm afraid
I didn't get anywhere.
Well, that's that.
Just because the king
doesn't see that a man
has any part to play
in childbearing.
Well, he doesn't.
But you'd think he'd know
that one likes to be around.
You can't just tell him no?
(sighs) Darling, I'm one of
the senior peers in the land.
What do you think that means?
What do you think I'm sworn to?
(sighs)
Lady Bagshaw,
could I have a word
before you ring for your maid?
Does Lucy know
that you're her mother?
She does.
For years,
I said I was her godmother,
but I told her the truth
on her 18th birthday.
How old was she when Jack died?
Six.
She'd lived with Jack
and his mother until then.
But I took her into the house,
and she went
to the village school
until, eventually,
she became my maid.
I suppose
if she'd been your ward,
people would have guessed.
Exactly.
Who takes notice of a servant?
I hid her in plain sight.
Did you love Jack Smith?
Everyone should know
a total love at least once.
Jack was mine.
My husband was very dull,
you know?
He wasn't a bad man, but...
but he wasn't a clever one,
either.
Then he died,
and Jack came to see me,
and it began from there.
How daring.
I know it sounds reckless,
but I was 39
when I got pregnant.
I thought I was barren.
Of course, I knew I couldn't
tell my father, so...
I went to America.
They must have
thought that wild.
Well, little did they know
how wild it really was.
But you were happy with Jack?
(chuckles):
Oh, very.
We had ten years together
before he died.
I'd have married him
if I'd had the courage.
I was weak.
But you never knew my father.
I suppose royal service
kept you silent on the subject.
Yes.
In a way.
But it was cowardice, really.
Now, by making Lucy my heir,
I will have taken
the first step.
You must tell Violet at once.
- I couldn't.
- You're wrong.
As soon as she knows the truth,
she'll fathom your plans
and cease to fight you.
The servants seem to be
enjoying themselves tonight.
(chuckles):
Especially Molesley.
What happened to the royal team?
It's a long story, milady.
But you're right.
We did have fun.
Well, I'm glad it's gone well
for everyone.
But I don't think
I could face doing it again.
You're not finished yet.
You've still got the ball
at Harewood.
Yes, but it won't be our fault
if anything goes wrong.
That's not very cheerful.
(sighs) The last few days
have made me think.
Should we really go on with it?
We're running the house
with too few people as it is,
and half of those here now
will leave soon.
What are you saying, milady?
Isn't it time
to chuck in the towel?
Lots of people have.
You mean... leave Downton?
We could sell it for a school
or an old people's home
or something.
And buy a manor house
with a modest estate
and live a normal life.
Is that what you want?
I want everything
to stop being such a struggle.
Will the staff stay?
Will the farms pay?
What are we going to do
about the roof?
When I was putting up
the chairs in the rain,
I kept thinking,
"What am I doing?"
I'll tell you
what you're doing, milady.
You're making a center
for the people who work here.
For this village.
For the county.
Downton Abbey is the heart
of this community,
and you're keeping it beating.
So you think
we should battle on?
- While there's blood in your veins.
- Hmm.
♪ ♪
(door closes)
Ah, Miss Smith.
Is she settled for the night?
She's more rattled than settled.
And I was right.
There was an argument.
It was about me.
I hear from Lord Grantham
she's planning
to alter your life
for the better.
He says Old Lady Grantham
was up in arms.
(chuckles)
I can imagine.
Are you entitled
to your good luck?
Do you know why she's doing it?
I do.
And I think it's fair.
Go forward in health,
and use your luck wisely.
I have such a feeling
that you can understand
what's going on inside my head
when no one else does
or ever could.
I'll miss our talks.
Would you like to write to me?
I could always provide
a shoulder.
May I?
Really?
I should be pleased
and flattered if you would.
♪ ♪
And now I think it's time
to say good night, Mr. Branson.
Good night, Miss Smith.
♪ ♪
(chuckles softly)
Here's to the triumph of Downton
and my beautiful wife.
Oh, here's to all of you
who brought it off.
Here's to Mr. Carson
for swallowing his principles.
(chuckling): Well, I shan't
sleep a wink tonight.
- (laughter)
- And here's to Her Majesty
for taking pity on Mr. Molesley.
For a moment there, I thought
I was headed for the Tower.
(laughter)
You're not coming round to 'em,
are you?
ANDY:
Uh, it was decent of her, Daisy,
when she could have let it
spoil things.
Not everyone's like Robespierre.
Let's hear it
for the king and queen.
ALL:
The king and queen.
I've got to tell you
something, Daisy.
(indistinct chatter)
It was me that broke the pump.
I don't know what I was doing.
I was just in a jealous rage.
- Why?
- It was that plumber you made eyes at.
I just saw red.
And then when I realized
I'd brought him
back to the house,
I went nearly mad.
I did not make eyes.
I liked him, but there was
nothing more to it.
Well, I feel a fool now.
You tried to wreck the visit
of the King of England.
You risked being sacked,
- you risked ruin...
- (sighs)
...just for the love of me?
I just...
my feelings took over.
That's all I can say.
Can you forgive me?
(chuckles):
Forgive you?
Oh, Andy, I'd have done it
myself if I'd had the nerve.
- (chuckles)
- Don't you see what it means?
We're alike, you and I.
Full of passion
for what matters.
I thought
you were easily satisfied,
but I see now you're not.
So we can fight our way
to a better world together.
♪ ♪
THOMAS:
I'm not sure I've shown
enough gratitude
for what you did.
ELLIS: We have to stick
together, men like us.
THOMAS:
That's the point.
I don't know any men like I am.
I've never just talked
to someone like me.
ELLIS:
Well, we're talking now.
THOMAS:
And it feels good.
Just to be two blokes,
having a chat,
not trying to fit in for once.
Well, we all have to do
what we must to get by.
But yeah. Feels good
to be two ordinary blokes.
THOMAS:
Will they ever see it our way?
ELLIS:
I don't know.
50 years ago, who'd have
thought man could fly?
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
Mrs. Bates?
Well, here's the dress.
We can try it before you leave.
No need. It'll fit.
Those are the things you wanted.
Why do you do it, Miss Lawton?
Doesn't it ever worry you
that on each table
in this house,
there's an ornament
that you couldn't buy
with a year's wages?
And what's your answer?
Because everyone
can't have them,
- no one should have them?
- No.
My answer is,
"Why can't I have them?
Or some of them."
Don't worry,
they won't miss what I take.
I doubt there's more
than one in 100
would even notice they're gone.
But they're not yours,
Miss Lawton.
And they never will be.
I'd give it up if I were you.
What if people were to think
Her Majesty was light-fingered
if things go missing
from every house she stays in?
Keep your advice for someone
who's interested, Mrs. Bates.
Those doors play up
something dreadful.
They jam and stick
for no reason.
It's happened to everyone.
Why didn't any of you look
for me?
I thought I'd seen you go out,
Mr. Wilson.
I'm afraid I was mistaken.
Just as you were mistaken
in not waking Monsieur Courbet.
- We thought he'd gone out and all.
- Oh.
(indistinct chatter
in other room)
CARSON:
Thank you, Mrs. Hughes.
Uh, a little more marmalade,
if you please.
(sighs)
The footmen have
telephoned this morning.
It seems it was a hoax
that took them up to London.
- But who would do that?
- Who, indeed?
COURBET: We can investigate
when we get to Harewood.
I should be careful,
Monsieur Courbet,
unless you enjoy ridicule.
- What?
- I'd say the dinner was a success.
They sent down
their compliments,
so I think it must have been.
Well, then,
why call attention to it?
Would you show to advantage
in this story, do you think?
But what do we say
if we're asked?
There was a confusion in London.
Monsieur Courbet was ill.
If I were you,
I wouldn't mention it.
Not unless they bring it up.
Quite right.
♪ ♪
There you are.
I've been looking everywhere.
What's the matter, darling?
Is it something I can help with?
Judging by last night,
I doubt it.
(sighs)
I just want to own my own life.
I want to say things that
I think and do what I like.
- Don't you now?
- No.
I spend my time entertaining
people who bore me to death
because they're entitled
to sit at our table.
I attend committees
that I haven't chosen
because they've chosen me.
I used to have a job
that I loved, but not anymore.
And now my husband won't
be there when I have a baby.
The woman in the lodge
is entitled to that,
but I'm not.
(Edith sighs)
♪ ♪
ROBERT:
Early warning.
Their Majesties
are getting ready to leave.
Very good, milord.
♪ ♪
Darling, what's the matter?
Nothing you can help with.
Can't I try?
(indistinct chatter)
Oh, uh, we should go up.
Their Majesties
are on their way.
HUGHES:
Oh, right.
- PATMORE: Come on.
- (Anna chuckles)
BAXTER:
Up we go.
So, you're off to London?
They'll drop me at the station.
Well, I hope
we can keep in touch.
I feel I've finally
found a friend.
Is that what you found,
Mr. Barrow?
A friend?
(chuckles softly)
- Their Majesties are going.
- Thanks.
(both breathing heavily)
I want you to have this.
It's not much,
but I've had it for years.
It'll remind you of me.
That's the point, isn't it?
So you can think of me
till we meet again?
♪ ♪
Thank you.
CARSON:
Mr. Ellis,
- you must come!
- (sighs)
I hope you enjoy your time
at Harewood, sir.
Yes. I hope so, too.
(chuckles)
QUEEN MARY:
It isn't really goodbye
when we'll see you all
this evening.
CORA: We're looking forward
to the ball.
Harewood
is such a wonderful house.
Well, let's mount up, shall we?
♪ ♪
- We'll see you later, Grantham.
- ROBERT: Your Majesty.
♪ ♪
(inhales deeply)
(exhales)
♪ ♪
Well done, everyone.
Shall we head back in?
♪ ♪
EDITH: Mary, what are you
wearing to the ball?
MARY:
Oh, I don't know.
Carson, what happened to
the royal servants last night?
Hard to say, milord.
They sort of gave up the ghost.
Well, you managed splendidly.
Although I could have done
without Molesley's aria.
But please thank the staff
for saving the day.
(indistinct chatter)
Oh, uh, Mrs. Bates?
- Excuse me.
- Can I ask you something?
What did you give
Monsieur Courbet?
A double dose
of a sleeping draught
from Mr. Bakewell's...
in his tea.
(chuckles)
I'm afraid I made rather a fool
of myself last night.
You could never be a fool to me.
Do you mean that, really?
I do.
And I think you know how much.
(chuckles softly)
(dishes clinking)
You're right, Mrs. Patmore.
It's time I started
to plan my wedding.
Well, I don't know
what took you so long.
I wasn't sure before,
but I am now.
Well, that's good to hear.
I'm happy, Mrs. Patmore.
I don't often say that,
but I am.
(both chuckle)
♪ ♪
Are you very shocked by it all?
I should be. Interfering
with the palace staff
on a royal visit...
and me part of it, to boot.
I don't know what came over me.
- But?
- (sighs)
They had it coming to them,
Elsie.
Let's face it,
they had it coming in spades.
- (vehicle approaching)
- Hello.
What's this?
♪ ♪
(sighs)
CARSON:
Welcome back, Mr. Talbot.
Hello, Carson. Mrs. Hughes.
Do you know where
I'll find Lady Mary?
After everything that's gone on,
I should think
she'll be lying down, sir.
They all will be.
Sounds ominous.
(chuckles)
That's nice that he's back
in time for the ball.
And thank the Lord
we don't have to organize it.
♪ ♪
Oh, darling, you don't know
what we've lived though.
I'm sorry I couldn't
get here sooner.
It was the first ship after
the last meeting, I promise.
Oh, never mind.
You're here now.
And I don't have to go
to the ball alone
like a sad little wallflower.
Well, I'll only come
if you promise
- to dance with me nonstop.
- Oh, it's a deal.
♪ ♪
(orchestra playing
classical music)
(indistinct chatter)
- Good evening.
- Your Majesty.
I suppose Maud has brought
that scheming little minx
with her.
If you continue in this vein,
you will only make yourself
look stupid.
- What-what do you mean?
- What I say.
Are you keeping something
from me?
Come with me.
What?
Why aren't you happy?
(chuckles):
I thought you'd be delirious.
Well, we are happy,
if you mean it. Very.
But how will you manage Henry?
By altering the way
we manage each other.
And it may not be easy,
but I've decided
that I'm staying with him.
I just don't understand
what changed your mind.
It was something
Mr. Branson said
about deciding what matters.
For me, the Crown matters more
than any of us.
I can make it work.
Branson? The Irish republican?
(chuckles):
Oh, you're well-informed.
I'm better informed
than you know.
So, he persuaded you to do this?
Oh, we were talking
after the parade.
Oh, there he is.
Ah.
Say something nice. Please.
BRANSON: I have to say, it's
been very quiet without you.
Mr. Branson.
I wish we had spoken more
while we were at Downton Abbey.
- Do you, sir?
- Certainly.
I believe I have more than one
reason to be grateful to you.
More than one.
- (music ends)
- (applause)
What was that all about?
I'll tell you when we're alone.
Why more than one?
(classical music resumes)
BRANSON:
Who is she?
MARY:
That's Princess Mary.
She was at Downton
for the parade yesterday.
Didn't you see her?
Not at the parade.
But I saw her afterwards
at the tea.
♪ ♪
(quiet, indistinct chatter)
MAUD: So, you see,
she has Brompton blood,
albeit from an unusual angle.
Why did you not say this
long ago?
It seemed too great a leap
for you.
Well, who do you think I am?
Some maiden aunt
who's never left the village?
Obviously not.
Well, don't think I approve,
because I don't.
But at least I understand.
Does Miss Smith know the truth?
Yes, she does.
When I get home,
I will hire another maid,
and Lucy can be my companion.
Well, that's much more suitable.
And I'm afraid
you'll dislike it,
but she says
that she and Tom Branson
have agreed to correspond.
(scoffs) Dislike it?
- I will lick the stamps myself.
- (Maud chuckles)
(Isobel chuckles)
You are amazing, Violet.
You haven't won, you know.
I don't believe in defeat.
But we can hammer this out
when you come back to stay,
you and Lucy,
when you've finished
your tour of duty.
You mean I am once more
a member of this family?
(Violet sighs)
She's right, you know.
Brompton is gone.
And you must all learn
to live with it.
I think we can get it back.
For Tom, at least.
That's why we need the girl
back here.
Oh, Violet.
After all these years,
you still astonish me.
Oh, good.
I'm glad I'm a revelation
and not a disappointment.
(Isobel chuckles)
- It's very important.
- Quite right.
- Oh, there they are now. Do ask.
- Ah, yes.
There you are, Hexham.
I'm sad you can't be part
of the prince's tour,
but we'll find something else
for you to do.
- What?
- Sir, I-I didn't, um...
I understood why not, uh,
as soon as Her Majesty
had explained it to me.
Congratulations to you both.
(both chuckle softly)
♪ ♪
- You're looking very sunny tonight.
- (sighs)
I'm happy.
Why? Does it bother you?
No. But tell me,
what are you playing at
- with Tom and Cousin Maud's famous maid?
- What do you mean?
I heard you
at dinner last night.
What are you up to?
You know she'll inherit
the Brompton estate.
- Well, so Mama told me.
- Well, then,
wouldn't you like Tom
to have a proper establishment?
- Oh, you devious cat.
- (chuckles)
Will they be happy?
Do you think they will?
Oh, I just want a word
with Granny.
♪ ♪
How long were you
planning to wait
before you told us why
you really went up to London
on Wednesday?
Since you ask,
I haven't decided.
So, if I tell you now,
will you promise
to keep it to yourself?
I promise.
Very well. I...
I had some medical tests
a few weeks ago,
and I went up to London
to hear the results.
- Yes?
- And, uh,
I may not have long to live.
It won't be too quick.
(chuckles):
But, of course,
you can never get
a London doctor to be precise.
- Oh, Granny.
- No.
No, no.
My dear, save your tears
for something sad.
Th-There's nothing sad here.
I have lived a privileged
and an interesting life,
and now it's...
it's time to go.
I'm leaving the family
and the place that I treasure
in talented hands.
- Well, I know Papa will be...
- Oh, no, no.
(chuckles):
No, I don't mean your father.
I... No, I-I love him dearly.
No, I... I mean you.
You are the future of Downton.
But I have such doubts, Granny.
Are we right
to keep it all going
when the world it was built for
is fading
with every day that passes?
Will George and Caroline
still be living that life?
- Are we living it now?
- No, no.
Our ancestors
lived different lives from us,
and our descendants
will live differently again,
but Downton Abbey
will be part of them.
Won't be the same without you.
Of course it will.
You'll take over
from where I left off.
You'll be
the frightening old lady
keeping everyone up to the mark.
(laughs)
Thank you very much.
You will, my darling.
And you'll do it wonderfully.
You're the best of me
that will live on.
Hurrah.
(crying)
Oh, Granny, I love you so much.
No, shh.
But should you be here tonight?
Won't you be worn out?
Oh, Mary, I can't spend
the rest of my life
in a shower of
"How are you feeling?"
and "Are you quite well?"
Oh, no.
The point is...
I'll be fine until I'm not.
- That's all there is to it.
- (door opens)
Ah, there you are.
- The dancing's starting.
- Ah.
ISOBEL:
You mustn't miss it.
No. Thank you.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
You know, you'll always be
with us, Granny.
Staring from every picture,
talking from every book,
as long as the house stands.
(chuckles):
Sounds very exhausting.
Do you know, I think...
I should prefer
to rest in peace.
(both laugh)
Come on.
♪ ♪
(applause)
(music ends)
♪ ♪
Darling.
LASCELLES:
What is it you want?
We have things in common.
The boys, horses, racing.
And there must be more
if we look for it.
I want us to be friends.
Well, we'll have to see.
No, dear.
We'll have to change.
Both of us.
How did that happen?
Was it you, Mama?
How did you do it?
Simple.
Bertie asked the king.
I asked the queen.
(chuckling)
I do love our adventures.
But isn't it fun
when they're over?
♪ ♪
(soft chatter)
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see the dancing,
so I thought I'd pretend
I was bringing Lady Bagshaw
a handkerchief. (chuckles)
I can give it to her,
if you'd like.
(man scoffs)
I wish you could dance with me.
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
I've got a question for you.
Hmm?
You'd never want
to leave Downton
and start up somewhere else,
would you?
And tell me truthfully.
What brought this on?
Just tell me.
Leave Downton?
I think we're stuck with it,
aren't we?
Yes.
Yes, I believe we are.
♪ ♪
We shouldn't come out this way.
Oh, they won't mind.
Not this once.
Well, they've gone,
and Downton is still standing.
Elsie, a hundred years from now,
Downton will still be standing.
And the Crawleys
will still be here.
And that is a promise.
We'll see, Charlie.
We'll see.
♪ ♪
(music fades)