¶ Ooh ooh ooh ¶
¶ heaven is my home ¶
¶ ooh ooh ¶
¶ ooh ooh ooh ¶
¶ now this sweet world
is precious to me ¶
¶ ooh ¶
¶ I have traveled
down this road before ¶
¶ on a journey for a friend ¶
¶ been away,
but now I'm back for more ¶
¶ going down this road again ¶
¶ you know
he answers every prayer ¶
¶ but you better do your part ¶
¶ his spirit's
all around you everywhere ¶
¶ but you gotta open up
your heart ¶
¶ you've gotta open up
¶ you're alone when
you come in this world ¶
¶ you're alone when you go ¶
¶ and it doesn't matter
who you are ¶
¶ doesn't matter who you know ¶
¶ keep on listening
for that choir, boys ¶
¶ that's the way to start ¶
¶ the door is open,
but you have a choice ¶
¶ you've got to open up
your heart ¶
¶ you've gotta open up
¶ oh, this world
is dear to me ¶
¶ heaven is my home ¶
¶ this is where I long to be ¶
¶ when your life seems gloomy ¶
¶ teardrops start to fall ¶
¶ send the word back to me ¶
¶ that I'll be there ¶
¶ when you call ¶
¶ I've been down
this road before ¶
¶ heaven is my home ¶
¶ not coming back here ¶
¶ anymore ¶
¶ heaven is my home ¶
¶ yeah ¶
Good night now.
Good night.
¶ Sleigh bells ring ¶
¶ are you listening? ¶
¶ in the land ¶
¶ snow is glistening ¶
¶ a beautiful sight ¶
¶ we're happy tonight ¶
¶ walking in
a winter wonderland... ¶
Right here is fine.
Think this is bleak enough?
My ears are frozen,
my feet are frozen.
This is as far as it goes.
Malt's not going to like this.
What's he not going to like?
He'll find something not to like.
Besides us, you mean?
Yes, besides us.
Huey...
You sit in the sled.
Santa, Sparky, presents...
Reindeer...
Fake snow...
What are we missing?
Children.
Oh, yeah.
Let them out!
Now what do I do?
You know what to do.
When they handed out the parts,
you got the heart.
That's right, I got the heart.
You got the brain.
Is that what you're saying?
I'm saying that between the two of us,
you've got the heart.
I'm saying that together,
we make a person.
It's Santa!
It's Sparky!
¶ And we're walking ¶
¶ In a winter ¶
¶ wonderla-a-and ¶
What is this, Craddock, a joke?
No.
Who was in charge here?
Me. I was.
That's right, mr. Malt.
This was Quinlan's baby.
Quinlan...
Let me ask you a question.
You was a big-shot
investigative reporter
for the Chicago Tribune.
Won some prizes.
Give him a biscuit.
Now, what do these
look like to you?
They're Indians dressed up as eskimos.
Indians, eskimos...
What's the difference?
That's what we thought.
Shut up, Driscoll.
You know the only prize
I ever got, Quinlan?
It's out there on the walls.
I got 4.5 million people
who buy the National Mirror every week.
Do you know how many of
those 4 1/2 million readers
are Indians or eskimos
or eskimo-Indians?
I told him. American children.
Americans want to see
pictures of Americans.
They are Americans.
Americans! Is that too much
to ask for Christmas?
No, sir, and I will
get someone right on it.
Aw, did you do that again?
If you don't teach
that dog some manners soon,
somebody else
is going to have to,
won't they, hmm?
How long were you in
Elizabeth Taylor's pool, ma'am?
Reincarnation.
Miss Uffler speaking.
Were you on the bed
when it levitated?
So you're saying
he's living in your refrigerator?
Uh-huh.
You know what?
Can I put you on
hold for a second?
I'm going to go to my desk
and take this call there.
Yes. Now, don't let him out.
Ok. Hold on.
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no.
Here's something interesting.
Ay yi yi.
Malt sent you for the tree this year,
didn't he? I forgot.
I found it in Montana.
Now, the second
I see this tree,
I know that it's too big
to fit on the truck.
Then I think, what if someone else
sees the same tree
while I'm out trying
to find something
that will fit on the truck?
Then Malt...
Gets the second biggest
Christmas tree in America,
and I'm screwed.
Yeah, well, that's good thinking.
So I cut the top off.
You did that?
How was I supposed to know
it was going to be such a major problem
to put the top part of the tree
back on the bottom?
He is never going
to fire you, Huey.
Look at the walls.
Look, look at the walls.
He's got millions of dollars
tied up in that dog,
and the dog belongs to you.
Hold on to that dog, Huey.
What?
Driscoll?
Driscoll!
Come in here!
We're going together, Sparky.
"Dear mr. Quinlan, I'm a great
admirer of your... prose
"and can tell you have
a sensitive nature.
"I have had an angel
named... Michael...
"Living with me for almost 6 months now.
"He's extremely polite.
"I have enclosed a photograph to prove to you
"that I have not lost my wits.
"I know that you and Sparky travel all over
"reporting on your stories.
"That one about the coconut
with the wedding ring inside
"was very, very nice,
and I think you should visit Iowa..."
"And see us for yourself.
Sincerely, Pansy Milbank."
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Did your mother drop you?
What was going on
in that pea brain
that lets you take this superb creation
of the lord almighty
and chop it in half?!
Whatever I'm paying you,
it's too much!
How much does Fred make?
What, the janitor?
Oh, mr. Malt,
I cannot survive on a janitor's salary...
Kill the dog.
Quinlan, did someone
invite you to this meeting?
Take him outside
and let him go on the highway.
Wait a minute...
what kind of person are you?
Who is this?
This is miss Dorothy Winters.
She works here.
I do?
I got the job?
Yes! You won't regret this, mr. Malt.
Do you know what that is?
That is an angel.
That is a genuine angel.
Huey discovered it.
Is this for real?
Absolutely.
You're going to go
get me this angel.
That's exactly
what we're going to do.
We'll put it on the front page, bold.
Some white fluffy clouds...
There you go.
A drift of sky...
You got it.
And some musical notes!
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah!
Poetry.
Don't play with me, Quinlan.
You really are going to go
and fetch me this angel for Christmas,
or... I fire the two of you,
and I keep the dog. Yeah?
Deal.
A little conference with my colleague.
You cannot live on Fred's salary.
You cannot.
That's a deal.
Don't you worry about a thing, mr. Malt.
We'll leave tomorrow.
We're taking Sparky with us.
And you're taking miss Winters.
They are?
Why are we taking her?
She's an expert.
In what?
Angels.
Miss Winters is
an expert in angels.
I have something to tell you.
I won't be taking care of you anymore.
Your parents will find
someone else and...
Stop looking at me like that.
I have this wonderful new job.
The only problem is, I have to pretend
to be an angel expert
for a few days on this trip.
It'll be fine.
I'll be fine.
And so will you.
Good dogs.
Have you ever had
an encounter with an angel?
No.
Yes.
Maybe.
Have you ever met an angel?
Yeah, once.
I got a flat tire
on the side of a deserted country road.
There was no food, no water,
108 degrees temperature,
and a man in a white robe
suddenly appeared
on the horizon
with a spare and a jack.
You're kidding.
Yes, I am.
Bradley used to tease.
Who is Bradley?
My ex-husband.
Oh, ho.
You better watch it, Quinlan.
I think we should start over.
You know, when something
isn't going well,
it's best just to start over.
I'll go first.
Ok.
Where'd you get Sparky?
Oh, no.
He comes up to Huey
in a parking lot one day.
Huey was eating a donut,
and he's trying to kick the...
trying to kick him away.
You were trying
to kick the dog?
I wasn't trying to kick him.
I was trying to shoo
him away very gently.
When Malt comes out the door,
he looks at the dog,
he stops dead in his tracks.
It turns out that Malt
was once a child
who had had a dog
just like that one.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Anyway, Malt's eyes get all teary,
and he pours out this story
all about his dog Sparky,
which ended up underneath a tractor tire!
Ha ha ha!
And you know what Huey did?
Huey turns to Malt,
and he says,
"Mr. Malt, that is amazing!
This dog's name is Sparky, too!"
Ha ha ha!
In no time at all,
the dog is famous.
He's got his own column.
He must've saved Huey's neck
a hundred times.
Milk bottle hotel.
Here, here, here!
Milk bottle hotel!
Looks like your angel checked out.
Somebody's here.
Mrs. Milbank?
Mrs. Milbank,
I'm Frank Quinlan
from the National Mirror.
About your letter?
Um...
This is my associate mr. Hugh Driscoll.
H-how are you?
And this is Dorothy Winters,
who is an expert in... various things.
And this is...
Sparky.
Oh! Oh!
Oh, you're just as handsome
as in the pictures!
Aww...
Oh, I think he's cold.
I wouldn't know why not.
We better get him inside.
Oh...
Sparky, here you are.
Oh, ha ha!
Mmm. What's that
wonderful smell?
You must be baking.
Well, it was nice
of you to come.
Ohh!
Mrs. Milbank?
Don't shake me, mr. Quinlan!
I'm contemplating my death.
Are you with the angel?
Do you see an angel?
I don't think I do.
Then how could I be with him?
Well, we don't know exactly
how it works with angels.
"How it works"?
If he's in the room,
then you're with him.
If he's somewhere else,
then you're not.
And that's why we
can't see him now.
He's not here.
Are you impaired in some way
that I haven't noticed, miss?
Miss Winters has
probably never heard
of an angel living in a motel.
Ha ha ha!
You think I'm full of shit.
No, no, nothing like that.
I don't judge these things, mrs. Milbank.
It's not for me to decide
what's real and what's not.
I've seen too many things myself.
We once heard there was
a werewolf in South Jersey.
We went there.
To locate the, uh, werewolf.
Yeah. In that particular case,
that person was...
Utterly convinced that the werewolf
was in the room with us.
They could see it, although
mr. Quinlan and myself...
We couldn't see the werewolf,
but that doesn't mean
it wasn't there.
Michael!
Michael? Are you coming down, dear?
Yeah...
Be right down.
Just gotta find my smokes.
They're beside the bed,
next to my cortisone.
Did you find them?
He'll be down directly.
That smell is so familiar.
It's like something
from childhood.
Ohh...
Michael, look who's come to visit us.
It's Sparky.
How do you do?
You'll have to excuse Michael.
He's not good at suffering fools,
but he'll be better in the morning.
It's freezing!
Whoa!
Where is the thermostat in here?
Are we talking
about an angel here?
We can't be talking
about an angel.
There is no...
Such thing such thing as an angel.
As an angel.
That is definitely the weirdest thing
I have ever seen.
It's like some great big bird
made love to that guy's mother.
Yes! And we... we reap the benefits!
I'm set for life!
I mean, I could even get a raise!
I thank you!
Thank you, Jesus!
¶ Thank you, Jesus ¶
¶ I thank you, Jesus ¶
¶ thank you, Jesus,
thank you, Jesus, I thank you, Jesus ¶
¶ I thank you, jes... ¶
What?
That is not an angel.
It is too!
It is not!
I will handle this.
Where... has he been?
Meaning what?
Meaning if he were
a man with wings,
which is the alternative here,
we would've heard about him.
He didn't just show up
at his age with wings.
There would've been a story
about him in the papers.
In the National Mirror.
Exactly. "Baby born with wings."
Yeah, "Birdman of Iowa."
It is not angel vs. man with wings.
There are other possibilities.
Like what?
It's fairly obvious, isn't it?
He's a younger man.
She's an older woman.
He's after her money.
A gigolo with wings?
A gigolo!
What money is he after?
The milk bottle motel fortune?
You don't have to have money
to have someone try
to take it away from you.
Lord! Oh...
Is it so hard for you to imagine
that a man would be
after a woman's money?
Is this, uh,
is this Britely or Brinkley
or whatever, what's his name?
Bradley.
Is this Bradley we're
talking about here?
Actually, no.
It's Myles.
Who's Myles?
My second husband.
Ah.
Myles was a wild man.
It only lasted a week.
You left him?
No. He left me in my Camaro.
Ahh!
I see.
I'll bet he racked up $5,000
on your visa bill, too, didn't he?
Didn't he?
Oh, you just know everything, don't you?
Angels don't smoke!
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
That is a horrible expression.
It is not... an expression.
Ooh, is that good?
Oh... Ha ha!
You're so hungry.
Ha ha!
Ok... Ha ha!
Aww... Ha!
Good boy.
Oh, what a sweet doggy.
Ha ha ha!
How would you like your eggs,
mr. Quinlan?
Oh, Sparky's look good.
Over easy!
You know, last night
we were discussing your wings.
Would you mind if
I took a closer look?
Let them look at your wings, Michael.
They're from the National Mirror.
Thank you.
They're not bad.
Compared to what?
Well, I've...
I've seen birds.
Would you mind if I touched... oh!
I'd rather you didn't.
Hey, well...
Ha ha!
We'd just like to take a look
to see how you have
these things attached.
Why don't you pull on your pecker
and see how that's attached?
Watch your language, mister.
Pecker.
An angel that says "pecker."
Language, gentlemen!
And how would you like your eggs, miss?
Is there something in the oven
that smells so delicious?
We are serving eggs this morning,
and that's that.
Over easy would be just fine.
Over easy!
I thought angels were...
Cleaner.
She doesn't mean to offend.
It's...
Miss Winters is an angel expert,
and she gets kind of...
Literal.
What she probably
wants to know is...
Can you fly?
I do not want to know if he can fly.
I know he can't fly.
Only little angels can fly
because their wingspan...
Says who?
I just thought...
Halos?
Yes.
Inner light?
I'm not that kind of angel.
What kind of angel are you?
Michael is an archangel.
He battled Lucifer
and threw him out of heaven.
Revelation 12, verse 7.
That was a long time ago.
He smote a bank for me!
A bank?
I knew it. Money was involved, wasn't it?
Oh, I should say so.
After Elmer died...
Who's Elmer?
My husband.
After he died,
they built the highway
and stole all my truckers.
And then the bank came
to take the milk bottle,
and I prayed for help
until God sent me Michael.
Well, she was persistent.
You came... down...
and smote the bank?
Eh, a branch.
First Iowa bank of commerce.
It was lovely.
He walked into the manager's
office and said...
what was that you said?
Moneychanger!
I shall turneth this earthly den
into a parking lot!
Come on.
Did I say that?
I didn't say that.
They didn't believe us,
so Michael flattened it.
You did that?
Had to.
Into a parking lot?
Well, they said
it was a tornado.
This town doesn't really
need a parking lot,
but it's, uh, more, uh... cosmopolitan.
And what about the money?
We never heard another
word about it, did we?
Nope.
You look like you must eat
a robust breakfast.
How would you like your eggs?
Poached?
Uh, that's... poached is fine.
Poached.
The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures.
He leadeth me beside
the still waters.
Look, she's...
she's happier where she is, right?
Heaven?
She's happier up there, right?
It isn't my area.
You hardly knew her.
She died cooking us breakfast.
She died making breakfast.
What is it that you keep
writing in that book?
Lyrics.
To what?
I write country-western songs.
It's my hobby.
Earth to earth,
ashes to ashes,
dust to dust.
The Lord bless and keep you
and give you peace.
Justine?
It's Quinlan.
Put me straight through.
What you got?
Wings.
Real wings.
Don't play with me, Quinlan.
This guy is about 6 feet tall,
and his wings
reach from his shoulders to his knees.
He's filthy, though.
We're gonna have to clean him up
and put him in a white robe.
Get Craddock to dig up
some of those sandals.
You know, the ones with those straps
that go up your legs.
It's too bad he's not
blond, all right.
Angels is supposed to be blond.
But Oprah, Barbara,
the Today show, Hard copy,
book the works.
Then let's don't mess this one up.
I want that guy on the first plane to Chicago...
or does the birdman fly himself?
I don't know if he
actually uses the wings,
but, God, wouldn't that be a draw?
Anyway, don't worry,
he's in safe hands.
Yeah, and I'm the queen of England.
Don't fret, Malt.
He's in safe hands.
In view of this development,
should we call the girl off?
No, no.
Leave her where she is.
I'm in a no-lose situation.
Heh heh heh heh!
Hey ya, Mike.
Michael.
Have you, um...
Have you ever seen
the world's biggest ball of twine?
No.
Listen, we have to get back.
I once saw the world's
biggest cannonball.
Mesopotamia.
I wonder if it's still there.
Mesopotamia isn't still there.
Ohh! Nothing lasts.
Listen, I have to ask a favor.
Huey and I,
we're on a little bit
of a losing streak.
Quit.
We can't quit.
He's got a mortgage.
He's got 3 kids in a soccer camp.
He's got a wife.
God knows he loves her,
but she's burning
a hole in his pocket.
And I...
Well...
Love to fight.
Like me.
We'll drive.
Where?
Chicago. That's where
you want to go, isn't it?
Yes!
Yeah. I know.
That's why I wrote you.
You wrote?
I thought...
Yeah. My idea.
Ah.
Why are we driving?
I mean, why don't we fly?
I mean, all of us,
together, in a plane.
It's safer, much safer.
Nobody believes it,
but, statistically, it's true,
and the paper will pay.
Nope. We need time.
Time for what?
Smokes.
Smokes. Ah.
Besides... I will get to see
the world's largest ball of twine.
It's on the way.
Great. Great.
One one condition:
you will owe me something.
Money. Yeah. I can't quote a figure,
but there will be plenty of money,
I promise you that,
once the world sees pictures of these babies.
No. You will owe me an apology.
An apology for what?
Oh, yeah, sure.
I apologize.
Whatever.
Not now.
When I say so.
And no pictures.
No pictures?
Are you kidding me?
Not until we get to Chicago.
Deal?
Deal.
Hmm...
I like your coat better.
It's yours.
The world's biggest ball of twine
is less than 2 hours from here.
I would like to see it
before the sun sets.
Michael, they are going to exploit you.
You have to know that.
I'm going.
Well, I'm not, for your sake.
Yes, you are,
or I'll have to tell them
the truth about you.
What?
I know why you're here,
and it has nothing
to do with angels.
How do you know?
I pay attention.
Also...
I would like you to sing.
A song?
Of course.
Fine. I'll sing.
Now?
No.
When I tell you to.
¶ Hoo! ¶
¶ there's a place up ahead,
and I'm goin' ¶
¶ just as fast
as my feet can fly ¶
¶ come away, come away ¶
¶ if you're goin' ¶
¶ leave the sinkin' ship
behind ¶
¶ come on the risin' wind ¶
¶ we're goin' up
around the bend ¶
¶ hoo! ¶
¶ bring a song and a smile
for the banjo ¶
¶ better git
while the gittin's good ¶
¶ hitch a ride
to the end of the highway ¶
¶ where the neons
turn to wood ¶
¶ come on the risin' wind ¶
¶ we're goin' up
around the bend... ¶
In financial news,
hog futures are down
1/4 in Chicago
and selling down 1/8 in Sioux City.
Hog futures.
Ha ha ha!
What?
Hog futures are down 1/4.
Hey. What's
the opposite of white?
Black.
Wrong. Yolk.
What?
What is that,
like, an egg joke?
Hey, Michael, when we stop to eat,
are you going to put your coat back on?
Why?
Your wings, Michael.
People are going
to see your wings.
Are you afraid they'll
think less of you?
No.
Just they won't know
what to think, you know?
A lot of people aren't
as sophisticated as me and Huey.
Oh.
You know, we don't
want any trouble.
We just want to get to Chicago.
Mm-hmm.
He's worried that
somebody will see you
and try to steal his story.
I am not worried.
Yes, you are worried.
Hey! Hey!
Look what Pansy left us.
Car bingo.
Oh. Dig the propaganda.
"The Miles will fly,
"and your children won't cry
if you play..."
Car bingo.
All right. Everybody gets one.
Here we go.
Hand them out.
So, what do we do?
Here are the pencils.
Instead of writing down a number,
you write down what you see on your trip.
Ok. Dog. One point for me.
No. That's not fair.
You've played this before.
It's not fair to me.
I'm driving.
Deal with it.
Bird on a wire.
Picket fence.
Policeman.
Where? Where?
Ah, that was good.
Oh-ho.
Oh. You gotta learn to laugh.
It's the way to true love.
¶ Come on the risin' wind ¶
¶ we're goin' up
around the bend ¶
¶ do do doo-doo ¶
¶ do do doo-doo... ¶
"The world's largest ball of twine
has a circumference of 45 feet."
What's the excuse?
Well, it's just going to take
a little longer than we thought
because we have to stay
off the main highway.
Fly.
He won't fly.
Why?
Because he can't fit
in coach seats.
His wings take too much space.
Wanna pay first class?
Drive.
"Eventually, it was
transported here.
"There is enough twine
to stock 5,000
hardware stores..."
Battle.
We'll be there.
Don't worry.
What can happen, you know?
Trust me.
Nothing.
Michael?
Don't fret, Malt.
Quinlan!
Michael!
What are you doing!?
Battle!
Michael.
Michael, you know what that is?
Battle!
Michael. Don't.
Michael.
Ha!
I am completely happy.
Are you all right?
Can you feel your legs?
Whooo.
Ha ha ha.
No injuries.
6,360 battles.
Can you sit up?
Of course I can sit up.
Ah. Now that...
That is my nature.
Yes.
I am a grass roller,
but I'm doomed to live in one place
and crave the pleasures of another.
But don't you feel sorry for me, no.
Why would we feel sorry for you?
Because this is my last blast.
26. That's all we get.
Thank you, Quinlan.
For what?
I think he's saying
there's no sex in heaven.
Is that what he's saying?
You know, it's really not polite
to talk about someone
in the third person
when that person is here.
I know. I'm very sorry.
Sparky!
What do you mean...
"Last blast"?
Only so many visits allowed.
I'm going to miss
everything so much.
Ooh...
Mmm!
Why are you here?
Why are you saying
it has anything to do with me?
The sun was having an argument
with the north wind:
Who was smarter,
who was stronger.
The north wind pointed out a man
walking down the street.
"I bet I can make that man
take off his coat, and you can't."
"I'll take that bet," said the sun.
The north wind blew
and blew and blew,
and the more that wind blew,
the tighter that man
held that coat around himself.
And then the sun
came out and smiled,
and it became warmer.
The man took off his coat.
What is that supposed to mean?
Did you make a bet about me?
Well, I had to get
back here somehow.
Hey, watch the wings there, buddy.
¶ sittin', thinkin' ¶
¶ sinkin', drinkin' ¶
¶ wonderin' what I'll do ¶
¶ when I'm through
tonight... ¶
That's not how you eat a lemon.
How do you eat a lemon?
You cut it in half...
Put salt on it.
That is how you eat a lemon.
That's how you eat a lemon.
Oh, is this a rule?
Hey.
Hey to you, too.
Thank you.
Do you have pie?
No.
I'm a writer, too.
Oh, really?
What did you write?
Psalm 85.
It wasn't called psalm 85 when I wrote it.
I had no idea
they were going to be
collected and numbered.
Yeah. Yeah.
It was right around the time
I invented standing in line.
You invented standing in line?
Before that, everybody
just milled around.
It was a mess.
So one day I said,
"why not make a line?"
A line for what?
To get in.
Why don't you ask him
what you want to know?
What do I want to know?
He wants to know why angels
don't solve big problems.
That is what I want to know.
Why don't angels
solve big problems?
You can't change
the nature of the world.
What can you do?
Small miracles.
Only so many.
Some angels aren't so smart.
They use them up in stupid ways.
Like the "parking space" angel?
I don't like to criticize other angels.
I'll, uh, be with you in a minute.
Yup.
This is how you eat a lemon.
Hey.
Excuse me.
They want me.
Now, remember what
John and Paul said.
The apostles?
No. The Beatles.
All you need is love.
Hello, ladies.
Do you believe in angels?
Absolutely.
Have you ever,
ever heard of an angel
that was interested in sex?
Of course not.
Angels do not have sex.
But is there one?
And I suppose he invented
standing in line.
Sparky,
I'm going to take you for a walk.
Let's go.
¶ I don't care if you love me ¶
¶ anymore ¶
¶ you never sho... ¶
¶ Chain chain chain ¶
Suzanne, what's going on?
¶ chain chain chain ¶
Hey. Suzanne.
¶ Chain chain chain ¶
¶ chain chain chain ¶
¶ chain of fools ¶
¶ for 5 long years ¶
¶ I thought you were my man ¶
¶ but I found out ¶
¶ I'm just a link
in your chain ¶
¶ oh! ¶
¶ you got me
where you want me ¶
¶ I ain't nothin'
but your fool ¶
¶ you treated me mean ¶
¶ oh! ¶
¶ you treated me cruel ¶
¶ chain chain chain ¶
¶ chain of fools ¶
¶ every chain ¶
¶ has got a weak link ¶
¶ I might be weak, child ¶
¶ but I gave you strength ¶
¶ oh, babe ¶
¶ hoo hoo ¶
¶ you told me
to leave you alone ¶
¶ hoo hoo ¶
¶ my father said come on home ¶
¶ my doctor said take it easy ¶
¶ oh, but your lovin'
is much too strong... ¶
Follow me, ladies.
Follow me.
¶ Chain chain chain ¶
¶ chain chain chain ¶
¶ chain of fools ¶
¶ oh! ¶
¶ one of these mornings ¶
¶ the chain
is gonna break... ¶
Awoo!
I invented the hole in the
coffee cup, you know.
When you get coffee to go,
I was the first person
to rip that little hole in the lid
so you could drink it in the car.
Could've made a fortune.
It's weird.
What?
She's an angel expert, but....
Battle!
Come on!
For God's sake.
Michael.
Stop.
Hey. You.
Battle.
You'd better believe it.
Over here!
It's caramels.
He smells like caramels.
It's cotton candy.
It's cookies.
He smells like cookies,
and the smell gets stronger
when he's in heat.
Eee-yah!
You're a great fighter.
I certainly am.
I'm cold.
My head hurts.
You folks from the National Mirror?
I got a 2-headed
chicken in my yard,
if you're interested.
What are we being held for?
Destruction of property,
assault, battery,
and disturbing the peace.
Magistrate will be here in the morning.
Your honor, I didn't have
anything to do with this.
Good night.
Hey. Hey, hey.
We have a phone call coming to us.
Hey.
Wah-yaaah.
Woo woo-woo.
Ralph got thrown in jail,
but at least he had the decency
to keep me out of it.
I don't want to spend the night here.
I hate you.
You hate me?
Not you.
The process of elimination.
Who is Ralph?
Another husband...
Has popped up.
Maybe Sparky can get us out.
Hey.
Sparky?
Go in the drawer
and get the key.
Sparky.
Go in the drawer
and get the key.
Dorothy can make him do it.
Dorothy's good with dogs.
I have noticed this.
Dogs don't talk.
They don't shave.
They don't run off in your Camaro.
When you want them to take a bath,
you just make an appointment.
Sit.
Stay.
Roll over.
No.
Now.
What?
Apologize.
Say you're sorry.
To her?
Be serious.
Or...
I'm not going to...
¶ Chicago ¶
¶ the toddlin' town ¶
¶ I'll show you around ¶
¶ you'll love it ¶
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it...
Ok?
Dorothy.
You cold?
Here.
Take my blanket, ok?
I'm going to sleep.
Me, too.
All rise, all rise.
The court of bickle county
is now in session.
The honorable judge
Esther Newberg presiding.
Please rise.
Ahem.
Be seated.
Now...
You are charged with...
Disturbing the peace,
destruction of property...
$1,200 worth.
I know.
I spoke to Jenny.
Who's, uh, Jenny?
That's his wife.
She told me
that sweet little painting
above the bar...
uh, 2 moose hunters in a canoe...
smashed to smithereens.
That is so sad.
Yep.
Isn't this a conflict of interest?
Did I say you could speak?
I know someone who can restore paintings.
I told Jenny, "stop crying.
I will take care of it."
Now...
Who can tell me
exactly what happened l...
Last night?
I can.
Anyone else?
We were having dinner...
Not you.
If I may...
put your hand down.
You.
Please.
In chambers.
All rise, all rise.
The court of bickle county,
judge Esther Newberg presiding,
is now in recess.
Please rise.
¶ Love ¶
¶ love ¶
¶ boom ba boom ¶
¶ it's easy ¶
¶ all you need is love ¶
¶ bop ba da da da ¶
¶ dat da da da da ¶
¶ all you need is love ¶
¶ love ¶
¶ love is all you need ¶
¶ there's nothing
you can't know ¶
¶ that isn't known ¶
¶ there's nothing you... ¶
¶ no one you can save
that can't be saved ¶
¶ nothing you can sing
that can't be sung ¶
¶ nothing you can say ¶
¶ but you can learn
how to play the game ¶
¶ it's easy ¶
¶ all you need is love ¶
¶ bop ba da da da ¶
Come on, sing!
¶ All you need is love ¶
Not you, not yet.
Just the guys.
¶ Love ¶
Come on, fellas.
¶ Love is all you need ¶
¶ love is all you need ¶
Bring it down.
¶ Love is all you need ¶
¶ love is all you need ¶
Hey! Wait a minute.
Wait, wait. Meadsboro 1 mile.
So?
So that's where the world's
largest non-stick frying pan is.
Oh, no, Michael.
We are not stopping
to see the world's largest
non-stick frying pan.
Why not?
Because we have to get back.
Well, me, too,
but before that happens,
I would like to see the world's
largest non-stick frying pan.
It is on the way.
Every time we stop somewhere,
he gets us in trouble.
But he also gets us out of trouble.
Huey!
What?
Well, he does.
I mean, look, that judge just took
one look at him and...
what is that?
What is it about you?
What?
As a woman, could you
explain that to me?
How should I know?
I'm not the least bit attracted to him.
No offense, Michael, but I'm not.
I put a block on you.
Oh, sure.
I did.
All right, to continue...
"Presumably...
"This frying pan was coated with teflon
"to save a wee bit on
the amount of cholesterol
"ingested by the town
of meadsboro every year
when they get together
to honor the egg."
Michael, we're not stopping.
You have 10 seconds
to change your mind.
10-hippopotamus.
9-hippopotamus.
8-hippopotamus.
How much more attractive
is he than I am?
7-hippopotamus.
Be honest with me.
Huey, this is not healthy.
5-hippopotamus
4-hippopotamus.
3, 2, 1!
There's no jack!
Of course there is no jack!
Just ask him to fix it.
He blew it, he can fix it!
Fix this tire!
Come back here this instant
and fix this tire!
No can do.
I miss my wife.
I don't miss any of my husbands.
Although Bradley
was handy with a jack.
He had to be.
I don't wanna ask why.
His tires were bald.
So was his head.
I wish he'd call,
but now he's dead.
He's not dead,
and he wasn't bald.
Poetic license.
¶ His tires were bald ¶
¶ and they went flat ¶
¶ so did our love ¶
¶ and that was ¶
¶ that ¶
Maybe you could write
a song about my wife.
Do you love her?
Oh-ho.
Hey, she drives me wild.
Mmm.
What about her?
She had her lips done.
Had little bits of fat
squeezed into them.
Now my wife has lips
like a blowfish...
But in a good way.
Mmm.
¶ My wife ¶
¶ has lips ¶
¶ like a blowfish ¶
I... I don't see it,
but you know, I could be wrong.
If I had any talent
as a country singer,
I wouldn't be sitting
on the side of the road
in the middle of nowhere.
¶ Sittin' on the side
of the road ¶
¶ in the middle of nowhere ¶
Sounds awfully familiar.
Mmm. But it's good, though.
This is one godforsaken road.
I'll bet you no one ever comes down it.
Yeah, well, they won't stop, though.
Hi there.
Bet you need a jack.
I spun around,
and the next thing that happened
was he came as 100 mouths,
open and stinking with decay,
and he tore at my flesh
from every angle of heaven.
So I grabbed beelzebub's
blue tongue in my fist.
Whoa, man.
Who's beelzebub?
Beelzebub is Satan.
Oh.
Satan.
Michael, get in the car.
¶ you are my sunshine ¶
¶ my only sunshine ¶
¶ you make me happy ¶
¶ when skies are gray ¶
¶ you'll never know,
dear... ¶
What'll it be, folks?
Do you have pie?
Do we have pie?
Buddy, you're in the
pie capital of America.
Well, we want...
We want pie.
What have you got?
I got them memorized.
Ok, ready?
We got apple, of course,
banana cream, coconut cream,
sour cream raisin...
Chocolate cream?
Definitely chocolate cream.
And...
strawberry-rhubarb pie
and cherry
and lemon meringue...
We want 2 slices of everything.
And vanilla ice cream on the side.
You got it.
Thank you.
¶ Crazy ¶
¶ arms ¶
¶ that reach to hold ¶
¶ somebody new ¶
¶ while
my yearning heart... ¶
Mmm. Chocolate.
Mmm. Ooh.
Ahh. Bliss.
Bliss.
That's banana cream
and that's coconut.
Everybody get out of
my banana cream pie.
Mmm.
That's... that's the pie.
What's is this?
What is this pie?
This is sour cream-raisin.
Very underrated pie.
Lemon meringue pie.
This is the key lime.
Mm-mmm. Lemon meringue.
What is it about pie?
It's pretty, you know?
There's nothing prettier than pie,
with the little scalloped edges around the sides
and little slits in the top
for the heat to escape.
Pie gives you the sense
that you're a four-square person
living in a four-square country.
Well, pie says home.
As american as apple pie.
I wish I invented pie.
I did.
I'm just kidding.
That was a good one.
God's in his heaven,
and all's right with the world.
Mmm. My mother made a great...
Blueberry pie.
Yes.
So do I.
I have to say I like cream pie
more than fruit pie.
Me, too.
That is so wrong.
I like them all.
I like you.
Mmm.
Dorothy...
Sing your song about pie.
You have a song about pie?
Actually, I do.
Sing, Dorothy.
Now.
¶ Pie ¶
¶ pie ¶
¶ me, oh, my ¶
¶ nothing tastes sweet,
wet, salty, and dry ¶
¶ all at once so well as pie ¶
¶ apple, pumpkin ¶
¶ mince and black bottom ¶
¶ I'll come to your place every day ¶
¶ if you've got 'em ¶
¶ pie, me, oh, my ¶
¶ I love pie ¶
That's great.
Sing another song.
Ohh.
It's, um, it's in B-flat.
It's pretty basic,
but watch out for the guitar
down there, ok?
Ahem.
Oh.
Ahem. Hi.
I'm nervous.
Oh, this is, uh...
you'll have to forgive me.
It's a work in progress.
Don't apologize, Dorothy.
Ok.
1, 2, 3
¶ I'm sittin' by the side of the road ¶
¶ in the middle of nowhere ¶
¶ I don't know where I'm going ¶
¶ but I hope I know it ¶
¶ when I get there ¶
¶ thinkin' about ¶
¶ how love never works out ¶
¶ I guess that's the way it goes ¶
¶ and how this story ends ¶
¶ only heaven knows ¶
¶ I always thought ¶
¶ there was an angel ¶
¶ watchin' over me ¶
¶ but even angels ¶
¶ sometimes make mistakes ¶
¶ as you will see ¶
¶ 'cause I've had my share ¶
¶ of bad love affairs ¶
¶ in fact ¶
¶ I married 3 ¶
¶ so here's my little story ¶
¶ about Myles ¶
¶ Ralph and Bradley ¶
¶ Myles made me smile ¶
¶ till he stole my Camaro ¶
¶ Ralph made me laugh ¶
¶ till I cried ¶
¶ and Bradley ¶
¶ oh, I loved him madly ¶
¶ but his tires were bald ¶
¶ and they went flat ¶
¶ so did our love ¶
¶ and that was that ¶
¶ now I'm sittin' in the middle of nowhere ¶
¶ by the side of the road ¶
¶ one of these days ¶
¶ I'll find true love ¶
¶ and learn how to say no ¶
¶ I know in the past ¶
¶ my love didn't last ¶
¶ as I guess this story shows ¶
¶ where was
my angel then? ¶
¶ only heaven knows ¶
¶ where was
my angel then? ¶
¶ only heaven ¶
¶ knows ¶
Yeah!
Whoo!
And then when I went
to college I was published.
You were published?
Yeah, I was published.
Well, kind of.
It's was like a yearly thing.
Poems, you know?
That's great.
Uh-huh.
That's really great.
Ahh, it's cold.
Yeah.
I'm in there.
This is Huey's room.
Where are you?
I'm in 4.
Where is that?
It's up there.
Where exactly?
On the corner.
On the corner right there?
Directly over my room?
Uh...
Mm-hmm.
Um...
You were great.
Really great.
Um...
Ahem.
It was...
Good night.
Yeah. Good night.
Ahem.
It was...
Mm-hmm.
¶ Something in your eyes ¶
¶ makes me want to lose myself ¶
¶ in your arms ¶
¶ something in your... ¶
What are... what are...
what are you doing tonight?
Not much.
Do you wanna come to my room?
Why don't you come to mine?
That's...
That's a good idea.
¶ The rest of my life ¶
¶ if you knew ¶
¶ how lonely ¶
¶ my life ¶
¶ has been ¶
¶ and how low ¶
Whew.
¶ I've felt ¶
¶ so long ¶
¶ if you knew ¶
¶ how I wanted someone ¶
¶ to come along ¶
¶ and change... ¶
I have to tell you something.
I know.
I'm not...
Ever falling in love
with anyone again.
I know.
¶ Feels like home ¶
¶ to me ¶
¶ feels like home ¶
¶ feels like ¶
¶ I'm all the way back ¶
¶ where I come from ¶
¶ feels like home ¶
¶ to me ¶
¶ feels like I'm ¶
¶ all the way back ¶
¶ where I belong ¶
Ok, ok.
Ohh.
Come on, Sparky.
Come on.
Come on, boy.
Yes.
Wings?
Far out!
Ha ha!
Some angel.
¶ I see trees ¶
¶ of green ¶
¶ red roses, too ¶
¶ I see them bloom ¶
¶ for me and you ¶
¶ and I think to myself ¶
¶ what a wonderful world ¶
¶ I see skies ¶
¶ of blue ¶
¶ and clouds ¶
¶ of white ¶
¶ the bright blessed days ¶
¶ from the dark sacred nights ¶
¶ and I think to myself ¶
¶ what a wonderful world ¶
¶ What a wonderful ¶
¶ world ¶
I needed the job.
Good morning.
What exactly are we
talking about here?
At the paper.
That's what I was trying
to tell you last night.
That's why I'm here.
I don't make excuses
for working there.
There's no reason for you to.
Here's a confession.
You wanna hear a confession?
Yours?
I needed the job, too.
Huh.
No one would go near me
after what happened at the tribune.
What did happen?
Oh.
I hit the managing editor.
Why?
He fired this really sweet old guy
who'd been there
for, like, 27 years.
Really?
Nope.
He changed my lead.
You hit him...
Because he changed your lead?
No.
It was late.
I was drunk.
The way I see it,
it makes no difference where I work.
That's what I call a lie.
I bet you have a half-finished novel
in the second drawer of your desk.
She got the desk.
Are you keeping something from me?
I'm not ethical.
Just because you write about angels
for a supermarket tabloid?
Are you keeping some
angel experience from me?
If you are, I forgive you.
I could forgive you anything.
This was not a mistake.
Don't say that you think
this was a mistake.
I couldn't bear it.
¶ We're here ¶
¶ because we're here ¶
It's going well.
It's a difficult case, though,
to give a man back his heart.
Mmm.
Listen.
Ooh... Listen to the earth.
Mmm.
I'm going to miss
everything so much.
You got to remember, Sparky,
no matter what they tell you,
you can never
have too much sugar.
Dorothy.
Quinlan.
Good morning, Michael.
Good morning, Sparky.
Sparky, no!
No!
Ohh!
Oh, he's all right.
He's all right.
Ohh!
No.
Ohh.
Oh, I killed him.
It's not your fault.
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry, Huey.
I'm so sorry.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Do something.
It isn't my area.
What is your area?
Explain it to me.
Would somebody tell me
exactly what is his area?
I don't know anything
about his area.
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
What?
I don't know anything about angels.
I'm a dog trainer.
That's why I was hired.
To train Sparky?
And then...
then after...
We screw up with the angel,
and Malt gets the dog...
I get Huey's job.
I didn't know you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Now bring him back to life.
And don't give me any of that
"it isn't my area" stuff.
Bring him back to life
or go back where you came from.
Bring him back...
Angel.
I don't have much longer.
Ohh.
We're here, Michael.
We're here.
Michael, look up.
"The sears tower in Chicago
is the world's tallest building.
"It stands 1,454 feet above street level,
contains enough concrete
for an 8-Lane highway."
Ohh.
Ahh.
Quinlan, I'm so sorry.
I didn't do what I came for.
I didn't finish.
I'm so sorry.
Um...
Good-bye.
Good-bye, Michael.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for letting me have a little fun.
Good-bye, my battling friend.
Good-bye, world's biggest angel.
Godspeed.
Ohh.
You're late.
I know.
Where's the angel?
Yeah, it was a hoax.
A hoax?
A hoax.
Definitely a hoax.
He had detachable wings.
And a halo made out of pipe cleaners.
And he smelled of cookies.
Just kidding.
So, I win.
You're fired,
and I get the dog.
Ha ha.
Come here, Sparky.
Come on, my little sausage.
You come to your daddy.
Come on... ow!
Bastard!
Sparky, come on.
Listen, Sparky...
Sparky!
Don't hate me.
I love you... ow!
Oh, gee.
Hey, listen, get the mutt out, will you?
Oh, right.
Like that dog could be gotten out,
like that dog can do anything.
That is the worst dog
I think I've ever met.
I thought you said
you could train any dog.
She was wrong.
Are you saying I'm stuck with
these two because of a dog?
You're stuck with Mr. Driscoll, not with me.
We met a guy with a 2-headed chicken
outside of cedar rapids.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey! Quinlan!
Hey! Hey, Quinlan!
Where are you going?
Hey! Get off of me!
Get... get back!
Listen, Quinlan, forget
what I said. Don't...
don't take it personally.
You're the best reporter I have.
I'm out of here.
Hey!
So you're just going to leave?
You don't want to talk about it?
Nope.
Hey, come on, talk to me, eh?
Well, disagree with me.
Argue me out of it.
All right, let's have a fight.
Come on, fight me, eh?
Hey, Quinlan, you're the only one
that ever fought with me here.
Well, who am I going to fight with?
You got to help me out here.
It isn't my area.
Wait!
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
Please stop and talk to me.
I appreciate what you said up there.
I thank you.
I'll see you around.
You said...
You said you could
forgive me anything.
I forgive you.
We had a good time.
What are you so upset about?
Oh.
It's you.
I remember you.
I thought you were gone.
¶ I took a trip on a train ¶
¶ and I thought about you ¶
Come on in, Rhoda.
¶ I passed a shadowy Lane ¶
¶ and I thought about you ¶
¶ 2 or 3 cars parked under the stars... ¶
Uh, good evening. Buona sera.
Um, for our specialties tonight, we...
we have angel hair pasta
with a pomodoro sauce,
uh, cappellini primavera,
a melange of vegetables
over angel hair pasta,
and finally, a light sauce
with lemon and parsley
tossed with angel hair pasta.
Anything else?
Yes, we want one
pumpkin nut muffin,
and...
A piece of angel food cake.
They don't have angel food cake, do you?
No.
¶ And what did I do? ¶
¶ I thought about you ¶
¶ and I thought about you ¶
¶ there were 2 or 3 cars ¶
¶ parked under the stars ¶
¶ a winding stream ¶
¶ the moon shining down on ¶
¶ some little town ¶
¶ and with each beam ¶
¶ the same old dream ¶
¶ so I thought about you ¶
¶ and I really felt good ¶
¶ and then I'd peek through the crack ¶
¶ and I looked in that track ¶
¶ the one going back to you ¶
¶ and what did I do? ¶
¶ I thought about you ¶
So, did you ever
tell anyone about, uh...
I was going to.
Oh, I couldn't wait to get home to tell Valerie.
And then I opened my mouth,
and the words wouldn't come out.
I'd take a breath, I... I...
I even opened my mouth a second time.
Nothing.
As far as I'm concerned,
it never happened.
Oh, but we saw it.
We were there.
It never happened.
So what are you up to?
I'm back on the novel.
If it didn't happen, where's your raincoat?
"If it..." what is this?
"If it happened?"
If it happened, you know what?
Then I've got to believe that someday
I'm going to be walking down the street
and some unknown force is
going to make me turn right
instead of turning left,
and, at that moment, a car is going
to come around the corner
with the woman of my dreams in it
and blow a flat...
Right there, next to where I'm standing.
No.
It never happened.
Ha ha ha ha.
You need any help?
No, thanks.
No, we're cool.
Ha ha ha ha.
Michael!
Michael, wait!
Ohh!
What are you doing here?
I live here. I live 2 blocks from here.
I was on my way home and...
I thought I saw...
He came around this corner.
That corner.
I love you, Dorothy.
I love you.
Marry me.
No.
Marry me, please?
Marry me, Dorothy.
No.
Ha ha ha ha.
Oh, my darling Dorothy,
will you marry me?
Yes. Yes.
Let's go home.
You know, Pansy,
I invented marriage.
Michael.
Well, I did.
Before that, you should have seen it.
Everybody was so mixed up,
they didn't know what to do.
So I said: "have a ceremony."
Hmm.
Let's go home.
¶ From the dark end of the street ¶
Do you smell something?
There's a bakery near here.
¶ To the bright side of the road ¶
¶ we'll be lovers once again ¶
¶ on the bright side of the road ¶
¶ little darlin', come with me ¶
¶ won't ya help me share my load? ¶
¶ from the dark end of the street ¶
¶ to the bright side of the road ¶
¶ and into this life we're born ¶
¶ baby, sometimes ¶
¶ sometimes we don't know why ¶
¶ and time seems to go by so fast ¶
¶ in the twinkling of an eye ¶
¶ let's enjoy it while we can ¶
¶ won't ya help me share my load? ¶
¶ help me share my load ¶
¶ from the dark end of the street ¶
¶ to the bright side of the road ¶
¶ oh, we'll be ¶
¶ lovers once again ¶
¶ on the bright side of the road ¶
¶ We were dreamin' ¶
¶ on a park bench ¶
¶ about a broad highway somewhere ¶
¶ when the music ¶
¶ from the carillon ¶
¶ seemed to hurl your heart out there ¶
¶ that's the scientific darkness ¶
¶ that's the fireflies that float ¶
¶ to an angel ¶
¶ bending down to wrap you
in his warmest coat ¶
¶ and you ask ¶
¶ what am I not doing? ¶
¶ he says your voice cannot come in ¶
¶ but in time, you will move mountains ¶
¶ it will come ¶
¶ through your hands ¶
¶ so whatever your hands
find to do ¶
¶ you must do
with all your heart ¶
¶ there are thoughts enough
to blow men's minds ¶
¶ and tear great worlds apart ¶
¶ there's a healin' touch
to find you ¶
¶ on that broad highway
somewhere ¶
¶ to lift you
high as music flyin' ¶
¶ through the angel's hair ¶
¶ so don't ask
what you are not doin' ¶
¶ because your voice
cannot come in ¶
¶ in time, you will move mountains ¶
¶ it will come ¶
¶ through your hands ¶
¶ Now, ain't it a shame ¶
¶ all the tears
that people cry? ¶
¶ we ain't got it right
in all of these years ¶
Sorry, man.
¶ There must be a way ¶
¶ to live a better life ¶
¶ and break all these chains
and get out of here ¶
¶ you've got to love God ¶
¶ you've got to love yourself ¶
¶ you've got to
love your brothers ¶
¶ and everybody else ¶
¶ you've got to walk that walk ¶
¶ you can't just talk that talk ¶
¶ you've got to love God ¶
¶ and everybody else ¶
¶ heard some people say ¶
¶ that all we need is love ¶
¶ it sounds so simple ¶
¶ but it's true ¶
¶ well, maybe today ¶
¶ we will rain down love from above ¶
¶ and wash us clean
and make us new ¶
¶ but you've got to love God ¶
¶ you've got to love yourself ¶
¶ you've got to love,
love, love, love God ¶
¶ and everybody else ¶
¶ hey, I want to believe ¶
¶ I got to believe ¶
¶ want to be true ¶
¶ I want to be true ¶
¶ I want to see a miracle ¶
¶ I want you to see it, too ¶
¶ now ¶
¶ love God ¶
¶ I want to love my neighbor ¶
¶ you've got to love God ¶
¶ and everybody else... ¶