Although your diplomas
are equally specific,
remember, you are all
going out into the world
as individuals.
I now proudly present
this year's
Woodrow Wilson School
of Public
and International Affairs'
graduating class.
[cheering]
[all chant]
Whoo!
Bye! We love you.
Write.
You have to write.
-Thank your mom
for the cookies, OK?
-Of course.
I'm very proud of you.
[Mia] Dear Diary...
Well, it's me,
brand-new college graduate-
slash-princess.
Oh, I can't believe
it's been five years
since Grandma told me
that I was a princess.
Me? A... A princess?
Shut up!
And right after that,
my mother surprised me
by marrying
my high school teacher,
Patrick O'Connell.
It must be going well,
because they are now
expecting a baby.
Lilly's remained the same,
as she continues
to cause turmoil,
but now as a graduate student
at Berkeley,
which she calls "Berserkely".
How's Michael, you may ask?
Well, we're just friends now,
as he went off
to tour the country
with his band.
Princess Mia,
look out the window
and welcome back
to Genovia.
Oh, there it is,
my beautiful Genovia.
Of course,
I'm completely excited
to be going back,
but I'm also a bit nervous.
[pilot over PA]
Genovia One has landed.
[Mia] Grandma Clarisse
will step down by the end
of this year as queen,
and I'll be taking over,
since I'm now 21.
Mira! La Princesa Mia!
It's the princess
from America!!
[man] Mira!
La princesa!
I know I studied diplomacy
and political science
at school,
but there was
no course in "Queen"
or "How to Run a Country 101."
But Grandma's
going to help me,
and I'll take over
when she thinks I'm ready.
Of course, I wonder...
will I ever be ready?
In the meantime, I'm going to
live in a beautiful palace,
like in a fairy tale,
and eventually sit on a throne
and rule the people
of Genovia.
Is that scary or what?
Well, maybe Fat Louie
can give me some help.
[Majordomo] Her Royal Highness,
Princess Amelia Mignonette
Thermopolis Renaldi,
has arrived.
Welcome home,
Princess.
[meows]
And her royal pussycat,
Sir Fat Louie.
The one downer
in my fairy tale is...
I've never been in love.
[Majordomo]
Countess Puck of Austria.
However, this evening is
my 21st birthday party,
and our tradition says
I have to dance with all
the eligible bachelors
in Genovia,
so maybe I'll meet
my Prince Charming tonight.
[Charlotte] The queen is coming.
Here she comes.
Look alive.
Places.
She'll have
a double-door entrance.
The eagle is flying.
Repeat, the eagle
is flying.
She's in the foyer.
Beautiful...
but you're late,
Your Majesty.
A queen is never late.
Everyone else
is simply early.
Of course.
[Majordomo] Her Majesty,
Clarisse Renaldi,
Queen of Genovia.
[heralds playing flourish]
[laughs]
Greetings, good friends.
I am delighted
to welcome you here
this evening.
Thanks for askin'.
Thank you.
I hope they have
string cheese.
Ah, good.
Many of you will remember
King Rupert's
and my granddaughter,
Princess Mia.
[all] King Rupert,
may he rest in peace.
Will you please
raise your glasses
in celebration
of Princess Mia's
21st birthday.
[Majordomo] Presenting
Her Royal Highness
Amelia Mignonette
Thermopolis Renaldi,
Princess of Genovia.
[drumroll]
To Princess Mia.
[all] To Princess Mia.
It happens
all the time.
Ohh.
-And happy birthday.
-Thank you.
[waltz]
[speaks Greek]
Oh, I don't speak Greek.
And you obviously
don't speak English.
[speaks Greek]
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
-one, two...
-Ohh!
Oh. Sorry.
[speaking German]
[jazz]
Have you met
the princess yet?
Briefly, but she wasn't
very friendly.
[Russian accent] I got
a hello and a goodbye.
Is this
an American custom?
I saw that.
Um...
[both squeal]
Oh, how I've missed you!
-Sebastian.
-Your Majesty.
-Sheila.
-Majesty.
What have you been up to?
Just partying, girl,
you know.
Ohh! Oh, your foot!
I'm so sorry. Are y...
Are you all right?
I'll survive,
Your Highness.
The fault was
entirely my own.
I apologize.
Are you sure you don't want
to exchange licenses
and proof of insurance?
No, no, these shoes
were a little big anyway,
and swelling should
help them fit better.
[tango]
Whoa!
Aha.
Get a load
of this guy.
[both giggle]
Shimmy-shim.
Whoa, hey.
Hey, hey, hey...
You are
a beautiful dancer.
Oh, why,
thank you so much.
...like a deer or a chipmunk
in the forest.
Looks like he's trying
to land a plane.
Woodland animals
are a lovely thing
to be compared to.
May I?
Your timing is impeccable.
Thank you.
You're welcome,
Your Highness.
-Mia. I like
to be called Mia.
-Mm.
And you are...?
Nicholas.
Just Nicholas.
Well, I'm very glad
to see that my clumsiness
hasn't affected your dancing.
I'm sorry I stepped
on your foot.
You can step on my foot
anytime.
[both] Aw...
It is
Prince Jacques' turn.
Your Highness.
If this were my party,
we'd be kissing by now.
That's Prince Jacques.
He's about 12 years old.
He's a very
precocious prince.
He wears aftershave
to make people think
that he's older.
May I blow in your ear?
Can you reach it?
-Princess..
-Hmm?
There's someone
from Parliament
you should meet, hmm?
Charlotte, how many members
of Parliament are there?
Only two left,
Your Highness.
Ah. Hmm?
-Aah! Oh, dear.
-Your Highness, pardon me.
I am so sorry.
It was only an accident.
It's fine, it's fine.
No harm, no foul, no bruise.
[laughs]
Thank you so much.
You should be more careful,
Your Royal Highness.
Somebody might try
to take that away from you.
Oh, I hope not,
but thank you so much
for all your help.
Someone like me.
Welcome back
to Eggs With Elsie.
I'm Elsie Kentworthy,
and today's topic
is Princess Mia...
Oh, hi.
How's it going?
[turns off TV]
I'm so sorry.
I thought I was alone.
No, miss. I'm Brigitte,
if it pleases you,
at your service.
And I'm Brigitta,
miss.
Brigitte and Brigitta?
I'm Mia, and, please,
don't curtsy like that.
-Not like this?
How do you like it?
-Like this, maybe?
No, no, no,
I didn't mean like,
you know, this...
No, no, not that way.
I didn't mean it at, um...
The queen bids you
good morning, Princess.
-She's in session
with Parliament.
-OK.
I see you've met
your lady's maids.
Yeah. Um...
[laughs]
[whispers] How do you
turn off the curtsies?
Oh. Enough bowing.
Back to your chores.
Her Majesty will meet you
in one hour at the throne room.
-OK.
-I'm sorry your suite
isn't ready yet,
but you're welcome to stay here
in Her Majesty's suite...
No, no, no, it's fine.
Hey, can I explore
the palace a little bit?
-Of course.
-[dog barks]
Well, you've met Maurice.
[barks]
[Mia] Hey, Mo.
The throne room in an hour?
[man] The parliament
of Genovia is in session,
Prime Minister Motaz
presiding.
Viscount Mabrey,
you have the floor.
[man #2] Sir Mabrey,
s'il vous plait.
As we all know,
the 21st birthday...
-[snoring]
-...of an heir
to the Genovian bloodline
is indeed a matter
of great public significance.
It signifies
that this young person
is eligible
to assume the crown.
Indeed, we are well aware
of this, Viscount.
The queen has already indicated
that Princess Mia intends
to learn more at her side
before assuming the throne.
It was not Princess Mia
to whom I was referring.
Oh, wow.
King Chevalier was
the great-great-
great-grandfather of...
Hello?
Uh....
[clears throat]
Proceed.
[gasps]
Nice.
Hello?
[squeals] OK.
Ooh.
[Viscount Mabrey] So, as of
the 20th of October last year,
on the occasion
of his 21st birthday,
another Genovian
of the royal bloodline
became eligible
to assume the throne.
What?
My nephew,
Lord Devereaux.
I beg your pardon.
My nephew's mother
was my wife's sister,
and therefore, Your Majesty,
I am pleased to say
that my nephew is ready
to take his place
as Genovia's rightful king.
Shut up.
I beg your pardon?
I mean, um...
Uh, "shut up"
doesn't always mean...
shut up.
[speaking French]
In America,
it's like "Oh, my,"
"Gee whiz,"
"Wow."
Thank you,
Mr. Prime Minister.
But isn't Princess Mia
first in line to ascend
the throne?
Not yet.
Genovian law states
that a princess must marry
before she can take the throne.
We have never enforced
that law.
A man doesn't have to marry
to be king.
This is the 21st century,
for heaven's sake.
My granddaughter should be given
the same rights as any man.
Yeah! [gasps]
[Palimore] Genovia shall
have no queen
lest she be bound
in matrimony.
Lord Palimore.
That is the law of Genovia
for the last 300 years.
Princess Mia
is not qualified to rule
because she is unmarried.
And forgive me,
Your Majesty.
Not all of us are sure
that the princess
is the most suitable choice
to govern our great nation.
[men] Ooh.
Now, now, gentlemen,
gentlemen, please.
I suggest
this honored body
allow Princess Mia
one year,
during which time
she must marry,
or she forfeits
the throne of Genovia
to young Lord Devereaux.
What? No.
I object.
I object most strongly.
-Sixty days.
-Two months.
[man] 60 days?
30 days.
How could Parliament expect me
to fall in love in 30 days?
It's like...
It's like it's a big trick
to get me to have
an arranged marriage or--
No. That's it, there's no "or."
An arranged marriage
is my only choice.
What kind of person agrees
to an arranged marriage?
Uh... well, you agreed
to an arranged marriage.
Right.
Yes, I did,
and it turned out
quite splendidly.
He was my best friend.
We grew very fond
of each other.
Yeah, I'm sure, Grandma,
but...
I dream of love,
not... fondness.
But you don't have to
do this, Mia.
You don't have to
become queen.
It's just so unfair.
[father] Amelia...
[together] ...courage is not
the absence of fear...
[Mia] ...but rather
the judgment
that something else
is more important
than fear.
There are 550 years
of Renaldis on these walls,
and I will be up there
next to my father.
I'm sure I want my chance
to make a difference
as a ruler.
Spoken like a true queen.
[Mabrey] You, my boy,
a true-born Genovian,
you should be our king.
I agree,
but... how can we
make it happen?
Give me one of your arrows.
I'm going to show you
a trick that I learnt
from an old
Italian philosopher,
Niccolo Machiavelli.
I can make this dart
hit the bull's-eye every time.
Haah!
Yes, but...
that is cheating.
You've got it.
[Queen] Lord Devereaux will be
arriving shortly, Mrs. Cout,
-with his snake of an uncle.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
-Your Majesty...
-Hmm?
I know Lionel is
the Prime Minister's nephew and
he's interning for the summer
because he wants to learn
about security,
but he never leaves my side.
He sticks to me
like Velcro, madam.
It won't last very long.
He returns to school
in the autumn.
He wants an audience
with you.
-What, now?
-Now.
Lionel?
Short.
I don't know if you've met
Mrs. Cout, our housekeeper,
and Priscilla and Olivia,
my lady's maids.
I'm doing a background check
on Olivia.
Oh, that's not necessary,
Lionel.
Everybody in this room
has high-priority clearance.
Of course,
of course.
-Your Majesty.
-Hmm?
I would gladly
take a bullet for you.
Oh, how brave.
Most interns don't even want
to fetch me my tea.
The limousine
is at the gates, madam.
[Queen] The viscount is not
staying. Just the nephew.
Joseph, I want you
to protect him
and keep your eye on him
at all times.
-Of course. Lionel.
-Oh, hello.
So, is this all right
to welcome the viscount
and his nephew?
Very appropriate
and pretty.
Oh, I can't believe Parliament
invited the guy who's trying
to steal the throne
to stay here with us
at the palace.
Oh, no, Parliament
didn't invite him.
-I did.
-Wha...?
I offered to have him
hung by his toes
in our courtyard.
-Excuse me.
-Yeah.
What about Joe's suggestion?
No. If there's any
mischief going on,
I'd prefer it be
right under my nose.
It's not a very difficult
job, you know.
You just have to open the door
before the passenger dies
of old age.
Hello. I'm here
to welcome you.
Your staff is incompetent
and unreliable.
I just so don't want
to be nice to this guy.
He is rude, he's arrogant
and self-centered, he's...
Have you met him?
I ju-- No.
Neither have I.
Yeah, but he probably is,
Grandma.
I mean, like now,
all of a sudden, out of nowhere,
he wants to be
the King of Genovia?
What is that about?
Ohh, tush.
Whatever he is,
we will be charm itself.
We will present ourselves
with grace and poise.
[Majordomo]
Announcing Viscount Mabry
and Lord Devereaux.
[staff thumps]
[Mabrey] Your Majesty.
-Your Highness.
-[Queen] Mabrey.
[Mabrey] Ma'am,
may I introduce my nephew,
Lord Nicholas Devereaux.
Nicholas, we are delighted
to make your acquaintance.
Your Majesty,
the pleasure is all mine,
and thank you so much
for inviting me to stay
at the palace.
May I present
my granddaughter, Mia.
Your Highness.
Mia, would you care
to welcome our guest?
[sighs]
Lord Nicholas.
Uhh! Humph!
[laughs]
Ahh.
She always does that.
Uh, I will personally
get some ice for that foot,
and I'll be with you
as quickly as I possibly can.
An accident.
Of course.
She's training to be
a flamenco dancer.
Would you care to explain
what was going on out there?
Sorry.
I, uh, have met Lord Nicholas.
Actually, yep,
at the ball. Mm-hmm.
Didn't know who he was,
so, you know, we...
we danced,
and I flirted.
I feel so stupid right now.
I see.
Well, as your queen,
I absolutely
cannot condone it.
As a grandma, I say...
right on.
Now, if you'll come with me,
I have something to show you.
Oh, OK.
I think you could
leave that right there.
[Queen] Thank you,
culinary people.
[whispers] I'll be back.
The renovations for your suite
are finally finished.
Should have been ready for you
when you arrived,
but unfortunately
we asked Rupert's cousin
to do the bathroom.
It's a good lesson.
Nepotism belongs in the arts,
not in plumbing.
This is your very own suite.
-Are you serious?
-Mm-hmm.
This is... Ah!
Wow.
This is my room?
[chuckles] Yes.
Oh, Grandma.
This is very nice.
Good.
Ha-ha!
We just made the bed.
This so cool!
[Queen laughs]
Ah, Fat Louie.
I think he rather likes
his new abode as well.
-[meows]
-There's more.
[chuckles]
Is that mine?
Why don't you go
and find out?
OK.
I have my own mall.
[Queen chuckles]
Ooh, very nice shoes.
[Queen] I'm glad you like it.
Try pressing
button number three.
Oh.
♪ Yeah ♪
They're charming.
I love these.
What do you think?
Grandma?
[Queen] I'm here.
Oh, hello.
Ooh, love that. This...
Now press
combination 6-5-6.
6-5-6.
♪ Cool ♪
[Mia] Um...
they're a little..
gorgeous.
Ooh! Oh! Oh.
[Queen] I had a selection
of the crown jewels
brought out for you.
They're yours to borrow
with great discretion
at appropriate times.
Now, for the best
surprise of all.
[meows]
Wow.
Gorgeous, Grandma,
but kind of a letdown
after the jewels.
I'm not gonna lie. Aah!
[gasps]
-[screams]
-[laughs]
Ohh....
[squealing]
Oh, I don't...
-You're here!
-I know...
-You're in Genovia!
-I know.
-You're in my closet!
-Yeah.
-You're blond!
-I'm blond.
I'm so glad to see you!
I think this is
as good a moment as any
to bow out.
I think I'll let you two ladies
catch up with each other.
[Mia] I can't believe
you're here. When did
your flight get in?
-Just a little while ago.
-By the way,
I'm getting married.
-To who?
-I don't know.
[Charlotte] Baron Johann Klimt.
[Queen] No, not appropriate.
He's a compulsive gambler.
[Mia gasps] Yes.
Oh, yes!
I-I-I-I absolutely accept.
Prince William.
He's not eligible
because he's in line
for his own crown.
Ohh.
If he's not eligible,
why is he included
in these pictures?
I just love
to look at him.
-Mm. Me, too.
-Mm-hm.
Your Majesty.
-[Queen] Next?
-[Charlotte] Antoine Suisson
of Paris.
-[Queen] Uh-huh.
-Plays the harp.
No title,
but good family.
-[Lilly] What about
the title "husband?
-Yeah, he's cute.
His boyfriend thinks
he's handsome also.
[both] Right on.
No matter.
Put him on all
the invitation lists.
He's a divine dancer.
Next.
Too old.
Too young.
Does this popcorn
taste like pears?
Genovian specialty.
[Joe] Arrested
too many times.
We need someone titled,
someone who can help you
run a country
without ego
getting in the way,
someone attractive, smart,
but not arrogant,
someone with compassion.
-Someone like him?
-[whines]
Yes. Someone very much
like him.
Good choice, Mia.
I wonder I didn't
think of him before.
Andrew Jacoby.
Duke of Kenilworth.
Ohh. Well, he looks... decent.
[Charlotte]
He was an Olympic swimmer,
rides motorcycles,
loves photography,
and he's a pilot
in the Royal Air Force.
-Can I do that?
-No.
You ever take
those shades off?
No.
[Elsie] Here we are at
the breezy seashore village
of Mertz,
and our two lovers
have perfect weather
for their first
public outing,
along with Andrew's parents
Susan and Arnold.
Must be rather hard
to get to know each other
this way.
Oh, they're waving at us.
-Oh!
-Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, Mia. A princess
should not run
for her scarf.
I got it!
-Whoo!
-[laughing]
Shall we have some tea?
-Scarf.
-Why, thank you, sir.
I think you might be
clumsier than me.
Oh, good shot.
-Whoa!
-Ohh.
No, no, let them bond.
Let them bond.
-Glasses off.
-I'm coming, Princess.
I'm coming.
I'm coming, Princess.
-[moans]
-There you go.
Ah.
[nervous laughter]
♪ They were smitten ♪
♪ While playing badminton ♪
♪ Where's my kitten? ♪
[Renee Olstead,
"A Love That Will Last"]
♪ I want a little ♪
♪ Something more ♪
♪ Don't want the middle ♪
♪ Or the one before ♪
♪ I don't desire ♪
♪ A complicated past ♪
♪ I want a love
That will last ♪
♪ Hmm-hmm-hmm ♪
Every marriage in my family
for the past 200 years
has been arranged, and...
-Andrew?
-Yes?
Could you try to talk
without moving your lips?
The lip-readers
have binoculars.
Here we find our favorite
new royal couple
nestled under Genovia's
famous pear tree.
And I have something
for you.
Oh, you don't have to
get me anything.
-My birthday was
last week, but it...
-Mia.
-Oh.
-There you go.
Cool. You know, film.
That's nice.
-[canister rattles]
-What is that?
It's a film canister.
What's in
the film canister?
What's in it?
-Why don't you open it?
-Oh, OK.
Oh.
[Andrew] It was my...
my great-grandmother's
engagement ring.
She and my great-grandfather
were married for 57 years,
so I... I felt it could
be lucky for us, maybe.
Do I have to
put it on myself?
No, I can do that.
-OK.
-Yes.
Oh, my goodness!
It was a ring.
A royal proposal
has been made.
-Fly the lovebirds.
-[cheering]
[heralds playing]
You ready?
If you are.
[Majordomo] Announcing
the royal engagement
of Princess Mia
and Andrew Jacoby,
Duke of Kenilworth.
[crowd cheering]
Yeah, just like
the princess.
[Nicholas] Uncle, I hate to say
this, but you were wrong.
Princess Mia has managed
to find a husband
within a week.
Mia cannot possibly be happy
with the idea
of an arranged marriage.
Your task is to romance her,
show her what
a real relationship
could be like,
a relationship filled
with heat and passion.
And change her mind
about Andrew?
Exactly.
And the 30-day deadline expires
and the throne is ours.
And you're sure
my father wanted this?
It was his dearest wish.
His last words to me were,
"Help him, Arthur.
One day, he could be king."
I don't recall him
ever mentioning that to me.
Well, he wouldn't.
You were only six years old
when he died.
But you do remember
who he named you after,
don't you?
Yes, Grandfather Nicholas.
No, no, no, no!
Niccolo Machiavelli.
Power, my boy,
means never having
to say you're sorry.
[Fat Louie yowls]
[barking]
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here, kitty, kitty.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you.
-Oh! Your Highness.
-Shh.
[softly] Andrew's plane
just took off.
He said he'd call
as soon as he arrives
in London.
He won't be gone long.
Why are we whispering?
[whispering] I'm hiding
from my lady's maids.
But I'm fine, I'm fine.
[sighs]
[whistling]
Are you having second thoughts?
No. Actually,
on the contrary,
I was just admiring
my ring.
It was Andrew's
grandmother's.
You know, he really is
so romantic.
Well, if you'll
excuse me,
I really must go see
to some wedding details.
I'm sorry. Is there something
you wanted to say to me?
No. No.
You are the one
who stomped on me
with your big feet.
Big feet?
Brigitte,
I found her!
Uh, B-B-Brigitta,
I'm not here.
It wasn't her.
It was a ghost.
Whoo!
Well, you know,
you danced
with my big feet.
Fine.
I danced with you.
Call the Hague, convene
the war crimes tribunal.
Mia, I would remind you
that we only danced
for about a minute.
It was more than a minute.
Well, maybe a minute
and a half.
Fine. It was
a minute and a half,
but it was also a lie,
because you didn't tell me
who you were and that you
were trying to steal my crown.
Well, please pardon me.
I had a momentary lapse
of good manners.
You see, usually when
I ask a woman to dance,
I always show her
my family tree.
Oh, well, aren't you
just... crafty.
[Mrs. Cout] Let's look
in the ballroom.
[Brigitta] The ballroom?
I don't think...
Do you want to know what else
you were doing while you were
doing your little lie dance?
Lie dance?
Oh. Yeah, that is exactly
what you did.
What is a lie dance?
[Mrs. Cout] I'll go
to the ballroom myself.
[Brigitta] All right.
[clears throat]
The lie dance
is not the point.
-The point...
-What is the point?
is that I--
The point is
that I'm onto you.
Oh, boy, am I onto
what you are trying to do.
And what am I
trying to do?
I think we both know
exactly what that is.
Oh, oh, please forgive
the intrusion,
-Your Highness,
Lord Devereaux.
-No, you don't... uh...
[Joe] I'm told
this Lord Devereaux boy
is a native Genovian,
recently graduated
Cambridge,
gourmet cook,
plays polo and rugby,
and is known as
quite the ladies' man.
-She was in a closet?
-With him, yes.
[sighs] Does she have
the makings of a queen?
Well, she's young,
but I've always
believed in her.
-The wedding invitations
have been sent out.
-Yes.
She and Andrew
make a fine pair, I think.
She's very set on it,
you know.
[Joseph] Clarisse, my dear,
forget the wedding
for a moment.
[clears throat]
In less than a month,
you will no longer
be queen,
and I will no longer be
your head of security.
I think it's time
we bring our friendship
out of the shadows.
-Oh, Joseph, I...
-Yes.
Yes, my dear, I would kneel
if it weren't for my
knee replacement.
Ohh... Oh, Joseph,
there's a wedding
to be planned.
Mia needs to win over
the people of Genovia,
all in less than 30 days.
Perhaps
it's time to consider
the duty you have
to yourself.
Ohh...
Clarisse...
my darling,
please think about it.
Please.
I will.
Dear Diary,
my queen lessons continue.
Surprise, surprise.
To fulfill
one Genovian tradition,
I must learn
to shoot a flaming arrow
through a ceremonial ring,
which will happen
on the eve of my coronation.
It's symbolic for lighting
my own eternal flame.
♪ We all want a holiday ♪
♪ Let's take a little time
For a getaway ♪
-It's coming.
-♪ It's all good ♪
♪ And better still ♪
♪ We can go crazy
And you know we will ♪
-♪ We'll have fun... ♪
-Oof!
[coughs]
♪ Everybody wants some ♪
-Ooh.
-[both scream]
♪ Fun in the sun
Everybody needs some ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Fun in the sun ♪
♪ I'm talkin'
'Bout a good time, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ Fun in the sun ♪
-♪ You know ♪
Sorry.
They're here.
The sparrow is flying.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I am almost in time,
though.
Aah! Oh, hey, sorry.
Got it. I got it.
You know what?
I'm OK. I'm fine.
So, what are we
learning today?
We are learning
the art of the fan.
-Fascinating.
-Yes.
Get up. We only have about
ten minutes in which
to communicate this.
Now, first of all,
one handles a fan
very deliberately.
It's a tremendous tool
of communication.
That's it.
You can say things like,
"I'm feeling flirtatious.
Come hither."
You can say, "I never wish
to speak to you again.
Go away."
You can say, "I'm feeling
terribly shy today."
♪ Three little maids
From school are we ♪
♪ Pert as a schoolgirl
Well can be ♪
-♪ Filled to the brim
With girlish glee ♪
-[laughs]
♪ Three little maids
From school ♪
♪ Everything
Is a source of fun ♪
And you...
Are you sassing
your grandma?
I would never sass you,
Grandma, I promise.
Oh, this is also a way
of showing your annoyance.
We will have somebody
come and visit your farm
in the morning
and perhaps we can
repair the well
and save your feed.
This is for your table.
Thank you.
Thank you,
Your Majesty.
You do this so well.
They just adore you.
It's part of an ancient
Genovian tradition.
One has to be fair
and very honest.
Even if you can't help,
you have to show the people
you care.
[Charlotte] Citizen
Jacqueline Grenault.
We will review
your scholarship application,
and someone will be in touch
no later than the end
of next week.
Oh, merci, Your Majesty.
Here is a melon
for your table.
Oh, merci, Jacqueline.
C'est gentile.
[Charlotte] Citizen Tiny Duval.
Your Majesty.
Bonjour, Tiny.
May I present my granddaughter,
Princess Mia.
-[Tiny] Princess Mia.
-[Mia] Monsieur.
Thank you
for seeing me today.
Something for your table.
Thank you.
She's my favorite.
I hope you like omelets.
May I...?
[Tiny] Of course.
-Be careful.
-[gasps]
-Oh. Oh, it's a chicken.
-[clucking]
Oh, dear!
It's OK. It's OK.
Oh! Oh, got it!
Please! Oh!
[laughing]
We have a chicken situation
in the throne room.
[laughing]
Uh, Mia.
Yeah.
A princess never chases
a chicken.
Dear Diary,
tomorrow my stress level
goes to 11
as I review the royal guard.
The whole court
will be watching,
plus the troops,
and I'm wearing
a floor-length dress.
I also have to be ladylike
while riding sidesaddle.
Ha!
I can't ride
sidesaddle.
No, no, no, I couldn't
ride sidesaddle, either,
when I was your age,
and frankly, dear,
it is acutely uncomfortable.
Herbie is
my riding companion.
-Here he is.
-Oh.
Herbie.
It's a wooden leg.
Yes.
That is impressively
sneaky, Grandma.
Did you come up with this
on your own?
Oh, no, it's
a centuries-old idea.
-And you put the riding boot
on it...
-Exactly.
Our ancestors knew
a thing or two, right?
You just drape your skirt
over it, and nobody
suspects a thing.
[Majordomo] Hear ye, hear ye.
Princess Amelia Mignonette
Thermopolis Renaldi
reviews the royal guard
of Genovia.
Now, the last time
we spoke,
you mentioned that, uh,
Princess Mia's horse, Sandy,
gets easily spooked
by snakes,
so let's get it
really spooked, shall we?
This is a fake snake.
Oh, you're very observant,
a regular David Attenborough.
That's rubber, yes,
but it will spook the horse.
I'm Nick,
Viscount Mabrey's nephew.
Aha, the chap who's trying
to stage the palace coup.
I'm Andrew Jacoby.
Nice to meet you.
Lilly Moscovitz,
official best friend
of future queen.
I don't like you.
Pleasure.
Attend. Hut!
I like all these men
wearing helmets.
Open rank.
[shouts ]
[Sandy neighing]
Sandy, whoa. Oh!
Oh! Ohh!
-My goodness. Oh, my...
-Easy.
-Princess.
-Sandy, easy.
-Oh!
-Princess. Princes.
It's OK, Princess.
I'm here.
[crowd murmuring]
Joe!
No wonder she's so clumsy.
She's got a wooden leg.
[laughter]
[Sandy neighs]
Talk about getting off
on the wrong foot.
[Majordomo] The ceremony
has officially ended.
[bangs staff]
[crying]
You shouldn't hide.
It only makes them
gossip more.
What do you want?
Why, just think, Mia.
One more leg, and, uh,
you could have easily
outrun your horse.
I don't need this right now.
Mia, I... I'm sorry. I...
[Mia] No, you're not.
You never think about
anyone but yourself,
so just this once,
can you please
let me be miserable
and not make me feel worse
about myself?
-Just go away.
Go away from me.
-Mia.
Princess, excuse me.
The queen has arrived.
Yes.
Nicholas, am I going to be
disappointed in you?
[footsteps]
Unfortunate incident, that.
I'm just leaving.
You going to come
and see me off?
I'd like to speak
with your uncle alone,
Nicholas, please.
Viscount, you may not be aware
of what my job entails
as the royal head of security.
My job is to protect the crown,
to make sure no harm comes
to the crown,
to step in when someone toys
with the crown's emotions,
you see.
I think the entire country
understands
how well you cater
for the crown's emotions.
If you hurt my girl,
you will answer directly to me,
and whatever crimes I commit
against you, remember,
I have diplomatic immunity
in 46 countries,
including Puerto Rico.
Sir, you will find
that the word "fear"
is not in my vocabulary.
Perhaps...
but it's in your eyes.
You forgot something.
Au revoir, Pierre.
Remercie beaucoup.
Tres bien, Majesty.
Nicholas, I... I want
to ask you a question.
Of course, Majesty.
Why are you so against
Princess Mia being queen?
My uncle feels
that Princess Mia
doesn't know the people.
And you feel you do?
Know the people?
Yes. I was born here,
I went to primary school here.
I am a true Genovian.
Mia didn't even know
she was Genovian
until high school,
and to be frank, she's spent
little time here since then.
Well, I happen to feel
that she'll make a great ruler.
She's terribly bright,
sensitive, caring.
-I know that.
-You do?
Yes. Yes, I do,
but, well, how can one
rule the people
if they do not know
the people?
Touché. That's
a very good question.
[piano]
[woman singing opera]
Opera's new rising star,
Anna Netrebko.
Looks good enough to eat.
[laughter]
How are your grandchildren
Willy, Charlotte and Sam?
They're wonderful.
Thank you for remembering.
How are you?
Good to see you.
How's your Dachshund?
Maury, right?
He is great.
You remember him
from last time?
Dobar dan,
Lady Zrinka.
Princess Mia.
Mia's doing well.
Some major mingling,
I see.
A little higher,
Olivia.
Mia, do you happen
to see who's here?
No. Who?
The king wannabe
with Lady Elissa.
Oh. Is she his... girlfriend?
Nicholas doesn't have
girlfriends.
He has dates,
but attractive ones.
You talk to him much?
Uh, we acknowledge
each other.
Andrew?
Yes, dear. Coming.
Guck.
Well, the camera's
all ready to go, so...
-All right. Um...
let's go this way.
-OK.
Oh, well struck.
-You did very well, Mia.
Very charming.
-Aw, thank you.
Wait, wait, wait.
The light is perfect.
Just one more...
-Please, no more pictures.
-Come on, please.
-It's very flattering, but...
-Mia, one more picture.
[camera beeps]
Ah.
Hello. Uh, I'm, uh,
Andrew Jacoby.
Oh, hello.
Lady Elissa.
Pleasure.
Your Highness.
Hello.
Elissa and I
were just discussing
her latest achievement.
She's received
the Rhodes scholarship.
-Nicholas, please.
-Why not brag?
You're an amazing woman.
Elissa, congratulations.
You know, Andrew has a PhD
in anthropology from Oxford.
Fantastic.
Elissa was in the Peace Corps.
Really?
Andrew spent four months
in Papua New Guinea
studying the bark
of a yam tree.
-Uh, Andrew--
-Elissa single-handedly...
Elissa is actually trying
to say something.
Yes, Lady Elissa?
Andrew, would you like
to get a drink?
I have a feeling
they're going to start
a "my horse is bigger
than your horse" run.
I would absolutely love to.
Excuse us.
No, her horse
actually is very huge.
-[Elissa] Oh, really?
-Yes.
S... Mm.
-Fantastic party.
-It is.
You two make
such a lovely couple.
We do, yeah.
-It's a shame you're not
attracted to him.
-I know. It...
You... I...
Come back here!
-[clears throat]
-[guitar]
Ladies and gentlemen,
a special treat for
our friends from Asia...
Jonny Blu.
[singing in Chinese]
[Mia] Ohh, you come back.
You can't just say
something like that
and walk away.
I will have you know
that I am very attracted
to Andrew.
-Well, obviously.
-I am. He's...
We are perfect
for each other.
He understands me.
Understands you?
Wow. What passion.
I didn't hear you
mention love.
[scoffs]
You are so jealous.
Why would I be jealous
of Andrew?
He's got to spend
the rest of his life
married to you.
I loathe you.
[gasps]
I loathed you first.
[gasps, squeals]
What... What are you doing?
What is wrong with you?
You can't just go around
kissing people,
particularly not
engaged people.
-You enjoyed it.
You wanna kiss again?
-Well, I--
Stop trying
to confuse me.
What's confusing
about a kiss?
You're just trying
to make me like you
so that I won't want
to marry Andrew
and so that you
can have the crown. Ah!
Well, maybe I am and...
maybe I just
like kissing.
You... You stay away
from me! Aah!
Aah!
Mia.
You know what?
I have an idea.
I have a great idea.
Why don't you go underwater,
and I'll count to a million.
Mia, careful. Mia.
Do I want to know?
-I don't think so.
-Mm.
I'll be two seconds, Mia.
She's going to be
a handful, isn't she?
You'll never be bored,
Andrew.
Yes.
-Olivia, enough goodbyes.
-Yes, ma'am.
Eagle is leaving.
In hushed tones, Lionel.
Hushed tones.
[Queen] When are you going to
start acting responsibly?
Hiding in a closet with a man
who is not your betrothed?
Coming out of a fountain
dripping wet
with the same man
who is not your betrothed?
Do you think I plan for
this kind of stuff to happen?
I lost it.
Sometimes you just lose it!
You can't afford to lose it.
Other people lose it.
We're supposed to find it.
People look up to us,
and we're held to
higher standards of behavior.
Can you try to grasp
that concept?
The concept is grasped.
The execution is...
a little elusive.
I would say so.
[sighs]
Try to get some sleep.
You'll want to look fresh
for the parade tomorrow.
Good night.
Humph!
Good night, Grandmother.
Bling blang by gudda
bidda bigga... aah!
Bling blag shuppadiou!
Well, Maurice,
it's just you and I.
Or are you
upset with me, too?
[whines]
[drums]
Royal Guard of Genovia,
fall in!
Big parade day.
Identify, Mustang personnel.
Why do you talk
like that?
I'm... Captain Kip Kelly
of the Royal Guard.
What if we all talked
like that?
Lilly Moscovitz,
best friend
of Princess Mia,
riding in the 'Stang.
[normal voice] That was
very nicely done, Miss Lilly.
-It's a pleasure to meet you.
-Hi.
[military voice]
The prettiest girl
is riding in the 'Stang.
-Flag?
-Thank you.
Flag? Welcome.
Welcome, Viscount Mabrey.
May I offer you a flag?
Thank you. I am not
a waving aficionado.
But I will wave
our national flag
when a true Genovian king
once again sits on the throne.
King Nicholas, hmm?
Flag?
How do you feel today,
my dear?
Honestly, Joe,
not that great.
Would you feel better
if you called me Joey?
-No, Joe.
-Good.
Come on, Joseph,
we're already late.
Her Majesty is ready.
Can't keep
the people of Genovia
waiting any longer.
Happy Independence Day,
Genovia.
Here we are in Pyris,
capital of Genovia,
for the big annual parade.
Oh, here they come.
[crowd] ♪ Genovia, Genovia ♪
[Elsie] There's
Prime Minister Motaz
strutting his stuff.
♪ Genovia, Genovia ♪
People are coming
from all over Genovia.
Here's the Mertz
Marching Band,
led by Lucy Carmichael.
And now, of course,
the Lippitz
folk dancers.
Also known as
the Leapers of Libbet.
-Yeah!
[Elsie] And now the queen
with Princess Mia.
[boy] Nyah-nyah,
I don't like your braids.
[boy 2] Hey, thumb-sucker.
Stop the carriage.
[whistle blows]
W-W-What's going on?
Mia!
She stopped
the parade.
How rude.
[Elsie] Oh-oh.
What's the princess
going to do now?
She's walking towards
the children's shelter.
Hello, everybody.
[children] Hi, Princesa.
Hello.
What's your name?
Carolina.
And what are your names?
-Blake.
-John.
Did I see you messing
with Carolina?
They were tugging
on my braids.
Mm.
Excuse me.
These children are...?
Most of them are orphans.
We care for as many
as possible.
Oh.
Kissing children.
Hugging orphans.
What a vulgar,
low, despicable
political trick.
Carolina...
would you like to be
a princess today?
I can't. I'm too little,
too piccola.
Oh, no, because I declare
that anyone can be
a princess today.
Well, why don't we
get you a tiara,
and you can wave
and march in the parade.
In fact, why don't you
all take tiaras?
All? Give them all
free tiaras?
-I'll take care of it later.
-Thank you.
[girl] Yo quiero un verde.
[girl #2] A silver one?
[all talking]
You won't be able to wave
with your thumb in your mouth.
I can wave
with this hand.
Very good.
[boy] I wanna come!
[boy #2] Can we in the parade?
Of course, of course.
We could always use
more princes in the world.
OK, so...
to be a princess,
you have to believe
that you're a princess.
You've gotta walk the way
you think a princess would walk,
so think tall.
You've gotta smile and wave
and just have fun.
So, are you ready?
[all] Yes!
She's letting the children
join her. How charming.
Not for everyone.
Drumroll, please.
Give the princess
a drumroll!
[drumroll]
Forward... march!
Hut...
♪ Dabba dab a da-da ♪
Just remember,
you are a princess.
♪ I'll spread my wings ♪
♪ And I'll learn how to fly ♪
♪ I'll do what it takes ♪
♪ Till I touch the sky ♪
♪ And I'll make a wish ♪
♪ Take a chance ♪
♪ Make a change ♪
♪ And break away ♪
There you go.
-Is everybody having fun?
-[children] Yes!
♪ But I won't forget ♪
♪ All the ones that I love ♪
♪ I'll take a risk ♪
♪ Take a chance
Make a change ♪
♪ And break away ♪
This has been
Elsie Kentworthy
and former Miss Genovia
Hildegard Hoffman
at the best
Independence Day Parade
Genovia's seen in years,
thanks to Princess Mia's
special surprise.
May the rest of your day
be sunnyside up.
[Mia] And so, gentlemen,
the children from the shelter
will be housed
at the winter castle
in the mountains of Libbet.
The use of the castle
as a resort
is sort of a perk
for Parliament members
and dignitaries.
-Exactly.
-Ah.
Well, I'm going to de-perk it
and convert it
into a children's shelter
until money can be raised
for one of their own.
I feel guilty having two homes
while they have none.
[whispers] You have to
do something...
Lord Crawley,
how is your brother doing?
I don't speak
to my brother.
Oh. Well, I've hired him
to be the architect
on the project.
-Mr. Crawley.
-Your Highness.
Gentlemen.
-Jerry.
-Dean.
[Mr. Crawley] I look forward
to getting your notes
on these plans,
but no one else's.
-Oh, I'll give you notes...
-Oh, no, you won't.
-I'm an architect..
-I am part of this Parliament...
-You just go skiing.
-And you're a couch potato.
-Outdoorsman.
-You're a couch potato.
-Couch potato.
-Outdoorsman.
-Couch potato...
[knocks on table]
The queen approves
of the plan,
and I intend
to see it through.
Now, gentlemen,
I don't think
it'll take too long
to raise the money,
do you?
We're setting up the ramp
in the ballroom.
OK.
-Hello.
My hello is insignificant.
Um, Rosencrantz,
Guildenstern,
come with me.
So... are you crashing
my bridal shower?
Sadly, no.
I wanted to tell you
that I was very impressed
by what you did at the parade.
Thank you.
I'm having a slumber party.
[laughs sheepishly]
Congratulations
on the children's center.
-That's...
-Thank you. Thank you.
...wonderful.
She needs to get ready
for the party.
She's busy.
Lenny, Squiggy,
zip it.
Lilly, the princesses
are arriving.
-Oh! Well, I should
go get changed...
-I should go and read my book.
-Yeah.
-That's it.
Bye.
Hello, hello.
Elsie Kentworthy here.
Weeks before her wedding,
Princess Mia, in a stroke
of skilled diplomacy,
has invited royal princesses
from all over the world
to her bridal shower
slumber party.
Hello, Princess Lorraine.
Oh, braces!
Yeah, I'm getting
two diamonds put in.
Oh. That must make 'em
more comfortable.
Hi, Charlotte!
Princess Aimee
of Majorca.
Is this my party?
No, this is
Princess Mia's party.
Oh.
[screams and laughter]
[Mia] So I want to
thank you all very much
for my fabulous
bridal-shower presents.
And now I have
a present for you.
It's time
for mattress surfing!
[girls] Whoo!
[Christy Carlson Romo's
"Let's Bounce"]
♪ Time to get
The party started ♪
♪ Everybody's there, too ♪
♪ So let's bounce ♪
♪ Into something new ♪
♪ Let's bounce ♪
♪ 'Cause we all want to ♪
♪ Let's shout ♪
♪ Gonna have some fun ♪
-♪ Everybody, everyone ♪
-♪ Everybody ♪
♪ And let's bounce ♪
♪ Get the party on ♪
♪ Let's bounce ♪
♪ Gonna dance till dawn ♪
♪ Let's shout ♪
♪ Gonna all tone down ♪
♪ Everybody everywhere ♪
♪ You know we've gotta
Make it loud ♪
♪ Whoo! I'm ready, baby ♪
♪ Let's bounce ♪
[music stops]
Princess Aimee
has to go potty.
[Avril Lavigne,
"I Always Get What I Want"]
[girls] Whoo!
♪ So give me what I want ♪
-Whoa!
-♪ 'Cause I'm a big shot ♪
I think I'll just have
some milk and cookies
in my room, Olivia.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Perhaps some earplugs.
Quite a party, darling.
Yeah. We're just having
a little bit of fun.
Oh, Rupert and the boys
used to love doing that.
[all] King Rupert,
may he rest in peace.
I did it, too, you know,
but a little differently.
Felix.
I thought
you never slide.
I don't, but I've done
a lot of flying in my time.
[girl] Hey, Jo-Jo,
watch me!
Is she really
going to do this?
[Pink sings "Trouble"]
May I?
♪ In trouble now ♪
Hah!
[cheering]
Ah.
Ta-da.
♪ I've been workin'
At the palace ♪
♪ Just to pass the time away ♪
♪ Can't you hear
The bells a-ringin'? ♪
♪ Rise up
So early in the morn ♪
♪ Can't you hear
The bells a-shoutin'? ♪
♪ Maids, go do your chores ♪
[girls cheering]
Bravo!
And now, to end
our little show,
if we all give her
a shout-out,
Her Majesty
may sing us a song.
Thank you. No.
[girls] Please?
Queens rarely
do karaoke.
Oh, Grandma,
come on. The song you sang
at my 18th birthday party.
Remember that?
They loved it.
Dear, we had music then.
Mia had a CD made
so you can sing along.
-Clarisse!
[all chanting] Clarisse!
Clarisse! Clarisse! Clarisse!
[chanting stops]
♪ Some girls are fair ♪
♪ Some are jolly and fit ♪
-♪ Some have a well-bred air ♪
-[piano]
♪ Or a well-honed wit ♪
♪ Each one's a jewel ♪
♪ With a singular shine ♪
♪ A work of art
With its own rare design ♪
♪ Dear little girl ♪
♪ You are terribly blessed ♪
♪ But it's your heart of gold ♪
♪ I love the best ♪
♪ And that will be
Your crowning glory ♪
♪ Your whole life through ♪
♪ It'll always be
Your crowning glory ♪
[both]
♪ The most glorious part ♪
♪ Of you ♪
-[electronic]
-[girls] Whoo!
What did you do?
Well, I might have tweaked it
a little bit on my computer.
Yeah, but I don't know how
to do this sort of thing.
Asana, now.
Grandma, just follow Asana
and sing!
-♪ Some boys can walk ♪
-♪ Some guys can groove ♪
-♪ Strike an elegant pose ♪
-♪ With the really
Hip clothes ♪
♪ Some seem to have no faults ♪
-♪ But we never like those ♪
-♪ No, we don't ♪
-♪ He'll praise your eyes ♪
-♪ Your melodious laugh ♪
[both] ♪ Call you more lovely
Than others by half ♪
-♪ The one who's right ♪
-♪ My gorgeous prince ♪
-♪ Will be honest and true ♪
-♪ He'll believe in me, too ♪
♪ And prize
Your heart of gold ♪
♪ The way I do ♪
♪ He'll know that that will be
Your crowning glory ♪
♪ Your whole life through ♪
♪ Your love will see
That it's your crowning glory ♪
♪ The most glorious part
Of you ♪
♪ And you ♪
Me?
Go on.
[girls] Whoa!
Whoo-hoo!
[girl] Yeah!
[girl #2] All right!
-Please?
-No, no.
♪ Darling, when they
Tell your story ♪
♪ They'll call your heart
Of gold your crowning glory ♪
♪ The most glorious part ♪
♪ Of you ♪
[Mabrey] Gretchen, hot water.
What are you saying?
She's... she's smart,
and she really
cares about Genovia.
Maybe... well, maybe
it wouldn't be so bad
if she ran the country.
Are you mad?
She believes in Genovia so much
that she's convinced herself
to marry someone that she knows
she can never love.
I can't believe
that I'm hearing this.
You want her to rule?
After all the effort
that we have put in,
to end up with nothing?
It wouldn't be nothing.
Genovia would be
in good hands,
and she would be happy.
Ah... you've fallen
in love with her.
No. No.
Uncle, all that I ask...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You listen.
What do you think
will happen, hmm?
That she will leave Andrew
and marry you?
I put in the effort
to make you a king,
not to have you marry a queen.
I will not have it, sir.
Don't worry, Uncle.
That will never happen.
Mia doesn't care for me
that way.
Oh, but you care for her.
Uncle, I just want us to stop
trying to sabotage her.
That's all.
All right.
If that's what
you really want.
I just want your happiness,
my boy.
Go to her, hmm?
Congratulate her...
and tell her
that we surrender.
Thank you, Uncle.
Elsie Kentworthy, please.
[both cough]
That's enough flaming ones
for now.
Are you sure
I didn't burn you?
[Lilly] Of course you did.
Look at his coat.
No, no.
It's very minor.
You just sort of seared
the sleeve. Look, uh...
[Mia] Sorry!
-[Nicholas whistling]
-[groans]
-[Mia] Lilly?
-Yes?
-Can I talk to you for a second?
-Uh-huh.
[whispers] Look over there.
Should I shoo him,
or should I shoo him?
Just tell me
who I should shoo,
and I'll shoo.
[Mia] I just want to talk
to Nicholas for a second.
OK?
Backing off,
please.
Andrew, why don't you
go introduce Lilly
to your parents?
Just tell them
I'll be up for brunch
in a second.
[Lilly] Yeah, I'd love
to meet Susan and Arnold.
We can have those tasty
finger sandwiches together.
Would you like some help?
He's not the one
she's marrying, is he?
Would you please try
to keep up, Brigitta?
He's trying
to steal the crown.
Thank... oh.
-Ready?
-Mm-hmm.
Take your stance.
OK.
[chuckles]
Elbow down just a bit.
OK.
Use your mouth
as an anchor.
Excuse me?
Touch your mouth.
Good.
Relax this hand.
And breathe in.
Release.
Ohh...
How did that feel?
Wonderful.
Turn around. We should
give them some privacy.
I have to go.
I really only came back
to pack my things.
You're leaving?
I think it's time
I bowed out gracefully.
Don't you?
Goodbye.
Oh.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
Mia...
Could I see you one more time
before I go?
Nicholas, I'm watched
like a hawk.
Princess. Princess.
-See?
-I'll find a way.
Yes?
Uh, nothing.
I'm just supposed
to watch you.
[pans banging]
-[Maurice barking]
-[meowing]
♪ Get your groove on ♪
♪ Groove on ♪
[Queen] There's only
2 1/2 days left, Olivia.
I'm beginning to feel
rather frantic.
Would you take Maurice out
for me, please?
I have to check
the orchestra selections.
And they asked you
to approve a place setting
for the reception,
Your Majesty.
Very well.
[woman's voice]
Our selections for dancing
at the royal reception.
[classical music]
-[laughs]
-Ohh.
Have you been
thinking about us?
[new classical piece]
Yes, I have.
I see.
If you'll excuse me.
No, Joseph, you had to know
what I was going to say.
Mia needs me now
more than ever before,
and it's the monarchy.
As queen,
it's my responsibility.
You know how it is.
You were never
just my queen, Clarisse.
You were the someone
that I wanted to spend
the rest of my life with.
But if you prefer
that I see you,
first and foremost,
as my queen,
I shall oblige you.
-No, Joseph...
-Your Majesty.
[music stops]
Your bed is turned down,
Your Highness.
If you don't need
anything else, Princess,
we're going to supper.
Oh, well,
enjoy yourselves, ladies.
Ah-ah-ah.
What did we talk about?
No more curtsying.
We're going to supper.
Thank you.
-Hi, Miss Lilly.
-May we announce?
I can announce myself.
Lilly Moscovitz.
-Mia, look out your window.
-Why, what's going on?
Just look out your window.
Prince Charming
is throwing pebbles.
[whistles]
[whispering] Nicholas?
Nicholas, what are you doing?
[clears throat]
Rapunzel, Rapunzel,
with hair so fine,
come out your window,
climb down the vine.
The feat you ask,
dear sir, isn't easy,
and I won't respond
to that line.
It's far too cheesy.
[Lilly] So what does he want?
He wants me
to climb down the vine.
-Well, do you want?
-Yes.
-So go.
-It's a recipe for disaster.
Mia, do something impulsive
for once in your life.
You're getting married.
Do you want a regular
bachelorette party
with 12 screaming girls,
or do you want
a stroll in the moonlight
with your
almost-Prince Charming?
I believe it's luck
and not chance.
I love that.
[gasps] Oh!
Your Majesty.
Oh, no. Ladies,
come in, come.
I was just about to leave.
This really is
more romantic in books.
My foot is stuck!
What was that?
[whispers] Help.
Oh...
♪ Frere Jacques ♪
[both] ♪ Frere Jacques ♪
♪ Dormez-vous?
Dormez-vous? ♪
Your Majesty, we never
got to finish our routine
at the slumber party.
And there's
more dancing, too.
♪ Frere Jacques
Frere Jacques ♪
-♪ Dormez-vous? ♪
-[window bangs]
♪ Dormez-vous? ♪
-And there's a big finish.
-Yes, the big finale.
Whoa! Oh! Aah!
Ohh! Ohh. Ow.
[whispers] I'm sorry.
Did I hurt you again?
No, I...
I'm used to it.
[both] And...
♪ Sonnez les matines
Sonnez les matines ♪
♪ Ding-dang-dong ♪
What a pity we missed it
at the party.
[Lilly] I'll cover for you.
Go, Rapunzel. Go!
[Nicholas] Tell me
your greatest desires.
[Mia] Tell me a secret.
Isn't that the same?
Almost, but anyone
can see your desires.
No one knows
what's in your heart.
Tell me something.
Um... I love
I Love Lucy reruns,
and sometimes I dream
in black and white.
Hmm.
I used to pretend I was sick
when I had a test in school.
We all did that.
[Nicholas laughs] OK.
Sometimes I put chocolate milk
on my cereal.
I am deathly afraid
of jellyfish.
I haven't danced with you
since your birthday.
That's a fact.
It's not a secret.
The secret is,
is that I still want to.
[Norah Jones]
♪ Love me tender ♪
♪ Love me sweet ♪
♪ Never let me go ♪
♪ You have made
My life complete ♪
♪ And I love you so ♪
♪ Love me tender ♪
♪ Love me true ♪
♪ All my dreams fulfilled ♪
♪ For, my darling,
I love you ♪
♪ And I always will ♪
[groaning]
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Hello.
-We stayed out all night.
-Yes, we did.
[gasps] We stayed out all night.
Is that...?
There's a man in that boat.
-[Nicholas] What?
-[Mia] Do you see that?
There's somebody over there.
He's probably
some fisherman, I suppose.
With a video camera?
What?
You're really low.
I have no idea
who that man is!
It's really a shame
you didn't get juicier stuff
last night, you jerk.
Mia, I have nothing
to do with this, I swear.
Mia, please. Come on.
Will you listen to me?
That is not my boat.
Hey, Nicholas,
have a nice life.
But that is my horse.
Mia...
Mia? Hello?
Good morning, my love.
I know it's a little early,
but I've been thinking.
Things have been
so pressured lately.
I was wondering
whether we should spend...
Lilly?
Good morning, Your Majesty.
What are you doing here?
-I just wanted t...
-[footsteps]
Mia.
-Doors.
-What's going on?
[Charlotte] Princess, I think
you should see this.
[Elsie] And here's the royal
exclusive I promised.
After generations of boring
royals who never misbehaved,
Genovia finally has
a world-class scandal,
proving that we
should have brought in
an American long ago.
Will Andrew Jacoby,
Duke of Kenilworth,
still marry such a naughty,
naughty princess,
or will Lord Nicholas Devereax
be the new king?
It's out of the frying pan
and into the fire
for Princess Mia.
Keep your eggs
sunny side up.
I'd like to tell her
what she can do with her eggs.
-Lilly, could we have
a moment alone?
-Yes.
So?
I got played.
Uh-huh.
Well, the big question is,
do we still have a wedding?
Andrew, I'm so, so sorry.
I ju--
Andrew, please wait.
I promise you,
nothing happened.
But Mia, you still went,
didn't you? You went.
I don't think you understand.
I'm an extremely eligible
bachelor in England.
I really am.
I've got plenty of friends,
lots of lovely
women friends, and...
I still think this marriage
is a good idea.
Mia...
[bleats]
The queen would not
approve of spying.
So?
Anything?
I really want to say yes,
but no.
There's just...
there's no... spark.
Me, too.
-Really?
-Really.
I mean,
it was pleasurable.
-Very.
-But no fireworks.
None.
Ohh. What are we gonna do?
We will...
We will figure something out.
Hmm.
Mia...
You chose me...
-No privacy.
-No.
You chose me,
and I accepted,
and a gentleman
never backs out
on his word.
We are going to...
We're going to
stand up in church
and say, "I do,"
and tomorrow,
we'll be man and wife,
and you are going to make
an amazing Queen of Genovia.
Thank you.
I'm getting married today.
[Queen] She's getting married
today, Maurice.
[Maurice barking]
Your Highness,
we're running very late.
Grandma says
the queen is never late.
Everyone else
is simply early.
Your Highness,
a strange woman came in
and said that she wanted
to hide in your closet,
so I let her.
Well, dear, that probably
wasn't the wisest decision
in the...
Now, this is what I call
a closet.
-Mom!
-Oh, my darling.
Oh, careful.
We're squashing Trevor.
Hi, Trevor.
He's sleeping. Shh.
Oh, he is the most
beautiful baby brother.
We were joking.
We knew it was your mother.
Your stepfather's
here, too.
Now, I'm your mother,
it's your wedding day,
I have to say something.
Being married
is about being yourself,
only with someone else.
Thanks, Mom.
[knock on door]
[mother] How are you feeling?
You look beautiful.
Paolo is back
to turn a caterpillar
into a butterfly.
-Oh.
-There she go, butterfly.
-Paolo.
-Coat off.
I say "butterfly,"
the coat comes off.
-Principessa.
-Paolo.
You remember
my mother, Helen.
Yes, yes.
And the new baby.
All Italian men love a baby
except Paolo.
You gotta get out now
because we have to go to work.
Five years ago, Paolo take you
from that to that.
Today, he give you this.
[assistants] A wedding look
for the bride.
I look like a moose.
Yes, but a very cute moose.
Make all the boy moose
go, "Whaah!" Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I have antlers.
Whaah. Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Go!
Ha-ha!
I look like a poodle.
That's just the way I feel.
Here we go again.
Good. Sit up.
She kinda does look
like a poodle.
I like it.
[Paolo] This time I'm so sure,
I use my own pictures.
So, un, deux, trois.
[Mabrey] Gretchen,
I can't find my gloves.
You go on.
I think it would be better
if I didn't go to the wedding.
My boy.
Don't give up so easily.
Come to church.
Sweep her off her feet.
In a week or two,
she'll be yours.
The game is over, Uncle.
She's going to marry Andrew.
Ah, you're so right.
Ah, well, this is
a disaster in the making.
Wouldn't miss
a moment of it.
I'll try to catch
the garter. Ha-ha!
The royal carriage approaches!
What did he say, Artie?
-The princess is coming.
-Showtime.
Suki Sanchez here
from the USA.
A long way from home,
but happily following
a story that started
in the streets of San Francisco
and is about to have
a happy ending here
in the small beautiful land
of Genovia.
[Captain] Prepare for
the arrival of Princess Mia!
Psst.
Sir...
I don't mean
to talk out of school,
but there's something
you must know.
Your uncle called Elsie
and set you up with that video.
Why doesn't that surprise me?
I should have known.
He's up to something.
He was much too delighted
that you aren't going
to that wedding.
-I must get to that church.
-Yes, yes, but how?
Everything on four wheels is
already rented for the wedding.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I'll run.
No. No, it's too far.
No. You'll take the bike.
The bike? Gretchen, what bike?
We don't have a bike.
Your grandfather's bike.
Buenas tardes, Tanya.
Buenas tardes,
su Majestad.
Aquí le presento mi tio
que noviecita de Rosario.
Oh, how do you do, señor?
Oh, I do better if
you and I get married.
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
I'm sorry.
My uncle
learned his English
watching the old
Three Stooges movies.
-Sorry.
-Ooh!
Yes, well...
What...?
You're not going
to believe this.
Lord Devereaux is riding
up the road on a bicycle.
Sir! Sir, may I borrow
your horse?
Oh, he needs my horse.
My bike is yours.
How am I supposed to herd sheep
with a bike?
[processional music]
Outspoken American activist
Lilly Moscovitz,
the maid of honor,
glides forward
as a vision in pink.
I'm a girl who loves black
and is wearing pink.
-Aw.
-Ohh.
[Elsie] And Duke Andrew's
little nephew Viscount Ludlow,
affectionately known
as James of the cherub cheeks,
comes down the aisle
as the royal ring bearer.
-[whispers] Hey, Joe.
-Hmm?
I just wanted to say
before I do this,
I'm sorry you're retiring.
Who told you that?
The maids know
everything.
Mm.
Well, the heart
does things for reasons
that reason
cannot understand.
You're preaching
to the choir.
[knocks]
Princess?
Yes?
Then you should know
that Nicholas did not
set you up at the lake.
You're sure?
The maids know
everything.
We're ready
when she is.
[organ]
[singing Pachelbel's
"Canon in D Major"]
[music and singing stops]
-Is this part of the plan?
-No.
I...
[laughs nervously]
[clears throat]
I'm going to need
a minute or two.
Thank you, Your Highness.
[crowd murmuring]
[Elsie] Now the bride is moving
swiftly back up the aisle
and out the door...
-Let me.
-...not the traditional route.
-[screams]
-[reporters] Princess Mia!
Princess Mia!
-Mia!
Mia, come here!
-[Trevor crying]
-[Patrick] Helen.
Honey, I'll be right back.
I gotta change
Trevor's diaper.
Please, be seated.
There'll just be
a momentary interlude.
Thank you.
Do we
rush after her?
No, we never rush.
We hasten.
You'll take care of them.
[Charlotte] Yes, yes.
Yes, just-just one moment.
[Queen] Out of my way!
[man] Long live the queen!
[cheering]
Ohh! OK.
Oh, my dear. Mia!
No, Grandma, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I-I-I just need a minute.
-No.
-I can do this.
No.
-I can't do this.
-I know.
Darling,
listen to me.
I made my choice...
duty to my country
over love.
It's what I've always done,
it seems.
It was drummed into me
my whole life.
Now I've lost the only man
I ever really loved.
[Lionel] Anyone
got a 20 on Joseph?
I'm with the eagle
and sparrow.
Mia, I want you to make
your choices as a woman.
Don't make
the same mistakes I did.
Make your own mistakes.
There'll be plenty
of them, believe me.
Now, you can go back
into that church
and get married,
or you can walk away.
Whatever choice you make,
let it come
from your heart.
[sobs]
-Excuse me.
-She's back.
[choir singing Pachelbel's
"Canon in D Major"]
[Elsie] The princess
is re-entering the church.
She's walking down the aisle.
More like cantering
down the aisle.
[singing faster]
[singing stops]
Andrew, wait.
Everyone deserves the chance
to find true love, right?
Yes.
Including us?
Uh...
Thank you.
Huh?
Well, for, uh,
saving me from doing
the proper thing
for once in my life.
Now all I have to do
is tell Mummy.
I have to tell everyone else.
[both] Good luck.
[Mia whispers] OK.
[mumbling]
Helen...
Welcome.
A few moments ago,
I realized the only reason
I was getting married
was because of a law,
and that didn't seem
like a good enough reason,
so I won't be
getting married today.
Sit. Sit.
There may be a dinner.
My grandmother has ruled
without a man at her side
for quite some time,
and I think she rocks at it.
So, as the granddaughter
of Queen Clarisse
and King Rupert...
[all] King Rupert,
may he rest in peace.
...I ask the members
of Parliament to...
to think about your daughters,
your nieces, sisters
and granddaughters,
and ask yourselves...
would you force them to do
what you're trying
to make me do?
I believe I will be
a great queen.
I understand Genovia
to be a land
that combines
the beauty of the past
with all the best hope
of the future.
-Not now.
-[women] Shh!
I feel in my heart and soul
that I can rule Genovia.
I... I love Genovia.
Do you think that I would
be up here in a wedding dress
if I didn't?
[laughter]
I stand here...
ready to take my place
as your queen...
without a husband.
[woman] Viva, Mia!
Every time...
Every time this charming,
young lady opens her mouth,
she demonstrates a contempt
for the customs of Genovia.
The law clearly states
an unmarried woman
cannot be queen.
Fortunately,
there is another heir.
No, there is not.
[crowd murmuring]
I decline.
I refuse to be king.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is Princess Mia
who should have the crown.
She is bright
and she is caring,
but more importantly,
she has a vision,
one that will
take Genovia forward,
and if the Parliament
were astute,
they would name her queen.
Listen to her.
She'll lead us
into the 21st century.
And besides,
just think how lovely she'll
look on our postage stamp.
[laughter]
Lovely on a postage stamp?!
You would look lovely
on a postage stamp!
And don't you walk
away from me, sir!
You have a duty, sir,
to Genovia!
He's, uh,
he is very distressed.
Your duty, sir,
to the country,
to me, sir!
To Genovia!
To your father!
Nicholas!
-The door.
-Shut the doors, quickly.
Nicholas! Nicholas!
Nicholas, I cannot have you
giving all-all this up
just for a girl.
-Now-Now, we can...
-Enough, Uncle.
We're finished.
What is happening here?
Who's next in line
for the throne,
the Von Trokens?
We accept!
Sit down!
[coughs] Make a motion.
Are you OK?
Make a motion!
[coughs]
Ah, um, Prime Minister...
Yes, Princess?
I move to abolish
the marriage law
as it applies to present
and future queens of Genovia.
Will anyone second my motion?
Just keep
eye contact with them.
Stare them down.
N-N-N... soften,
soften. Good.
Ahem. I second the motion.
It's time we had
a new tradition.
I like change.
I may grow a moustache.
I think you'd
look marvelous
with a moustache.
My father always favored
a Van Dyke....
Gentlemen, please.
All those in favor
of abolishing
the marriage rule,
say, "Aye"
Aye.
-Aye.
-You're not in Parliament.
Sit down.
-Someday.
[all] Aye.
The "ayes" have it.
Congratulations, Princess.
If I may say so myself,
you rule!
Lionel...
Your Majesty...
Hmm?
The princess
would like a word.
Oh. Um...
Grandma... just because I didn't
get my fairy-tale ending
doesn't mean you shouldn't.
Oh, uh,
did you hear that?
Not if you didn't
want me to.
Oh, Charlotte.
Uh...
Oh...
Ahem... well...
Joseph...
Your Majesty.
Dear Joseph.
Am I too late to ask you
to accept
my hand in marriage?
Ahem.
Well, I thought
you'd never ask.
Shades, you're in charge now.
Good luck with Lionel.
I'm going to a wedding.
[Mabrey] Open up, I say!
The door is shut!
Let me in!
[Gretchen laughs]
Put me down. Put me down!
Ha-ha-ha.
I know it was
short notice,
but you were
all dressed.
[guests murmur]
My Lord Archbishop,
I would like to take this man
as my husband, if you please.
Finally.
We have come together
for a different wedding.
-What did I miss?
-She's not getting married.
-She's not getting married?
-No.
With this ring,
I thee... finally wed.
Now the queen's
getting married.
-The queen's getting married?
-Yeah, to Joe.
I pronounce you
man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
-[organ plays]
-[choir sings]
[applause]
Whoo-hoo!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
[Majordomo] The ceremonial
shooting of the flaming arrow
through the coronation ring.
[Elsie] Good morning.
It's been almost a week
since the almost-wedding,
and busy workers are setting up
for Genovia's grand day,
the coronation
of a new queen.
Somewhere in the palace,
Princess Mia's getting ready
for the ceremony that will
change her life forever.
So what do you say, Fat Louie?
You think I'll make
a good queen?
Indeed you will.
If I may be so bold,
I would like an audience
with Your Highness.
Uh...
What is your dilemma,
young man?
You are, in fact.
I am in love
with the queen-to-be,
and I am inquiring
if she loves me, too.
Do you have a chicken
for my table?
No, no. My kitchen
is out of chickens.
Ah... hmm.
Mia.
[Captain] Company, attention!
Forward march!
Left, right, left!
Left, left,
left, right, left.
Left, left.
Company, halt!
I heard you're going back
to Berkeley to finish up
graduate school.
You heard right.
May I call you
in California?
I think I can hear you
without a phone, but, uh...
The sparrow is taking off.
The eagle is flying
for the last time.
She looks beautiful.
[breaking up]
They both do.
[man] Will you
solemnly promise and swear
to govern the people
of Genovia
according to the statutes
in Parliament agreed on
and the respective
laws and custom of the same?
Will you, in your power,
cause law and justice and mercy
to be executed
in all judgments?
[Mia] I solemnly promise
so to do.
♪ Genovia ♪
♪ The land I call my own ♪
♪ From the green, clear.. ♪
[Captain] Attention!
♪ From blossoming pear trees ♪
♪ Magnificent ♪
♪ Her mountains and seas ♪
♪ Genovia, Genovia ♪
♪ You're noble,
Proud and brave ♪
♪ Genovia, Genovia ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Will your banner wave! ♪
[Majordomo bangs staff]
Presenting Her Majesty,
Amelia Mignonette
Thermopolis Renaldi,
Queen of Genovia.
♪ This is my time to shine ♪
♪ This is my place to find ♪
♪ All that I have inside ♪
♪ I never knew ♪
♪ When dreams come true ♪
[new song]
♪ I decide how I live ♪
♪ I decide who I love ♪
♪ Choice is mine, and no one
Gets to make my mind up ♪
♪ I decide ♪
♪ I decide where I go ♪
♪ Where I sleep, who I know ♪
♪ I'm the one
Who's runnin' my life ♪
♪ I decide ♪
[fanfare]
♪ I decide how I live ♪
♪ I decide who I love ♪
♪ Choice is mine and no one
Gets to make my mind up ♪
♪ I decide ♪
♪ And don't think that
You can tell me what to think ♪
♪ I'm the one who knows
What's good for me ♪
♪ And I'm stating
My independence ♪
♪ Gonna take the road
I'm gonna take ♪
♪ And I'm gonna make
My own mistakes ♪
♪ It's my life ♪
♪ I decide ♪
♪ I decide where I go ♪
♪ Where I sleep, who I know ♪
♪ I'm the one
Who's runnin' my life ♪
♪ I decide ♪
[new song]
♪ Say it all but not at all ♪
♪ Don't wanna hear
What you're really feelin' ♪
♪ Forsakin' the meaning ♪
♪ Take away the words I say ♪
♪ Realistic thoughts
That I'm dreamin' ♪
♪ Are you believin'? ♪
♪ Tell me what I wanna hear ♪
♪ How far do you
See this so ♪
♪ My truth is spoken whether ♪
♪ Or not you wanna hear it ♪
♪ I'm sorry ♪
♪ I worry, though ♪
♪ Don't you ever say never ♪
♪ Don't turn away ♪
♪ Say it all, but not at all♪
♪ Don't wanna hear
What you're really feelin' ♪
♪ Forsakin' the meaning ♪
♪ Take away the words I say ♪
♪ Realistic thoughts
That I'm dreamin' ♪
♪ Are you believin'? ♪
♪ Don't stray too far ♪
♪ The closer you are ♪
♪ The further
The pain'll fade away ♪
♪ I don't really care
Where you are ♪
♪ It'll be either here or far ♪
♪ All in all, this feelin'
Will bring home my man ♪
♪ Say it all but not at all♪
♪ It'll be either here or far ♪
♪ Take away the words I say ♪
♪ Bring home my man ♪
♪ Say it all, but not at all ♪
♪ Don't wanna hear
What you're really feelin' ♪
♪ Forsakin' the meaning ♪
[new song]
♪ Staring out at the rain
With a heavy heart ♪
♪ It's the yen
Of the world in my mind ♪
♪ Then your voice pulls me back
Like a wake-up call ♪
♪ I've been
Looking for the answer ♪
♪ But now I know
What I didn't know ♪
♪ Because you live
And breathe ♪
♪ Because you made me
Believe in myself ♪
♪ When nobody else can help ♪
♪ Because you live, girl ♪
♪ My world ♪
♪ Has twice as many
Stars in the sky ♪
♪ Because you live ♪
♪ There's a reason why ♪
♪ I carry on
When I lose the fight ♪
♪ I want to give
What you've given me ♪
♪ Always ♪
♪ Because you live
And breathe ♪
♪ Because you made me
Believe in myself ♪
♪ When nobody else can help ♪
♪ Because you live, girl ♪
♪ Because you live ♪
♪ My world ♪
♪ Has everything
I need to survive ♪
♪ Because you live ♪
♪ I live ♪
[Joe] And don't forget,
the next time you're
planning a family vacation,
consider visiting Genovia,
a country of majestic mountains
and sun-baked beaches,
filled with
friendly, peppy people.
Come see us.
Genovia awaits you.