What's he doing?
Working.
It doesn't look anything like the picture.
Maybe it's been modified.
The tail is wrong.
It's just backwards.
Why have you failed me?
We're working.
Diligently.
I let you live.
This is how you repay me?
It's very complex.
He's trying very hard.
On his knees.
You think I'm a fool?
I'll get the truth.
We're both working.
Open your mouth.
You think I'm a fool?
What's going on?
Tell me the truth.
He's building your Jericho.
Where is Stark?
He was here a moment ago.
Go look for him.
Hurry it up.
Put the women in the trucks.
Stack the weapons here.
Clear all the houses.
That one there.
Faster. Faster.
Grab that dog.
Put him with the others.
What the hell is this?
Shoot this dog.
You're all incompetent.
Turn your head.
This is the only gift you shall receive.