Max!
Come here.
Let's not make the sisters wait.
This is Frey.
She's new here too.
Can you read?
This is a giraffe.
They lived in Africa.
Can you read?
Yes.
Max, are you stealing again?
It breaks my heart. Why do you do it?
To save up?
You want to buy a ticket to go up there?
That place is not for you, or me.
It's not fair, sister.
Why can't I go?
There are things that can't be explained in life.
We just have to accept them.
But one thing I know for sure.
You're a very special person.
One day you'll do something marvellous.
You were born for it.
My little Max.
Max, very good!
Wanna make the world better?
Please kids! You think I got money?
I can buy my ticket to Elysium, huh?
Tag her quick!
Hello, Madame Delacourt.
- Hello.
Hi, Ivan, how you've grown.
Hi. You alright?
Fine. Are the kids here?
- Yes, with Dominica.
I have a present for you.
Wanna see? It's in the salon.
Go get it with your mother.
It's, by the canape.
- OK
Bye.
Impact imminent. Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Only one made it.
As usual, the police man.
Attention, doors are not aligned. Worker attend.
Sister, they beat me up.
I only want to live there.
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Yes.
Well, now...
See how beautiful we look to them up there.
Keep this.
Now it belongs to you.
So you never forget where you come from.
Go! Get to work, Mr. Carlyle.
Lower it to me.
He's awake!
Yes
I'm shitting myself with fear.
Thanks ma'am.
You're too heavy for me. Max, help me!
What is this?
Guy.
We all have something special, Max.
Something we're destined to do.
Something for which we were born.
My baby. My dear.
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Now look how beautiful we look from up there.
Now it belongs to you.
So you'll never forget where you come from.
My little Max.