Pull over to the side!
That old lady is crazy.
You can say that again.
Get her.
Can you believe this?
Good morning, all.
Good morning.
l trust we reviewed
our cases over the weekend?
-Yes.
l see you're watching
that Mabel Simmons case.
-lt's all over the news.
-Right.
Now, that old woman has been giving
the police the blues all of her life.
-She was an ugly baby.
-Okay.
-Petty theft at nine.
-My goodness.
lllegal gambling at 1 8.
That afro is thirsty.
-Check fraud.
-Not bad. Not bad.
-ldentity theft.
-Lord, help her.
lnsurance fraud.
Okay, everything except attempted murder.
-Attempted murder.
-Here we go!
Goodness!
-Assault.
-Nice.
The list goes on and on.
And so on and so on.
Unfortunately, our fine officers may have
made a mistake on her takedown,
so we have to handle this with care.
Who wants it?
Don't all volunteer at the same time.
You're supposed to be
helping me out with this.
We have no volunteers
for the Simmons case?
Okay.
Linda. lt's all yours.
-Thank you.
-God.
-Stop laughing.
-By the way,
let's congratulate our Linda Davis
on her 89% conviction rate.
Thank you.
With numbers like that,
you'll be D.A. one day.
-Okay.
-That's my girl.
Everyone else, let's check the boards
for the new cases, and let's get to court.
All right.
Honey, there goes our appointment.
l know. And you're just
all broke up about it, aren't you?
l am. You know what?
l've got a lot of work anyway.
l know. That's all right.
l guess after this case,
it's just you and me, Tanya.
Oh, good. That'll give me time to talk you
out of these taffeta bridesmaids dresses.
You like them, don't you, baby?
Take my advice, just nod and say yes.
-Of course...
-You're weak.
-He's smart. You're smart.
-Unbelievable.
l'm smart.
-Thank you.
-All right, l'll see you later.
-All right.
-Excuse me.
-And you have fun with that.
-Thank you.
So...
-You set a date.
-Yes, l set a date.
You know you're gonna
need a best man, right?
l told you, l got brothers.
Okay, but your brothers have not been the
kind of friend that l've been to you, man.
Chuck, the only reason
why you want to be in my wedding
is 'cause you want to be seen.
That hurts. That really hurts.
But you are right.
Linda's parents, they're loaded, Josh.
l know the governor's gonna be there,
-l know the mayor's gonna be there.
-Get out of here, man.
Come on, man. Hook your boy up.
-Please, l need you to be my usher.
-Please.
-But l don't want... Listen.
-That's an important job.
What could l say...
l just don't... l just don't know, Cora.
l just don't know.
Uncle Joe, are you all right?
Uncle Joe?
Breathe, Joe. Breathe.
You okay?
l'm good, Cora. Turn that oxygen up.
Now, you're not supposed
to be smoking around oxygen.
That's the problem.
Oxygen is everywhere in the air.
Every time you light a cigarette,
you lighting it in oxygen.
lf you ain't got no oxygen,
the fire won't work.
Learn some chimistry, honey.
Learn some chimistry.
Chemistry.
What the hell you talking about?
You don't know what you're talking about.
This help my blood pressure.
That what the doctor say.
Smoke to help my blood pressure.
You gonna fool around and blow you
and your blood pressure up.
That's right.
This here is good for you. lt's good for you.
lt came straight down from heaven.
God sent it down.
And he sent Viagra, he sent this,
and he sent that oxygen.
And if you put them all together,
you'll take a woman to heaven and back.
Thank you.
Joe, how you gonna
sit there and talk about God
with a joint in your hand and some Viagra?
God made this.
He made the birds and the bees
and the flowers.
And these trees.
Joe, you just like your sister.
Both of y'all going to hell!
-What?
-Uncle Joe?
-You want some?
-Joe, l...
No, l need you to focus, Uncle Joe.
Focus on what?
Why were y'all running from the police?
Madea? What happened?
Mabel always run from the police.
Cora, you know that.
Your mama been running from the police.
She's a ho. Po-po...
When the po-po come, she run like a ho.
You mama always been
running from the police.
l'm sorry to tell you,
but your mama's a po-po ho.
That fool is a thug.
Cora, that's right. Your mama a gangster.
King Kong ain't got nothing on her.
Got nothing on her.
Daddy!
Stop talking about my mama.
-l'm not talking about her.
-You going...
-Hey, Brown, Cora, how you all doing?
-Hey, Brian.
-l just saw the news.
What is going on with you and Madea?
What's happening? Are you all right?
No, l ain't all right.
What's wrong?
l can't feel my big toes.
Thank you, Lord.
l tell you what.
When your parents get to be a certain age,
it's like raising children.
My kids don't give me as much trouble
as you and Madea giving me.
What is the matter with you?
Have you done lost your mind?
And Madea is already on probation.
l don't know what she was thinking about.
That ain't never stopped your mama before.
l done got her out of trouble
three times already.
Yeah. That's true. That's true.
Well, she's going to jail this time.
To the big house! Prisoner. The slammer.
They gonna lock her up, press her down,
and shake her together and run it over.
Gonna be in her bosom, l'm telling you...
Mr. Brown!
Too much?
-Yes.
Wait. You all go ahead.
Finish saying what you all was saying.
Come on, Cora. Let's go down here
and see if we can help get her out of there.
Come on. We going. They gonna lock
her up. She going to the slammer, Cora.
-To the big j...
-Mr. Brown, Mr. Brown.
We don't need you to go, Mr. Brown.
We good.
Oh, no. l got to go.
They gonna put her in Alcatraz.
She's gonna be
in solitary condensement this time.
-They going to lock her big behind up!
-ln Alcatraz?
-Same thing.
-Bye.
Get the hell on out of here.
You better behave yourself
while l'm gone, you understand?
What the hell l'm going to do?
l'm so high,
you look like your real daddy right now.
City of Atlanta vs Washington.
Ms. Washington,
you were arrested for prostitution.
Yes, Your Honor, she was.
Ms. Washington was arrested
several times before.
Candy?
Joshua?
l'm sorry, Your Honor.
l need to pass this case to my colleague.
lt seems that l know this defendant.
Then give it to one of your colleagues.
-Hey, what's going on?
-l know her.
How?
lt's a long story. But will you take it?
What's the case?
Simple prostitution.
All right. But then you have to
take my drunk and disorderly.
-Fine.
-And then you have to
-give me a foot rub later.
-People, today!
Your Honor, Ms. Washington has been
arrested twice for prostitution.
The People request no bail.
Your Honor, this woman was simply
walking home from the bus stop when...
Save it. Save it. Bail is set at $1 ,500,
cash or bond, until trial date.
-$1 ,500?
-Yes. $1 ,500.
Ms. Washington,
if you manage to make bail,
you better be back here for your trial.
Do you hear me?
-Yeah.
-lf you're not here,
you will regret it.
Go see the clerk for your trial date.
Next case.
City of Atlanta vs Mabel Simmons.
Hey, Cora. Hey, Brown.
lf the Lord get me out of this,
l'm going by the church.
-You better mean it, too.
-l'm going by the church.
-You better mean it.
-l mean it.
Hey, Judge. Girl, your hair is so pretty.
Who doing your hair? Lord have mercy.
How you doing?
Mabel Simmons, you come before me
more than you go
to the doctor for a checkup.
Listen, l done changed my life.
You ain't got to say nothing.
l am living for the Lord.
Hallelujer.
l feel Him down in my spirit.
You know, as l think
about the goodness of Jesus
and all that he has done for me,
my soul cries out,
"Hallelujer! Thank God for saving me."
You finished?
l don't believe that no more
than l believe that you'll stay out of trouble.
-Your Honor...
-Save it. l saw the video.
And l told you that if she came back
before me again, she was going to jail.
She's going to jail this time.
Your weak ass.
You supposed to be a lawyer.
You supposed to be getting me off.
Weak ass.
l gotta get me a real lawyer.
Some Matt Johnson or somebody.
You weak-ass lawyer.
Oh, Lord.
Your Honor, there's something
you need to understand, though...
Brian, there's nothing you can do.
She's going to jail this time.
-l don't know about that.
-And why not?
Apparently, Your Honor,
our officers forgot to Mirandize her.
l was waiting for Miranda to come in,
and nobody came in.
l was waiting for her.
That's right. Ain't nobody Miranda me.
Miranda wasn't even in the room.
Excuse me?
We were fighting for our lives, Your Honor.
You forgot to Mirandize her?
That old woman got the strength
of any man.
l've got to let you go.
You gotta let me go.
-As much as l hate it, l have to.
-Yes, you do.
But l'm going to suspend
your driver's license indefinitely.
Suspend my license?
My license been suspended.
Hell, you ain't doing nothing.
l ain't had a license in 38 years.
Say, what the hell she talking about
she's gonna suspend my...
What that gonna do? l got keys.
l'm going to order you
to anger management counseling.
She'll take it. Thank you, Your Honor.
We appreciate it.
Go see the clerk. Get the paperwork done
and get her out of my courtroom now.
-You're free to go.
-Free to go?
Look at my neck! Hold on.
Wait a minute. Did you see my eye?
Saw your eye. Saw that face, too.
You're tore the hell up. l'm free to go.
l don't know if you's going home,
but l'm going home. l'm going home.
Calm down, Officer. lt's your fault.
You forgot to Mirandize her.
This is ridiculous.
Take care, Judge! l love you.
But l got to go.
But the saving grace is
she couldn't stay out of trouble
if you paid her.
She'll be back.
Hey, Joshua.
Hey.
Hey, Ellen.
-Who's this?
-This is Mindy.
Mindy.
Wait in the car, baby.
She's only 14, Josh.
Pimp found her in the bus station
and put her out in the streets.
l'm glad you found her.
Thank God.
You know, Ellen, l gotta tell you,
l think the job that you're doing
with these girls, it's great.
lt's just me trying to do
the work of my Lord.
l know you make Him proud.
Thanks again.
Hey, Ellen.
l want you to meet somebody.
Candy, this is Ellen Holmes.
She's a minister and she helps
get girls off the street.
-Hi.
-Hey.
Here's my card if you need anything.
Do l look like l'm on the streets to you?
No, but you look like
you work in the streets.
You know what? l ain't got no time
for no Jesus jokers, all right?
Fine. Then l ain't got time for you, either,
sucker.
See you later, Joshua.
What kind of minister is that?
l know. l know. She's the real deal, though.
So you bail me out?
Yeah.
So where do you want to do this?
We can go to your car,
we can go to your house, l'm not sure...
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you talking about?
You bailed me out,
so you must want something, right?
So what, do you think
l want some sex from you?
What you want, then?
What about, you know, like,
"How you been? How you doing?"
Ain't no man asking a woman
how she doing
unless he wants something, so what is it?
What you want from me, Josh?
Okay. What are you doing out here
on these streets, Candy?
How about you don't worry about that?
l gotta go. l ain't got time for...
Candy, hold on. Hold on. Just...
All right.
Let me take you to get something to eat.
You hungry?
Come on. Just... Please?
-The Lord is so good.
-Yes, He is.
He is so good he delivered your mama
out of the belly of that jail.
-Yes, he did.
-Yes.
We going to church Sunday, huh, Madea?
l ain't going to no church.
Now, hold up. Wait a minute.
Let me put some churching in it.
You said that if the Lord got you
through this,
you was going by the church.
And you're going.
And that's just what l'm going to do.
l'm going by the church.
-So when you coming?
-We just did.
l said l would go by the church.
We just passed by one. Hallelujer.
St. Philip and them. Hail Mary, full of grace,
and all you people, God bless you.
All you little Catholic people, hello.
Mabel. The Lord is just so...
You just make the Lord mad.
Bow your head. Let's pray for her.
Cora, bow your head.
-Brian, bow your head.
-Mr. Brown, l'm driving.
-Yes.
-The Lord know.
He can watch the wheel. Bow your head.
Mabel, you bow your head.
Brown, if you don't shut the hell up and...
Mabel, bow your head! Put your head
in your lap and smother yourself.
Bow your head!
Lord, don't send Madea to hell.
Just give her a little house
right outside the gates of heaven
so she can watch all of us go in.
Amend.
-And amend.
-Amen.
But, Madea, you can't make
those type of promises and break them.
-Cora.
-Yes?
-Do me a favor.
-Yes, ma'am.
Put the "shut" to the "up," okay?
"Shut" to the "up."
-l say, what?
-Madea.
Cora, don't even worry.
Just let it go.
l'm telling you, when she get in trouble,
then she come running to the church.
No, no, no.
Madea ain't fitting to get in no more trouble.
l ain't fitting to have that.
That's enough.
Between you and my daddy, that's enough.
You ain't getting in
no more trouble, Madea.
l'm telling you. You got off easy this time.
Who in the hell are you talking to?
l'm grown.
l am grown, okay, Brian?
You don't tell me nothing. l'm grown.
l wasn't in trouble that time.
You don't tell me nothing.
Madea, l was reading this pamphlet
from the courts about anger management.
lt says as women get older,
our bodies
don't produce as many hormones
as it needs to stay calm
and have stable moods.
But you going to see this doctor
is going to be real good for you.
l'm not going to no anger manager, Cora.
What the hell you bring
them down here for, Brian?
Why you yelling at me?
They wanted to come.
l mean, what was l supposed to do?
Mr. Brown jumped in the car.
You was happy to see us
when you wanted some of our prayer.
That's right.
l'm telling you,
you need to go see one of them doctors.
They gave me one of them...
What they said, Brian...
Coca-cola-osomy.
You had a colonoscopy, Mr. Brown?
Same thing.
l thought that fool said Coca-Cola.
He was making me thirsty
for a good ol' Coke.
Now, Mabel, when we get old,
we gotta keep ourself checked.
Now, you know they checked my prostate?
Mabel, you need to get
your prostate checked, too.
Women don't have a prostate, Mr. Brown.
Cora, l'm telling you. Madea got a prostate.
You know, there's more
where that came from.
Why you bail me out ofjail?
'Cause you're a friend.
l don't understand why you...
Why you have to do this.
You a smart girl.
You used to get straight A's.
You remember?
-Wow.
-What?
You really have tricked yourself
into believing that that night
ain't ever happened.
Well, Josh, it did happen.
And it changed my life forever.
l tried to look for you every day after that.
You must have been looking
in some pretty high places, Josh.
Candy, l don't understand
why you're out there on those streets.
Look. You deal with things your way,
and l deal with them mine.
l don't need you to be
judging me right now.
-l'm not judging you.
-Yes, you are!
What you think you doing sitting in here,
talking to me crazy!
-Will you... Please?
-Don't you shush me!
Tell me to be...
Oh, am l embarrassing you now?
So you all got something to say, too?
What you got? What?
Anybody else?
Please. l'm not your enemy.
Hey. What's up, Josh?
Chuck, this is an old friend of mine.
Okay. How you doing? l'm Chuck.
Okay.
Hey, Baby.
-Hey.
Thought you were in court.
l was. lt got kicked. She wasn't Mirandized.
What's this?
She's a friend of mine.
What's her name?
l tried your friend. You made bail quickly.
Candy, this is my fiancée, Linda.
Wait, hold on. You said that's your fiancée?
You marrying her?
That'll never work.
l gotta go.
Hey, Candy.
Look, this is my number.
lf you need anything,
just give me a call, all right?
Yeah.
Are you going to handle it?
Honey,
you are an assistant district attorney.
You shouldn't be hanging out
with the likes of those people.
What are you doing with her?
Don't answer that.
She's an old friend,
and l was just trying to help her out.
Bad move.
-What did l say, Linda?
-You did.
-Didn't l? Didn't l say it?
-Yeah, you did.
What did you say?
l was talking to your future wife here,
remember that?
About the fact that you feel guilty, Josh.
l know. l made it out of the ghetto, too.
But l don't apologize for it.
But these people,
they will never let you forget.
And as long as you let them do that,
you will always feel
a sense of obligation to them.
-Now, am l right, or am l right?
-That is not it.
Don't talk. Just agree.
Well, whatever it is, the point is
they were afforded the same opportunities
you were.
You did something, they didn't.
Linda, it's not always that simple.
Just agree to disagree
and change the subject.
Okay, can we just order some food, maybe?
Yes.
-We're back at the house.
-My daddy is having a party here.
l gotta go pick up my kids.
You all gotta handle this.
l know Joe ain't having no party
at my damn house!
How could you...
l know Joe ain't having
no party at my damn house!
Yes, he is, Madea. He up and...
Wait. Just stay calm.
-Cora! Who these people, Cora?
-l don't know.
Cora, who are these people
up in my house?
l don't know.
Holy smoke.
-Look at all these people.
-The music's too loud.
Uncle Joe having a party.
l know Madea will be upset.
Madea's upset.
Hey, sexy.
You look like a bowl of peach ice cream.
l could...
Get out of my face before
l throw this oil all over you!
Oh, now you want to get kinky, huh?
Kinky? You...
l like that.
-The devil is a lie.
-He is.
Hey, sexy.
You want to spend some time with me
and be my client?
What kind of work she do, Cora?
A lawyer in the sickroom?
A doctor in the courtroom?
She's a...
Say it, baby!
l'm a prostitute.
A prosti-what?
"A prostitute" is what she said.
Streetwalker.
Woman of the night.
Cora, give me that oil.
The devil is a lie. The blood! The blood!
She a Mary Magdalene, Cora.
-Madea, just stay calm, okay?
-Mabel, don't have no nervous breakdown.
Stay calm, Madea. Just stay calm.
-Mabel, just...
-Where the hell is Joe?
He know l just got out ofjail.
Hey, Mabel. Hell, l didn't even know
you was coming home.
How you doing? Good to see you.
Joe, who the hell are all these people
in my house?
When l saw the news,
l said, "They're gonna lock my sister up,"
so l'm gonna invite
all these people over here
so that she can have a good time
when she come home and l'm so...
Yeah, right.
You know better than this, Uncle Joe.
What the hell... What you doing?
You all right?
He is smoking out of this pipe.
l'm glad you home, Mabel.
l'm so glad you home.
Madea, l just want you to stay calm.
Stay calm? For what?
All these people are for you, Mabel.
Enjoy yourself. Enjoy yourself.
Excuse me. Excuse me, sexy slim.
-You look calm.
-l'm calm.
-You look calm like a quiet storm.
l'm calm. l'm calm.
What the hell you doing
upstairs in my house?
Get the hell out my bedroom!
She's got a gun!
l can make it work.
l can give you some lndian hair.
Yeah, that's right. Be $75.
Got to make that work.
That's cute, too. l like that.
What about you? What you gonna have?
Ladies.
-All right.
-There you go. Here.
-How you doing tonight?
-Thank you.
-All right?
Y'all take care of yourselves out here.
And listen,
if you need anything, just come see me.
347 Trotter Lane.
That's right. All right.
Take care of yourselves.
-Hi, Donna.
-Hi, Ellen.
This is my friend Candace.
Here you go again.
We've met.
This is my girl right here.
We were in New York together.
l begged her to come down here.
And she finally came.
ls that right?
Taking care of yourself out here?
Why you all in my business?
Candy. Ellen is good people.
l'm just here to help.
By thumping your Bible at me every
five minutes the way my grandmamma did?
Child, l don't even know your grandmamma,
and l don't carry no Bible around with me.
lt's at home on my mantel.
You ain't got to carry it
'cause you know every word in it.
You better know it.
Amen.
So, you gonna give me
some of them or not?
You asking me?
Go on, act right, man. She's good people.
May l have some, please?
"May l."
Look at you sounding all educated.
Here.
Here's a voucher
for some food if you need it.
What?
You don't know how to say thank you.
Thank you.
-You on drugs?
-Why?
What is it, heroin or coke?
Lady, don't you be touching me.
You don't know me. You need to back up.
-Need some clean needles?
-l do. What's wrong with you?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Ladies, take care of yourselves.
And, Donna, l'm still waiting.
l know.
Donna, who is that fool?
Man, l've been on these streets
since l was 1 6 years old.
l've seen all kinds of people say they come
in the name of one god or another.
But that woman right there, she's real.
She's good folks, man.
She be around all types of dope boy,
pimps, addicts.
She treats us all the same.
She preaches down at the prison.
Why she say she waiting on you?
l keep telling her
l'm gonna get off these streets.
No, sir. l... That's all l have.
The first, the last name.
That's all l have. Sure. No, l understand.
All right. Okay. Okay. Thank you.
-Any luck?
-Nope.
What about you?
Nope.
You know, tell me again.
Why are we doing this?
l'm just trying to find somebody
to help her get off these streets.
You never done this before, so it's...
We got history.
-Oh, you...
-No!
Not like that.
Here you are,
you trying to help this girl, man,
and l've never heard you mention her.
Okay, l've known you for what, three years?
And you know what? On top of all that,
we're supposed to be looking for
vacation spots for your honeymoon, man.
-We are.
-No, no, no. No.
"We." You call me up, you say,
"Man, come..."
Hey.
-Hey, baby.
-Hey, how you doing?
-Good. How are you?
-l am good.
Okay. You know what?
l'm gonna leave you lovebirds alone.
-Where you running off to?
-l gotta...
-To do... Yeah. Yeah.
-You ain't going nowhere.
l got a date, so...
-What's your date's name?
-Lucky girl.
Leave me alone. l'm out.
So today was incredible.
l found these shoes.
The girls are gonna flip out.
And l also found the most
amazing new dressmaker,
and she agreed to do the dress for us.
-That's great.
-l know.
Did you find any places
for the honeymoon?
No, actually, l was...
l was looking for
some of Candy's family in Texas.
Okay, so you're still
talking about this prostitute?
-Babe, why are you calling her a prostitute?
-That's what she is.
Babe, where l'm from
if somebody needs help,
you try to help them out.
Okay, sweetie, you know that you can only
help someone that wants to be helped.
Those people don't want help.
Honey, why are you calling them
"those people"?
l mean, those people,
people like her, from that side of the tracks.
l'm from the same street.
We were in college together until this...
Sweetie, that doesn't make any difference.
lt's not the same thing with you.
Sweetie, she's not like you.
lt is her own fault
if she didn't make something of herself.
Linda, you've always had things
handed to you.
-You've always been Daddy's little princess.
-What?
Until you've been on the streets,
you really wouldn't understand.
That is my cue to leave.
-What you mean...
-So l'm gonna let you cool off for a minute.
-What are you... Linda.
-Yes?
l'm sorry. l am.
But it bothered me seeing
that woman on the street.
-lt bothers you?
-Yes, it bothers me.
Okay. When she stops
bothering you so much,
why don't you give me a call?
-Linda. Linda.
-Okay?
Hey, l don't want you to go.
l don't want to hear about this girl anymore.
-l'm done with her.
-Okay.
Now, you've helped her enough.
You won't hear about it again.
You still out here?
Yeah, girl. lt's a slow night.
No, it's not. Those Army boys just got paid.
You turned down, like, three
when l was here before.
What's up, girl?
l ran into somebody
who l knew from before earlier today.
l see.
You started thinking about
what your life could have been.
No, not me.
l know l ain't got no time
to be chasing no dreams.
You ain't like the rest of us, Candy.
You can get out of here
and make something of yourself.
What?
Me, some Betty Crocker mom or something?
No, you smart.
l see how you be reading them books.
Listen. Terry McMillan ain't doing nothing
to get me no fix, okay?
All l'm saying is
if anybody can get out of here, you can.
l've seen you talk to a million people.
l've seen you talk your way
out of all kinds of stuff.
You can do it.
Whatever, Donna. Please.
All right, l'm gonna make a deal with you.
lf l get off these streets,
you gotta get off these streets.
All right. That's a bet.
Maybe we can help each other.
Now, you know we always do, girl.
You know what l was just thinking about?
Remember when we were
in New York, right...
Donna!
Candy, come on. Run! Run!
-Oh, my God.
-Think you can hide from me?
-No.
-l told you
not to be out here solo, Donna Lynn,
you hear me?
Okay, Daddy, please.
-Okay.
-Now get your ass out of here!
Okay. Candy, let's go.
-No, no, no. Not you.
-What you want with her?
You want a real woman.
You don't want her.
l see what l want!
Now get your ass out of here!
She's just been here a couple of weeks!
l'm trying to show her the ropes.
She ain't ready! She ain't ready!
Where do you think you're going, huh?
Where the hell
do you think you're going, girl?
You're not going nowhere.
You understand me?
Nothing goes down...
Where do you think you're going?
Please. Please. Please.
l won't tell anybody. l promise.
What? You think that scares me?
Please. Please, let me go. Please, let me go.
What are you gonna do for me
if l let you go?
What do you want me to do?
You belong to me.
You're my slave.
lf a slave want to be free,
they got to buy their freedom.
Okay. Okay.
l want you to get in that bathroom,
and l want you to get cleaned up.
l can get a premium for you.
All right, go on, baby.
Go on, it's all right.
You're gonna learn you ain't gonna be
protected on these streets
unless you got a pimp. You understand?
l've got this nice party
l'm going to take you to.
A lot of new potential clients.
A couple of Gs, easy.
l want you to make yourself
look real nice, girl.
l got a good feeling about you.
You'll become my special girl.
Don't be wasting time in there, girl.
Come on now. We got to get there
in an hour. l don't want to be late.
l don't hear that shower in there, Candy.
What's going on in there?
Candy? Candy?
Okay. Okay.
Operator, l need District Attorney
Josh Hardaway.
Just connect me to his phone, please!
lt's an emergency!
Hello.
Hey.
You okay?
Are you serious? Where are you?
Okay, l'm coming right now.
l'm coming... l'm coming right now.
All right. l know. All right. Bye.
Candy? Can you walk?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Okay. Okay.
lt's okay.
Baby?
l fell asleep.
How come you're not in bed, sweetie?
What? What's the matter?
l can explain. l can explain.
ls that my robe? You can explain?
She's in trouble.
l'm just trying to help her out.
Why did you bring her here?
Linda, she needs somebody.
l don't care what she needs!
Shush? Are you kidding me?
What is it with you and this girl?
What is going on here?
Linda, l told you,
l'm the only one that can help her out.
No, Josh. You know what?
You have some decisions to make
and some thinking to do.
l am leaving!
And stop shushing me!
Shushing me so the prostitute can sleep?
l am done, Josh. l cannot believe this.
Linda, just don't slam the door.
You slammed it.
Do you know how much a door costs?
You always did know how to pick them.
She's not your type.
How do you know what my type is?
You haven't seen me in five years.
Josh, l know you. Okay? And she is not it.
She's entirely too much of a princess.
lt ain't gonna work.
l bet you ain't even proposed to her.
Then why do you think
we're getting married then, smarty?
Because she told you you were.
You don't know me.
You think you know me,
but you don't know me, girl.
Josh, l know you. We grew up...
We spent every day together
when we were kids.
l know you.
Candace, people change.
l know that's right.
You're shaking. You cold?
This ain't the cold shakes, baby.
When did you start using?
When you got out of school?
Had to find some way to cope, just like you.
What are you talking about? Me?
Ambition.
Working two jobs
while you were in school full-time.
You did that so you
don't have to think about what happened.
That's a interesting concept you got.
Josh, l don't want to talk about this, okay?
All right. We don't have to...
We don't have to talk.
Hey, Josh.
Yeah?
You remember that bed-and-breakfast
that we were gonna open in Savannah?
Down by the river.
Bells. l remember Bells.
-You remember?
-Yeah, l remember.
Oh, Josh.
l was gonna buy it
and live happily ever after.
So why didn't you buy it?
l couldn't find a job, and...
l ain't have no money.
l was so hungry.
And then l met this man,
and he said he loved me.
He said he was gonna take care of me.
And he said that if l loved him, then l would
sleep with him and his friend.
And it turned into his other friends,
without him.
And then strangers.
lt took me four years,
four years
to get away from him.
CeCe, l'm sorry. l...
CeCe?
Yeah.
That little girl, she died a long time ago.
Boy, are those tears in your eyes?
You better man up.
Don't you sit over there feeling sorry for me.
At least l get paid for what l do now.
You do not get paid for what you do.
l told all y'all
l ain't got no anger manager problem.
Y'all still insisting on me going.
Madea, you have
a anger management problem.
Fine, Cora. Take me down there, then.
l don't understand why...
That's why l'm gonna get you one of these.
One of what?
-This, right here. One of these.
-What is that?
lt's a reminder on how to treat people.
WWJD. l'm gonna get you one.
You know what that mean?
What that stand for?
"What's Wrong with Jermaine Dupri"?
No. lt means "What Would Jesus Do?"
Everybody know that, Madea, come on.
-Come on.
-l don't know that.
Did you see that?
-Did you see him?
-Yes, l saw it.
Cora, what you gonna do?
l'm gonna WWJD.
Cora, Jesus did not have no car.
You better go get that fool.
Madea, he gonna get his. No, l can't.
-Cora, Cora.
-He gonna get his.
Look at him, rushing.
He got stopped by the light.
Pull up on him, then. Roll up on him.
-Okay.
-l'm gonna do a drive-by.
No, you not.
You just calm down. l got this. l got this.
Excuse me, sir. Excuse me.
-Hey, fool!
-What?
You just cut in front of me.
Did you see that?
Go to hell.
What... Did... What?
-Did you hear that?
-Did you show him your bracelet, Cora?
-Did you show him the WWJD?
-Don't be funny, Madea. That is not...
Cora, l didn't raise no punk.
You better go get that fool.
l'm not no punk, Madea, but he...
-Cora, you ain't gonna be no punk!
-l'm not no punk, Madea!
We punked that dude in his face!
We got that fool!
Mama?
Girl, l ain't your mama.
Good morning.
What are you, a size five, six?
Why?
Probably a three.
You don't look like you eat much.
Josh, what... What the hell is this?
We both set up a job interview for you.
l think l can cover that eye up.
We have companies
that work with our ministries
to get women off the street.
That's if you want to be.
Who said l wanted to be, huh?
-Candy, you said that's what you wanted.
-Well, l told you.
l mean, sometimes women like her
say one thing one day,
and then they wake up and they say...
Okay, what you mean, "girls like her"?
You don't even know me!
Chicks, junkies like you with a problem
say one thing one day
and another the other,
because you're on that stuff.
Go to hell.
You go first.
l ain't no damn addict.
Candy? Candy?
lf the public defender can show the judge
that you got a job,
that's gonna look really, really good.
And they may even suspend your sentence.
l need to know...
l need you to try this, please.
Fine! Fine!
Fine.
-Thank you.
-Okay, we'll see you there.
l gotta go to work.
Candy, after you're done,
can you come down to the courthouse?
l want to talk to your lawyer.
l want to see if l can help him through this.
Okay?
Yeah. Okay. Sure.
You want to try to get this job or not?
l told them that l didn't need to come here
and see you, okay?
You know, l don't usually
see people individually,
but when l saw this tape
of you getting arrested,
l thought, "l have got
to talk to this woman."
What is wrong with you?
Why are you... Why are you so angry?
First of all, ain't nothing wrong with me.
Secondly, l'm not angry.
Okay? l'm not angry.
You seem angry right now.
No, l'm not angry. This is how l am.
l don't have no hostility at all.
Do you have to be in control
all the time of everything?
l don't have to be in control all the time.
l ain't got no problem with that.
Then why do you get so angry?
l don't get angry.
l keep trying to tell you and that judge
that l do not get angry.
lf somebody do something to me,
l do something to them.
That's just common sense.
So you believe in getting even?
Hell to the yeah.
Why do you feel the need that you gotta
get somebody all the time?
lt's like, "Get 'em, get 'em, get 'em."
You don't think that's angry?
lf they got me, got me, got me,
l gotta get them, get them, get them.
Yeah, that's what it is.
What you call getting got
is a whole lot different
than what other people call getting got.
lt doesn't take much to "get you," does it?
When you're "getting got" and somebody
done got you and you go get them.
When you get 'em,
everybody's gonna get got.
Yeah, but if you're getting somebody
that you say got you
when they didn't get you to begin with,
then you're getting the gotters
when they didn't do anything to you
to get you.
Yeah, but if the gotters get me,
l'm going to get my Glock.
Yeah, well, but you don't get the Glock
when you haven't been got.
So what l'm trying to explain to you
is l don't care who done got me,
l'm gonna get them first.
You get me? l'm gonna get you.
Why is it so important?
Okay. l'm tired of you
asking me all these questions
'cause l didn't sign up for this.
lt's the judge that
told me to come here, okay?
Everybody wants to get even.
Everybody want to get even.
All right. All right.
Let's just talk about your childhood.
Okay? Let's talk about your childhood.
Let's talk about your childhood.
Talking about my childhood
isn't gonna help us.
So what was your childhood like?
-What was yours like?
-Do you... Why...
Let's talk about your anger.
That's why you're here, right?
l'm not angry. l don't know why l'm here.
-Let's just try another approach, okay?
-Let's try another approach.
All right. Do you sleep well at night?
Do you sleep well at night?
Let's try not to answer a question
with a question.
Could we do that?
Could we at least do that?
Yes, if we at least
stop asking me all these questions,
l wouldn't have to answer a question
with a question, now will l?
Can you stop? Can you just stop?
Can you just stop? Can you just stop?
-Okay.
-Are you getting angry, Doctor?
This isn't getting anywhere.
This is not getting anywhere.
No. l think l am gonna talk to the judge,
but l don't think this is getting anywhere.
-l think we're done.
-Thank you so much. l appreciate it.
-Okay, that's good.
-Wonderful to see you.
-Yes. Right.
-Great.
Come on, Cora.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Wait a minute.
Well?
This lady is out of control.
She is... l can't help her.
Wait a minute now. Wait a minute now.
Now, you're the best.
Go see somebody else. l'm done.
Come on, Cora! Hell!
Now, what am l gonna do?
l don't know who's going
to be able to help me. Ain't nobody...
Linda.
-Hey.
l've been trying to call you.
You know what?
l got really busy with some stuff.
Avoiding me, right?
-No.
-l can explain.
Look, this isn't making any sense to me.
Okay? l mean, this girl,
she popped up out of nowhere.
Look, what if l had a pimp
who was a friend of mine
and he's in town for a month or so
and he needs a place to sleep
so he's on my couch in your bathrobe?
How do you feel about that? ls that okay?
l mean, seriously.
What would you have me think?
l know it sounds bad...
Yeah. We have built cases for death
on less than this.
So what do you want me to do?
l just want you to let this go.
Really, l just want you to let her go back
to wherever it is she came from.
Josh, this is not our responsibility.
Look, l gotta go.
-Okay.
-Can we finish this later?
-All right. Thank you.
-All right. l'll call you.
Josh. Josh, Josh.
-What's up, man?
-Hey, what's going on, man?
-Nothing. You...
-l don't want to talk about it.
-Okay. We don't have to talk about it.
-Please.
l may have found a possible lead
for a brother of hers.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Thank you, man.
-lt's all good, bro.
-Yeah.
-lt's what l do.
You know, it's funny, man.
They really don't get along.
lt says here that you went to college.
Yeah, l did two years.
-What happened?
-l ain't finish.
l see that.
There are some blanks here
that you didn't fill out.
l didn't know the answer.
What you want me to do?
Looking at this application
tells me that you don't finish anything.
So why should we hire you?
Listen, man, l just need a job.
You gonna give me one or not?
lt's real simple.
How bad do you want it?
l won't ask you to do anything
you haven't done a million times.
l've seen your record.
Oh, God. No.
-What happened?
-Your Christian help ain't so Christian.
This is what your A-word get.
You're supposed to help these girls.
-You know how you set her back?
-Oh, God.
Dear Jesus.
Now l don't know where the hell Cora is at.
l done told her l need to go to the store.
And people done already told me
l can't be driving,
and she know that l need to go to the store.
That child gonna leave you
to starve to death.
l told you when you were little
that the way you were treating her,
she's gonna leave you
to starve to death one day.
-And now's that time.
-Shut up, bastard.
Oh, Lord. Hello?
-Cora.
-Hello, Madea. Yes?
-Corard!
-Yes, ma'am?
Where the hell you at?
l'm still at the hair salon.
What the hell you doing at the hairdresser?
You been there five hours!
Your hair ain't but an inch and a half long!
What the hell they doing to you?
l'm coming. l'm just trying to...
Can l have some "me" time, please?
Hello? Hello?
-You need some what?
-Some "me" time.
Some what?
Some "me" time. Some time for myself.
-Cora?
-Yes, ma'am?
Did l ever ask you
for some "me" time, Cora?
-No, ma'am.
-Did l ask you for some "me" time
when l had to get up every four hours
and cook for you
up until the time you was 1 7 years old?
-No, ma'am, you...
-Did l ask you for some "me" time
when l had to hit that stripper pole
every night
trying to bring some money
into this house?
Did l ask you for some "me" time then?
-No, ma'am, no.
-All them old men...
l'm up there trying to make it drizzle
'cause they sure in the hell
couldn't make it rain!
-What the hell is "me" time?
-l'm just taking care of myself.
That's what l'm doing.
Getting some "me" time.
Time for nothing! l'm going to the store.
Hell, l don't need you to...
l'm a grown-ass woman!
-l'm gonna go to the store myself.
-You can't go to the store.
You're not supposed to be driving.
l'll be there soon, okay?
Who the hell you think you talking to,
telling me l can't drive?
lf l feel like driving, l'm driving!
-You can't drive! You're gonna...
-Shut the hell up.
You get in that car, you going down, Mabel.
l'm not playing around.
You going down. You understand?
l'll be glad when you go down.
Down to the graveyard
and become some maggot food.
Hell, l'm grown. l'm home.
What l'm supposed to do?
Just sit up in this house?
You can miss a few meals.
One or two.
Three or seven.
Nine or eleven.
Keep it up, Joe. Keep it up.
Them people called! Them people called.
You ain't got to worry about no food.
You can call them.
They said they'd bring it down here to ya.
What the hell you talking about, Joe?
Stop smoking that weed!
What the hell you talking about?
You're crazy as hell!
They said they'll give you three meals a day,
and they'll give you a percentage
of the peoples who come through and pay.
Well, where they feed you that much?
One of the whales died.
They need another whale at the aquarium.
Go on down there and swim around for 'em.
You rusty old bastard.
You fart, and dust come out.
-Go to hell.
-Dead man walking!
Walking the green mile.
Getting right with Jesus.
l'm gonna walk the green mile.
Get right with Jesus.
l don't know what the hell you blowing at,
but keep blowing at me.
Come on, Grandma!
You coming... You coming out?
Hey! You coming out?
-Move it, lady!
-l guess you ain't coming out.
l like them shoes.
Come on, come on, come on!
Here's a spot.
Now l got the groceries now,
l just need to get up in here.
Come on out.
l know... Did she...
l know damn well that you just...
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Lady, l know...
l know damn well you saw me
getting ready to take this spot.
l saw you. l took it.
Why don't you move your little red car
before l move it for ya?
Okay, go on in the store.
Go on in the store. Just walk off.
Just walk off like you bad.
You bad? You bad? Okay.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
l said l was waiting for that spot, lady.
Well, it's my spot now, Grandma.
Lady. Lady, look here.
Lady! Lady, let me explain something...
-Are you going to follow me into the store?
-Lady, let me explain something to you.
Lord have mercy. Lord have mercy.
She gonna make me
tear the "K" and the "B" off of this Kmart.
Let me back up.
l ought to run right into her,
but Lord help me.
l don't want to get in no trouble, Lord.
Help me, Jesus! Help me, Lord!
You know, l'm ready
to go drive straight through this glass.
That's all right. l'm gonna beat her ass.
Are you insane?
Didn't l tell you? That was my parking spot.
And you gonna jump in front of me
and take my damn parking spot?
Are you insane? Put my car down!
Okay, l'm gonna put it down for ya.
Old woman, put my car down now!
Okay.
My husband is a police officer,
and he is on his way right now!
l ain't scared of no po-po-po.
Call the po-po! Call the po-po!
Honey! This woman... This Jemima the Hun,
she ruined my car!
And l'm gonna get the hell out of here.
lf he want me
he better come to my house to get me.
He will!
Get over here now! The Kmart!
Am l forgiven?
Well, after those flowers
and those chocolates...
-Yes.
-And that great movie that we just saw?
-You are definitely working on it.
-That's good.
Because l do not like it
when you're mad at me.
Well, l don't like being mad at you.
-Oh, boy.
-Why don't we go inside and make up?
Let's go ahead.
Can you just move a little faster, babe?
Please. lt's me. lt's Josh.
-Josh?
-Yeah.
She's probably strung out on something.
l'm sorry. l'm sorry. l'm sorry.
-l'm sorry.
-You ain't gotta be sorry.
All right?
-Just try to... Try to relax.
-Okay, rest, rest.
Josh, l promise, l'm trying to stop.
l'm trying to...
Rest. Rest.
You have never done that for me.
What are you talking about, Linda?
This. The care that you're showing her.
You've never done that for me.
Baby, please, not tonight.
Okay?
Josh, you're in love with her.
Babe, what are you talking about?
l'm just trying to help out a friend.
l don't even know how to compete
with a drug-addicted prostitute.
Linda, there's nothing going on with us.
l have to go right now. l can't do this.
-l can't do this, Josh. No. l'm sorry.
-Where are you going?
-l can't do this right now.
-Linda.
Please come and lay with me. Please.
Look, Candy...
l don't think that'd be a good idea.
Josh, l don't mean like that.
l mean, remember when we were little
and my stepdad would be trying to get me
and you'd protect me.
Please, Josh, please.
Josh, please, Josh.
All right.
-All right.
-Please.
All right.
Okay. lt's gonna be okay.
lt's gonna be okay.
This is the DeKalb County SWAT team.
Put your hands in the air
and walk backwards.
You have the right
to speak to an attorney...
-Don't move!
-l tell you what,
l ain't going down without a fight!
Come on, you bad.
What you gonna do? Come on.
You have the right to remain...
What the hell!
Don't move.
Get off of me now!
You're giving me a mammogram.
You squeezing my...
Candace.
Candy?
Okay.
Good morning.
You scared me.
What are you doing here so early?
l am preparing for court.
You are preparing for court, huh?
This is the... Candace Collins.
Sarah Lester. Wait, whoa.
l remember this one.
This is Sarah Lester.
Yeah. Sarah... Sarah Lester.
This case was closed a couple years ago.
Are you padding
this woman's file with a closed case?
Chuck, let me handle this, all right?
-You can't do that, Linda.
-lt's done.
So, wait, wait, wait.
ls this how you been
winning all your cases?
ls this how you've been
winning all your cases, Linda?
l'm not gonna stand by
and let you do this, okay?
-l've got to...
-What? What do you have to do?
Don't you forget your bar exam, baby.
Remember how you cheated?
Don't try me, Chuck. l have the proof.
And l will use it.
Why are you doing this?
l mean, this woman
has done nothing to you...
How would you know that?
He's not in love with her.
He loves you.
How deep is your commitment
to this girl, Josh?
She's a friend.
A friend?
You know what a binge addict is?
No.
They can stay clean for long periods of time
and then something sets them off
and they can go off
for days, weeks, and binge.
'Cause this doesn't just go away like a cold.
This is a disease that has to be cured.
And if you're in it for the wrong reasons,
it's gonna destroy you so fast.
l'm gonna ask you again.
How deep is your commitment
to this girl, Josh?
When we were both back in college,
she...
l was the only person
that she knew at the school.
And l knew her from the neighborhood.
You know, the other students,
they really used to make fun of her.
You know, like, her hair and her clothes.
l started getting embarrassed.
And they...
l started avoiding her.
And l was on the football team.
We were having this, like, big party.
And, you know, they told me
to invite Candy over.
You know, so l did.
l had a date, you know?
l really didn't want to...
l didn't even really want to be there.
They told me that they would,
you know, keep her company
while l was gone. And
l came back that night,
and...
l came back from... l came back that night...
l came back that night,
and l went in my room,
and...
They had...
They raped her.
And l didn't do...
l didn't do nothing about it.
l'm like, "What... What..."
But l never, like, "Candy, l'm sorry."
l never told her l'm sorry.
Josh, look at me. Josh.
You can't carry that weight.
-What... Oh, my God... Girl...
-Josh,
look at me.
-Josh, look at me.
-Yes?
-Yeah. l'm trying.
-Look at me. Look at me.
-You can't carry that weight.
-Okay.
She had problems long before that party.
-Mabel.
-Brown.
Listen, listen.
l'm trying to see Judge Mablean.
-Will you please be quiet?
-l'm trying to pray for you. Now pray.
God don't like you.
He grew you in a petri dish, Brown.
-l'm trying to help you.
-l don't need you to help me here!
Hey, hey, hey, Brian.
Judge Mablean always give me
a slap on the wrist.
Well, this is not Judge Mablean.
This judge is tough.
-How tough could he be?
-All rise!
The Honorable Judge Mathis presiding.
You may be seated.
First case, DeKalb County
calls Mabel Simmons.
Wait a minute.
-ls that who the hell l think it is?
-Yes.
lt's all spelled out for you there,
Your Honor.
Yeah, l'm looking at this case,
-and your record is ridiculous, ma'am.
-Thank you.
l don't even know
how you're still on the street.
-Your Honor, the reason l'm on...
-l'm talking!
You should have been locked up
a long time ago with this.
-Your Honor...
-Look, l speak, you listen.
And then l'll allow you to respond,
you understand?
Yes, sir.
Who the hell he think he talking to?
Y'all better...
-Mabel, be quiet.
-Madea!
You better be quiet.
What do you have to say for yourself?
Oh, now is my turn to talk?
You've heard the saying,
"Speak when you're spoken to,
or otherwise shut up."
Oh, it's Simon Says.
That's how this go, huh?
l don't have time for this.
lt's time for some sentencing.
Bailiff, what time you have on your watch?
Five to 1 0:00, Judge.
Five to ten. That's your sentence.
-Have a good day. Next.
-Oh, hell, no! You gonna...
Five? You gonna give me five years?
You ain't gonna take me back there to jail.
Come on here. What you gonna do?
Where the hell you going?
Give me five years.
-l got you.
-Let's go.
You ain't gonna take me out of here!
l ain't going! l ain't going!
-l ain't going!
-Come on!
l ain't going! l...
Linda.
-Oh, hey, baby.
-Hey.
-Thanks for letting me borrow this.
-Oh, sure.
How'd it go today?
-Seventeen years.
-What?
Seventeen years?
Babe, it was only two counts.
Sweetie, sweetie,
you didn't see her New York sheet.
lt is as long as my arm.
-Yeah.
-Wow, l had no idea.
-She just was...
-l know, l know. l'm sorry. l'm so sorry.
l really tried to be lenient with her, but,
you know,
once the judge saw the charges...
And on top of that,
she didn't show up today.
You know, maybe it's for the best.
Maybe now she can get her life together.
Maybe you're right.
So, she still at your place?
No, she left.
Maybe now l can stop being mad at you
and we can go back to planning our future?
l would like that.
Me, too.
-All right.
-Okay.
How you doing?
Hey, sweet thing.
What you looking for?
A good time.
What's it gonna cost me?
l'll give you a special. $50.
Get in.
Where you going? You want to party? Huh?
Hey.
Get your damn hands off me.
Put your hands down.
l'm telling y'all right now,
l ain't scared of none of ya.
Yeah, keep it up. Keep it up.
You ain't got it.
We ain't all gonna be the same height here.
l'm here. Now let me go!
What the hell wrong with you?
How you do'ern?
Guess this is my cell.
What the hell you smiling so much for?
You the Martha Stewart of prison
or something?
No.
l'm T.T.
-You're who?
-l'm T.T.
Like two of these?
l'm T.T.
-l'm...
-Oh, T.T. T.T., how you do'ern?
l'm Mabel, but everybody
call me Madea. Heller.
l'm so happy that we are sharing a cell.
This is your bunk. l made it for you.
Thank you, honey. l appreciate it.
But l ain't into none of that freaky deaky.
Just 'cause you making the bunk,
don't mean l'm giving you nothing.
You ain't getting none of this good stuff,
you understand?
You put your hands on me,
l'm gonna punch all that Spanish
out your throat.
You gonna be talking straight-up English.
You're so funny. l was just being nice.
When l saw you come in, l thought,
"l hope she's in my cell."
Ta-da!
Brownies for my brownie!
l made them myself.
What the hell you mean,
"Brownies for your brownie"?
You trying to call me black or something?
Brownie!
Ain't no oven in here.
How the hell do you make a brownie?
l have my ways.
No, thank you.
l saw you on TV. That was a great chase.
How long you have here, Madea?
They tell me l got five years.
But l'm breaking the hell out of here
the first chance l get.
Can l come with you?
You seem like a nice, sweet person, honey.
What the hell you in here for?
Stealing flowers?
What'd you do?
Steal some candy from the Girl Scouts?
What?
No.
l murdered 1 8 men.
-And the...
-l'm sorry.
You what to a ATM?
l murder 1 8 men.
-Eighty?
-Eighteen! One-eight men.
l'm one of the first female serial killers.
l'm going to be here till l...die.
But l'll be making you brownies,
my brownie!
Hey, which one's yours?
You can take either one.
Donna?
Candy. Oh, my God.
Candy!
How are you doing?
-l am so glad to see you.
-l know.
l didn't know what happened to you.
l've been trying to reach you,
but you ain't got no address.
You look good.
Yeah, l'm doing good. How you doing?
-What?
-They gave me 1 7 years.
-For... For what?
-Donna, l don't know what l'm gonna do.
No, that ain't right.
They had to trump your charges.
l don't know what happened.
l just know this ain't right.
Donna,
what am l gonna do for 1 7 years in here?
l've been going to Ellen's services.
Now wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
She teaches classes here.
You should come.
l ain't trying to be in no church.
lt's not like that.
She teaches a group session here,
and she's really good.
l mean, she preaches,
but not like a preacher, you know?
She makes it clear
so you can understand it.
Well, look at me.
l've been clean all this time.
And, if you take a course,
you get time off your sentence.
You should come.
l don't know how people eat this.
This is crazy as hell.
l've seen people on Survivor
eat better food than this.
She ran like she was
running from some roaches.
-You're a cute little thing.
-Get your hands off of me.
-Feisty!
-Sal, leave her alone. That's my friend.
Was anybody talking to you?
Young man.
This little lady don't want to
be bothered with you.
Now get on up and go on back to
where you came from. Now, go on.
Who you think you're talking to, old lady?
You don't know me.
l'm gonna give you the benefit of the doubt.
Now get the hell up from the table
and go on now.
Go on. Go on, sir. Go on.
l see nobody told you l run this prison.
l'm Big Sal.
And what Big Sal wants, Big Sal gets.
Get it?
l guess nobody told you that l'm Madea.
Ma to the damn D-E-A.
You understand that?
And what l want, l get.
Do you understand me?
l'm from the West End.
That's where we cut a fool first
and run like hell afterwards.
You understand? You don't know me.
You don't know who the hell you talking to.
l will come across this table
and rip out your urethra tube.
l see l have to break you in.
You gonna get broke the hell in, but...
We'll have our time.
Yes, we will. l look forward to it.
A officer and a gentleman.
Get the hell on out of here
with Alvin and the two chipmunks.
-What the hell is that?
-Thank you.
l wasn't doing nothing for you, honey.
l just don't like people
messing over nobody, that's all.
l'm Terry, but everybody calls me T.T.
She say her name's T.T.
l thought she said titty, too,
the first time l talked to her.
l can't understand
what the hell she's saying.
Yeah, l'm Candace.
And l'm Donna.
Thank you for sticking up for my friend.
Yeah, y'all welcome.
You have a letter.
Why won't you talk to him?
'Cause l ain't got nothing to say to him.
Yeah, but maybe he can help you figure out
why you're in here so long.
Listen. l don't want to talk to him.
Well, obviously,
that man wants to be there for you,
so why don't you just let him...
Why don't you just see him?
Why don't you just drop it?
Drop it. Yeah, all right.
So l told them
they gonna give me five years.
Judge Mathis.
l said, "l don't care if it's Judge Judy, hell.
"You ain't fittin' to give me no five years."
But they did, and l'm here.
But l've been looking for a way
to break the hell out of here.
These folks don't know me up here.
l will set it off.
Hi, sweetness.
-This...
-You looking good.
Oh, listen, l know you ain't talking to me.
She must be talking to you.
l ain't fittin' to let her take my "vigintitive."
-What's so funny?
-You funny.
You funny as hell,
looking like Lou Ferrigno.
Old lady, you don't know
who you talking to.
Yes, l do. l'm talking to you.
You better back the hell up out of my face...
-Leave me alone.
-Go ahead on, bro.
Go ahead on. Go ahead on, bro.
Y'all better tell him. He don't know.
So when are you coming to see me,
sweetness?
Young man?
Didn't this little girl tell you
she don't want to be bothered with you?
Why the hell do you keep talking to her?
What is wrong with you?
What you gonna do?
Now, what you gonna do?
That's what l want to know!
What you gonna do?
You gonna sit there
and tell something to me?
-You stop it! Stop it!
-l don't need this.
l don't need this!
Please, Grandma!
Come on, come on, you big hefer!
-Come on! Over in there.
-Yeah! Come on! Yeah!
Cover her up here.
Hey! What's going on in here?
We not doing nothing.
l'm just telling how good God is.
All right, today,
we're gonna talk about forgiveness.
Why is this so important?
Yes, T.T.?
Because you have to forgive
-to be forgiven.
-Correct.
We must forgive others
as Christ forgave us.
Now, last week we talked about
the first steps to forgiveness.
Anybody know?
-Acknowledging what was done.
-That's right.
You know, a lot of times, we don't want to
acknowledge what we've done.
You know, when you don't
forgive somebody,
you give them power over your life.
They're sleeping at night,
and you're walking around
remembering everything that they've done.
You all know a little bit of my testimony.
Sixteen years living on the street.
Drug addiction, prostitution.
And l did it because l was hurting myself.
l was hurting my daddy.
l was hurting my mother.
l was hurting every man
that did anything bad to me.
Until one day the Lord spoke to me.
And He said,
"Forgiveness is not for the other person.
"lt's for you."
And the longer you hold on to it,
the longer you hold on to
the pain and the past and the hurt,
the longer you hold yourself back
from being free.
Well, l can't forgive my daddy
for what he did to me.
He's the reason l'm in here.
Well, Cookie, you know what?
Don't forgive him.
Because he's living his life. You're in here.
Forgiveness is not for them. lt is for you.
Well, l can't forgive him.
You don't know what he did to me!
Lord, do l have to listen
to all this melodrama?
ls there something wrong, Ms. Simmons?
ls there something wrong?
l'm sorry, Reverend Doctor
Bishop Preacher Lady,
whatever your name is.
l don't agree with all of this stuff.
l hear what you say about forgiveness, yes.
You supposed to forgive people.
But this child over here
talking about what her daddy did.
Honey, your daddy is somewhere
living his life, and you on lockdown.
Honey, you're in jail 'cause of what you did.
Learn how to take some
responsibility for yourself.
For your own stuff.
l can't stand for a woman to be the victim!
"This person did this,
that's why l'm this way."
Everybody in this place has got a story.
Your mama and your daddy
done gave you life.
That's all they was supposed to do.
No matter how good, how bad the life was,
it's up to you to make something out of it.
Suck it up and shut the hell up.
-But you don't know what he did!
-Let her talk!
Thank you, Biggie Smalls.
l love it when you call me Big Papa.
You're such a gentleman.
They say if l come here
l can get some time off,
and l'm just trying to get some time off.
Do my time.
l don't want to mess with nobody.
l don't want nobody to mess with me.
But this is crazy.
People, all of y'all up in here
need to understand something, okay?
Everybody got a life,
and what you do with that life is up to you.
Stop being the victim.
That's all l got to say. l ain't...
l don't feel like preaching, all that stuff.
l'm gonna leave that to you.
Matter of fact, l don't even want to be here.
But l got to get out of here
because this is working on my damn...
This is working on my nerves. Sorry.
l can't be bothered with this.
Guess she told you.
l'm glad you decided
to let me come see you.
Yeah.
So how are you?
l'm making it.
So you're getting married soon, huh?
Yeah.
Congratulations.
Good luck with that.
l... l really don't know what to say.
l feel like l keep letting you down.
l've been going to Ellen.
And l've really been listening
to what she has to say.
And she says that if you love the Lord,
then everything's gonna
work out for good for you.
Do you believe that?
Yeah. Yeah, l believe that.
l know l do 'cause...
Josh, l gotta believe in something.
You can believe in me.
l know l wasn't there that night,
but l guarantee that'll never happen again.
Did you know they were
gonna do that to me that night?
Did you know that they were
No, Candy, l didn't.
Josh, l needed you.
You weren't there for me.
You weren't there. l screamed for you.
And you never came for me.
You left me there.
Candy.
You didn't protect me.
Candy, l'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Please.
l was so mad at you, Josh.
l was so angry for so long.
But, Josh...
l forgive you.
You gotta go on,
and you gotta live your life,
and l gotta live mine.
l'm not gonna be a victim anymore.
l gotta change my life for me.
Now you, go get married.
Be happy.
And l'm gonna try to do the same thing.
l gotta go.
Have a good wedding day.
Joshua? Joshua!
Why are you not dressed?
Get the jacket on.
Linda's gonna be here in five minutes,
and l am not getting
cussed out behind you.
Get yourjacket on.
The mayor and the governor
are out there right now.
Are you gonna make them wait?
You just gonna make them wait?
-You gonna keep working?
-Whoa. My goodness.
-You gonna look at me like l'm stupid?
-Okay.
l will be out there. Thank you.
-Thank you, Josh. Thanks a lot.
-Just calm down. Calm down.
-Nice. Nice.
-l got it. l got it. l got it.
-Josh.
-Hey.
What are you doing?
Okay. lt's your wedding day.
Why are you working?
-Brother, get dressed.
-l'm getting dressed, man.
l'm getting dressed. Yeah, you're right.
Hey, l was looking at...
l was looking at Candy's file. And...
Something's not adding up.
A girl gets 1 7 years, right?
And the maximum of this count is...
lt's strange.
Josh, l gotta tell you something.
The couple has written their own vows.
These vows are from the heart
and will bind them together forever.
Josh,
you are my heart and soul.
l thank God for you every day.
l promise to love you
in sickness and in health.
l promise to give myself only to you.
And l promise to be honest
and to love you forever and ever.
Linda,
l will always know
that you are a wonderful woman.
But you are a conniving
and a manipulating human being,
and you disgust me.
Joshua.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this beautiful, insecure woman
that l refuse to marry,
she padded charges on a case
that she handled,
sending somebody to jail for time
that they did not deserve.
Thank you, man.
What are you doing here?
-You're supposed to be getting...
-Hey, Candy. Candy. Come here.
Come here.
No touching.
Shut up, man!
-What are you doing?
-l gotta get you out of here, okay?
l gotta get you out of here.
l gotta take you home.
-You understand me?
-What are you talking about?
l'm gonna get you out of here.
Linda is the last person in my life
that l'm gonna let hurt you.
l'm gonna be here for you.
l'm gonna help you kick that crap
and the streets and all the other stuff
if it takes every breath in my body.
You understand me?
l love you.
No touching.
The heck with it.
lt's a public issue
because justice is for everyone.
God bless you.
You're on with Frank and Wanda. Hello?
It was when I was
reviewing Candace Washington's file
that I discovered Linda Davis had tried...
...judges who presided over each case
gave sentences...
The goal of the District Attorney's office
is to see that these seven
unjustly imprisoned women
be released immediately
and be reunited with their loved ones.
lt's 1 5 past the hour.
And it's The Tom Joyner Morning Show.
Sybil, this morning l am outraged.
l am outraged about this prosecutor
that has got Madea in jail.
This story is so unbelievable to me.
There is...
This is Reverend Al Sharpton. We're back.
l want to talk about
this hotshot district attorney
that's trying to build up a career,
trumping up charges on...
lt's Michael Baisden.
First the Gina Six, now the Georgia Seven,
which includes Madea,
an elderly woman sentenced for five years
for a victimless crime.
You know l would do it...
lt's 1 7 minutes after the hour.
Welcome back to the ride, y'all,
on The Steve Harvey Morning Show.
Call us because Madea deserves to be free.
...march down to the D.A.'s office
and get this accomplished!
We are back. Now, Mabel Simmons,
also known to the general population
as Madea, has been arrested,
and there's been yet another
"Free Madea" rally.
Now, come on.
-Okay, she carries a gun!
-She has to carry...
But she has to carry a gun.
She's a vulnerable, older black woman.
-Madea is not vulnerable.
-They're out to get her.
That's how l see it.
We have a right to carry
our guns and bear arms.
lt's in our Constitution.
She bears all those arms. She got guns.
She's just cutting people down.
And she was not the only one.
You put six, seven women in jail,
and with these kind of sentences,
l mean, is this the kind ofjustice
we're looking for in the United States?
We have a news alert.
l am standing in front
of the Georgia State Courthouse,
where Assistant District Attorney
Linda Davis
was indicted today by a grand jury,
and the charges include fraud, tampering,
-and providing false documents.
-Man, l wish that chick had tried my case.
At some point, maybe today,
maybe tomorrow, but at some point soon,
Linda Davis will have to turn herself in
-to the authorities...
-l don't believe that.
...and she will be officially processed.
What does that mean?
-That means that she will be fingerprinted...
-Unbelievable.
...and at some point,
she will stand against the wall of shame
and have her mug shot taken.
What a fall from grace for Linda Davis.
Turn the TV on!
We're sitting here looking at that!
What the hell's wrong with you?
Bernice Davis, lda Mae Jones,
Taketa Matthews, Andrea Thomas,
Candace Collins, Mabel Simmons,
and Elizabeth Bryant.
There's been an investigation
in the D.A.'s offices
that has led
to the overturning of your convictions.
Get your things. You're going home.
What?
You're going home!
-This has got to be some kind ofjoke.
-Girl, go.
-Really?
-Yes.
Bye, Madea!
So you feel like justice has been served?
Yeah, justice is served.
You know, justice with...
Brian know about the justice
'cause he in justice.
l just think that we all are really,
really happy
-that this justice has been overturned.
-Yes, and you know what?
l'm gonna go buy her
a white dress with a white hat,
and white ruffled panties
and white ruffled socks and white shoes.
She's going to church this time.
You know, a better person to ask is Madea.
-Here she comes now.
-l'm out ofjail!
l watched the news! l watched the news!
l watched the news!
Soulja Boy!
l ain't got nothing to say.
l have nothing to say at all.
lt's just been really tough
being up in that prison.
And they really did all this stuff
to try to get me down.
But you can't keep me down.
Praise the Lord. God bless you. Hallelujer.
Wait! Wait! Let's go, then.
Mabel, you're going to church.
We're gonna take you to church.
They tell me you're the best.
Well, look, l don't usually do this.
l mean, you need to know that.
l don't usually see people individually.
l saw the videotape of you getting arrested
and l thought,
"l have got to see this woman."
You can't think what you did was okay.
You don't know what happened.
What do you mean,
l don't know what happened?
l saw it on tape.
l saw you forklift a lady's car
out of a parking space.
You talking about that time.
l've been on several tapes.
l ain't know what you talking about. But...
They have that on video, too?
You know what happened?
That woman just...
l been riding around that parking lot
in the heat.
My air conditioner don't work
in my Cadillac.
l got that '78 Cadillac.
And l was driving around, driving around,
and could not get a parking spot.
And there she was, zoomed in there,
knew l was waiting for that spot.
What else was l supposed to do?
You go on to another space.
Do you have to be in control all the time?
No, l don't have to be in control all the time.
But that was my parking spot.
l wasn't going to another space.
That was the closest one to the door
and that's the one l wanted.
Other people want stuff, too.
lt's not just about you.
lt's not just about you all the time.
ln my world, it's about me.
This is Madea's world.
lt's about me, Dr. Phil.
So, do you get angry
when you feel out of control?
l'm never angry.
l keep telling people l am not angry, okay?
lf somebody do something to me,
l do something back to them.
You don't bother me, l don't bother you.
That's just common sense.
So you weren't angry when you took
this lady's car and flipped it over?
Not at all. l was calm.
As cool as a cucumber.
-l was sitting there smoking a cigarette.
-Are you crazy?
-A little bit.
-Okay, l got a question for you.
Okay, l got a question for you, too.
-What about your childhood?
Talking about my childhood's
not going to help you with your anger.
How do you know l'm angry?
l keep saying that l'm not.
But you keep insisting that l am.
-What's going on?
-Are you happy to be here talking to me?
No, l would rather...
l'd much rather be at the casino
playing blackjack or something.
But they told me
l have to come here and see you.
-So l'm here.
-Why?
Because the court made me come.
You forklift a woman's car
out of the parking lot!
Does that seem reasonable to you?
She took the parking spot.
lt isn't your parking spot.
Yes, it was.
l was standing there waiting for it.
-Did it have your name on it?
-You didn't see it.
Did it have your name on it?
lt had handicap.
And that matches what l had in my car.
She just took it with her red convertible,
so l lifted it, flipped it. That's right.
Well, yeah, l believe the handicap part.
l got that.
Oh, wow. What are you trying to say?
You saying something's wrong with me?
Did you see me walk in here? l'm fine.
Then what are you doing
in a handicap space?
Because it was closer to the door.
What?
And they always leave the spot,
the handicap, close to the door.
That's why l take 'em.
Do you feel like
you always have to get even?
Hell, yeah.
Why do you always have to get even?
Why can't you just let it roll off
like water off a duck's back?
'Cause l ain't no damn duck.
You don't have to
attack people all the time!
lf somebody do something to you,
you supposed to do something to him.
That's what the Bible say.
The Bible say in ll "Deuteronomo"
of the book of Jericho
that the eye for the tooth
and the tooth for the people
and everybody who got the eye,
you punch 'em in it.
What?
l can tell you don't read the Bible.
So the Bible say turn the other cheek.
So somebody hit that cheek,
you turn to the other cheek.
You only have two cheeks.
Now how many cheeks you supposed to
let them hit before you whoop their ass?
Well, l don't think you ever
have to whoop their ass.
lt ain't about ass-whoopin'.
You don't open up a can of whoop ass
on everybody that you meet.
-You go with the flow.
-What do you mean?
Just letting people
walk over you like a doormat?
That's crazy as hell.
No, l've been in this life too long
to let some people just walk all over me.
l'm not fittin' to do that.
But it's easy for you
to get bothered, isn't it?
-No, it's not.
-lt doesn't take a whole lot
for you to get bothered.
No, it doesn't.
Yes, it does.
l beg to differ.
-Do you sleep well at night?
Okay, let's try not to answer a question
with a question, okay?
Well, if you stop asking questions,
l'll stop answering a question
with a question.
-Can you stop?
Okay. All right. Look.
Are you getting angry, Doctor?
Yeah, l'm getting angry.
Answer the question!
Answer what question?
This isn't working. This isn't helping.
l don't think it's helping, either.
l told the judge l didn't need to come here.
-But you're here.
-Yes, l am here.
You're not making any sense.
-You're not making any sense!
-Do people...
Do you talk to people like this all the time?
What? What they gonna do?
Did you see me? l'm 6'5".
What the hell they gonna do?
Yes, l say what's on my mind.
Ain't nobody gonna run over me, Dr. Phil.
l'll say what's on my mind.
What's on your mind?
Okay, what, is there...
What are you, a parrot?
ls there an echo in here?
No, there's not a parrot.
There's not an echo.
None of those things are in here.
l'm talking to you.
They told me to come see you.
Now what? You're supposed
to help me with anger.
l keep telling you that l'm not angry.
-You're not angry?
-No, l'm not angry! l'm not angry!
l don't know how many times to tell you
l'm not angry, Dr. Phil!
How can you tell if you're angry?
l can tell if l'm angry if l'm angry.
But if l was angry,
then l would know l'm angry.
-You don't think you're angry now?
-No.
You're yelling, you're screaming.
You're yelling and screaming.
You're driving me crazy!
But you're the doctor! You have a Ph.D.
You supposed to be
able to handle this here.
You are a psychologist.
You have studied with the best of 'em.
You done been all over the world
learning about people
and you gonna let a little old woman
upset you.
Yeah, they never told me about you.
l missed that class, l can tell you for sure.
l missed the class
where they went over Madea.
Yeah, that's right. Madea 1 01 , baby.
You need to learn it.
Yeah.
All right. Look. We're getting nowhere.
That's enough.
-Okay, that's enough.
-That's enough.
l've had it. That's enough.
We're out of here. You're fired.
Great. Thank you, Dr. Phil Trump.
Can we go now? ls it over?
lt's over. Yes. You should leave.
Please. Please.
Will you please tell the judge
that we had this session
and it was successful?
l'm gonna tell the judge
that you would have to get better
to be crazy.
l would have to get... Wow.
Well, l guess that's it, then.
l'll see you later.
-l guess that's it. You can leave.
-Thank you...