CLARENCE: Honey?
Hmm?
Have you seen my checkbook?
Downstairs
in the living room.
(GASPS)
Shh.
Darling, are you okay?
(STAMMERING) Fine!
CLAIRE: Are you sure?
I'm just gonna take
the dog for a walk.
Okay.
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(WHIMPERING)
Nice office.
Nice family.
(SIGHS)
Sorry to disturb you
at this time of night...
but we have a little problem.
Your boss owes me money.
A lot of money.
And I'm here to collect it.
(STUTTERS)
I'm just the accountant.
I don't know anything.
You don't need to
know anything...
except the combination
to the safe.
You do know
the combination, yes?
Yes.
Perfect. Please.
(BEEPING)
Get in.
Ah.
(LINE RINGING)
STUART: (OVER VOICEMAIL)
This is 310-555-0199.
Leave a message.
(BEEPS)
Hello, my friend.
It's Malankov.
I came to your office
to collect my money.
What a disappointment
to see it's not here.
But I am leaving you
something here in return.
As a reminder.
(GRUNTS)
I cannot wait any longer.
My best to the family.
(INDIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOLLYWOOD MUSIC PLAYING)
Sweet.
Yeah.
How old?
No matter how old
they are, my friend...
they will always
be our baby.
Ain't that true?
Come on, big guy.
Thank you.
(SHOP BELL RINGING)
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
Whoa!
BRYAN: Happy birthday!
Dad!
My birthday's
not even for three days.
You're always saying
I'm so predictable.
I wanted to shake
things up a bit,
make it a little
less predictable.
Sorry.
Come in.
(KIM SIGHS)
Champagne glasses?
KIM: You know me.
Why would I have
champagne glasses?
Or a giant stuffed panda?
I heard that.
(CHUCKLES)
Inappropriate, huh?
Well, I mean...
not if I was 7.
I can return it...
or you can hang on to it
until you have
a 7-year-old of your own.
Not funny.
(DOOR OPENS)
JIMY: Hey, baby. Babe?
Hey!
Hey, look who's here.
Mr. Mills.
Hello, Jimy.
How are you?
Good. You?
You know. Hey.
Hi.
Hey, if you guys are having
a father-daughter moment,
I can really...
No, no, no.
I just dropped by.
I thought I'd do
something unpredictable.
Kim's always pointing out
how predictable I am.
That's funny
coming from her.
You wanna talk
about predictable?
I'm not predictable!
Oh, come on.
Every single day...
she goes to
the same exact store,
right off campus,
every morning
before class...
and gets the same
peach yogurt drink.
Stop.
The fourth one
from the back.
Not the fifth one,
not the third one.
The fourth one
will stay cold,
but not too cold.
That way,
when she's drinking it, uh,
as a snack
in between classes...
It's still cold.
I know. I would do
exactly the same thing.
Yeah, the OCD gene.
JIMY: (LAUGHS) Uh...
What's with the bubbly?
Uh, pre-birthday
celebration.
If you don't mind,
I just think
it's a little early
to pop open a bottle.
Yeah, no problem.
I'll put it in the fridge.
What's that?
Whoa. A panda.
That was awesome.
I'll leave you two.
Dad, don't...
You don't have to take it.
Now I feel bad.
Yeah, you should
feel bad.
I'll exchange it for
something more predictable.
Love you.
Take it easy, Jimy.
Bye.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLEARS THROAT) Hey, babe.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Are you sure, babe?
Mmm-hmm.
Stop. Stop.
I just need
a second, okay?
You might want
to buckle up, Phillip.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Bryan.
How did it go?
Great. Fantastic.
Couldn't have gone better.
The panda was not a hit,
I take it.
Careful what you say.
He's sitting
right next to me.
When did she grow up, Lenore?
I know. It goes so fast.
All of it.
Where are you?
Just going home.
Make a little dinner.
If you'd like to join us.
"Us"?
Me and the panda.
I'll, uh, take
a rain check on that.
If that's okay with you?
And the panda?
That's fine by us.
I'll see you.
See you.
I know what you're thinking.
Keep it to yourself.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Oh, God.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey.
Lennie.
You changed your mind!
Yeah. Uh, you left
the door open.
Come on in.
Okay.
I'm not intruding?
No, of course you're not.
I was just preparing
dinner. Drink?
Yes, please.
Thanks for coming over.
Cheers.
You look stressed.
Yeah.
What?
Stuart and I...
We've tried everything.
Therapy. Counseling.
Together, separately.
He wants it to work.
He really does.
And you?
I know I'm hurting him.
I just don't feel
anything anymore.
I hate that.
I hate not feeling.
I hate going through
the motions.
The only thing
I feel is trapped.
(CHUCKLES) I have
the worst taste in men!
Thanks.
Oh, no.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
No, not you.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Do you know what
I fantasize about?
I'm afraid to ask.
Us.
Yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
And right after...
the guilt comes roaring in
and I feel like such a shit.
Does it make me
a bad person...
being married to one man,
fantasizing about another?
Confused maybe. Bad? No.
You must think I'm crazy.
If you are, Lennie,
you're not the only one.
Oh, Lennie.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's me that should be
apologizing.
It's not that
I don't want to.
Believe me.
But until you and Stuart
clear up your situation...
I think it would do
more harm than good.
For all of us.
(SCOFFS) Why do you have
to be so damn honorable?
Believe me, right now,
I wish I weren't.
Uh, I'm gonna go.
Wait.
Here.
I'm going out of town
in a couple of days
for a month on a job.
If you ever feel
you need to go someplace...
just to be by yourself...
use it.
Thank you.
BERNIE: I put on
six pounds of muscle.
Oh, you guys are
giving me a hard time.
CASEY: Well, it's not
helping your stroke.
BERNIE: You were
plus two on the last one.
You?
Me?
Did the rest of you
get on the green?
SAM: I'm not even
on the green.
But seriously, it's money.
It would be fun.
I know.
I can't go, Sam.
It's a four-man job.
We can't do it without you.
I know. But a couple
of things have come up...
and I'm not comfortable being
away for a month right now.
Kim?
It's not Kim.
Man, you gotta let this go.
You do.
Lenore's a grown woman.
She can take care of herself.
You're not her
husband any longer.
But she is my friend.
I think you better talk
to somebody about this.
A shrink, maybe.
Why would I go to a shrink
when I got you guys?
(SCOFFS)
There's a good point.
BERNIE: Can somebody
drop the flag stick?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
BRYAN: Hey, Kim.
What's up?
You want me to take it out?
If you wouldn't mind.
Sure. When?
Okay, baby.
SAM: Okay.
The big moment.
BRYAN: That's a good shot.
(SAM GASPS)
(ALL EXCLAIM)
This is an
unexpected treat.
Yeah, I, um,
need some advice.
Okay, shoot.
Um...
I guess it's not something
I was really planning on...
or even thought about, ever.
Anyway, I just
wanted your advice.
I'm flattered.
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Whoa. (LAUGHS)
Poor lady.
That is going to be serious
trouble in a few years.
You mark my words.
What was it
you wanted to ask?
KIM: Um...
A puppy.
A puppy?
Yeah.
I was thinking
about getting a puppy.
From where?
Um...
My friend found one
behind her building...
and we were trying
to find it a home...
we put it on Facebook,
but nobody
claimed it yet, so...
You wanna know
what I think?
Yeah.
I mean, it's a lot of work.
It's a lot of
responsibility.
With your lifestyle
the way it is at the
moment, with college.
With a puppy
you have to be there
all the time
and feed it, walk it.
It's no different
than having a kid.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Have you had a chance
to look at the menus?
Uh, not yet, Annie.
What will I have?
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
Stuart.
Hey, Bryan.
What are you
doing here?
Um...
Everything all right?
Yeah. It's fine.
Can I talk to you inside?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I was just making some coffee.
Milk?
Sugar?
STUART: Um, both, please.
Okay.
Milk, cold or hot?
Uh...
Hot, please.
So, how's business?
Oh, you know.
Some days good,
some days great.
Yeah.
One sugar or two?
Um...
Two, please.
Here we go.
Thanks.
Um...
I'm sorry to
bother you this late...
but I thought it was more,
um, respectful...
to say what
I have to say to you
face-to-face,
man-to-man.
So to speak.
I know that Lenore has...
She's spoken to you about the
problems that we've been having.
Um...
You're a good guy, Bryan.
I like you.
You're a respectful guy.
And, listen, I'm not
accusing you of anything.
But Lenore and I...
if our marriage
is gonna work... (SCOFFS)
that can't happen
with you in between us.
But, Stuart...
there's nothing
between Lenore and I,
other than we share Kim.
I didn't say there was.
Obviously...
you share a daughter...
and, uh, you've tried to be
the best father that you can,
under the circumstances.
And, uh, part of that
means the two of you
talking and staying in touch.
But I still want you
to stop seeing my wife.
Until we sort things out.
Does she know you're here?
It doesn't matter
if she does,
or if she doesn't.
That's not the point.
I'm asking you
to stop seeing my wife.
Can you do that?
I can do that.
(EXHALES) Wow.
That's great.
Thank you.
I gotta go to Vegas tonight.
Some business
meeting tomorrow.
I really don't want to be
worrying about...
you know.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
BRYAN: "Need to see you.
Urgent. Bagels."
(BEEPS)
Uh, four bagels and some
cream cheese, please.
Okay.
Be careful.
They're really hot.
Thanks.
Have a good day. Thanks.
Take care.
BRYAN: Hello?
Lennie?
(SCRAPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Lennie?
Lennie.
Jesus, God.
Lennie? Wake up!
Come on, come on!
Lennie!
Freeze! Don't move!
Step away
from the knife.
Get your hands up!
Sir, back away, now.
I didn't do this.
COP 1: Get your
hands up, now!
Slowly.
Get your hands up.
You gotta listen to me.
On the floor, now!
Listen to me.
Down on the floor!
Step away
from the knife!
COP 1: On your knees. Now!
COP 2: Down!
COP 1: Get your hands up!
Hands up!
Hands up! Higher!
BRYAN: I didn't do this.
(GRUNTS)
(COPS GROANING)
COP 3: Shit! Moving in!
(GRUNTS)
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
COP 4: He's there!
(PANTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Hey! Hey!
Drop your weapon!
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
(GRUNTS)
COP 5: Oh, he's heading west!
(BARKING)
He's heading north.
22nd street. Back alley.
Stop!
(GUNSHOT)
(GRUNTS)
COP 5: Suspect in sight.
(WOMAN GASPING)
COP 4: Go inside.
I'm heading back.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
Hey!
Hey! Police!
(GRUNTS) Door's sealed!
I just saw him inside.
COP 6: Shit!
Clear! Moving in!
COP 4: You see him anywhere?
He disappeared.
God damn it.
He's gone.
This is 103.
Suspect is gone.
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yeah.
BRYAN: (OVER PHONE)
Kim, it's Dad.
Where are you?
I'm at Mom's.
Looking for my
yellow sweater.
Are you alone?
Stuart is in Vegas. Why?
I have something
to tell you.
Dad?
(SIGHS)
Dad, what's wrong?
Something terrible
has happened.
And I want you
to hear it from me first.
Your mom...
She's dead.
Someone murdered her...
in my apartment.
It looks like I did it.
I don't know why.
I don't know who.
But I'm going
to find out.
Listen carefully, Kim.
No matter what anyone says,
don't trust them.
No.
You hear?
I'll find a way
to contact you.
But Dad...
Try to be strong.
Dad?
I love you.
Wait.
(DIAL TONE HUMMING)
(SIGHS)
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
Sergeant Dotzler,
suspect's name is Bryan Mills.
His?
His.
Not his.
The officers arrived
on the scene because...?
Anonymous call came in,
reported a woman
screaming...
"He's killing me.
He's killing me."
Her name is
Lenore St. John.
We sent a car to her address.
It was listed on her license.
Her daughter was there,
but her husband was in
Las Vegas on business.
He's, uh, taking
the first flight home.
Any witnesses?
We're canvassing now.
Call came from
an unlisted number.
We're checking out
the cells as well.
Download both of the phones,
correlate the data.
I want to know
when these two people...
spoke, texted, emailed.
Every form of communication.
Dates, times...
duration of calls.
DOTZLER: Let's bag this.
OFFICER: Detective, bag that.
What's wrong?
Good.
FEMALE REPORTER:
Right now, this is still
a very active crime scene.
Investigators have been here
on the scene
all morning, but so far...
police have not told us what
happened inside the apartment...
where earlier this morning...
a woman's body was discovered.
Bryan Mills is the owner
of the apartment...
and the ex-husband
of the deceased.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Who's this?
BRYAN: It's me.
You're on the news.
I didn't do it, Sam.
Obviously, you didn't do it.
Are you all right?
I'm going down
the rabbit hole.
The code still the same?
Yeah. It's still the same.
I'll be in touch.
Be careful.
So, this is the area
we lost him, sir.
The guy vanished.
Uh, that's the gun
that he took, uh, off
one of our officers, sir.
He had a gun,
and he didn't fire at you?
No, sir.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
And the helicopters...
saw nothing?
Choppers didn't see
anything, sir. No.
I know he's good...
but...
vanishing into thin air?
Let's move the truck.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(EXHALES)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
Do you know why your wife
went to visit Mr. Mills?
No, I don't know.
Their relationship
was mostly centered
around their daughter.
Um, but I think...
he wanted more
than friendship.
I asked her
to speak to him...
and tell him that he should
stop bothering her about it.
So you think that's what
she was doing over there?
(SNIFFLING) I don't know.
What are you doing?
Stuart, why are they going
through all of Mom's stuff?
Hey, Kim.
Miss St. John,
Frank Dotzler.
Mills.
My name is Mills.
Sorry for all the chaos.
We're just
looking around
to see if we can find
something to help us.
I know what
you're looking for.
I would just really like
them out of her bedroom
for a few minutes.
Garcia, let's vacate
the bedroom.
Everybody
out of the bedroom.
Thank you.
If I could just have
a few minutes
of your time.
Ask you a few questions.
Why aren't you out there trying
to find out who did this...
instead of just
standing around,
going through our home?
We have people
out there looking.
But in order for me
to get a full picture...
I have to ask
questions of him.
questions of you.
My mom went to see my dad.
I don't know why.
Probably to talk about me.
Look, there's just...
(SOBBING)
He didn't do it.
He just didn't.
There's no way on earth
he would lay a hand on her.
Just, don't.
He loved her.
That's all I know.
Please.
That's mine.
That's not even hers.
Excuse me.
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(SOBBING)
(GASPS)
(SOBBING) I'm sorry.
Oh, God.
Come on,
let's get you home.
If something comes to mind,
anything at all...
it might not be
anything.
Um, you know what
happened in Paris
and Istanbul
a couple years ago...
where Bryan
saved his family.
Sure. You think
that's connected to this?
I never really wanted
to know all the details...
but a lot of people ended
up dead and now this.
So what you're
telling me is...
I'm dealing with
a very dangerous man.
No.
No. Bryan's not dangerous.
The world
he lives in is.
He loves his family...
but he has
a lot of enemies.
I see.
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
FEMALE DOCTOR:
Bring him into Room Three.
DOTZLER: Garcia will, uh,
get you back home.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
DOTZLER: This guy's a ghost.
At 21, he's in the army.
At 23, he joins
Special Forces.
Then he's gone.
No service record.
No discharge.
Nothing. Nothing.
Sounds like spy shit to me.
Until we have another suspect,
he's our man.
So here's our best way
of finding him.
His daughter
with the deceased.
Her husband says that
he's really close to her.
Devoted to her.
So let's keep
a close watch on her.
Where she goes,
who she calls,
who she talks to.
Let's not screw
this up, okay?
So, this is gonna be
our best shot...
at finding him.
Do we have
the deceased's car?
Yeah, that just came in.
They have his, too.
All right. Garcia, Smith.
Let's do a full
sweep of the car.
GPS downloaded,
see where he went and when.
See if they correlate.
See if we can find out
what's going on.
Just came in, his and hers.
Let's go, then.
Follow me.
IMPOUND TECHNICIAN:
So, what's this about?
GARCIA: Some guy
offed his ex.
SMITH: Allegedly.
Right. Allegedly.
He didn't do her
in the car, did he?
No, in his house.
IMPOUND TECHNICIAN: Good.
I hate going in those after.
Blood. Pieces of flesh
and shit.
It's disgusting.
Which GPS
you want done first?
His, then hers.
IMPOUND TECHNICIAN:
Right over here.
What the hell
were you doing
all the way
out there, Lenore?
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Excuse me.
Inspector Mallory, LAPD.
We're following up on a missing
persons investigation.
I was wondering
if you'd seen this woman.
Nope.
She was here
about 10 p.m. last night.
I was here then.
I didn't see her.
I didn't see hardly nobody.
Not exactly
a bustling destination,
if you know what I mean.
MAN: Hey, Sally.
WAITRESS: Excuse me.
Duty calls.
WAITRESS: Amanda?
Excuse me.
Inspector Mallory, LAPD.
Are these security
cameras operative...
or are they
just there for show?
Yeah, they work.
Follow me.
You have the tape
from yesterday?
I wasn't here.
The other guy was.
But if someone was here,
it will be on there.
Just push that button
for the playback.
I'm just gonna stay here
while you look at that.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
You have problems
with this system?
MAN: Breaks down sometimes.
They keep saying
they're gonna replace it.
GARCIA: Excuse me.
Have you seen
this woman?
(SCOFFS)
You fellas should get
more coordinated.
Coordinated?
What do you mean?
Like, color-coordinated?
No, like, one of your guys
was just in here
asking the same thing.
One of our guys?
Yeah.
Him?
Yeah. Him.
Took off
to the gas station.
Shh.
(CLATTERING)
Freeze!
Mr. Mills?
GARCIA: Step out, buddy.
SMITH: Get out of the room.
GARCIA: Freeze!
Stop what you're doing,
Mr. Mills!
Step away from the desk!
SMITH: Back away
from the desk, sir.
Step away from that desk,
or I'll shoot you!
SMITH: Back away
from the goddamn desk!
Now!
Step away one step
from the desk.
Just keep your hands
where we can see them.
Stay perfectly still.
(HANDCUFFS RATTLING)
SMITH: You know the drill.
Anything you say
can and will be
used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney...
to have one present
during questioning.
(CONTINUES TALKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(PHONE RINGS)
Brooks. All right.
BROOKS: Garcia and Smith.
They got him.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Garcia.
Yeah, just picked him up.
Easy-peasy.
If he's a pro
like you said...
he wasn't on his game today.
He's playing you!
What are you talking about?
Where is he?
He's back
in Phillips' car. Why?
Stop the cars!
What?
Now!
SMITH: Oh, come on!
Phillips.
Yeah?
GARCIA: (OVER RADIO)
Our boss has got a hair
up his ass about something.
Just keep an eye
on this guy, all right?
Yeah, okay.
JOHNSON: They think we're idiots.
PHILLIPS: It's unbelievable.
He acts like I've never
done this before.
He's just being Dotzler.
You know what it is?
He's a control freak.
If he's not doing it himself,
he's not happy.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
(YELLS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Keep driving!
Phillips!
Come on.
What the hell is he doing?
(HONKING)
Pull it over!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Back it up!
Get out of the car!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Drive!
Stop the car.
Come on, move.
Radio.
Cell phone.
This is gonna
end bad for you.
Don't be such a pessimist.
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Connecting to LAPD
protected files.
PILOT: (OVER RADIO)
All units, code 10-29
on a police car number 706.
Number 706.
OFFICER: Suspect in sight.
(SIREN WAILING)
Here, here!
(COPS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Send some backup, now!
(GROANING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(BEEPS)
Dotzler.
By now, I'm sure
you know who I am.
You know
what I'm capable of.
I am beginning to.
Let me ask you something,
just so I'm clear.
CIA operative?
Division 6?
Division 7? What?
All you have to know
is I'm innocent.
Give me two days,
I can prove it.
I can find out who did it.
You may very well
be innocent, Mr. Mills.
But that's the court's job
to decide, it's not mine.
My job...
is to bring you in and let the
law take its course, that's it.
Good luck.
(BEEPS)
I got a GPS on the phone.
He's heading north.
You want me
to send units?
Don't bother.
He's gone.
It's a dead end.
Wait, wait.
Why does he want us
to have this?
He fucked up.
This guy doesn't fuck up.
He wants us to watch it.
GARCIA: Why?
I don't know yet.
Who is she waiting for?
Who are these guys?
Holy shit!
Give me our tech guy.
I need some magic done
on a security tape.
Now. Right now.
SAM: Hey, let me guess.
Pileup on the 710 North.
Massive clusterfuck
of police vehicles...
15 miles headed south.
Sounds about right.
Hey, thanks, Sam.
You want to tell me
what's going on?
Lenore sent me a text.
Asked to come over
to my place for bagels.
I got the bagels.
When I came back,
I found her car out front.
Um...
She was in my bed
with her throat slashed.
Oh, Jesus.
What else?
I found a location
on her car's GPS
from the night before.
She was out at this gas station
in the middle of nowhere.
I saw it
on a security camera.
She was snatched.
What do you
want us to do?
I downloaded
all her phone records
from the police files.
And mine.
Maybe there's
something there.
I need analysis of this.
Her hair.
Might turn up something,
might turn up nothing.
Anything else?
I want to go
to the funeral.
PASTOR: The Bible
constantly tells us...
that there will be
difficult times in life...
when we feel like
we are walking...
through a dark,
dangerous valley.
Valley of the shadow
of death.
But what the word of God
does make very clear...
is that, as we move
through such times...
"the Lord is my shepherd.
"He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures.
(OVER SPEAKER)
"He leadeth me
beside still waters. "
In the name
of the Father...
and of the Son...
and of the Holy Spirit.
CASEY: Are you holding up?
Right there.
MAN: Mmm-hmm.
Get me sound on that.
Right there.
Kim, I'm so sorry.
If there's
anything we can do...
Hey.
BERNIE: We're there for you.
You know that, right?
KIM: Mmm-hmm.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
KIM: I just want to go home.
(JIMY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(STATIC)
You hear that?
You hear that click?
Yeah. We're getting some
interference somewhere.
(SOBBING)
(BEEPING)
There it goes again.
KIM: Hey.
Hi.
Oh, sweetie.
They're jamming our signal.
I know.
I'm so, so sorry.
Listen.
He'll be in touch.
Just stick
to your schedule.
Your very
predictable schedule.
You want me to
put a tail on them?
No, it's a waste of time.
It'd be a waste of our money.
These guys could lose a tail
if it was attached to a dog.
We're done.
Cut the feed.
Stuart,
why are there still...
Why are there still
cops camped outside?
Uh, I think it's standard
operating procedure.
They think my dad's
going to show up here?
Are they stupid or something?
I don't know
what they think.
Inspector Dotzler asked
if we minded and I said no.
You should have asked me.
I mind.
I'm sorry.
And who's he?
STUART: Well, um...
We need protection.
Kim, honey,
I know it's hard on you,
but it's hard on me, too.
I'm sorry. I didn't realize
it was a competition.
(CHUCKLES)
It's not a competition.
Please, don't hate me.
I'm not responsible
for what happened.
I don't hate you, Stuart.
But for the last two years...
every time I looked
into my mom's eyes...
the only thing I saw
was hurt and sadness.
And for that...
I do hold you responsible.
Where are you going?
School
If I'm allowed.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
(DISTORTED MUSIC)
I got you, baby.
I got you.
Hmm.
Why are you following me?
It's for your
own protection, miss.
Protection?
From who?
My father?
You really think
my father would hurt me?
Your mother probably
didn't think so either.
Asshole.
(CHUCKLES)
(BELL DINGS)
Hey.
MAN: Hey.
Anything?
GARCIA: She's on campus.
You want me to follow?
Is the bug active?
Yes.
Okay. Stay there. Listen.
If he shows up,
we'll hear it.
What else?
She went into this
convenience store,
chugged down
a drink of some kind...
right from the fridge.
All right.
Keep me informed.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
PROFESSOR: As you might
remember, last week...
we discussed
disassociations...
and interactions between
dorsal and ventral streams...
(OVER SPEAKER)
in object recognition.
Now, a dominant hypothesis...
(SCOFFS)
is that the dorsal stream
is supporting
motor interactions
with objects.
While ventral stream
structures extract
visual information...
about the object
that is independent.
(WHISPERING)
I'm feeling
a little nauseous.
Would you mind
taking notes for me?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
PROFESSOR: Now,
in other words,
object knowledge
is represented
in the ventral stream...
(HUFFS)
Excuse me.
I wonder if you could, um,
help me out with something?
Sure.
There was a young woman
in here...
about an hour ago?
Oh, yeah.
Poor kid.
Does she come here often?
Every day.
She bought what?
Same thing,
a peach yogurt drink.
But today, she drank it all
right there from the fridge.
Must have been thirsty.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
You got anything?
GARCIA: (OVER PHONE)
Yeah, she went to school.
Got nauseous in class.
Now she's on her way
to the bathroom.
Call for back-up.
I'm coming right now.
(SIREN WAILING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
Shh!
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(STATIC)
Shh.
Here, Kim. Drink this.
I put something in the yogurt
to make you nauseous.
This will take it away.
Hi, baby.
Hi.
Oh, Kim. Kim.
(SOBBING)
Oh, Kim.
Daddy. I don't know
what to do.
I'm pregnant.
What?
Dad?
I'm okay.
I have low blood sugar.
I haven't eaten
since yesterday.
Um...
Eat this.
Don't you worry.
Let's get through
this first and then...
we'll figure out
what's best for...
What you have to do
is act natural.
This cop is really smart.
Anything out of the usual...
he'll become suspicious.
Okay?
I love you.
I love you, too.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
(LINE RINGING)
GARCIA: (OVER PHONE) Yes.
Where are you?
I'm in the science building.
East wing.
She's in the bathroom.
Don't move.
Wait for me.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
Where are you staying?
I'm still at Mom's.
I started packing her stuff.
It doesn't feel real.
Oh, I know.
I know.
(GIRL LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Dad, there's...
Stuart's been acting
really weird.
He must be scared
about something.
He hired bodyguards.
(DOOR OPENS)
(ems LAUGHING)
GIRL 1: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
It was so much fun.
But you know what?
He was such a jerk.
GIRL 1: Really?
GIRL 2: He made me pay for
my own drink at the bar.
I was wearing something
more skimpy than this.
More skimpy than that?
I don't know
what was happening.
GIRL 1: Maybe he's blind.
I don't know.
GIRL 2: I don't know.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
GIRL 2: He is such a jerk.
I'm not gonna do
it again, though.
GIRL 1: No, it's cool,
I've seen him.
I completely understand.
GIRL 2: He's hot, right?
(SIGHS)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
GIRL 2: Go, go, go!
GIRL 1: I'm going!
GIRL 2: Go, go, go.
(GRUNTS)
What the...?
Excuse me?
Perv!
He just left.
She's in the can.
I can't let you leave.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
Seal all the areas.
Hey!
(GROANS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
There he is.
Down the south corridor!
Freeze!
(FIRE ALARM RINGING)
(STUDENTS CLAMORING)
Go, go, go!
(STUDENTS SCREAMING)
(MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY)
Move!
MAN 1: Just move! Come on!
MAN 2: This way!
Move, move!
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(SIREN WAILING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
I know you think
you're helping him...
but you're not.
You're not.
Unless we get him
to come in...
I can't start trying to make
sense of what happened.
Someone killed my mom.
That's what happened.
It was not my father.
Without hearing
his side of the story,
they can't know that,
can they?
I do.
Is there anything else?
You know we can arrest you
for obstructing
an ongoing investigation?
Arrest me.
Rather not.
Well, then,
if you're not going to,
can I go home?
Of course. Of course.
Thank you.
Interesting family.
MALANKOV: (OVER PHONE)
Don't worry,
we will take care of this.
Do as we planned.
Call the car.
BODYGUARD:
Where are we going, boss?
STUART: The Malibu house.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Okay, let's go get drunk.
(WHISTLING TUNE)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER STEREO)
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I need a ride.
Mind if I drive?
Okay.
What's your name?
Mike.
I'm Bryan.
You have kids, Mike?
Yeah, two.
Uh-huh.
How old?
Owen is three,
and Tori is seven.
Great age.
A piece of advice.
Don't miss a day of it.
Before you know it,
they'll be having
kids of their own.
Know what I mean?
BRYAN: Thanks, Mike.
Uh-huh.
You know,
if you stand in a field
with a book of matches...
you can have hundreds
of rabbits in seconds...
like this.
You know how?
No.
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(LAUGHING)
Come in, all rabbits.
You like this?
(GROANS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GUN CLICKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
Who hired you?
(PANTING)
Huh?
(BRYAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Who are you working for?
(SCOFFS) Your accent is shit!
I'd rather die than tell you.
Scumbag!
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMS)
(EXHALES)
Boss?
They're at the gate.
Let them in.
Oh, and take a stroll.
I need a little privacy.
(DOOR BUZZES)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(THUDDING)
Many?
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(GROANS)
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTS)
Oh! (GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WATER SPLASHING)
Bryan?
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(SPUTTERING)
(COUGHING)
None of this is making
sense to me, Stuart.
I was hoping
you could help me out.
How did you...
Survive the crash?
The Russians
who were following me
when I was following you...
do they work
for you, Stuart?
(STAMMERS) No.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
What do you know?
The only thing I know is that
you were fucking my wife.
And I know
that she's dead!
No, no, no!
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(COUGHING)
What do you know?
I don't know anything.
I swear.
If I believed that,
we wouldn't be here.
No! No! No!
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED) Malankov,
Malankov, Malankov!
What?
(SPUTTERING) Malankov.
Oleg Malankov.
Who is Oleg Malankov?
I owe him money.
You don't know him.
He'll never give up.
It's only a game for him.
I lost everything.
He said he'd kill my family.
Why didn't you tell
this to the police?
You let them
think it was me.
I was angry with you.
God damn it, you promised!
You promised
to stop seeing her!
So what do you
think happened?
She came over to my place.
This Malankov
followed her there?
If you weren't seeing her
behind my back...
she wouldn't have been there
in the first place, would she?
They would have killed her
someplace else.
So why are they
coming after me?
Because I told them
who you were.
That you would find them
and kill them.
How convenient
would that be for you?
I kill them,
your debt is cancelled.
(SOBBING) I'm sorry, Bryan.
But I loved her.
You gotta believe me.
I loved her!
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna go to the police
and tell them everything.
I can't.
I can't. He's crazy.
You don't know him.
You can do whatever
the hell you want.
Either way...
I'm a dead man.
I'm dead.
They kill you,
they don't get paid.
You're not the one they're
gonna come after next.
Kim.
(SIGHS)
SAM: Hey.
Can I get
your keys, please?
Do you know what you're
getting yourself into, man?
Yeah. As a matter
of fact, I do.
Could I get your keys
and your phone, please?
BERNIE: You mind putting your
hands on the steering wheel?
(SCOFFS) Or what?
What are you gonna do?
Shoot me?
(GUN COCKS)
Left or right?
Go ahead, put the cuffs on.
(SIGHS)
Thank you very much.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(CLAN KING)
(GRUNTS)
(MUGS CLATTERING)
(CREAKING)
Dad!
Let's go, Kim.
What's going on?
We're keeping you safe.
KIM: Sam?
Hey, Kim. We're gonna
get in the truck.
CASEY: Hi, Kim.
Let's go.
DOTZLER: Bernard Harris.
He's a trained sniper.
Left the army at 24.
Nothing, nothing after that.
Nothing until he registers
as one of three founders
of something called Private
Securities International.
The other two being,
Casey Mark,
Navy SEAL,
eight years' service.
"Explosives expert."
It's right there.
Next time we hear
from him, he's 45
and Senior Vice President
of Private Securities
International.
Sam Grossman,
communications expert,
a wizard,
And he's the COO of Private
Securities International.
Now, our primary person
of interest...
Bryan Mills.
Is listed as an "employee"
of Private...
You get the picture.
(SIGHS)
These are very
serious people.
If you don't
bring your A-game,
they're gonna run around you,
through you, under you.
I need it to stop
right now.
There's one more thing.
This.
The Russian,
he killed himself.
Probably because he didn't
wanna give up the information
that Mills was
asking him for.
Because obviously,
he's not trying to kill you.
Obviously, he's not
trying to kill anybody.
He's only trying
to get information.
He's only trying to figure
this out, just like we are.
Except for the fact that
he is a step ahead of us.
I'd like to know the relationship
between the Russians
and the wife's murder.
One of these four people,
they know something about it.
They know the answer.
I need you guys
to find them.
I need you
to bring them in.
BRYAN: Anything yet?
SAM: No.
Nothing came up from the
samples you gave me.
But this is gonna take
a while to sort through.
Bryan, there's a shitload
of data here.
STUART: What is that?
I downloaded
the police computers.
For what?
BRYAN: The first thing
they're gonna look at...
are the phone records to see
if there are any clues.
Mine and Lenore's.
What's it gonna tell you,
that you and Lenore
spoke to each other?
You know what?
Don't worry about it.
We're almost
done here anyway.
So, what's the plan?
The plan is to make sure
my daughter is safe.
And the only way
to do that, so it seems...
is to eliminate the thing
that will make her unsafe.
Malankov.
Good one, Stuart.
I'd like to help.
CASEY: Oh, you're
gonna help, all right.
Like bait helps
to catch a shark.
Excuse me?
BRYAN: Start talking
about Malankov.
I want to know every detail.
Who he is, what he does,
where he lives...
where he works.
(SIGHS)
Oleg Malankov.
He's as tough
as they come.
He served in the Russian Army
when they invaded
Afghanistan.
(GRUNTING)
He was Spetsnaz.
It's like our Navy SEALS.
After the collapse
of the Soviet Union,
when everyone was
grabbing what they could...
there was a real demand
for men with
his kind of skills.
He became
one of the grabbers.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(ALL SCREAMING)
STUART: I met him
when I was doing a deal
involving heavy machinery.
Since then,
we did business
on a number
of different occasions.
Some deals worked out.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I don't have the money.
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
Last one didn't.
What?
My mom is dead because of one
of your shitty business deals?
No.
Kim, that's not
what happened.
Fuck you!
I'll fucking kill you!
Kim.
BRYAN: We need him.
We need him.
Call him.
Why?
Because you're gonna
set him up for me.
Make the call. Now.
On speaker.
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
Pow.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Stuart. I've missed you.
I have your money.
You have it?
That was fast.
How can I trust you?
You can trust me.
Where do you want me
to bring it?
Meet me at the building
downtown.
In one hour.
Sure, one hour.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Scumbag!
Tell me how
his security works.
STUART: Malankov works out
of his penthouse apartment.
He has a private elevator
with two bodyguards.
Malankov is coming.
Send the elevator.
STUART:
The elevator is controlled
by security upstairs.
Once they see who's inside the
elevator and give the okay...
they will send
the elevator up.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
STUART: Outside the elevator,
upstairs...
is a security station
and three more bodyguards.
Two sets of doors.
Through the second set
of doors
is Malankov's
private apartment.
SAM: Can you
help me out, here?
I got an address
but I don't have a name.
I got a back
full of perishables.
Go to the first floor
and ask for the desk.
First floor.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Hello, sir.
STUART: I'm here to see
Oleg Malankov.
Okay, sir,
have a good day.
Thanks.
BRYAN: Get out.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
It's Dotzler.
Answer it. Act normal.
Don't try
anything smart.
Hello?
DOTZLER: Mr. St. John?
Frank Dotzler.
Where are you?
Um, I'm in
a business meeting.
Is there anything wrong?
Bryan Mills removed your
stepdaughter from your home.
I'm there right now.
STUART: Oh, my God.
That's, um...
When are you coming home?
I'm leaving immediately.
It should take me
about an hour to
get there from where I am.
Where exactly is that?
Malibu.
Listen, Inspector,
I don't think he
means her any harm.
Mr. St. John, this man
is the prime suspect
in the murder of your wife.
His associates
held guns on my men
in the front of your home.
As far as I'm concerned,
he is dangerous
and has to be
taken into custody.
So, if you'd like,
I can send a car for you,
but I need you
somewhere safe.
No, no, no.
It's fine.
I'm leaving right now.
I'll be waiting for you.
Get me a location
on St. John's phone.
SAM: As soon as he finds
out you're not in Malibu,
he'll be headed right here.
I'd say we have
less than 30 minutes to do
this before he shows up.
It's enough time for me.
Can you handle this, Kim?
What do I have to do?
Just keep me up to
date on what comes up.
Thanks, Sam.
Inspector, the tape you gave
us from that gas station...
here are the stills,
frame by frame.
GARCIA: Hey.
He lied to you
about where he was.
What a surprise.
He's downtown.
Let's call out
the cavalry.
All right.
DOTZLER: We're out
of this location!
We're on the move!
Let's go!
They're gone.
Okay. Cops on the move.
Okay. Let's go.
You do exactly
as you were told.
Don't improvise.
Try anything funny,
and they'll kill you.
And if they don't, I will.
I don't know how many times
I can say sorry.
Come here, Kim.
There.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Dotzler.
I found out something
you might wanna know.
Matching insurance policies
on St. John and his wife.
$12 million. Each.
How about that?
Stuart St. John.
Mr. Malankov's expecting me.
MAN: What's in the bag?
We're in.
Okay.
Stuart St. John is clear.
Unlock the elevator.
(BEEPS)
(ELEVATOR tunes)
Okay.
Got him.
Go! All right.
(GUARD SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
What's going on?
Everything okay?
(MAN 1 SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
MAN 2: Mmm-hmm.
Call the elevator.
(MAN LAUGHING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(YELLS)
Get back to the truck.
Bingo.
Right on.
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
Mmm.
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
He's coming up.
Go, go, go.
Showtime. Bingo.
What the hell's going on?
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GUNSHOT)
Guys?
(BEEPS)
Go check it out.
(MAN YELLING IN RUSSIAN)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT)
(GUN CLICKS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MAN YELLING)
(STRAINING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MAN GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(PANTING)
Get up.
Get up!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(PANTING)
Who are you, old man?
You killed my ex-wife.
(SCREAMS)
But you're not gonna
kill my daughter.
Your daughter?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Shit!
We are fucked
by the same man.
What are you talking about?
Stuart St. John.
First, he gets me
to kill your wife...
then you.
And when that
doesn't work...
he pushes you
to kill me, no?
Either way, he wins.
Your wife was just
part of a business deal...
like many before her.
It is my turn
to lose the game.
Finish me!
Finish me.
I deserve it.
Yes.
You do.
Dad?
Listen.
SAM: What is it, Kim?
No!
Ahhh!
Sam! Sam!
Kim.
Come on. Let's go.
STUART: Come on. Move.
Kim!
(GRUNTS)
Get in the car!
Let's go, come on!
Where are we going?
Get in the car.
(SIREN WAILING)
(FEMALE DISPATCHER
TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(BEEPS)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
He's still alive.
Let's get a medic in here...
SMITH: (OVER RADIO)
ASAP! Medic!
Inspector!
SMITH: Yeah?
The elevator!
Dotzler, it's Smith.
We're in Malankov's building.
I think, uh, Mills is here.
Really?
Yeah. We're gonna check
the apartment now.
(SIREN WAILING)
Shit!
Hey! Can you move?
Back it up.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
All right, let's go.
Everybody in.
Come on!
Let's go!
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
This guy's still warm.
We got a good chance
he's still in the building.
Call downstairs,
lock it up.
Nobody in, nobody out.
COP: Lock it up.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
(BEEPS)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
BRYAN: "Text from your phone
asking Mom to meet you...
"at the Rancho Berrego
the night she died.
"Someone used your phone?"
(ENGINE REVS)
(COPS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Call Dotzler!
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
WOMAN: (OVER PHONE)
Santa Monica Aviation.
This is Mr. St. John.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Get the plane ready.
It'll be ready.
Why are you doing this?
Because your father
and his friends
are homicidal maniacs.
You're a lying piece of shit.
Shut up.
You killed her! I know...
You shut up!
Shut up!
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Brooks.
I want the full work-up
on a black Porsche,
license plate number
6-8-9-M-J-C-6.
Okay.
Connect me to the Porsche
phone and trace it.
All right.
I need a run on
a California plate
6-8-9-Mary-Jane-Charlie-6.
I need a phone, too.
(RINGING)
Pick up the phone.
PILOT: Black Porsche's
phone position received.
Heading west.
(RINGING)
Yes?
Listen, Mr. Mills.
It's Dotzler.
I've started to piece
this thing together.
There's two
life insurance policies.
One for St. John,
one for your ex-wife.
You understand?
Stuart owed money
to these Russians.
A lot of it.
The ones who abducted her.
Then they took her
to my place
and killed her to
keep me out of the way.
I need you to step back...
and allow me to handle this.
I got it.
What's your first
priority here, Inspector?
To arrest St. John
and charge him
with your ex-wife's murder.
My first priority
is my daughter.
Get out of the car.
Come on, let's go.
Go!
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Okay, we're leaving now.
Come on, let's go.
PILOT 1: Yes, sir!
PILOT: Approaching
Runway Two.
Ready for takeoff.
Come on, guys.
Let's go.
PILOT: Requesting
permission for takeoff.
HELICOPTER PILOT:
We got a visual
on the Porsche.
He's heading to
Santa Monica airport.
(GPS BEEPING)
I want all units in the area
of the Santa Monica airport...
to be on the lookout
for a black Porsche.
(PILOTS SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
No.
Let's go!
Come on!
PILOT 1: We don't have enough speed!
Let's go!
STUART: Give me
the goddamn gun!
Give me the goddamn gun!
(KIM GRUNTS)
I'll shoot you
in the head!
Shut up!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Very smart...
Playing me off
against the Russian.
(GROANS)
Coming over for coffee.
Taking my phone,
sending texts
and then erasing them.
So that your pals...
could plant Lenore's body...
and make it look
as if I killed her.
All your problems solved.
All your worries over.
But it didn't quite
work out that way.
(PANTING)
STUART: Oh, listen, Bryan.
They're coming.
(LAUGHS)
You can't kill me now.
Oh. yeah?
(GRUNTS)
Dad...
I know you know
a lot of people...
and with a good lawyer,
you'll get out of jail
in a few years.
And then I'll come for you.
I'll find you.
And we both know
what's gonna happen.
(GROANS)
(SIREN WAILING)
(KIM SOBBING)
(BRYAN SIGHS)
DOTZLER: I knew
from the beginning.
It was the bagels.
They were warm.
I had to ask myself...
what kind of guy
goes out for warm bagels...
and comes back
and commits murder?
So, I compared the timestamps
to the deleted texts...
that you downloaded
from our computers.
Which, by the way,
is illegal, and I could
arrest you for it.
I could.
But it's got me.
And I was able
to figure it out.
She was leaving him.
He needed the insurance money
to pay Malankov.
You didn't help us out
by escaping, you know.
He figured,
what better way
to get rid of Malankov and
keep the insurance money...
than by getting me
to kill the guy
who would kill him...
because it was the only way
to keep my daughter safe.
Almost worked.
Almost.
So, are we done, Inspector?
Of course.
Of course we're done.
We're done.
Could you, um,
just stay in town
for the next month or so...
just in case I have any
other questions for you?
Sure.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(EXHALES)
BRYAN: Now, you two.
I've thought
about this all night.
It's a very
important choice.
Whatever you decide...
the two of you, together...
I'll support you 100%.
And I know your mom would have
said the same thing, too.
Tell him.
Dad...
we've been talking.
We thought that...
if it's a girl...
we'd like to
name her after mom.
She'd like that
very much, Kim.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SINGING)
Hot nights coming
Keep the car running
Lavender fingers
Swallow my pollen
Gold, I swam into your spell
On the rite of God we fell
You were plush and I laid bare
You had me howling
Cold, I fell into your skin
On the night
you led me under your sin
You had me howling
Golden siren
Under-exposing
Come lay your weakness down
On the floor in the backseat
Gold, I swam into your spell
On the rite of God we fell
You were plush and I laid bare
You had me howling
Cold, I fell into your skin
On the night
you led me under your sin
You had me howling
Ooh, ooh, blush