Seattle Today!
I am the captain
of the Pinafore!
And a right good captain too!
You're very, very good but...
It's almost ready, you guys.
We'll be right down.
...occasionally say...
I'm never, never sick at sea
- What never?
- No, never
- What, never?
- Well, hardly ever!
Michael!
Emma, stay right there.
What's the matter?
Claire, stay here.
Mommy?
Hey!
- Sorry.
- Hey, hey, hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing here?
- Mommy?
- It's okay, sweetheart.
This gentleman says
the Better Way Society sent him.
Better Day.
- Sorry. Better Day Society.
- Yeah.
Yeah. The Better Day Society
helps place
the mentally disabled with employment.
I live there.
Of course!
You're here to build the fence.
Yeah.
I tried knocking.
Solomon, right?
Rene Peterson told us
about the work you did.
I'm Claire
and this is my husband, Michael.
- Yeah, we met outside.
- And this is Emma.
Hello.
It's nice to make your acquaintance,
Emma.
I'm gonna throw some shoes on,
show Solomon around outside.
See if our guest would like
anything to drink. Okay?
My mom says to ask
if you want anything.
I'd like a brand-new bicycle
with a big basket on the handlebars
and some gears.
That sounds neat.
Okay, okay. I see.
You wanted to take away this?
Yeah.
The new fence should contain
the whole area here,
and the gate should be right there.
Do you want the fence
to keep people in,
or keep people out?
Well, both.
But mostly, it should keep people out.
Okay.
One,
two,
three,
five,
nine.
Just kidding.
I got a tape measure. See?
All right. Is everything all right out here?
Right as rain.
- Mrs. Bartel?
- That's me.
The doctor will see you now.
This is your first exam with Dr. Mott?
Yes, it is.
The doctor who delivered
my little girl retired.
Dr. Mott was kind enough
to take me on midterm.
He's one of the best.
Expecting his own, you know?
Really?
Take everything off,
put the gown on, open at the front.
Okay.
Doctor.
Mrs. Bartel!
- Hi.
- Hi. I'm Dr. Mott.
- It's nice to meet you.
So, how are we today?
Just great.
The baby's kicking up a storm all day.
This is your second child.
You're a pro at this, aren't you?
I see you have a history of asthma.
- Any problems?
- No, none at all.
Why don't we take a look? Feet up.
Okay.
I didn't think it was usual to give
pelvic exams after the third month.
We won't again until the 36th week.
But I want to make sure my new patients
have a full exam on their first visit.
It's Mrs. Miller.
She's calling again for the test results.
Go ahead and give them to her.
She's all clear.
If she has any questions,
I'll call her back.
Would you hold, please?
Maria, when you're in the lab,
call in the results
of yesterday's ViraPaps.
Yes, Doctor.
- Sorry about that.
- It's okay.
Why don't we start
with the breast exam?
Weather's been beautiful these days,
hasn't it?
It has. Yeah.
I love taking walks after the rainstorm.
It's very important to be able
to give yourself your own breast exams.
Relax.
Mrs. Bartel, we need to schedule
your next appointment.
- Claire?
- Michael!
- Honey, what's the matter?
- Michael.
Honey, what's wrong? Claire?
It was the way he was touching me.
He wasn't examining me. It was like...
He was getting off on it.
I mean...
What if I accused him and I was wrong?
Do you think you're wrong now?
No.
Then we have to file a complaint.
- Michael, I don't think I can do that.
- Claire, listen to me.
If we don't report this,
he's gonna do the same thing
to somebody else.
You have to trust yourself.
I don't think I can, Michael.
I think you can.
We'll go through it together.
Even with food
and supplies flown into the area daily,
the aid is not reaching
many of the refugees.
Dr. Victor Mott, Seattle gynecologist
and obstetrician,
was brought up today on charges
by the District Attorney's office.
The scandal began last week
when one of Mott's pregnant patients
went to the state medical board,
claiming she was sexually molested
by the doctor during an examination.
Since the patient's initial accusation,
four more women have come forward
alleging that they, too,
had been sexually molested.
Citing the possibility of criminal
misdeeds, the state medical board
turned the case over to the
District Attorney's office.
Dr. Mott was unavailable for comment.
The suicide provision is quite clear.
However, we may be able to get
the insurance company
to return a small settlement.
Mrs. Mott, although your husband
had sizable assets,
they've been frozen by the state.
Frozen.
This is normal procedure
when the estate
is probably going to be sued
by a number of sources.
You are free to stay in the house
until you have your baby,
but you should begin
to make alternative plans.
I'm very sorry, Mrs. Mott.
Can I help?
Get an ambulance here right away!
My baby-
We'll need blood.
Four units cross-matched now!
- I want vital signs!
- Pediatrics is standing by.
- My baby.
- Now lift.
She's hemorrhaging.
Get this baby out or we'll lose them both.
- I feel it kicking.
- You can?
Keep her still.
Can't stop this blood. Call Anesthesia.
I'm gonna operate.
Chest compressions are reducing.
We're losing him!
No!
Hold her down.
- He's gone.
- No.
Anesthesiologist is on the way.
Increase the drip to 90.
Her pressure is 80 over 40.
- She didn't touch it.
- Emergency hysterectomy.
She's been so depressed,
she won't talk. Let me try.
...against the late
Victor Mott's estate.
The suits were filed by four women
who claim they had been molested.
You have got to eat.
The investigation was dropped
when Dr. Mott was found dead
from a self-inflicted gunshot wound.
Claire Bartel has not filed a suit,
although she was the first
to accuse Mott
of molesting her during an exam.
I'll leave your food.
Her accusation prompted
the other women to come forward
I'm coming up to the back door.
I'm getting close to the back door.
I am now entering the back door.
Good morning, Solomon.
Good morning.
Thank you.
Hi, little baby.
Get back here. I got you!
Sorry, Mom.
Don't cry, baby.
Yes, that's a big boy.
Thank you, Solomon.
Don't cry, sweetheart.
Remember the rule
at the Better Day Society?
They said it's best
if you didn't handle the baby.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
- I only wanted to help.
- I know you did. Thanks.
They're replacing the greenhouses
at the botanical gardens.
- I might get one of the frames.
- Let me guess.
You want to build your own greenhouse.
Yeah!
The frame's there, the hardware's there.
All I'd have to do is erect it
and replace the glass.
Honey, don't you think
you're taking on too much?
Have you given any more thought
to hiring a nanny?
I'm not comfortable
having any of the girls I interviewed
take care of Joey.
Claire, it's not like when we had Emma.
You don't need to do
everything yourself.
What about Solomon?
He could be our nanny.
Honey, I don't think Solomon
would make a very good nanny.
Why not?
Remember we had the talk
about what a special person
Solomon is?
Yeah.
Well, there are some things
that he can't do.
What's gonna happen to Solomon
when he finishes painting the trim?
Well,
when he finishes painting the trim,
I guess we'll have to find
something else for him to do.
Okay?
Okay.
Hurry up, sweetheart.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
Mrs. Thompson?
Mrs. Thompson!
Thanks.
- Thanks for stopping.
- No problem.
- Here you go, sweetheart.
- Thanks, Mom.
Thanks. I think it's gonna rain later.
That was nice of you.
- You're welcome.
- Well, thanks. Thank you.
Excuse me, do you know
where the Bartels live?
Well, I'm Claire Bartel.
- Hi. I'm Peyton Flanders.
- Hi.
I was coming about the nanny position.
All right.
You wanna come up to the house?
Yeah.
I can't believe I forgot
I had an appointment.
I'm usually so good about these things.
Actually, I didn't have an appointment.
Did the agency just tell you to stop by?
Well, no. I'm not with an agency.
The truth is,
I've only worked with one family.
They're moving and I didn't know
what I was gonna do next.
I was with their little girl in the park.
Nannies talk and I heard
that your family needed someone.
I shouldn't have showed up.
I've made you uncomfortable.
No, it's fine. You're here, so come on in.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
Usually I have a set of questions
I ask, like,
- "Are you old enough to drive?"
- Thank you.
Here. Don't lose this.
My husband's been after me
to fix this thing.
Well...
How did you come to be a nanny?
A few years ago, I was pregnant.
I lost the baby and my husband
within days of each other.
The miscarriage prevented me
from having more children.
It was a very difficult time.
A mutual friend set me up with a family
looking for a nanny.
It turned out to be a wonderful
experience for both of us.
I adore children.
I love being with them,
taking care of them.
For me,
it's the next best thing
to actually being a mother.
Well, I'm building my own greenhouse.
And although
I'll just be right in the backyard,
I'm anticipating being very busy.
That's Joe.
I'd love to meet him.
The nursery is across
from the master bedroom.
Claire? I need to ask you something.
I'll be right back. Excuse me.
Try to open the window
from the inside.
If you can't,
wait till Michael comes home.
Solomon, this is Peyton.
Peyton, Solomon.
- Nice to meet you, Solomon.
- Hello.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
That's all right. It was an accident.
Anyone can have an accident.
Okay.
He's beautiful.
He's very hungry-
I've taken up half your morning.
No problem, I really enjoyed it.
I should be going.
I'm gonna leave a letter of reference.
I can show myself out.
You don't have to get up.
Peyton,
would you like
to have dinner with us tonight?
I'd love you to meet the family.
I'd love to.
Good. Say around 6:30?
I'll be here.
I'm in charge of the salad dressing.
And now you're in charge
of setting the table.
Daddy's gonna be home any minute.
What does your husband do?
Michael's a genetic engineer.
He works for a research outfit
called Biotechnics.
Daddy is a mad scientist.
It's Daddy!
- Here, let me help with that.
- Thanks.
Give me a kiss. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
You helping Mom out?
What are you shushing me for?
Joey's asleep.
Thank you.
- Hi, beautiful.
- How are you?
Peyton, this is my husband, Michael.
Hi.
I gotta tell you guys, that was
one of the all-time great meals.
It was delicious.
I was in charge of the salad dressing.
That's right. She did.
She made it all by herself.
When Mom finishes the greenhouse,
- I'm in charge of the strawberries.
- Really?
- That sounds like a very important job
- It is.
She seems terrific. What's the catch?
There is no catch. I think she's great.
I think we can get her
to commit for a year.
- Let's grab her.
- Yeah? Okay.
Oh, my God!
- What happened?
- He had this in his mouth.
- Mommy's earring.
- It must have fallen out.
He's okay.
I'm sorry I frightened everybody.
- I'm glad you caught it.
- I'm glad you got there in time.
- Hi.
This is for you.
Thank you. You didn't have to do that.
That's very pretty.
They say a wind chime
helps a baby sleep.
Why don't we
get you settled downstairs,
then we'll hang it up
outside the nursery.
This is a little bit dark,
but your room gets more light.
This is the laundry room.
And this is your room.
It's perfect.
Like it?
There we go.
Yes.
Mom, look! We did it.
Boy! Let's see.
- Emma, you can certainly shovel!
- Thank you.
How pretty!
It looks just like your house.
I know. We put it out every year
when the martins come back.
Who are the Martins?
They're large swallows.
The same family comes back
every year to visit us.
Yeah.
I would come back, too.
That is a beautiful bracelet, Claire.
I got that at an antique show.
- You can borrow it anytime.
- Well, thank you.
This must be a special occasion.
I always feel sexy and glamorous
when I wear this dress.
It's a present from Michael.
Okay, which shoes should I wear,
red or black?
- Are you wearing a jacket?
- Yeah. Well,
no. Maybe not.
- Then I'd go with the black.
- You think so?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
That's them. Now I'm really late.
- Where are you guys?
- Oh, we're running late.
- Does Marlene want to come in?
- Nah, she's on the phone.
Damn.
- What is it?
- It's a stain.
It's perfume oil.
I must have perfume oil on my hands.
- I'll go get some club soda.
- Thanks.
Marty, this is Peyton.
- Hello, Peyton.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- I need to get something for Claire.
- Okay.
Maybe we should go ahead
and have kids.
I want to inform you
this place will not hold our table.
- Hello, Marlene.
- Hello.
What's with you?
What do you mean? Nothing's with me.
Nothing my ass.
Hi, I don't believe we've met.
I'm Marlene Craven.
You must be Peyton.
Nice to meet you.
- Poison.
- Excuse me?
The perfume.
You're wearing Claire's perfume.
Well, Claire needs me upstairs.
You look great.
- You don't think that's funny?
- No.
There she is.
- Hi.
- Sorry.
Hi. You look great!
I thought you were going to wear
that dress I got you.
Is there something wrong
with what I'm wearing?
That's not what I meant.
Boy, you look good!
- You look beautiful.
- Let's go. I'm starving.
You have the number where we'll be.
I do. Have fun.
Bye.
Zombies.
The living dead.
This is great!
Mom never lets me watch these movies.
That's why we have to keep it a secret.
Do you know what a secret is, Emma?
Yeah, something you can't tell anybody.
- No matter what.
- That's right.
Now we have our own little secret club.
That's our sign.
It was fun meeting
your Aunt Marlene and Uncle Marty.
They've known your mom and dad
a long time?
Aunt Marlene grew up with Daddy.
They were boyfriend and girlfriend
when they were little.
Is that right?
Do you have any boyfriends?
- No, I hate boys.
- You do?
If I tell you something,
you promise not to tell anybody?
I promise. Secret club.
Well, this mean kid at school,
his name is Roth,
he's been really mean to me.
But he said if I told, I'd be dead meat.
He said that to you?
Did your mother do anything about it?
She tried, but she couldn't help.
You never, ever let an attractive woman
take a power position in your home.
- It's bad business.
- A power position.
You heard what I said.
What's that saying?
- "The hand with the baby" that...
- Hey, Marl?
How much did you get
for the Fletcher house?
Three and change.
All I'm saying is watch your back.
I'm serious! There's too much pressure.
A woman can feel like a failure
if she doesn't bring in 50 grand a year
and still make time for blowjobs
and homemade lasagna.
Marlene's not much of a cook.
I think I'm gonna bum one of these.
You're such a bad influence.
He only smokes around you now.
- One isn't gonna kill me.
- Oh, I got it.
"The hand that rocks the cradle
is the hand that rules the world."
You want to look at the baby? Look.
Hi.
Look, honey. A boy or a girl?
A boy. His name's Joe.
How old?
Three months.
- He is beautiful.
- Thank you.
He has your eyes, you know.
Do you really think so?
Absolutely.
Do you have any other children?
Yes. He has a sister. Her name's Emma.
She looks more like her father though.
We have one more, too,
don't we, sweetheart?
- Peyton.
- Hi, Emma.
Tell me, which one is he? Where?
The one with the blue and gray shirt?
Okay.
- Watch it, trippy!
- Sorry, Roth.
My arm! My arm!
I got a message for you, Roth.
Leave Emma alone. Look at me.
If you don't, I'm gonna rip your head off!
- I get it, ma'am. Let me go!
- Don't forget it.
Awesome!
Wow, that was cool.
Secret club.
Good morning.
What's the matter?
You're not hungry, sweetheart?
Claire, I thought
you could use a cup of coffee.
Thanks.
- Peyton?
- Yeah?
Have you noticed
anything different about Joe?
No, I haven't.
Why, is something wrong?
No. I was just wondering. I'm real tired.
Michael was up all night finishing
his proposal. I got up at 4:30 to type it.
- I hope it works out.
- Good morning.
- See you tonight.
- You're not gonna have pancakes?
No, I've got to go to Federal Express.
Let me. That's the last thing
you need to worry about.
You have the time?
My proposal has to go out today.
Okay. Thanks. I love you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Michael.
How long
have you been volunteering here?
Gee, about seven years.
These days, I just take care
of the morning maintenance.
- Hi, Claire.
- Hi, Stan.
Like a big botanist family down here.
Yup.
We sit around talking about root rot
and drainage properties of shredded
bark and other fascinating topics.
Is your greenhouse
going to be something like this one?
Well, hopefully.
On a much smaller scale though.
I've always loved growing anything.
When I was little,
my parents thought I was crazy.
They thought I should've been born
on a farm.
Hey!
Hello.
Hello!
Do you have relatives in Seattle?
Oh, no, I don't.
My husband was my only family.
He's the only one
who ever really understood me.
He took care of me.
He was murdered.
Murdered?
They never caught who did it.
But I firmly believe
what goes around, comes around.
Is there a bathroom here?
Yeah, down through there
on the right side.
I'll be right back.
Come here, little one.
Do you need to be changed?
Come here.
Michael's proposal.
I can't find it.
It was in your purse.
I saw you put it in there!
Claire, are you all right?
Asthma. I'll be okay.
Asthma.
Michael, it's just disappeared.
I've retraced my steps.
I spoke to the manager in the restaurant.
He said he'd call in the morning.
What did they say
when you called again?
They said they'd consider it
next quarter.
- But they said they'd consider it?
- Claire, come on.
We've been over this.
Look, everything is gonna be okay.
- Michael, I'm so sorry.
- I know you are, honey.
I know you are.
- Maybe I left it at the botanicals...
- I'm going to get back to work.
I'm sorry.
Michael, I'm worried about Joe.
Why? What's wrong?
It's his eating habits.
He's stopped nursing
the way he used to.
How long has this been going on?
It's not all the time. A couple of weeks.
- Did you call the doctor?
- Yeah.
What did she say?
She said it's fine as long
as he keeps gaining weight.
Well, I'm sure he's fine, honey.
Someone named Peyton
is here to see you.
- Peyton's here?
- She's in your office.
She's our nanny, Gilbert.
Okay.
Let me in on where you do your hiring.
Hi.
He's out cold.
Sorry to bother you at the office,
but I wanted to talk to you in private.
- Everything all right?
- Oh, yeah.
I just had an idea.
It's Claire's birthday coming up.
I thought it would be nice
to throw her a surprise party.
She's been feeling low lately.
Especially with this thing
with your proposal.
That's a good idea.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Do you think Marlene
would want to help out?
Help out? You kidding me?
She'll take over.
Maybe it's best not to tell her
it was my idea.
Why not?
I wouldn't want her to think
I was competitive.
About Claire's friendship.
You understand Marlene
pretty well already.
Good. So I'll be going.
Okay, good. I'm real glad you came by.
- Bye.
Solomon!
I want to show you my sculpture.
Okay.
Is that the head? Or is that the foot?
No, that's part of the fur.
Okay, I see.
That's a piece of art.
- I knew you'd see it.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Hi, Emma.
- Hi, Peyton.
Hi, Solomon.
Emma, go inside.
I've got to talk to Solomon.
- Okay.
Are you a retard?
No.
Did you like looking at me?
Don't fuck with me, retard.
My version of the story
will be better than yours.
I won't let you hurt them.
They're my friends.
I won't let you hurt them!
Boy.
Solomon!
Would you step inside for a minute?
Okay.
Surprise!
It's for you, big guy
I was in charge of picking it out.
You're my friends.
Oh, my.
You should've seen his face
when we gave him the bicycle.
Emma adores him.
Claire, there's something
that's been bothering me.
I feel a little awkward bringing it up.
I've been noticing some behavior
that I feel might be inappropriate.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean, "inappropriate"?
Something about the way
he touches her.
I'm sure you must've misunderstood.
You're right. Solomon would
never do anything like that.
It would be obvious
if Emma were keeping a secret.
- I'm sorry.
- No, please. It's okay.
She's coming around.
I love you very much, sweetheart.
You know that if anything happened,
good or bad,
you can tell me
and I would love you just as much.
- Do you know that?
- Yes.
We shouldn't have any secrets.
Secrets between people
who love each other aren't good.
What's the matter, baby?
Nothing.
You don't have to say.
Why can't I see through this glass?
It's fiberglass, a different kind of glass.
We put real glass in the ceiling
to let the sunlight through.
And this lets the air in so it doesn't
get too hot in the greenhouse.
Joe's intercom conked out,
and I couldn't find any batteries
in the kitchen.
Think Solomon's got some in his cart?
Well...
He's got everything else there.
Let me take a look.
Sweetheart?
Come away from the window, honey.
Emma?
Come sit down.
Peyton.
But I don't understand.
Why did they take Solomon away?
I guess your mommy
didn't like Solomon very much.
I wanted to help Solomon,
but I was afraid
she'd send me away, too.
I hate her.
I bet your mommy
wasn't mean like mine.
I didn't have a mommy.
She died when I was very little.
Your mommy died?
Then who took care of you?
I had to take care of myself.
Peyton, if something happens
to my mommy,
would you take care of me?
Of course I would.
And your daddy, too.
I'd take care of all of you.
Last of the boxes.
Emma's going to be okay, Claire.
She's so different around me lately.
She's not my little girl. She's so angry.
And guarded.
I think
maybe she blames me
because I didn't protect her.
I don't think so, Claire.
Marlene wants to get together tonight
to make out a guest list.
I'm not sure this party's
a good idea now.
We should go ahead with it.
Everyone could use some cheering up.
Especially Claire. You know
how she's been blaming herself.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Guess I just needed to hear it.
Thanks for lunch. I liked the part
where we picked up the fertilizer.
- Oh, you liked that?
- Oh, yeah.
Hi, you two.
- Can I take him?
- Oh, sure.
Hi, sweetheart. Hello.
- Let me help.
- He's getting so big.
He's a different kid every time I see him.
He's got a great set of lungs,
doesn't he?
- Oh, what's the matter?
- You want mommy?
- You want to go?
- What happened?
I don't know what got into him today.
Want me to try?
- Wanna go to Peyton?
- It's okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's okay, little one.
What is that annoying noise?
Wind chimes. A gift from Peyton.
Charming.
Well, I gotta go.
- Bye-bye. Thanks for lunch.
- Okay.
Marlene,
Peyton's making
one of her famous souffles.
Why don't you and Marty
stop by for dessert?
I'm showing the Fletcher house tonight.
Didn't you sell the Fletcher house?
Actually I did,
but the financing fell through.
I have to start all over. Bye. I'll call you.
Okay.
That smells great.
You know what they say.
Chocolate's a substitute for sex.
Chocolate's great,
but I don't know about that.
Guess you and Michael keep
those fires burning all the time, huh?
Well, we certainly
have enjoyed each other.
When we first moved into this house,
we christened every room.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, you know.
When you have a baby, you start to feel
tired and unattractive and fat.
I'm sure Michael is as attracted to you
now as he ever was.
A man never loses it for his first love.
But I wasn't Michael's first love.
No?
You'll never guess who was.
Marlene?
Am I right?
Yeah, how'd you know that?
Wild guess.
You know, it's a shame
Michael's not here. He's gonna miss it.
What's he doing so late
at the lab anyway?
That's a good question.
I'm gonna give him a call.
- Randy and Cecie.
- Dave and Loreeta.
- And Mitch.
- Mitch and the Harrisons.
- Oh, come on.
- They always invite us.
You got a light?
Can't find my lighter.
Marty's gonna throw a fit.
You know, I'm still not sold
on this whole surprise party thing.
- Because of Emma?
- And Claire.
She just hasn't been herself lately.
How's Peyton doing?
Boy, Peyton's been great.
Has she?
I don't know what we would have done
without her.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hi.
- How was your night?
- Fine.
Yeah?
Michael, I called the lab.
There was no answer.
I was in a room without a phone.
Honey, come on.
I didn't mean to frighten you.
- You been smoking?
- No, I haven't been smoking.
One of the techs was.
Must be in my hair.
Michael, you never let
anybody smoke at the lab.
What is this, an interrogation?
- Well?
- Well, what?
It's been a long day.
I just wanna go to bed.
I heard something.
I dropped something.
Well, good night.
Can I fix you something?
- No, thanks.
- Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Good night.
Your mom and I want to talk to you.
The Better Way Society
is putting Solomon back to work.
- Better Day!
- Better Day, sorry.
Your mom and I want you to let us know
if you see him
around school or at the house.
You don't have to be afraid.
I'm not afraid of Solomon.
Peyton! Wait for me!
Peyton !
- Mrs. Bartel.
- Hi, Joe.
Let's see. Three pants,
a dress, one shirt. Like starch?
Yeah, and this jacket here
kind of smells of cigarette.
I didn't know
your husband was a smoker.
He's not.
What's this?
Mrs. Bartel, your husband's
got a habit he's keeping from you.
Mommy, what's wrong?
Mom, let's go inside.
Go upstairs to your room and play.
But, Mom...
Emma, please! Go upstairs.
Claire?
Honey, what's the matter?
Michael.
How could you do this?
- What are you talking about?
- You've been lying to me.
- Honey, calm down.
- Don't tell me to calm down,
you son of a bitch.
You don't understand.
I understand
you've been fucking Marlene.
All right, Claire, that's enough!
There are people in there.
What are you talking about?
- Talking about a surprise party.
- Oh, my God.
Everybody's in there.
Surprise.
Did you speak to Marlene yet?
No.
I can't seem to face her.
Michael, I can't go on like this anymore.
I can't say I'm sorry
any more than I already have.
I can't go on like this anymore either.
I was thinking,
maybe we could go away
for a few days.
You mean,
Peyton and the kids, or just us?
No, I was thinking
just the family without Peyton.
You like having Peyton around.
I do, and then sometimes I don't.
You sound like you're turning on her.
It's just... You know.
So many things have gone wrong
since she's been here.
You saying those things
are Peyton's fault?
No.
I don't know.
I just don't feel like myself.
Claire, honey, come on.
Peyton's come through
in some very tough times.
I know.
We'll talk about it when we go away.
We'll go away, just the family.
If there are any further services
that I might provide,
do not hesitate to call, blah, blah, blah.
These are all in the Magnolia District
in that price range.
Eastwind, Hobart. These are old.
They still haven't unloaded
the good doctor's house.
Waiting for a tip?
- Cancel my morning.
- What should I tell Lambert?
Make something up.
You've got a Harvard education.
Hi, sweetheart. I'll be back in a while.
You're not working here?
No, I have to go to the botanicals
to pick up seedlings. I won't be long.
Fucking A.
Hello?
Let me speak to Claire.
May I ask who's calling?
Marlene Craven. Want me to spell it?
Claire's not here.
- I'll tell her you called.
- Sure you will.
What is this, a parade? Let's go!
Claire, I didn't know you were here.
Marlene called, said it's important.
Oh, okay, thanks.
Hello, Marlene.
Claire! It's Marlene! Claire!
- Marlene, is everything all right?
- No.
I need a doctor. Know of any, Mrs. Mott?
Where's Claire?
Marlene, please?
Where is she?
She's in the greenhouse.
But, please, Marlene,
please don't go out there.
Claire! This is important!
It has nothing to do with the party!
Claire!
This little piggy stayed home.
This little piggy had roast beef.
This little piggy had none.
911 emergency.
Here's the O2.
This isn't going to work.
Get me my laryngoscope
and a number five line right away.
- What happened?
- Paramedics are with her now.
What happened?
Everything's gonna be fine.
She's a friend? It's gonna be okay.
She has trouble breathing.
She has asthma.
The paramedics
have everything under control.
Hey, Al.
Take a look over here.
It's okay, Joe. It's okay.
Claire, honey? Can you hear me?
You're safe now. You're in a hospital.
Just try and rest, okay?
Michael.
I keep seeing Marlene's face.
I can't believe she's gone.
Come inside.
That's better.
You're soaked.
Soaked through.
Peyton.
There's only one woman for me.
That's all you need.
Thanks.
Thank you very much.
- You okay?
- Fine.
Emma?
Fasten your seat belt, sweetheart.
I got it.
- Hi, Peyton.
- Hi, Emma.
Hello, Claire,
it's good to have you home.
It's good to be home.
Michael, the school secretary called.
The meeting is Thursday.
I wrote it in your book.
Okay, great, thanks. It's a fund-raiser.
Peyton heard about it
when she picked up Emma.
You said I could borrow it. Is it all right?
Yeah.
I'll be right back.
I don't want to burn dinner.
It's great to have you back.
You like it? Peyton did it.
Someone could have asked me first.
We thought it would be a surprise.
We thought you might like it.
If you don't, I'll have her take it down.
It's okay.
All right, well, I'll put your things away.
All right, do you have any sevens?
Go fish.
Look what I took, huh?
Do you have a ten?
Go fish!
Keep your cards up here
so Peyton can't see them.
So you can't see them.
Yeah, that's it.
There we go.
Did she tell you
where she was going in such a hurry?
No, she just took off.
Told me to cancel her morning.
What was she doing before she left?
I had just given her these listings
she had asked for.
She looked at them.
A minute later, she hurried out of here.
- Listings? These?
- Those are the ones.
Mrs. Harris?
I'm glad you made it.
Bruce Silverman, Windemere Realty.
- Would you care to take a look inside?
- Yeah.
I'm glad you made it.
I was just on my way out.
The house was custom-built
three years ago.
It's listed well below market value.
They're very motivated.
- May I?
- Of course.
The original owners
lived here a very short time.
New carpet throughout.
There is a nursery?
Perfect room for kids.
That's a strange-looking toy. What is it?
It's a breast pump.
Breast pump?
She used it to keep her milk up.
I don't understand where she could be.
I don't either.
Here she is.
- Where have you been?
- Michael, I've got...
Claire, we were worried about you.
- Claire, my God!
- She's Dr. Mott's widow, Michael.
She's what?
Get out of our house.
She's turning on me,
just like you said she would.
She doesn't realize
how I've come through for this family.
You have to tell her, tell her about us.
There's nothing to tell.
You should leave.
Michael, what are you saying?
You told me
there was only one woman for you.
I meant Claire, my wife.
Okay, fine.
I'll just get my baby
and we'll be on our way.
I meant, I'll just go get my things.
Michael.
You don't understand.
I mean, leave now.
We'll send your things.
You're right, Michael. That's best.
The keys.
Of course.
I'm sorry. You've been so kind.
- Mommy, Daddy, what's happening?
- Emma, stay there!
It's okay, Emma.
Mommy and Daddy want me to leave.
Goodbye, Peyton.
Peyton !
- Call the police!
- Claire, calm down.
You don't know what she's capable of!
We have her keys!
I think she rigged the greenhouse
for me!
Get the kids' things.
We'll go to a hotel.
Go upstairs, sweetheart.
Can you get someone
over here right away?
It's not an emergency situation.
Well, no.
I'll have a car there as soon as I can.
All right, we live at 808 Yakima.
Emma, sweetheart, we're gonna go
away for a few days, okay?
Bring dolly with you.
Peyton?
Michael?
Daddy?
Emma, I want you to lock
this door behind me.
- Don't open it until I come back.
- Yeah.
Stay here.
Michael?
Claire.
- Michael.
- I'm okay.
She's in the house.
I can't move. My legs are broken.
- I'll get the kids.
- Call the police.
Mommy?
911, what is your emergency?
Hello, yeah.
We need help at 808 North Yakima.
Mommy!
My family!
It's my family.
It's okay, Emma.
Mommy's here.
I'm gonna take you and Joe.
We're gonna have a real family.
You never have to see
those people again.
So tell your mommy, where's Joe?
Where is he?
He's in there.
You're not my mommy!
Emma!
Quiet.
Emma.
You're being very bad, Emma.
You.
- You give him over.
- No!
- No?
You give me my baby
or I'll bash your skull in!
Peyton !
It's my family, Peyton.
Don't hurt my mommy!
Something the matter, Claire?
When your husband makes love to you,
it's my face he sees.
When your baby's hungry,
it's my breast that feeds him.
Look at you.
When push comes to shove,
you can't even breathe.
- Now, give him to me.
- No!
No!
Solomon.
He's okay. I didn't hurt him.
- I know, I know.
- Okay?
Emma! Emma, it's okay.
Come on, come on, up we go.
Mommy!
Let's go down to Daddy, okay?
Solomon, I need you
to do something for me.
I need you to take Joey downstairs.
No, I'm not supposed
to handle the baby.
That's okay.
I trust you, Solomon.
It's okay?
Okay? Yeah.
Boy. There you are.
Come on, sweetheart.
- Let's go and get Daddy.
- Oh, my, little baby.
Solomon?
Come on.