This is the Army.
It's learning how to be a soldier.And how to be much more.
It's cold streams that chill your bonesand a hot meal to warm you up.
It's softball and low bridges.
It's a hundred waysto prove yourself.
This is the Army.
If you'd like to be part of it,call this number toll free.
That's my philosophy,$100 shine on a $3 pair of boots.
Yes, sir.
I don't think I've everbeen this happy.
- Thank you so much.- Thank you.
I got a nice, warm cab right here.You sure?
- Let's go. City centre.- Hey, let's go, man.
Thanks for the ride, pal.
Shit!
God, I thought that was a dogaround your neck.
If that's humour, don't bother.
I want to be taken to the airport.Be very careful with the bags.
Don't scratch them.
Allow me.
Thank you.
Would you be careful with those?
Madam, perhaps you'd liketo eat your luggage.
I'm in a hurry.
Oh, my balls. Oh, my balls.
Good morning.
This is Basic English.
My name is Russell Ziskey...
...and I'm gonna be your instructorfor the next five weeks.
I want you to call me Russell, and I'mgonna call you by your first names...
...because I would have a tough timepronouncing some of your last names.
Okay, I know you're anxious to jumpright in and start speaking English...
...but there are a couple of thingsI need to know first because...
...I've never done this before.
So how many of you wouldsay you speak English fairly well...
...but with some difficulty?
A little English?
Yes, you speak some English?
Son of bitch. Shit.
I've never gone this way before.
I'm sure there's a lot of waysI've gone that you haven't.
What is your name?
John Ringer? What kindof a name is Ringer?
Winger. I'm adopted.
I spent most of my lifein institutions.
Doesn't surprise me. You look likea typical lowlife character to me.
Actually, I'm a photographer.I took this job because I love people.
There's nothing I enjoy more thanmeeting someone like yourself...
...and getting to know you,then taking photos of you while I drive.
Will you stop?! Turn around! Watchthe road! Stop with the pictures!
Thank you so much.
Aren't you going too fast?
No, it's not the speedreally so much.
I just wish I hadn't drunkall that cough syrup this morning.
Oh, my!
- We're going to be killed!- Oh, no.
- Just keep your hands on the wheel!- Not killed! Not killed!
You...
You should have your licensetaken away.
I am going to writeyour name down...
...and see that it's given tothe proper authorities, G-E-R.
You're a bum!
And that's all you'll ever be,a bum!
Well, that hurts, ma'am.
And I don't thinkI want to take your abuse.
I know I don't want to take youto the airport. How about that, huh?
Hey, move that cab, buddy!
Hey! You can't stopin the middle of a bridge!
Would you get back in the car?!
Okay. That's really very good.I'd like to try just one more time...
...and then we'll call it a day.
Okay, great, great.All right, we'll see you next week.
We'll learn some new tunes.We'll have a great time. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
That's my car!
- Hey, man!- Instant Finance.
You're late on the payments, pal.
It's me.
- John, is that you?- Yeah.
- Did you remember to get my dress?- Yeah.
Hi, baby. You're homea little early, aren't you?
- Yeah.- How was your day?
Fine.
I got you a pizza too.
I had a real bad day.
Yeah. Yeah, I bet you did.
I quit my job.
I just can't take this anymore.
I know. I gotta straighten out.
- This is ridiculous.- Right.
That's what you said last week.
You know, how much can youstraighten out in one week?
It hasn't been a week, John.It's been six months.
Nothing's changed.
You sleep in till noon, thenyou watch Rocky and Bullwinkle.
Then you drive your cab,what, a couple hours?
You come home,you order out food...
...and then you play those stupid TitoPuente albums until 2 in the morning!
Tito Puente is gonna be dead,and you'll say:
"I've been listening to him for years.He's fabulous. "
Then you watch movies until dawn,and then...
...then you come to bed with me.
You don't think that takes energy?You're a sexual dynamo.
Most guys couldn't evenhandle you.
I've been reading books on the outsideso I can keep up with you.
It's not funny.
You're going nowhere, John.
It's just not that cute anymore.
It's a little cute.
Come on. I'm part of a lostand restless generation.
What, you want me to runfor the Senate?
I don't know what I want.
I just know that I don't want you.
So the basic problem isthat I'm still around?
Where's that sharp knifewe have? Anita!
I need you.
Come on, John.
I knew that wasn'tgonna sound good.
- Anita.- No.
John, no, it's not gonna work.I like you, but I need something more.
I need somebody who's gonnadevelop with me and grow. Goodbye.
- Who could grow more than me?- Goodbye.
Talk about massive potentialfor growth.
I am the little acornthat becomes the oak.
You can't go!All the plants are gonna die!
And then depression set in.
Go away.
Hi, John.
What's the matter with you?
Nothing.
Nice shot, John.
Need a little help.
Hey, can I take your last beer?
- No.- We'll split it.
I've had an interesting morning.
In the last two hours...
...I've lost my job, my apartment...
...my car and my girlfriend.
You still have your health.
Hey. Yes, thank you.Toss that up here.
Yo. Here we are, my man.
All right, come to papa.Toss that thing. Let's go.
Jeez.
Thank you.
The Army can mak e you feela lot of ways.
- Tired, challenged, trained and proud.- This doesn't look bad.
What, the Army?
You're kidding.
No. I've always thoughtabout joining the Army.
Bullshit. You're not the type.
What do you mean,I'm not the type?
I've seen the kind of guysthat enlist in the Army.
I saw them when I was working onunemployment. They're like us.
Except they're not as sophisticated.
Yeah, they're not as old either.
I bet you can't do five pushups.
Five pushups?
I got $3 saysI can do five pushups.
Okay, let's go. Five good ones.Come on.
- Not Marine pushups.- No, simple pushups.
I've never heard bonescreak like that.
That's none.
- I'm praying.- You ought to.
Let's go. There's a time limit here.
He's almost set.He's eyeing that rug.
And that's one.All right. He's off.
He's moving now. That's two.
Not that good though.
That's three.
I think you're readyfor the Special Olympics.
- That's four.- Four.
I was testing you.
And here goes five. Will he do it?
Congratulations.You just doubled your money.
I gotta get in shape.
I gotta dry out,or I'll be dead before I'm 30.
The Army's my only chance.
You could join a monastery.
Did you ever see a monk getwildly fucked by some teenage girls?
- Never.- So much for the monastery.
Brew.
- Thanks for splitting it.- No problem.
You're welcome to stayat my place if you want.
Pretty much gotthat roach problem licked.
I'm going Army.
You've got some warped ideaabout the Army.
You think it's like a health clubwith neat uniforms or something.
I go in the Army, they turn my bodyinto a dangerous weapon.
They make me a black belt.
I'll come out a human killing machine.
I think we should goto California again and pick fruit.
- They give you money.- Who?
The GI Bill.Borrow all the money you want.
Will you shut up about the Army?
You borrow the money,you buy a Winnebago.
They ship it anywhere you want.
You get lots of travel.Kathmandu, guaranteed.
Yeah, dysentery guaranteed.
I'll be over there in Nepalwith those monkey-head chicks.
They'll all be hitting on me."Hey, John...
...thanks a lot for keeping the Chineseoff our backs. We appreciate it.
Is there anything we can do for you?
Oh, and by the way, handsome...
...we've never been in a Winnebago. "
You figure it out.
You ever heard stories aboutthe gratitude of the Nepalese people?
- No.- They'll probably teach me to levitate.
A black belt who can levitate.
- With a Winnebago.- Check, please.
I can see you've got this allfigured out.
You're nobody's foolwhen it comes to your future, John.
I'm falling apart here.
All I've got are a lot of bad habitsand a lot of bad debts.
I need some heavy disciplinein my life.
You know who would be incrediblein the Army?
Who?
- You.- Get out of here, I'd hate it.
You would be, man.You could go right into Intelligence.
- I'm not going in.- You could be a commander.
You could probably be a generalin a year.
I mean, Charles de Gaulle wasa general. You're smarter than him.
That guy was like a memberof the steel-plate club.
I ought to run right down thereand join up, huh?
Well, I was gonna go over there.We could use your car.
- We'd have to, wouldn't we?- Yeah.
You coming in?
Hey, this is a loading zone.You can't park here.
We're not parking it.We're abandoning it.
I can't believe we're doing this.
Listen, if I get killed,my blood is on your hands.
Just don't get it on my shoes, okay?Hello?
I'm not saying that the Army will beable to do for you what it did for me.
All I'm saying is you get out of itexactly what you put into it.
Now, sometimes the Army'syour best shot.
There's some questions I have to ask.They're a little personal.
Have you ever been convictedof a felony or a misdemeanour?
That's robbery, rape, car theft,that sort of thing?
- Convicted?- Yeah.
- No.- Never convicted.
That's good. Good.
Are either of you homosexuals?
You mean, like, flaming or...?
Well, it's a standard questionwe have to ask.
No, we're not homosexual,but we are willing to learn.
Yeah, would they send ussomeplace special?
I guess that's no on both.
All right, now if you'll just giveUncle Sam your autograph here.
"Sammy, get well soon. "
That's good. Now your name.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I was wondering if you...Are you...
...you know, holding?- No, man, I'm not.
Well, I was wondering if you couldhold something for me.
What, are you smuggling fursor something?
Drugs.
Excuse me. General Hansen?
No, I'm not a general,but may I help you?
Yes. I want to thank youfor saving my life over in Vietnam.
- I don't think that was me.- You're right. It was Normandy Beach.
I was shot up pretty bad.
You grabbed me, pulled meinto a foxhole and patched me up.
I don't think so and I don't careand I don't have the time.
- See this arm band? MP.- Yes, ma'am.
Stands for military police.Are you on one of these buses?
Not yet, ma'am.
My job is to see thatbig, strong men like you...
...get on these buseswithout getting lost.
So why don't you just move alongand get on the bus.
Did you check him off, Louise?
You know, there's a strip searchbefore you get on the bus.
- Really?- Yeah. Be careful, man.
So, what, I guesswe dig each other...
...and we'll be seeing each otheraround the officers' club?
Watch out for this guy.He's a troublemaker.
- Do you have your papers?- Yes. Here.
What happens if I refuseto get on the bus?
You look like a sensitive,intelligent guy.
Don't make me shoot you.
Climb aboard, soldier.
- What do you think?- I hope we don't go to war.
Excuse me, stewardess.Is there a movie on this flight?
- Bus.- A movie on this flight.
Inside. Off the bus.
Off the bus. Right on inside.
Move it out, son. Move it out.
Move it out!
Off the bus.
Right on inside.
Sergeant Hulka.
Yes, sir?
At ease, sergeant.
I'm Captain Stillman,the new company commander.
Pleased to meet you, sir.
Fine-looking group of men,wouldn't you say so?
Boy, I hope this is the mess hall.
How's it going, Eisenhower?
Yes, sir, a fine-looking bunchof men.
Yes, well. Get them inside...
...and carry on, I guess.
I'll be in my officeif you need me.
Yes, sir.
Inside.
Have that removed, corporal.
Move it out!
Men, welcome tothe United States Army.
I'm Sergeant Hulka.
I'm your drill sergeant.
Before we proceed any further...
...we gotta get something straight.
Your mamas are not hereto take care of you now.
It's just you, me and Uncle Sam.
And before I leave you...
...you're gonna find out that meand Uncle Sam are one and the same.
Uncle Hulka?
When I tell you to move...
...you'll move fast.
When I tell you to jump...
...you're gonna say, "How high?"
And make no mistake.
I don't care where you come from,I don't care what colour you are...
...I don't care how smart you areor how dumb you are...
...because I'm gonna teachevery last one of you...
...how to eat, sleep...
...walk, talk, shoot, shitlike a United States soldier.
- Understand?- Yes, sir.
I didn't hear you.
- Yes, sir.- Yes, sir.
You don't say "sir" to me.I'm a sergeant. I work for a living.
- Yes, sergeant.- I didn't hear you.
- Yes, sergeant.- Now that's what I wanna hear.
You think this guy'soverdoing it a bit?
You got a problem, boy?
No problem, sergeant.
On your feet, boy.
What's your problem, boy?
I was just making a joke, sergeant.
Well, why don't you tell meyour joke, son?
I don't think you'd thinkit's funny, sir. Sergeant.
How do you know?
I got a hell of a sense of humour.Ain't I, Corporal Briggs?
Yes, sergeant!
Corporal Briggs, we have a comedianin our midst.
Will you takethis comedian outside...
...and watch him do 50 pushups.
Get your goat-smelling assout of here!
Move it!
Hut, ho, hut!
Anybody else want to bea comedian in here?
- No, sergeant.- I didn't hear you!
No, sergeant!
Shut up! Just shut up, will you!
- I didn't mean it.- How come yours is so long?
Fifteen and a half.
Thirty-three.
Forty-two.
- Thirty-seven.- Thirty-seven?
Step down. Grab your papers.
These are 34s,and they're loose.
I gotta live with 37?
Sergeant Hulka?
I'm sorry about what happenedat the meeting.
I certainly meant no offence by it.It won't happen again.
Keep it moving! Let's go!
- Think he bought it?- No.
Boxer or jockey?
You got something in a low-rise bikini?Mesh, if possible.
So where you from, Tex?
Don't you ever touch me again, ever.
This is pretty sweet.Free clothing.
Look at this stuff. Chicks in New Yorkpaying top dollar for this garbage.
How about that lunch?What was that brown stuff?
All right, men, fall in alongsidethis roadway in a column of two.
Fall in!
Move it! Move it!
Hi.
Move it!
You know something, soldier.I've noticed you're always last.
- I'm pacing myself, sergeant.- Move it!
Sorry.
Left face!
Left, right, left, right.
You stand in place.
Forward march!
Hey, we're walking.
Left, right, left, right, left, right.
My name's Howard J. Turkstra.I'm from Kansas City.
My hobbies are fast carsand fast women.
Because... That's why guys inmy car club call me "The Cruiser. "
Should call him "The Dork. "
Knock it off.
Go ahead.
I joined the Army because my fatherand my brother were in the Army.
I thought I'd better joinbefore I got drafted.
Son, there ain't no draft no more.
There was one?
What a jerk!
Next.
The name's Francis Soyer.
But everybody calls me Psycho.
Any of you guys call me Francis,and I'll kill you.
You just made the list, buddy.
And I don't like nobodytouching my stuff!
So just keep your meat hooks off.
If I catch any of you guysin my stuff, I'll kill you.
Also, I don't likenobody touching me.
Now, any of you homos...
...touch me, and I'll kill you.
Lighten up, Francis.
You're all in this together.
One of these men may save your lifeone of these days, understand?
Then again, maybe one of us won't.
- You, go ahead.- Me?
Yeah.
My name's Dewey Oxberger.My friends call me Ox.
You might have noticedI've got a slight weight problem.
- No!- Yeah, I do.
Anyway, I went to this doctor.
Well, he told me I swalloweda lot of aggression...
...along with a lot of pizzas.
Pizzas!
I'm basically a shy person.
I'm a shy guy...
...and he suggested taking oneof these aggression-training courses.
You know, these aggressive-trainingcourses like EST, those type of things.
Anyway, it costs 400 bucksto join this thing.
Well, I didn't have the money.
And I thought to myself,"Join the Army. It's free. "
So I figured while I'm hereI'll lose a few pounds.
You got a six- to eight-week trainingprogram here, a tough one.
Which is perfect for me.
I'm gonna walk out of herea lean, mean, fighting machine.
- Good thinking, Ox. Real good.- It is.
Ziskey.
I've always been kindof a pacifist.
When I was a kid my father told me,"Never hit anyone in anger...
...unless you're absolutely sureyou can get away with it. "
I don't know what kindof soldier I'll make...
...but I want you guys to know thatif we ever get into real heavy combat...
...I'll be right behind you guysevery step of the way.
Okay, Mr. Pushups.Let's hear your story.
Chicks dig me becauseI rarely wear underwear...
...and when I do,it's usually something unusual.
But now I know why I have alwayslost women to guys like you.
It's not just the uniform.
It's the stories that you tell.
So much fun and imagination.
Lee Harvey...
...you are a madman.
When you stole that cow...
...and your friends triedto make it with the cow.
I want to party with you, cowboy.
The two of us together,forget it.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here.
I'm gonna volunteer my leadershipto this platoon.
An Army without leadersis like a foot...
...without a big toe.
And Sergeant Hulka isn't alwaysgonna be there...
...to be that big toe for us.
I think that we owea big round of applause...
...to our newest, bestest buddy...
...and big toe...
...Sergeant Hulka.
Well, okay, hotshot.
We're gonna see what kindof soldier you are.
Reveille is 0500.
We're gonna fall outwith locker boxes...
...and we're gonna havea locker-box inspection.
And then we're gonna do 10 miles,rain or shine.
So you better hit them bunks,my little babies...
...or Sergeant Hulkawith the big toe...
...is gonna see how farhe can stick it up your ass.
Out of them bunks!
We got a full day ahead of us.
We're gonna start outwith a five-mile run.
I know I'm speaking forthe entire platoon when I say...
...this run should be postponeduntil this platoon is better rested.
Well, I'll tell you what, soldier.Let's make it 10 miles.
Any more complaints?
Thanks a lot, Winger!
Nice going, asshole.
You're making friends fastaround here, John.
Oh, my... Oh, my God! Mama!
Captain Stillman.
Major Ellis would like you to look overthese interim reports, captain, sir.
Interim reports!That's all I ever do around here.
I want some action!
Hold that, corporal.
Oh, look at those men.
Are those my men, corporal?
No, sir. Those areCaptain Benton's men, sir.
Well, where are my men?
Let's see. Sergeant Hulkais on the confidence course.
Sergeant Crockeris on the mortar range.
Terrific. Corporal,bring up the jeep.
Yes, sir.
Grenade!
Go get them!
Those are damn fine men.Are they in my company?
No, sir. Oh, here comeyour men now, sir.
Hit it!
Stand up whenI'm sticking you, boy!
Get down and give me 50, mother!
Come on! I'll walk on your ass, boy!I was killing...
Fifteen, 16, 17...
Twenty-seven, 28...
Wait a minute.
- You got the light one.- Yeah, my mistake.
- Yeah.- Here, let's switch.
- I kind of thought it was a mistake.- I got it.
It's real heavy.
This one's light.Stand out of the way.
Fall out!
- Stop! Fall in!- Hey, sergeant, it's raining.
Sergeant, I think it's a bad ideato march today.
You know, this isthe cold and flu season.
Fifty-one, 52...
- When's the good part, John?- This is the good part.
Get your butt down, soldier.You'll get it shot off someday. Move it!
Move it!
You all right?
I should've kept my head down.
I learned a lot of things today, John.
I've never felt more alivein my whole life.
I think this is the greatest dayI've ever spent.
And I want to thank youfor making me join the Army.
Get me out of here.
I'll take care of you.
Going south today? All right.
- So, what are you taking?- Oh, I got these from Elmo.
I told him I get sick when I fly.I think they're Dramamine.
These are Elmo's microdots.That's acid.
John.
- John, I took a lot of these.- How many?
Well, one just nowand one in the barracks.
Two in the jeep.
- Two when we got out of the jeep.- Oh, no. Six hits.
What a tragedy. Hey. Hey.
We're not gonna let you drive now,you sit right down here.
Buckle up here, cowpoke.
Stow your tray tablein the upright position, will you?
You're gonna be just finein about 12 hours.
It's gonna be kind of weirdtill then, but...
The plane's coming apart.
Hello!
I'm Captain Hollister, SpecialOperations Group. Who are you?
- I'm Major Dodge.- Captain DeSoto.
Pleasure to meet you, Hollister.Heard a lot about you.
Well, I never heard of you.And you're not on my roster.
That's just the waywe like to keep it, captain.
It's double double top-secret.
- Intelligence?- Some.
Anything I could tell youwould be a lie, captain...
...so how about we tag alongwith you to your destination...
...and then we'll goour separate ways.
Dismissed, captain.
Okay, major, let's go!
Go!
Russell!
They're all going backpacking, John!
Go! Go! Go!
The important thing is not to panic.
We should, like, build a shelter,I think.
Then we make some stone tools andwe can cut some spears and arrows.
Because tonight we're gonna go outand kill a wild boar.
And then we're gonna dry the meatfor travelling.
And in the morningwe can chop down a big tree...
...and make a dugout canoe.
And we could find a riverthat'll probably run down to the ocean.
If we're lucky, we'll drift intoone of those major shipping lanes...
...we'll probably get picked up in a dayor two by a Liberian freighter.
What do you think?
I think we should find a hotel room.
That's a good idea.
Hello!
I think some of these plantsare edible.
- Yeah.- Not that one.
I think we might have to settlefor a motel.
- This looks like a main road.- Oh, yeah, this is the interstate here.
Yeah. We just find a gas station,they'll tell us where all the nice...
What a rush. The sky is brown.
Hi.
Thank you.
Sit down.
Colombia. Love weed.
Good, good, good.
Pills.
For you.
Good, good.
Oh, yeah.
- Oh, it's good in stew, yeah.- Yeah, put about 30 in there.
That's good. Oh, great.
Time to get out of here.
What is their struggle?
It's cutting time.
I can't hear you!You two should tie the knot!
Hey, captain, could we get a ridewith you?
Just get on the plane.
You bet.
Oh, God, look at that.
Wash off the soap.That's right. Wash it off.
Look at that. Bend over.Drop the soap. Oh, tits. Good.
Oh, God, I wish I was a loofah.Look at that! That's...
Those muscles.
Oh, I didn't knowthey could do that.
- Excuse me, captain.- I don't want to be disturbed.
Stillman!
- Yes, sir?- Colonel Glass to see you, sir.
I can see that, corporal.Dismissed.
It's a pleasure to see you, sir.Welcome to Fort Arnold.
- Let's skip the bullshit, captain.- Yes, sir.
I've got a problem,and I need your help.
You've heard of the EM-50 project?
Yes, sir. It's a tank or something.
- It's an urban-assault vehicle.- Of course.
The Pentagon wants to unveil itfor the news media next month in Italy.
What General Barnickewants from you...
...is a real crack platoon ofnew recruits to man the EM-50.
Real go-getters.
We'll have them photographedputting the 50 through its paces.
"Our newest soldiers with ourlatest weapon. " That kind of thing.
Yes, sir. You can count on me, sir.
You screw this up, Stillman...
...and I'll have you assigned to aweather station above the Arctic Circle.
- You got that?- Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
Good.
Attention!
- I'm gonna fold.- Okay.
Well, I'm still in.Cruise, how about you?
Maybe I should fold.
Well, let me see.Let me see first.
No, not with a hand like that.Come on.
Dare me. Go on, bluff me.Come on.
How much should I bet?
If it were me, I'd bet everything.
But that's me. I'man aggressive gambler. Mr. Vegas.
Come on. Go for it. Go for it.
Yes, yes, there we go. I'm in.
- What do you got?- Well, I got a full house.
Three threes and two sixes, that'sa full house. What have you got?
- Two fours, I got an ace.- You got an ace, an eight and a seven.
Well, you lose. If you would've hadfour fours, you would've won.
- You're getting good.- Starting to get the hang of it.
Isn't this fun? You're pretty goodfor a first time, really.
Attention!
Fall in for muster. Move it! Move it!
Ten-hut!
It's come to my attention...
...that several members ofthe 3rd Platoon Bravo Company...
...left this military postwithout permission.
I wanna know who it was.
You can tell me now...
...or I got waysof finding out myself.
Okay, mister...
...you just got yourself 24 hoursof scrubbing garbage cans.
Step back!
Now, since nobody elsehas got the guts...
...to admit it...
...the rest of this platoon...
...will do the next two weekendson KP.
How's that sound to you, mister?
I think it sucks.
It's time you and mehad a private talk, Winger.
Step into my office.
I'm getting the idea, Winger,that you don't like me.
Maybe I just don't know youwell enough yet, sarge.
What do you say let's cut outthe bullshit between you and me.
- Oh, let's.- I think you're a punk.
I've been in this Army 28 years.
I've seen your kind come and go.
You think you know somethingabout everything, don't you?
Let me tell you something, mister.
You don't know a damn thingabout soldiering.
Oh, it's real tough stuff. Especially thatmarching-in-a-straight-line business.
I ain't talking about that crap! I'mtalking about something important.
Like discipline and duty and honourand courage. You ain't got none of it.
Those words mean so much to a manwho scrubs garbage cans.
Look, if you don't want mein your Army, kick me out...
...but get off my back.
Maybe you'd like totake a swing at me.
I'd like to take a big swingat you, sarge.
Well, go ahead andgive it your best shot.
I don't think I wanna goto the stockade.
I'll take my hat off.
There we are, Winger.Ain't no more drill sergeant.
It's just you and me, kid,man-to-man.
So go ahead, give ityour best shot.
Swing at me.
Gutless.
Punk.
I'm willing to forget aboutthis little incident.
And I want you to thinkreal hard about it.
And maybe someday you'll understandwhat the hell I'm talking about.
No. No, don't stop.
Don't stop.
I'll still respect you.
I'll respect you even more.
Just use more whipped cream.
John. John.
I just had the weirdest dream. John.
John?
If I call Anita, she has topick me up at the train, right?
I go back, get a new apartment...
...I see if I can getmy cab job back.
Where are you going? You goingAWOL? Are you going AWOL?
- No, I'm deserting.- You idiot!
You desert now,it's a federal offence.
- Come on.- I'll take my chances with the feds.
Get up. Come on.You're not going anywhere.
Now listen to me.You're gonna finish basic training...
...you're gonna keep your mouth shutand do everything he tells you.
- And you know why?- Why?
Because you talked me into this,that's why, you idiot! It was your idea!
I didn't talk you into this.You needed this.
I'm gonna kill you! Damn you!
Where's the great pay?Where's the travel?
Where's the Winnebago?Goddamn it! Shit!
This isn't what you think.
No, we're just good friends.
In the jeep.
Come on. Let's go.
I was going to the laundry,get my uniform.
Save it for later.
Okay, guys, you're home.Get out.
You're not gonna report thisor anything, are you?
I'm gonna treat itlike a UFO sighting.
"I saw something, but I'm notquite sure what it was. "
Thank you.
Oh, goodbye.
Move it! Do it!
Why, boy...
...we got women can climb thatbetter than you. Get up!
Get on your feet!
Hit it!
He said he couldn't make it.Why don't you do it?
Take one step back, Winger.
Move it!
All right, soldier, let's seehow you fire that mortar.
- What coordinates, sir?- Coordinates?
Yes, sir. They determinewhere the mortar's...
Soldier, the Army has spent a lot ofmoney teaching you how to fire that.
Now set it and fire it.
- We don't know where the shell's...- The only way to learn is to do it!
Now fire the weapon.
All right!
Any of you suckholes want tocome up here and knock me off?
Oh, shit.
Incoming!
Sergeant, does this meanwe're through for the day?
- Save your strength, sarge.- Yeah.
Get him off! Get him off!
Men, I realize this tragic injuryto your drill sergeant is a real shock.
Especially this close to the endof basic training.
As far as I'm concerned, SergeantCrocker's 100 percent responsible...
...for the entire thing.
That's not what I heard.
Who said that? Pick that up!Who said that?
- Did you say that?- No, sir.
- Did you say that? Who said...?- I said that.
Now, I don't care what you heard.
My report states that Crocker wasnegligent in his mortar instructions...
...and totally unable to controlhis men.
Have it your way, sir.
You bet I will, soldier.
I do not want to hear one moreinsubordinate word...
...from anyone in this platoon.
The subject is closed.
You'd better stop worryingabout what happened to Hulka...
...and start worrying about how you'regoing to pass muster at graduation.
You've got three daysto get it together.
And if you want my honest opinion...
...you're not gonna make it.
No stragglers. Now come on.
We owe it to Sergeant Hulka to end upface down in the gutter tonight.
Hey, baby, want to cometo my place?
Where were you two blocks agowhen we could've used you?
Come on. Don't waste it.
All right, we're here!Come on.
It's the Pom Pom. It's famous.It's world-famous.
This might be fun.
Hi.
Oh, amazing.
I used to wrestle.There's no tables.
- Here's a table. Excuse me.- Sounds good.
- You wrestled, huh? Nice seats.- Yeah.
Give me a kick, honey.
Oh, parted my hair.
Okay, girls, go get them!
We're gonna start the bidding.
I'm not gonna acceptanything less than $100.
The bidding has gotta start.Now give me 100.
- You gotta do it for us, Ox.- I can't.
- You said you used to wrestle.- I used to lose a lot.
Yeah, but these are girls.They're weak and soft.
- I need 150!- One-sixty!
One-seventy-five now!One-seventy-five here! One-eighty!
- It doesn't seem fair.- Fair?
Who cares about fair?The world isn't fair! Truth isn't fair!
Is it fair that you wereborn like this? No!
They're not expecting somebody likeyou. They're expecting some clown.
You're different. You're weird.You're a mutant. You're a killer!
You're a trained killer!
You're a lean, mean,fighting machine!
I'll do it!
- All right. Give me your money.- Four hundred and thirteen bucks!
My man. My big man hereis gonna do it all for us...
...for $413...
- And 58 cents.... and 58 cents!
Four hundred thirteen dollarsand 58 cents!
I'll take that right now!
Ladies and gentlemen,the big event you've been waiting for.
A three-round match,five-minute time limit, one pin only.
And during this matchthere will be absolutely no biting.
Cut that out! Cut that out!
And no pulling of the nose.
Hey, do something about this, ref!What kind of place you running here?
And no kicking,ladies and gentlemen.
All right, go to your neutral corners,and we will begin the match!
Hey, wait a minute! Wait! Hey!
Hey, just a second here!
Oh, jeez! Now you done it.
Beat the shit out of them, Ox!
- You hit me! I'm a girl!- I'm sorry! I didn't mean to hit you!
That's my man out there!My champ! Now stop it!
Behind you!She's not even in the fight.
Cut that out. Cut that out.
You get in here. Come on.
I'm a gentleman. Now stop it.
All right.
Okay, all right.
- Thanks.- No problem.
- Thanks again.- Okay, all right.
- You're very competitive.- I don't wanna go back.
You gotta go back.You're already dirty. Come on.
All right, there you go.
They got him downand they got him pinned!
Bravo Company!
Go, man!
Way to go, Ox! Kill them!
- Should we?- Yeah. Let's go.
We'll take care of these two.
It's okay. Special assignment.
Yeah, we're with them.
Louise, it's so nice to see you.What are you doing here?
Well, explain yourselves.
Well, sir, we were...
We were goingto the Bingo parlour...
...at the YMCA.
Well, one thing led to another...
...and the instructionsgot all fouled up there.
- We ended up...- Shut up.
Okay, sir.
You men are a disgrace.
Maybe a few daysin the stockade...
...would help changeyour rotten attitude.
But we're supposed tograduate tomorrow, sir.
That's even better.
Tomorrow you'll be on paradein front of General Barnicke.
And when he seeswhat total fuck-ups you really are...
...I will personally recommend...
...that your whole platoon...
...repeat the entire courseof basic training.
Well, get out.
All right, now this is the second timewe've let you guys off.
So let's not let it happen a third time.Is that clear?
- Very clear.- Get back to your barracks, all right?
- Good night.- Good night.
So, what are you guys gonna do?
We're gonna check out GeneralBarnicke's house. He's in Washington.
Barnicke?
Barnicke?!
He still owes me money.Hey, Barney!
Get him!
Mom! I'm home!
John!
- No, no.- Now, don't worry about a thing, okay?
Oh, this is nice, really.
Listen, if this is gonna get youin trouble, we'll leave. All right?
No, it's okay. General Barnicke'sgone until tomorrow morning.
Good.
Thank you.
I feel like I'm 16 years oldin my parents' house...
...and they're away on a trip.
Sixteen?Wanna play Spin the Bottle?
This guy's doing pretty well.Interested?
All right, you've looked atthe general's refrigerator long enough.
- Let's go. Come on.- Let's look at the general's cupboards.
John!
You know, you're very pretty...
...for a cop.- Oh, thanks a lot.
No, thank you. You knowwhat your problem is, baby?
- No, I don't.- Your problem is that you're armed.
You're heavily armed.
Guys have trouble with girlsthat are armed.
They don't know how to come on.Do you know the rest of your problem?
Tell me.
You've never had anyone give youthe Aunt Jemima treatment.
- No, I certainly haven't had that.- First you get up on the grill.
- I'll get you up to cruising speed.- Stop it!
You're sticking on the bottom, dear.Keep hopping. Keep hopping, honey!
There you go. A little bit lumpy.You're a little bit lumpy.
A little bit lumpy.
- I'm not enjoying this! Now quit it!- You're not, huh?
Maybe you need this.
- What are you gonna do with that?- This. And this.
Who's your friend?Who's your buddy?
I am, aren't I?
- You're crazy about me, aren't you?- No.
You're head over heels in lovewith me.
You're hopelessly, deeply in lovewith me, aren't you?
Yes.
I knew it. I had that feeling.
Even before I picked this up.
It's about time you came around.
So, what do we do now?
Let's go upstairsand check out the general's closets.
Nice to know you canmove like that when you have to.
Well, it's nice to knowyou can make me so hot.
You say the nicest things.
Hold on, honey.I got a special tool for you.
Come here.
I can't believe we're playing this.
- Okay, down on your knees.- Sounds good.
All right, now the waythat you play it is...
...you pretend there's a force fieldall around your body...
...and you try and get as closeto each other as possible...
...without actually touching.
- Okay?- It sounds easy.
It ought to be.
I think I'm good at this.
Maybe.
How do you win?
Well, if somebody breaksyour force field, then you win.
- You just broke my force field.- Yeah, you win.
Well, that was interesting.
It's all over with now. We might as wellnot even show up to graduation.
You white guys'll probablyget five years.
- But we gonna get hung.- Yeah, man.
Guys! Hey!
What's everybody so down about?
Didn't everybody make itwith a beautiful MP tonight, huh?
Oh, Stillman freaked outwhen the MPs brought us back.
If we screw up graduation, we'llhave to take basics all over again.
Oh, Cruise, it's been a lot of funthe first time, hasn't it?
I can't handlebasic training again, man.
You're number oneon the death list now, Winger.
Take it easy, Francis... Psycho.
Will you guys just relax? We gotplenty of time. What time is it now?
- Two a. m.- Okay, 0200.
- What time we get up?- Five a. m.
0500. All right, we have three hours.Didn't you ever cram for a test before?
I learned two semestersof geology in three hours.
We can do this.We just have to practice.
We've been practicing all night,and we stink.
- Yeah, well, the brains have arrived.- Yeah, that's good news.
We go down to the motor pool.
We work on it all night.We get it together.
- We can do this, right?- There's no way in hell we can do it.
Right shoulder, arms!
Forward, arms!
Inspection, arms!
Right shoulder, arms!
Right face!
Your left, your left, your left.
Come on, rhythm.Hut, two, three, four.
Black guys,help the white guys, okay?
- What did he say?- He said the black guys...
...help the white guys.
Come on, guys!
Wait a minute!
Cut it out! Stop!
Hey, stupid,look at yourself!
Cut it out! Cut it out!
What the hell'sthe matter with you?
Stupid!
We're all very different people.
We're not Watusi.We're not Spartans.
We're Americans.With a capital A, huh?
You know what that means?
Do you? That meansthat our forefathers...
...were kicked out of everydecent country in the world.
We are the wretched refuse.
We're the underdog.We're mutts.
- Here's proof. His nose is cold.- So is his brain.
But there's no animalthat's more faithful...
...that's more loyal,more loveable than the mutt.
Who saw Old Yeller?
Who cried when Old Yellergot shot at the end?
Nobody cried when Old Yellergot shot? I'm sure.
I cried my eyes out.
Yeah.
So we're all dogfaces.We're all very, very different.
But there is one thingthat we all have in common.
We were all stupid enoughto enlist in the Army.
We're mutants.
There's something wrong with us,something very, very wrong with us.
Something seriously wrong with us.
We're soldiers,but we're American soldiers.
We've been kicking ass for 200 years!We're 10 and 1!
Now we don't have to worry...
...about whether or notwe've practiced.
We don't have to worry...
...about whether Captain Stillmanwants to have us hung.
All we have to do...
...is to be the great Americanfighting soldier...
...that is inside each one of us.
Now, do what I do...
...and say what I say...
...and make me proud.
- Fall in!- Yeah!
Platoon...
...ten-hut!
Right shoulder, ho!
Order, ho!
Maybe they couldn't findthe parade grounds.
- It's right in front of the barracks.- That's what I mean.
Eyes right!
We checked the barracks, sir.They're not there.
If they're not here in five minutes,I want them arrested.
Hey, graduation's at 2:00.What time is it now?
Three o'clock. We've still gotan hour to sleep.
Oh, good.
Three o'clock! We're missing it!
John! John!We're missing graduation.
- We're missing it.- Let's go.
Wake up, man! We're missing it.
Where is it?
All right, let's doa little singing this morning.
Oh, my God!
Platoon...
...a- one, two:
Where the hellhave you been, soldier?
- Training, sir!- Training, sir!
What kind of training, son?
Army training, sir!
Platoon, just like last night,only better!
And right shoulder, ho!
Order, ho!
Side step right!
Left flank, left!
Queen Anne salute!
Three, five, seven!
Razzle-dazzle!
Hut, two, three, four!
Hut, two, three, four.
The quick brown fox jumpedover the lazy dog, sir!
- Where's your drill sergeant, men?- Blown up, sir!
Blown up, sir!
Sir, these are Sergeant Hulka's men.He was injured during basic training.
I see.
So am I to understand that you mencompleted your training on your own?
- That's the fact, Jack!- That's the fact, Jack!
- Captain.- Yes, sir?
These are exactlythe kind of go-getters...
...I want working on my EM-50project in Italy.
- Oh, but, sir, these men...- Don't "but" me, captain.
I want them on the plane tonight.
Gentlemen, it's party time,Italian style!
Not bad! It's great.
Best bunk? Best bunk is...
Best bunk, right here.
- Okay, who's up for the Vatican?- No, I can't.
Let's get some peopleand some relics, and we'll do it.
What are you doing? No, get off.See, you gotta make my bunk.
See, we're in Italy.The guy on the top bunk...
...has gotta make the guyon the bottom's bed all the time
It's in the regulations.If we were in Germany...
...I would have to make yours.
But we're in Italy, so you'vegotta make mine. It's regulations.
Who's gonna make the beds?
Buona sera, gentlemen.
It is alive.
Welcome to Italy.
We can forget all aboutthe tearful reunion.
There's a couple things I want to getstraight with you right off the bat.
I don't know what kind of shityou pulled at graduation...
...but this ain'tno glamour detail we're on.
I want to see you walking tall...
...looking good and mentally alertat all times.
I'm gonna bust your butts...
...to make this the best damned outfitin the European command.
Get these bunks made up!Get your gear stored!
We're gonna muster in frontof the motor pool at 0600! Got it?
Hi, sarge.
"Hi, sarge. " Just shut up.
0600!
As you may know,General Barnicke...
...is particularly interestedin this project.
He has selected this platoonfor this assignment...
...and he expects you to performparticularly well.
Raise it, sergeant.
Gentlemen, this is the EM-50Urban Assault Vehicle.
A real beauty, colonel.You can count on us.
Fall in!
I need two volunteers.
You and you.
You'll guard this vehicleuntil 0800 on Monday morning...
...and the rest of yougot the weekend off. Dismissed!
- Sarge, why me?- Oh, I don't know, son.
I ain't got no military reason for it,I just don't like you.
Have a nice weekend.
Oh, yeah. I want that so cleanI could eat off the floor.
This is amazing. You wouldn't believewhat this thing could do.
John.
- Do you think I'm officer material?- God, I'm worried about you.
Come on. I'm in good shape.I'm walking tall.
I'm looking good.First weekend in Europe.
Yeah. We're spending it inan airplane hangar watching a truck.
We got each other.
Well, I was kind of thinking we'd geta couple companions this weekend.
Too bad the girlsare in Germany.
We could get...
...a hotel room somewhere.- Yeah.
Spend a few dayseating room service.
Would've been good.
We could take them up in the Alpsfor a little spin.
- No.- Oh, yeah.
- No, no, no.- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.- No, no. No, John, no.
- I'll drive.- Okay.
We're here.
Don't forget, you promised mea real expensive dinner...
...before we see thiswhatever it is.
Right.
Come with me, my dear.
Now, don't forget, this is a big secret,so you can't tell anybody, okay?
- Not unless they torture me.- Come on.
- Official business.- May I see your identification, sir?
Thank you, captain.
Yeah. Just follow me.
When the Army entrusts an importantproject like this to an officer...
...it usually means they're priming himfor a major promotion.
- I really think you're gonna like this.- Yeah?
- Are you gonna get sick or something?- Where the fuck's my truck? Where...?
Where's my truck? Hey!
Hey, where's the EM-50?
A couple of soldiers took itto get it washed, sir.
Took it to get it washed?!
Is there a bathroom around here?I gotta pee.
- Hold it!- They had proper ID, sir.
Do you want me to notifypost security, sir?
You keep your mouth shut about this.Do you understand me?
And you let no one in there.No one! Not even the colonel!
Yes, sir.
You know, I think this guyStillman is really dangerous.
Yeah, I'm becomingaware of that, you know.
Okay, let's go.Let's load that truck.
Sergeant.
We've traced the EM-50 to Germany.
They're probably headingright for East Berlin.
Sir, if you'll take my advice,there's a crack squad in the 42nd...
...that could link upwith Air Recon.
We'd have that EM-50 back hereinside of 24 hours.
Nothing doing.We'd be the laughingstock...
...of the entire armed forces.We will do this ourselves.
Sir, those numb-nuts can'teven tie their own shoelaces.
I don't care, sergeant. Just loadthe truck, and let's move out.
All right, we're moving out!Move!
I guess we're going afterJohn and Russell.
I can't believethey're Russian spies. Can you?
All I know is,I finally get to kill somebody.
Hey, Russell.
Have you been doingyour special exercises?
- I brought the magic suitcase.- You did?
Does this do anything for you?French girls do it all the time.
No. I've seen that.
I've seen that on cable TV,and it did nothing for me.
Hey, watch it. A guy could get hurt.
- My gosh, my gosh.- Come on, John.
- Come on.- I'll do it!
But just one more time.
Off the low meter board.
From the United StatesMilitary Academy, John Winger.
He's gonna do a reverse mo-fo.
A somersault up to the knees,to a butt banister...
...a backflip...
...all they way backto a double backflip.
A face bounce!A double face bounce!
A triple head! Oh, no!Oh, he's hurt!
That does sound nice.
You know, my father was hereduring the war.
- In this bathtub?- Your ears need cleaning.
Easy. Louise,what do you think of me?
When we first met, I thoughtyou were kind of screwed up.
And now?
I still think you're kind of screwed up,Russell...
...but you're so cute.
- A face bounce...- John.
...a dismount...
...and a remount.
John!
How's this? How's this?
- How's this for you?- Perfect.
- Is this good? Is this good?- It's great. Oh, it's perfect.
- What about this? How about this?- That's better. Oh, so much better.
Oh, I like that.
That's different.
Oh, where did you learn that?Oh, where did you learn that?
Oh, not yet. Please, not yet!Oh, please!
I can't stop! Please!
Oh, I wanted it... Oh, I'm sorry!
- I can't see a thing up ahead, sir.- The turnoff is just up to the right.
No, sir. If we turn right,we're gonna...
Sergeant, when I want your input,I will ask for it. Thank you.
For chrissakes, captain.We broke through the...
This is my mission. I would appreciateif you let me run it. Thank you.
Fuck this.
- Where you going, sarge?- Hey, sarge, where are you going?
Sarge, what are you doing?Sarge, what are you doing?!
Here you go. There you go.Hand them off there, boys.
Stupid jerks.
Gunther, get yourselfa new Volkswagen, huh?
Folks, don't order the schnitzel.They're using schnauzer.
Hey, Hansel, Gretel!Hey, we're your allies.
It's cool. All right.
All right, Klaus,hold it up right here.
We got some naked animals in herewe don't want you to see.
Here you are.
- More worthless money for you.- Come on.
- All right.- Hey, did you leave the radio on?
- What?- That's the shortwave radio.
This is the EM-50?
Mayday, mayday.
Mayday. Code 21, Status 7.Mayday. Code 21, Status 7.
Code 21. Go ahead.
I'm with the U. S. Army, 41 stArmoured Division, Bravo Company.
I have a platoon and CObeing held by hostile enemy...
...at coordinates 416-397.
They're Russian troops,about 200.
Send help. I gotta get moving.
416-397.That's Czechoslovakia.
- Forty-first Armoured?- Yeah, Bravo Company.
- That's our unit.- Oh, no.
- They came looking for us.- Oh, they've had it.
We've had it.
If it's a Status 7 like you said,they went in undercover.
So the DOD won't evenacknowledge it.
Those guys are dead.
- We gotta go get them.- Yeah.
- No.- We're responsible.
- Russell.- Come on, it's Czechoslovakia.
We zip in, we pick them upand we zip right out again.
We're not going to Moscow.It's Czechoslovakia.
It's like going into Wisconsin.
I got the shit kicked out of mein Wisconsin once. Forget it.
- Russell, what are you afraid of?- I'm not afraid.
There are two things I promisedmyself I'd never do:
Kill and die.
What if the Russians wereraping your sister?
Come on, you know my sister.You practically raped her one night.
The Russians would just have tobuy her dinner.
Russell, that is our platoon out there.That's Ox and Elmo and Cruiser.
I love those guys.We're their only chance.
Two things, John:First of all, they hate your guts.
Those bastards.
Second, when I finish all my training,I'm probably gonna be a typist.
Now, when you invadea hostile foreign nation...
...you don't send your typistsin the first wave.
They got guys who like to do that,John. Let's give them a call, okay?
Okay.
Yeah, we won't go in.
- Okay.- Okay, let's go.
Oh, my hero.
Damn it, though, we're so close.I'd love to just go take a look.
I mean, the Iron Curtain, it's gotta lookgreat. I'd love to have a picture of it.
Think we could do that?
Take about an hour. We could driveover, get pictures and come back.
- We'll just look?- Yeah.
- Okay. Let's look.- Yeah, that's a much better plan.
We're so damn lost.Where the hell is Innsbruck, Austria?
We're trying to get over there,do some skiing.
- Do you know Brandy? Hi, girls.- Excuse me.
- What a darling border guard.- Is there a bathroom here?
Bathroom, girls. Bathroom.
There must be a bathroomhere somewhere.
Bathroom. Bathroom.
Hi. I'm John Wingerof the United States Army...
...and you are my prisoner.- Why are you doing this?
Chicago.
Why do we want prisoners?What do we want with prisoners?
Come on, move!
Do the words "act of war"mean anything to you, huh?
- I have a plan.- Great. Custer had a plan too.
We are in serious trouble.
He said he had a plan.Now, just give him a chance.
Hello, hello!
What an idiot.Get in here.
- All right, we're in.- Nice work, John.
- What's the plan?- I'm working on it.
Oh, my God, what an idiot.He's working on it.
The absence of a plan is ridiculous.
Hey, they're aboutto start shooting at us.
- Good. That's fine. Let them.- It's working.
- Louise, get this thing moving.- You're dangerous, you know that?
Oh, this is interesting.
I got it figured this way: They gotone big gun, a couple of tanks.
They got a hundred Baryshnikovsrunning around.
- And what do we got?- What do we got?
We got one heavily armedrecreational vehicle here, man.
Okay, find that truck,and we find them.
- There's a gun in that tower, Russell.- I see him.
All right, steady, steady.
- Got him!- All right! Oh, God!
Good one, Russell.
- There's the truck.- Must be them. Get ready!
Out, please!
John, over here!
- That was stupid.- Yeah.
- You know who would love this?- Who?
Russell. He should be here.
- Russell!- Russell!
Help!
- Thank you.- That helped.
They'd better be in there.
You can beat meas much as you want!
- Are you okay?- Where are they?
- Hi.- Where are the others?
Hello?
Hello!
- Hello?- Hello.
- Who is it?- It's Idi Amin.
- It's Winger!- We're free!
It's us, Winger! Get us out!
All right, stand back from the door.I'm gonna blow it.
Everybody back! Everybody back!
Get it.
Get down.
- Whoa, tough door!- You got it locked on the inside?
It's because of you peoplethat I cannot get outside!
It's always your fault.You are not capable of handling...
To take orders from me, who is...
- Open this door, please!- I'm gonna squash him!
- Winger! Oh, I'm so glad!- What are you doing here?
Look out, Louise!There's a tank behind us! Move it!
Find John, will you?I'm gonna kill him.
We had a car waiting.
Russell?
Let's get out of here!
We're here!
John!
Come on!
You are in trouble!This is government property...
Something's blocking the road.Hang on!
Hang on!
I'm getting too old for this shit!
Gentlemen, we are in Germany!
Platoon, ten-hut!
Queen Anne salute!
Get up!
Thank you.It's great to be back home.
My people, we're number one.All right.
Ox, we got medals. Look.Valortorious Service. Thank you.
What the...? A surprise party!
I'll kill you. Whose idea was this?
All right, everybody's comingto my place. This is ridiculous.
Senator, hang onto that,will you, for me?
Oh, I wrote.I didn't know if you'd come.
No questions, please.
We just want to get backto our hotel rooms...
...and have some really serious sex.
What are you looking at?Keep your eyes out there.
Oh, you old dog.
Right face!
Forward march!
Left, left,Your left, right, left.
Five, six, seven, eight.