Sorry, we can't come
to the phone right now.
If you'll leave a message
we'll get back to you
as soon as we can.
Thanks.
Hi, Mamie. It's Jack.
We're going to leave London
as planned,
but we'll take a cab
from the airport,
so nobody has to bother
to drive in and pick us up.
Ah! Eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven... Ohh!
You already own that.
You own everything.
I'll put another
hotel on it.
...and listen, we completely
forgot about Sally's goldfish.
If by some miracle
they're still alive
will you feed them
and change the water, and...
Your turn, Dad.
Uh, Mom will make my move,
honey.
And if they're not,
will you go to the store
and see if you can find a couple
that are sort of the same size?
Okay, we'll see you soon. Bye.
One, two, three...
What's happening?
...five, six! Yes!
Oh, no.
Yay!
Another hotel?
What does... what does
he owe you?
You owe me
1,000 and 100 pounds.
I haven't got it.
You win.
I'm out.
This girl is rich.
I want to go to sleep.
Good evening, sir.
Uh, yes?
Will these do?
Uh... yeah. Bring them in.
My wife, I guess.
Ahh...
candles, champagne...
Oh, honey.
I'm sorry I didn't
think of this.
That's all right.
Only one of us had to.
Is she asleep?
Mm-hmm.
What about your speech?
I'll wing it.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
We have all watched, I think,
with a sense of awe,
the protean events
which have taken place in
Moscow and the Republics
and the enormous changes
resulting from these events.
In this volatile climate, then
I must conclude that
we can only speculate
on the future of
Soviet fleet development
and deployment.
I would like to thank
the trustees
of the Royal Naval Academy
for their
very kind invitation
to be here with you today.
He's impressed, Sally.
He just can't show it.
He's a professional soldier.
It's his job
not to be distracted.
Come on. We got to go
meet Daddy.
I'm impressed.
Find it on the map there?
Uh-huh. We're right here,
and when we get to the street
there, we turn left...
No, right.
Yeah, right.
You sure?
Turn right, yes.
Okay, we're going to turn right.
I'm following your map.
Okay, okay, all right.
You mind your
bottom, Paddy-boy.
Move sure and fast.
You told me that, didn't you?
So I'm telling
you again.
This won't be like anything
you've ever done before,
little brother.
Target leaving the palace now.
Right.
Stay awake, lads.
Here they come.
Up!
Okay right here?
That good?
Any more? Little more?
Okay.
There's daddy.
Go!
Down! Get down!
Ready!
Get down!
Come on!
Oh!
Get down. Keep her down!
Get out of the car!
Come on!
Get out!
Open the fucking door!
Open it!
Jack!
Open it, or I'll blow it off!
Come on, let's go!
Go! Go! Go!
Paddy?
Stop! Army! Drop it!
Grab his arms!
Help the boy.
No, he's had it.
It's all right, sweetie.
I want you to stay here.
Everything's
going to be okay.
Stand back, please.
Stand back, ma'am.
That's my husband.
I'm a doctor.
I'm going to treat him.
Oh, Jesus, Jack!
What were you thinking of?
I'm going to
set you down, okay?
Stay with me, Jack.
You hear me?
Stay with me.
Jack?
Jack, stay with me.
The feeling here today
is one of outrage
over this unprecedented
terrorist attack
on the Royal Family.
And while no group
has yet claimed credit,
there is, among many here,
speculation already
of Irish Republican Army
involvement.
According
to eyewitness accounts,
Lord William Holmes,
the Queen Mother's cousin
and Minister of State
for Northern Ireland,
along with his wife and son,
would have most certainly
been killed
were it not for the heroic
efforts of this man--
John Patrick Ryan,
the American tourist
who broke up
the assassination attempt.
An author and professor
at the United States
Naval Academy
in Annapolis, Maryland,
Ryan is a former
Marine lieutenant.
Wounded in
the exchange of gunfire,
he is listed
in guarded condition
at an undisclosed
London hospital.
This is Deborah Weston,
CNN news, London.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
You're alive.
I forgive you.
Otherwise...
Hey, pumpkin.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You dignify their cowardice
with your silence.
They left you.
They drove off without you.
I'm curious as to what it is
you think you owe them.
If any of my mates
ever drove off
and left me in your hands,
I'd not only feel no
great sense of loyalty,
I'd make sure to remind meself
to kill them.
Who are they, Sean?
Where are they?
The trip was unscheduled.
How'd you know Lord Holmes
would be there?
I can't help you if you
don't talk to me, you know.
I'd tear your heart out
and serve it up
to you with chips
if I didn't know
you'd enjoy it,
you Fenian bastard.
No. Not in all eternity.
He'll not chirp a word.
Not Sean Miller...
and not while his brother
is lying on a slab.
What's the matter, Jimmy?
Don't you
believe it?
It's the entire thing
I don't believe.
The royal family, Kevin?
You know that only
turns people against us.
Look, this was
totally unauthorized,
and the other
brigade commanders,
they know that
you were behind it.
Fuck the bloody IRA.
All these
years of war,
and they've got
us nowhere.
In its heart and soul,
England is still a monarchy,
and that is where
we must strike--
at the royals
and the ruling class.
You're either with us
or you're against us, Jimmy-boy.
Make up your mind.
Oh, I'm with you.
Good.
That's all I wanted to hear.
I'll leave you to it.
Kevin...
Charlie's going
to drop by tonight
to try to straighten
things out.
Be smart.
Talk to him.
And hold your temper.
I promise.
Thanks, Jimmy.
Kevin.
Kevin, lad...
it's me, Charlie.
That's me holding my temper,
Jimmy-boy.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Oh, damn!
What?
I forgot.
Where's my bag?
You're not going to make me
wear a rubber, are you?
You know, the Church says
wearing one of them's
a sin, darlin'.
So is this...
darlin'.
So what can you
tell me about, uh...
about this guy?
Sean? Oh, he's a nice boy,
Sean Miller.
Shot a parish priest
in Derry...
during confession,
if you can imagine.
He thought the Father
was informing for the British.
Excuse me, Sergeant.
I don't think it's in
Mr. Ryan's best interests
or the prosecution's
to discuss matters
not directly related
to the events at hand.
If you can
confirm for me
that the man in
that photograph
is the same man you
disarmed in the square,
I think we'll
be through.
I can.
Do you have anything
to add, Mr. Ryan?
Yes.
Uh...
the man I killed was Miller's...
Brother.
Patrick.
Not even 17,
Paddy-boy.
Recruited by Sean
into the IRA...
Again, I think we'd
all be better served
if we could preserve
the clarity of your
eventual testimony.
I read it in the newspaper.
I can hardly see...
I'd appreciate
you refraining
from reading
the newspapers.
Not even Doonesbury?
Well...
do you have
anything to add?
No.
Mr. Ryan?
Yes.
My name's Jeffrey Watkins,
principal private
secretary to Lord Holmes.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
This is my wife, Catherine.
How do you do?
Hello.
So, Dr. Ryan, how is
your patient healing?
Just fine.
We're looking forward
to going home, though.
I can imagine.
May I introduce
his Lordship?
Oh, hello.
It's my great honor
to finally meet you, Dr. Ryan.
Thank you.
I owe you a debt of gratitude
that I shall never
be able to repay.
Not at all. Thank you
for your kind note.
I'm delighted
that you're here
to share in the
good news, Mrs. Ryan.
Her Majesty's decided
to invest
your husband KCVO--
Knight Commander
of the Victorian Order.
My congratulations, Sir.
Thank you.
Good luck today.
Sir Jack?
Lady Catherine.
Perhaps if I'd had
more time to think about it,
I would've preferred
to do something else.
So you're saying
you didn't have time,
is that it?
That's correct.
So you didn't.
Didn't what?
Think, sir.
You didn't think,
is the point I believe
you're trying to make.
No. Instead you raced
into a situation
of which, by
your own admission,
you had no understanding,
attacked my client, who was,
in fact, another pedestrian
hurrying to help.
Wearing a ski mask.
Shot a second man in the chest,
this one taking you--
can it be...?
After they shot me.
...three shots at
point-blank range
in order to fell
the second victim.
I used that force
I deemed necessary.
I should say so.
I doubt very much
whether anyone in this
courtroom would disagree.
Excuse me.
I didn't make this happen, sir.
No further questions.
He did.
Oh, My Lord, there is
one more question.
Are you still, Dr. Ryan,
in the paid service
of the Central
Intelligence Agency?
I should remind you
that you're under oath.
No.
I beg your pardon?
That's all.
Thank you.
The witness may stand down.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Gentlemen, I think this might be
an appropriate moment...
Bloody proud of yourself,
aren't you?
You stuck your nose in
where it didn't belong,
and now you've killed
my baby brother.
Hey, Daddy!
Hey, pumpkin.
Hey.
Wow! You guys
have really grown.
How are you feeling?
Not so good.
Tired?
No.
I have no idea
what time it is.
Feels like morning to me.
You're telling me.
Did I miss something?
No...
but I did.
I'm pregnant.
Honey!
Can I watch some TV?
I'm not at all tired.
What?
Plates.
I don't have any
say in this, do I?
Sure, you do, honey.
This is a family.
Everybody's got a say.
But my say's after the fact.
Or am I wrong?
No...
you're right.
Michaela really despises
her little sister.
Yeah?
Well...
Are you ready for this?
It could be even worse.
It could be a baby brother.
Oh, no. Boys.
I mean, do you refer to
these fighting men as terrorists?
No. You call them patriots.
Jack.
Boys are...
Do you, in fact, deny that the
Provisional Wing of the IRA
was behind
this assassination attempt?
When the IRA
carry out any form of campaign,
they admit to it.
Thank you.
That's the policy.
They'll proudly
say they did it.
Have the IRA admitted to this?
I mean,
common sense, logic,
some form of reason...
May I at least suggest
some names?
Some think your efforts in
America raising money
for the Irish cause
will be affected...
Sure, you can, honey.
Good morning, Mr. Cooley.
And to you, madam.
How is business?
Fine, thank you.
I came upon this first edition
at an estate auction.
Can your man restore it?
And when would you
want this by, madam?
Soon.
As you can see,
it's very pressing.
I'm not sure. The binder may
have some trouble with this.
Is that so?
I'll see what I can do.
He's not a miracle
worker, you know.
No, obviously
he's not, Mr. Cooley.
The best you can arrange, then.
Good day, Mr. Cooley.
Good day, madam.
Hello, Sean.
Don't mind if I come
along with you, do you?
Although I disapprove
of the things
you've done, Sean,
I can't quite bring
meself to condemn ya.
I can't...
because I understand
where the hatred comes from.
I more than
understand it.
But the present fact is
that we're very near now
the darkest hole
in all of Great Britain,
and you still
won't speak to me.
They're raising the bridge.
We'll be here
about five minutes.
Understood.
Mobile Three,
Lymington.
Hello, Lymington!
They jammed
the radio.
Open the door!
Open it, or
I'll kill him.
They've got the bridge keeper.
What do we do?
We open the door.
Open it!
But for Christ's sake...!
But what?
Wait until they kill him,
then open the door?
Your guns!
We are unarmed.
Just who the hell are you?
Get them out!
Get your heads down!
Lay down on
the bloody ground!
Don't you fucking move!
Didn't think we'd
forget about you, did you?
Inspector Robert Highland,
this is a
friend of mine.
We meet at
last, Mr. Highland.
Tell me, what do they pay you
to turn against
your own people, eh?
Get on with it
and be on your way.
Very well, if that's the
way you feel about it.
Come on, Cath!
Have I got the tickets,
or what?
I don't have them.
They're on the fridge.
Dad...
Honey, there's plenty of time.
Hello, Admiral.
Good morning, Jack.
You know Marty Cantor.
Marty.
How's the shoulder?
Not too bad.
Something's come up.
Can we sit down
and have a chat?
They were moving him to
Albany Prison on the Isle of Wight
when it happened.
We think
he's left the country.
Marty, excuse me.
Let's deal in what we know,
and not what we don't.
We know he's escaped.
We know it happened in Kent
near the Channel.
If he's left the country--
Jack, you listening?--
the chances he'd come here,
that he'd try
that he could come here
are so remote,
I have trouble
even saying it.
And yet your first instinct
was to come all the way out here
and tell me.
Marty, want to excuse us
a few minutes?
I've got a few more weeks
before school starts,
but I've got to... dig in
and prepare a few lectures.
Want to come down
and look over what we got?
You might turn up
something we haven't.
You're asking me
if I want to come back.
Yup.
We'll try and go
next week, honey.
All right.
Sorry.
Sean Miller escaped.
Well, what does that mean?
They just wanted me to know.
They thought I might
be concerned. I'm not.
The IRA's not stupid.
They're not going to
follow me all the way over here.
We talked about it.
They agreed.
They're gone. That's it.
They didn't ask you
to come back to CIA?
I said no.
Just like that.
I don't want
to go back, honey.
I saw them coming,
and I just...
I know.
I can't go back to that
life again... you know?
Sally! Wait up, honey.
I bet your cell was
even better than this--
the bloody Ritz in comparison.
At least you always had your
own toilet bowl, eh, Sean?
Come on, Sean, cheer up.
You've just been spared
a lifetime of hell on earth.
A word of gratitude
might even be in order.
I don't feel
like resting,
laying around in the sun like
some complacent tourist.
If we're to build an army, we've
got to train like soldiers,
and we can't do that
in Ireland. Not now.
Bleeding waste of time.
There's laying about,
and there's laying low.
There's a difference.
Is there?
It's Lord Holmes who should be
worried about complacency.
Next time he won't be so lucky.
Post him back to Whitehall
in little pieces
if that's what it takes
to free every Irish
political prisoner.
That's not who
I'm thinking of.
I know that, Sean, but what Ryan
done can't be undone,
so you should stop
thinking about him.
I can't.
How in the world could something
like this have happened?
Inspector Highland
picked the day,
picked the decoy routes,
picked the men,
and still they knew.
He had two children,
apparently.
It's tragic, tragic.
SO-13 have narrowed it down
to 31 people who had prior
knowledge of your itinerary
on the day of the attack
and of Miller's transfer,
five of whom are now dead.
Sir, I think it
might be best if we limit
your appointments
for the time being.
I will not have my itinerary
dictated to me
by terrorists.
Whoever this traitor is,
they better pray to God
I never find him.
We know you'll do
your best, Sergeant.
...You got to backstroke,
sidestroke to get to shore,
You got to backstroke,
And we don't know
if we're ever coming home,
Stand up, buckle up,
shuffle through the door,
Jump on out and shout
Marine Corps...
Egesta appealed to
Athens on what basis?
On what grounds?
Mr. Viederman?
Bad time for you?
Well, uh, they...
said they'd be grateful
didn't they?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Um...
Mm-hmm.
"Fight our battle,
and the rest of the world
will fear and respect you."
Yeah, but didn't
the rest of the world
fear and respect Athens already?
It didn't matter.
Why not?
Pride, sir?
That's the battle they lost.
The real battle.
Attention on deck!
Attention to orders.
I have a presentation
to make.
For service above and beyond
the call of duty
of a tourist,
even a Marine...
we recognize Professor
John Patrick Ryan
with the Order of
the Purple Target
and hope that he
will duck next time,
lest he become part of history
rather than a teacher of it.
How old is he?
Ten.
Plate glass window?
Mm-hmm.
Here we go.
Hi, guys.
Good morning, Cathy.
Hmm. I've got
a retina at 1:00.
We might have to bump it.
This could take some time.
Yep, let's bump it.
We're all set to go.
Okay, let's do it.
So you just waded on in
like John Wayne.
Why did you do it?
What were you thinking, man?
I don't know.
I wasn't thinking.
That's it?
You sound like
some of my students.
Just pissed me off.
I couldn't just stand
there and watch them
shoot those people
right in front of me.
It was... rage.
Pure rage.
It just made me mad.
Here's hoping you
never get mad at me, man.
Oh...
Okay, now it's my turn.
She's late, Sean.
Yeah, and then what?
And she was at this dance,
Yeah?
and then this guy,
at the end, he...
Eww!
Kind of cute, isn't she?
Is she?
Bye. See ya.
Hi, Mommy.
Hi, sweetie.
How are you?
Let's do it.
Goddamn!
Whoa! Not here.
Highway 50. West.
Good night, Doc.
Good night.
Dr. Ryan!
Clear the way!
Where's Sean Miller?
Dr. Ryan, get out
of the way, please!
Dr. Ryan!
This is surgery.
Yeah, Dr. Catherine Ryan,
please.
Dr. Ryan, Dr. Ryan,
are you all right?
She's left for the day.
How long?
Dr. Ryan.
Come on!
Surgery.
Yes. This is Dr. Ryan.
I'd like the results
on the Thompson boy's
retinal scan.
Hold, please.
Come on, Cathy,
get off the phone.
Look, Mom.
Ooh, it's beautiful.
Are you still holding?
Yes, I'm still holding.
Look, I'd like to speak
with Dr. Sutton.
Operator, I want to make
an emergency breakthrough.
The number is 555-3464.
Yeah, it's a mobile phone, yeah.
What do you mean I can't?
Faster, damn it!
Come on, Cath.
Watch it, buddy!
Dr. Ryan, we have the results
of that retinal scan,
and everything is fine.
That's great. Thank you.
Jesus!
Hello.
Cathy.
Jack?
Cath, something's
happened, honey.
Is Sally with you?
Yeah.
Hi, Dad!
Is everything all right?
Yeah, everything's fine.
There she is.
Right.
Honey, I want you
to get off the highway
and get to the nearest
police station
as quick as you can, all right?
The police station?
Cathy, just get
off the highway right now.
Steady, mate.
Steady.
Where are you now?
I'm at Rowe Boulevard.
There's a State Police
barracks at Houston Street.
I'll meet you there.
Okay.
Is something
wrong, Mom?
No. Everything's fine.
It's okay.
They're gone.
I got it!
Coming in!
Mr. Ryan?
Yeah.
Your wife's okay.
She sustained a concussion,
but we ran a complete skull...
She's pregnant.
I know.
The baby's okay.
You don't have to worry...
What about my daughter?
Let's sit down for a moment.
No. Talk to me.
It's going to be
a little while before we know,
maybe in the morning.
She, uh...
Where's Sally?
She's in the recovery room,
honey.
They're watching her.
We'll know in seven
or eight hours.
They had to remove
her spleen.
She's in pretty bad shape.
I'm sorry.
Harry Johnson is standing by.
In a few moments,
he expects to have a statement
from Mr. Paddy O'Neil.
Mr. O'Neil is the Sinn Fein
representative...
Jack.
Here you go.
You okay?
And now we go
to Harry Johnson
ready to speak
with Mr. Paddy O'Neil.
I've come to stand vigil
and to pray for the recovery
of the victims
of this senseless attack.
Sinn Fein are outraged,
as indeed are most
Irish Catholics this morning
at this heinous crime.
Look, I want to share
with Dr. Ryan, personally,
our empathy and anguish,
but I will wait
as I feel it proper
for the most
appropriate time.
Can you confirm or deny
that funding
for the IRA...?
The IRA are not
responsible for this attack.
What you're saying is
the IRA had nothing
to do with this incident?
Uh, no more questions.
Thank you, Mr. O'Neil.
She's going to be okay.
Thank you.
She's all right.
Ryan.
Mr. Ryan.
Mr. Ryan, I'd like
to share with you
our deep regret about...
No bullet wounds.
Mr. Ryan.
Cathy Ryan's
concussion is mild, however.
We expect her to be released
within two to three days.
You know the deal, Jack.
Come on, you are involved.
Marty, don't tell me about the deal.
I know the deal.
That is not good process.
You are the victim of a crime,
I...
and that does not make
for the best analysis
even if you knew something
about terrorism,
which you do not.
I have guys on it
guys who know something
about the IRA.
Marty, I am not standing here...
This is not Naval intelligence.
Marty, I am not standing here
with my hat in my hand.
I am telling you,
I want back in.
Jack.
Sir.
Thank God about Sally.
Thank you.
Alice and I
are relieved beyond words.
You manage any sleep?
Not much, sir.
I'm interrupting something.
You were explaining to Jack
about how we'd be better off
without him
around here...
or something
along those lines.
Marc Spiva, Jack Ryan.
Nice to meet you.
Tony Ferro.
Hi.
Alex Winter.
Jack.
Nice to meet you, Alex.
Well.
Rose.
I have to say you're looking
better than I expected.
It's an illusion, I'm afraid.
Of course it would have
to be, wouldn't it?
Well, it's good to see
you again regardless.
You, too.
Look, we've carved
a niche for you,
and here's your
night-table reading.
Oh, my.
"Father killed by RUC."
"Belfast. 1979."
This way.
Over here.
Good morning, sir.
Cut the engine, please.
Can I see some form
of identification, please?
Did you see the game, then?
Yeah. It was all right.
That penalty...
What the hell?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Nobody move!
Get them up!
Morning.
Kevin O'Donnell,
longtime IRA strategist,
friend of the Miller family.
He was there when
Timothy Miller was killed, '79.
Looked after his boys,
Sean and Patrick.
This photo's
not a year old.
I think if we could
find O'Donnell,
we'll find Miller
still standing at his side.
Are you with me? Jack?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm just thinking.
What about the gun?
What about it?
Think it's going
to turn up registered?
Son of a bitch.
What?
Um...
Look, um...
SO-13 gets an anonymous tip
about some bomb-like stuff
on a table in an apartment.
They go in, and they get
some IRA bad guys,
they look around,
and they see there's no way
anybody could have seen
through the window
like the tipster said.
We got three IRA hit men
at a farmhouse
hit by somebody else.
That's British soldiers
getting out of hand, Jack.
They're not above it,
not after a hit
on the royal family.
No, no, no, no, look.
We got Brigade Commander
of the IRA, Jimmy O'Reardon
who checks into
a cheap hotel room,
ends up dead.
Double tap to the head--
very professional.
And that was... how long
after the farmhouse?
Same day.
What are you
coming to, Jack?
Jack!
Where are you going?
I'm just going to go
throw some water on my face.
Jack!
Excuse me.
I, uh, think one of us
is in the wrong room.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Jack!
Get down!
When the IRA carry
out any form of campaign,
they admit to it.
Get down!
I mean, common sense, logic...
Get down! Get down!
We didn't get any prints
or anything like that.
Listen, who are
we looking for here, huh?
IRA terrorists
or some ultraviolent
faction of the IRA
fighting the cause their way?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jimmy O'Reardon
checked into a hotel
with a woman with long hair,
long red hair.
This is who
we should be looking for.
We find her, we'll find him.
I saw his wife
and daughter die,
but she and Neddie blew it.
Ryan's still alive.
They're not dead, Sean.
What?
They survived it.
I can't say it any
plainer than that.
It doesn't matter.
The trip served its purpose.
It does matter.
Sean, Americans
hold their breath
every time a little girl falls
down a pipe in a backyard,
but you've shot at one
with a submachine gun
on her way back
from school.
Well, we've started
the bleeding war.
The Brits
are tearing apart Belfast
for the IRA,
and their American money are
denying the hits so loud,
it only makes them
look more guilty.
The war is raging,
and when it's over,
we'll be the only ones
left standing.
Sean, I let you go
for Paddy-boy,
but that's it.
We've got work to do,
and it's not
in Maryland.
Hello.
Yeah.
How's the family, Ryan?
You nearly lost them,
didn't you?
It's easy to get at them.
You should look after
your family better, you know.
Are you there?
Yeah.
I understand your little girl's
feeling better, eh?
Lost her spleen, though, yeah?
Pity that.
Make it mighty tough on her
to fight off infection,
eh, Jackie?
You sick son of a bitch.
It was him,
wasn't it?
He's never going
to leave us alone.
He'll never get that close
to us again, honey.
That's why he's making calls
in the middle of the night.
That's all he can do.
You get him, Jack.
I don't care what
you have to do.
Just get him.
Here's to you
My brave Irish laddies
We'll not be broken,
downhearted, and sad
So let us drink a toast
to all our comrades
That stand for the honor
And pride of our land...
Can I buy you a drink?
No.
Let me buy you one.
Barney, two whiskeys.
The IRA's not responsible
for all this.
I know that.
Are you waiting for me
to agree with you?
I've been saying this
to the press
till I'm blue in the face.
Well, that's the
point, isn't it?
You claim responsibility
for one thing,
deny it for another.
Nobody believes you anymore.
I want to know
where Sean Miller
and Kevin O'Donnell are.
Let me try
and understand this.
You want me to sell out
my fellow Irishmen to you?
Is that why
you came down here?
You don't understand me
at all.
Oh, I think I do.
Look, I don't give a damn
what they've done,
but the day that I
sell out my countrymen
will be the day
that I put a bullet
through my own head.
That's it, then, huh?
That's it.
You know, on second thought,
maybe I won't have
a drink with you.
Okay, then I'll go home.
Have a safe trip.
I'll go home and call
the TV stations,
give them what they want--
let them take their cameras
into my daughter's
hospital room.
Put it on the evening news.
I don't give a shit
whether you did it or not,
and neither will anyone else,
but I will put
such a stranglehold
on your gun money,
you'll be out in the
street throwing rocks.
I will fucking destroy you.
I will make it
my mission in life.
Excuse me.
Well, lads, did you hear that?
Stand sideways-- you're
less of a target.
Yes!
Satellite's coming!
Celts, let's go!
Come on.
Get inside!
So...
SO-13 traced
the weapons used
in the Lord Holmes incident
to an arms dealer
that supplies Kaddafi.
Now, when
Sean Miller escaped,
he was last seen in a zodiac
heading out into the Channel
in a gale,
which didn't make sense until
I checked on the freighters
that were out there that day.
Syrian registry.
Known to carry arms
from the Middle East
to client states
in the Mediterranean
including Kaddafi.
So Miller takes a slow boat
to North Africa.
Exactly.
Now, we send our birds
up over the desert,
photographing, what,
how many camps?
182.
182 camps a day
in North Africa.
Libyan bases, PLO, Red Brigade,
Action-Directe,
West German Red Army Faction.
But on the day
that this particular ship
docked in Benghazi,
there's activity
in only nine camps
with people arriving.
Now, this one
we know for sure is PLO.
This one's Shining Path.
These seven we're not
so sure about.
Why?
Well, we got satellites...
Well, because the
people in those camps
know probably better than
we do exactly what time
the satellite's
going to pass overhead.
And, Marty...
unless you authorize us
to retask those satellites
so we can get a look before
they're overhead from the side,
we are never going to know
which camp they're at.
Jack, do you have
any idea how big a deal it is
to retask those satellites?
Yeah.
Bring up camp 18 again.
Tighten on the camp here.
Let's look up in here...
see what we can see.
Show me this grouping here.
Hmm.
Hmm. No, that's nothing.
Go back to the, uh,
bigger picture.
Let me see down here.
What's that?
Tighten up on that,
will you?
Hmm...
Can you enhance that,
sharpen it up?
Tits.
I don't know.
SAS could take out
any one of these camps
in under two minutes,
kill everybody there,
and be gone before
the echo fades.
Are you sure
this is the same woman?
Keep at it, then.
Son of a bitch.
Hi.
Read it again, Daddy.
"The sun did not shine.
"It was too wet to play,
so we sat in the house
all that cold, cold, wet day."
"I sat there with Sally.
"We sat there, we two,
"and I said, how I wish
we had something to do.
"Too wet to go out,
too cold to play ball,
"so we sat in the house.
"We did nothing at all.
"So all we could do
was just sit, sit, sit, sit.
And we did not like it,
not one little bit."
"And then something went...
boom."
Dr. Hamani, please report
to the second floor
nurses' station. Dr. Hamani.
Paddy O'Neil
can sleep at night.
In fact, he probably
enjoys the irony.
She's not Irish. She's English.
And this is the girl
you saw...
in the blink of an eye
in a jeep as it
passed you doing 40?
Yeah.
What am I supposed
to do here?
Tell SO-13 you know who she is.
Tell them her name.
Give them her picture.
Tell them that she poses
as a rare book dealer
and ask them
to look for her.
What do you mean
what do you do?
What am I supposed
to do with you, Jack?
You walk into a bar, half of
whose customers want you dead.
You walk up to
the IRA's bagman,
and in front of his guys,
you threaten him?
You're not a field man,
Jack. You never were.
You are an analyst.
Analyze that.
I am not after
your job, Marty.
I'm after the man
who tried to kill my family.
Then will you think?
You tell O'Neil that
you're looking for a girl.
He gives you the
pictures of a girl.
He obliges you
to get you off his back,
and you believe him?
I didn't tell him
I was looking for a girl, Marty.
What's going on?
Sarge?
Hmm?
Come and look at this.
Bit of a bookworm meself,
not that you'd know it
to look at me.
What's your passion, then,
mysteries? Spy novels?
Familiar with Ian Fleming,
are you?
This is a
rare book shop.
Rare books?
Yeah, so they are.
Can you locate
the problem,
or do I have to call
someone else?
Already have.
The wiring in
this whole place
dates from
before the war.
The first war.
It's what we call in the
electrical business "rare."
Yes. Can you fix it?
Oh, sure. I can fix it.
Can you afford it?
That's the question.
Just fix it.
Hello.
He's seen it,
hasn't he?
I don't know.
He's got it. Look.
Hey, what do you
make of this?
I, uh...
I... I have no idea.
Damn!
Um...
I have to go out now
for a few minutes...
to deliver some books.
Please keep about
your repairs.
I'll be here all week, guv.
Don't worry.
He's mine!
Damn!
Dinner at the White
House is no problem.
What is the problem?
No problem, we're just
running out of dates.
Yes. We could do that.
Move that to there,
which would leave us...
the 14th?
The 14th.
Geoffrey
let's check
with John Ryan
about scheduling
a presentation dinner
at our embassy
in Washington on the, uh...
14th.
The 14th.
So let's go over this again
so I can get it clear.
Geoffrey Watkins.
Oh, I beg your pardon. I'm
trying to reach Mr. Titus.
Is that extension 2691?
No, this is 2619.
I'm terribly sorry.
What are you doing up?
Go back to bed.
I wanted to be there
when she wakes up.
I'll go with you,
and then I'll take a cab back.
Okay.
Hello.
Yes. Just a minute.
It's for you...
Sir John.
Hello.
Excuse me, sir.
Mr. Ryan has a special
celebration that evening
that he can't change.
He wondered if you
might care to join them.
Where, at his house?
Yes, sir.
Why not?
We shot this eight
days ago in Berlin.
Mm-hmm.
One...
two...
three, four Brits
traveling with him.
Light arms.
The heavy stuff's
in the cars.
He's German...
he's German.
This boring you, Sean?
Four, six altogether.
Should be the same security
when Holmes flies to Washington.
We've got to find the moment
when he's unprotected.
Four days in Washington,
one day in New York.
Shopping.
Yeah. Two Caucasians.
Take a look at
the one with the hat.
His arms look a little pink.
Sunburn. New arrival.
What do you think,
same guy?
That rare book dealer,
Dennis Cooley...
he's bald.
Now, it's possible
there could be a woman
in some of these camps,
but with her and Cooley
in the same place--
if that is Cooley--
the odds of coincidence
are dropping fast.
Still, I... I don't know.
There's no way I can be...
absolutely certain.
Excuse me, Jack.
Tell me one thing in life
that is absolutely
for certain.
My daughter's love.
What I need to hear from
you is your best guess,
and I think I've heard it.
Haven't I?
The bastards took away
my book shop.
They took away my books!
I'm sorry, Dennis.
You can't come.
You haven't got the training,
and this mission's
going to be very messy.
I can fire a gun.
Sorry, Dennis.
Where are you
taking me, Marty?
It's you who've
taken us, Jack.
Satellite now
entering target area.
Into battle.
Sir.
Enlargement sector four.
Airborne support
approaching target area--
ETA, 35 seconds.
SAS team on ground.
Enlarge camp 18.
Enlarging.
Enlarge primary target.
That is a kill.
Roger, roger.
It's go, go, go.
Targets have
been neutralized.
Airborne support approaching.
Enlarge sector five.
Angle on sector nine.
Sector nine.
Angle sector two.
Sector two.
SAS team withdrawing.
Keyhole is passing
out of visual.
It's over.
Come on, honey.
Jump.
See?
Appreciate it. Thanks.
Surveillance team one,
all clear.
Roger that.
You sure your men outside
wouldn't like some coffee?
No, thank you, Mrs. Ryan.
They'll be just fine.
Okay.
And I'd to thank
you, Miss Ryan,
for allowing us to impose
upon your homecoming.
You're wel...
You're a beautiful
and gracious young lady,
You're wel...
and it's my distinct pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
You're welcome.
I thought I might make
the presentation
after dinner if you agree.
Oh, sure.
Would you like to see it now?
Uh, Geoffrey...
Oh, my. That's very nice.
Didn't I already give
you one of those?
Help yourselves.
Is that your second piece
of cake, my little sweetie?
Where's the bathroom, Jack?
Um, second door on the left.
Thank you.
More coffee, anyone?
I'd love some.
Uh, excuse me.
Here it comes.
Bathroom?
Someone in there.
No, that's not it.
That's... the basement.
Hello.
Jack? Marty.
Hey, Marty. What's going on?
I'm sorry to interrupt
your party,
but I thought
you'd like to know right away.
SAS just made positive ID
on Dennis Cooley.
What about the others?
Well, it was pretty messy
as it turns out.
It's going to take 48 hours
to verify the dental records,
but they're keeping right on it.
Oh, great.
What?
The storm just knocked out
the power here to the house.
I got to light some candles.
I'll light one for you, too.
Okay, Marty. Thanks.
What, forget to pay
your bill, Cath?
Oh, Robert... very funny.
Everyone all right?
We're fine, Jack.
This doesn't happen
very often.
Only when we have
royalty over for dinner.
I knew you'd understand.
Something wrong?
Come with me, will you?
If the storm had
knocked out the lights,
they'd be out in
the boathouse, too.
So?
Power comes in
from the street,
and then branches off to here.
Jesus.
This is Ryan. Any DSS agent?
Any DSS agent, this is Ryan.
Maryland troopers? Anyone?
Is anyone reading me?
Anybody?
Can I come back down
when the lights are on?
No, sweetie.
You got to get some sleep.
It's very late.
Goddamn.
Don't tell me.
Quite a storm.
Take your hands off me.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
Jack!
Gun.
Jack.
Uh-uh. Stay right there.
Shit.
Rob, over here.
What's the plan?
How many are coming?
Where's Sean Miller?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Give me the gun.
Five, six...
I don't know. Maybe more.
I'll get the others.
Don't turn on the lights.
Take this. Get down
in the basement quick.
Where's Cathy and Sally?
They're upstairs.
She's putting Sally to bed.
Go.
What's wrong?
Come on, Ryan. Show yourself.
Annette, upstairs.
Right.
Come on, sweetie, come on.
What's wrong, Mommy?
Shh, Shh.
Now, you've got to help me.
Climb up on the stool.
There's a shotgun there.
Oh, God, Jack,
what did you do with the shells?
Go. Go, go, go, go.
Get down.
Mommy!
Go on.
Get back.
You all right?
Where's Sally?
Daddy...
Sally?
It's okay, honey.
Come on, come on.
Honey, you just got
to be real quiet.
Real quiet.
Gotcha.
Christ.
Hold on.
Come on, come on.
What are you talking about?
Who is off the air?
DSS, state troopers, everyone.
The security company rep...
Get me Hostage Rescue
at Quantico now.
Robby! Open up.
Robby, it's us.
Jack?
They're outside.
Sean, cool it.
It's the royal we want.
We can't ransom a dead body.
They're all over
the place, man.
Stay close to me.
How were you going
to get away, huh?
Want to go
for the other knee?
Come on.
Boats. Bottom of the cliff.
There are ropes.
Kevin!
You killed him!
No, Sean, no!
We need Holmes alive!
We're past that!
Alive!
Come on!
Any contact?
Still off the air.
There he is!
Stay down there.
Come on, you bastards.
Come on! Come on!
He's alone!
He's leading us away
from the royal!
Turn around, Sean.
No.
Turn it round, Sean!
-Turn it round, Sean!
-No!
Sean!
Turn it round!
Forget about Ryan!
Don't blow
the mission now, boy!
That's not my mission!
You crazy bastard!
Damn!
Had enough to eat, honey,
or do you want something else?
Want some toast or...?
Pancakes.
There's no time
for pancakes, honey.
Do you want toast
or toast?
Toast.
Is somebody going to get that?
I'm getting it.
Sally?
Hello. It is.
Yeah, hold
on a second.
Where's your backpack?
It's Dr. Zaillian.
The amnio.
Yeah.
Hello.
Is it going to be okay?
It's going to be fine, honey.
We're just waiting to find out.
Great.
What do you want
on your toast, honey?
Strawberry?
Strawberry.
Hold on a second.
Do you want to know
what it is?
Did he tell you?
He's asking. I'm asking you.
I don't know.
Do you want to know?
I don't know. Do you?
Well, I thought I wanted to
know, but now I'm not so sure.
Hold on a second.
We're discussing it.
Me, neither.
I mean, I do and I don't.
Um...
He's waiting.
Okay.
Tell us.
Okay, tell us.
Thank you.
I would travel
Back through
twisted years
Through the bitter
westward wind
If the God above
would let me lie
In a quiet place
above the wind...