My children.
From the very beginning, it was
the children who gave me my power.
"The Springwood Slasher,"
that's what they called me.
My reign of terror
was legendary.
Dozens of children would fall
by my blades.
Then the parents of Springwood
came for me...
...taking justice into
their own hands.
When I was alive,
I might have been a little naughty.
But after they killed me,
I became something much, much worse.
The stuff nightmares are made of.
The children still feared me...
...and their fear gave me the power
to invade their dreams.
And that's when the fun
really began.
Until they figured out a way
to forget about me.
To erase me completely.
Being dead wasn't a problem.
But being forgotten, now that's a bitch.
It's only a dream!
Die, motherfucker!
I can't come back
if nobody remembers me.
I can't come back if
nobody's afraid.
I had to search the
bowels of hell...
...but I found someone.
Someone who'll make them remember.
He may get the blood,
but I'll get the glory.
And that fear is
my ticket home.
Mike?
Is that you?
All right, fuck you then.
I'm heading in.
Mike?
Come on, it's not funny anymore.
Ah!
No!
Jason.
I should have been watching them,
not drinking.
Not meeting a boy at the lake.
I deserved to be punished.
We all deserved to be punished.
Jason.
My special, special boy.
Do you know what your gift is?
No matter what they do to you,
you cannot die.
You can never die.
You've just been sleeping, honey.
But now the time has
come to wake up.
Mommy has something
she wants you to do.
I need you to go to Elm Street.
The children have been very bad
on Elm Street.
Rise up, Jason.
Your work isn't finished.
Hear my voice and live again.
Make them remember me, Jason.
Make them remember
what fear tastes like.
I've been away from my children
for far too long.
Marry, fuck or kill.
Your choices are the Three Stooges.
Go. Kia.
Oh, God.
Which one had the super
bad toupee hair?
Harry. Mar--
- No, no, no, it was Moe.
- Moe.
- Yeah.
- Either one, I'd kill him.
Okay, who would you fuck, then?
- This is stupid, y'all, stupid.
- Oh, come on.
Oh, God, whatever.
Look, I'd fuck the bald guy
and I'd marry Larry, Jesus.
Is this what we're doing all night?
Because, y'all, this is really stank.
Hey. Gibb, what are you doing?
I thought you were gonna quit.
- I only smoke when I drink now.
- But you're always drinking.
Yeah, well, I'll work on that next.
Hey, okay. I got another one.
Fred, Scooby or Shaggy?
I'm not answering that
and neither is she.
- Do you guys think I should get a nose job?
- Oh, my God.
Oh, please.
Kia, what you need is a lobotomy.
I think I'm gonna get some candles.
I'm gonna get some beer.
Do you guys want anything?
- Are you sure you should be driving?
- I'm so under the limit, Lori.
- Surprise.
- Oh, Trey, you answered my prayers.
Thank you.
Whoa, babe. What did I tell you
about kissing me after you smoked, huh?
Lighten up. They're menthols.
Yeah, I brought Blake.
Where's Linda?
It's "Lori."
This is her house,
so don't be a total cocksmith.
Whatever.
- Where are the ladies?
- Relax, they'll be here.
I'm relaxed, man.
I'm just wet. It sucks.
Did you know they were coming over?
You gotta be quiet.
Hey, we knew you gonna be here
all alone this weekend.
I mean, Blake's cute.
- He's not my type.
- Who is?
No one's ever gonna live up to the
fuzzy memory of your first love, Lori.
You were fucking 14, get over it.
Yeah, I know we were young,
but what Will and I had was real.
Well, correct me if I'm wrong...
...but didn't Mr. Real just drop-kick your ass
without so much as a goodbye handshake?
He ever even call or maybe even write
to you after he moved?
- Send you an e-mail?
- No.
You see my point.
It's time to leave the convent, Lori.
You need to meet a guy.
Ugh.
Hey, Lori,
I like the flow of your place.
- Got good feng shui.
- Yeah.
You know about feng shui?
Oh. Oh!
Oh, you should see her bedroom.
Great flow in there.
Lori, why don't you go upstairs
and show Blake your feng shui?
Shut up.
I got a kink in my neck.
Come on, you can massage
it out for me.
I think I need a few more drinks
before there'll be any massaging.
- What do you see in him?
- I don't know.
But he has a cute ass.
Babe.
Don't make me ask you twice, okay?
So, Lori, am I gonna
get that grand tour or what?
Yeah. You know, why don't you start
in the kitchen and get us some beers?
Cool.
Oh, my God, Kia, he is a total idiot.
Get him out of here.
Oh, Lori, come on,
give him a chance.
I don't like him.
You know what? You don't like anybody.
Lori, you've barely gone out since--
Since what? Since my mom died?
Yeah, you know what, my dad needs me.
So I can't just go out
with guys all the time.
And if I did, it would not be
with somebody like Blake.
Yeah, fuck me, baby.
Your back door was open.
I closed it.
Babe, you know I don't like
to be touched after, okay?
Fine. I'll go have a shower then.
Good.
Your hair smells
like menthols, anyway.
Asshole.
Ah!
Trey.
What the hell are you doing?
Ah!
Help!
- Help us!
- Help us! Please, help us!
- Help! Help! Somebody help us!
- Somebody!
Wait! Help us!
- Help us.
- You kids need some assistance?
What the fuck do you think?
We need to lock this down now.
Keep it contained, you hear me?
Killed in bed? Jesus.
It's even the same damn house.
1428 Elm.
It's gotta be him, right?
It's gotta be Freddy Kru--
Hey, don't even say that son
of a bitch's name out loud.
Let's just keep it together.
We've been through too much
to let this thing spread now.
Take all these kids to the station.
Keep them separate. Do it now.
Yes, sir.
- We'll be in touch.
- Thank you. Let's go.
So?
She doesn't know anything.
None of them do.
- I'm sure we're good.
- Pretty sure?
Make sure none of those kids
knows anything...
...or I'll send your ass
up to Westin Hills with them.
- Knows what? What do you mean?
- Good work there tonight, Stubbs.
Right place, right time.
But we'll take it from here,
all right?
Your father's on his way.
- Do they know who did this?
- No, not yet.
But I thought I heard one of
the officers mention a name.
You know, to tell you the truth, Lori,
I just moved here about a month ago.
But if they have a suspect, I'd know.
They asked me all these really
weird questions, like, about my dream--
What was the name?
Freddy.
Hello?
Are you okay?
Oh!
His name is Freddy Krueger.
And he loves children.
Especially little girls.
Freddy's coming back.
Soon he'll be strong enough.
It's okay to be afraid.
We were all afraid.
Warn your friends. Warn everyone.
Ah!
One, two, Freddy's coming for you
Three, four, better lock your door
Five, six, grab a crucifix
Seven, eight, gonna stay up late
Nine, ten, never sleep again
One, two, Freddy's coming for you
- Ah!
Blake, we have to talk.
What the hell were you
doing over there?
You were supposed
to be watching your sister.
What, were you drinking?
My best friend was just killed, Dad!
So how about giving me
some fucking space?
You watch yourself, boy.
I'm gonna get him for you, Trey.
Cop let it slip.
Somebody named Freddy.
I'm gonna take him out myself, Trey.
Swear to God.
Who is that?
Someone there?
Jesus.
Ah!
I'm okay. I'm all right.
Not strong enough yet.
Well, I will be soon enough.
Until then,
I'll let Jason have some fun.
Dad.
Ah!
"Hypnocil."
What does this shit do, anyway?
How come we all have to take it?
Keeps you nice and docile
while I kick your little ass.
I'm fine with that.
We interrupt this program
for a special report.
After tonight's murder
in this neighborhood of Springwood...
...Sheriff's Department has confirmed
that there is one victim.
Hey, turn that up, man.
Details of the tragedy
remain sketchy--
Sorry, Will. You know the rules.
Turn that back on.
I know somebody that lives in that house.
Come on, turn it back on, man.
I never ask for anything.
Just turn on the fucking TV, please.
Fuck you, man.
What the fuck is your problem?
What are you doing? You want 10 cc's
of that pink tranquilizer in your ass?
That was Lori's house.
They said something about a murder.
I gotta go there.
I gotta go see if she's okay.
Back to Springwood?
Do you want me
to start having nightmares again?
Don't start with that dream-demon
shit again, okay?
You know that's all just in your head.
Yeah, and who are you?
The poster boy for sanity?
You're the one that told the cops
Lori's dad killed his wife.
Looks like someone else got killed
in the same house.
You think that's a coincidence?
Two murders in one house?
Kurt.
How may times do I have to tell you, man?
I don't do checkers.
I'm an Uno guy, all right?
So go grab the fucking Uno deck
and we'll play, okay?
Please. Thank you.
Look at us, Will.
Look around you, man.
We're institutionalized.
We're stuck here.
We're not going anywhere.
I do miss my family, man.
I mean, it's been four years
since I've seen them, you know.
All these years, you're still
convinced you saw her father do that?
I know what I saw, Mark.
Fuck what the doctors tried
to get me to believe.
I need to know if she's okay.
You wanna play?
Sweet dreams, monkey boy.
What the hell was that for, man?
You're a fucking lunatic, you know that?
I know you are, but what am I?
Are you sure you didn't see anyone?
No, Dad. None of us did.
I already went over this with the police.
It's just, I don't know what I'd do
without you. You're all I have left.
Dad, I'm not going anywhere.
I promise.
Look at you.
You're exhausted.
Lori.
We need to get you to bed.
I don't wanna go to sleep, Dad.
I just wanna see my friends.
I don't think it's a good idea
for you to go to school today.
You've been through
a traumatic experience.
Dad, please.
I just need to get out of the house, okay?
I'll be fine, I promise.
Well, at least drink your juice.
Will Rollins and the Davis boy escaped
from Westin Hills last night.
Oh, Jesus.
It's all coming apart again.
Don't worry. We'll find them.
Keep this thing contained.
- Lori.
- Oh, my God.
Hello. -God, you guys,
I'm so glad you're here.
Blake's dead too.
What?
Yeah, he....
He was stabbed to death late last night.
- Same with his dad.
- What?
Shit, shit. This is bullshit. The police
are blaming everything on Blake...
...like it's some kind of Columbine thing,
or something. They say he went crazy.
Killed Trey, killed his dad
and then took his own life.
This is so fucking messed up.
This is messed up.
Excuse me, sorry.
Lori?
- What is it, Linderman?
- Hey, Kia.
Well, I heard what happened,
and I just wanna express how--
Or to tell you how sorry I was.
Thank you. That's sweet.
Right. You know, if you need anybody
to talk to or maybe--
Whoa, Linderman, let me give you a tip.
Place your hormones back in the box
and quit while you're ahead, okay?
We don't have time for date-a-dork
right now. Thanks.
Right. Sorry.
I swear, every day it's the same thing.
He's like one of those fucking froufrou dogs
that keeps humping your leg.
- Give a couple to some ladies.
- I see what you're saying, Gibb...
...but that's why you should go.
Be amongst friends where it's safe.
There's gonna be a whole lot of loving
there for you and my boy, Trey.
Yeah, you're right. I should go.
I could use a few dozen drinks.
- For sure.
- Attagirl. Let your freak-flag fly.
See you there.
You wanna go?
- What is it?
- No, I don't think so.
- Why?
- I didn't get much sleep last night.
And when I did sleep,
I had the most terrible nightmares.
Lori, you had to sleep at a police station.
I'd have nightmares too.
No, no, no, it wasn't like that.
I mean, this was really real.
I mean, there was this man,
but he was more like a monster really.
And they kept calling him Freddy,
and he was so real.
Shh. What did he look like?
He had this dark-brown hat...
...and his skin was terribly burned.
And then on his right hand he had,
like, these razor fingers, and--
- You must be tripping.
- No, no, no.
- And then there was these little girls--
- It's okay, it was a bad dream.
They were singing like this song, like--
One, two, Freddy's coming for you
You know why they sing that?
Because that's when he comes for you.
In your dreams. You're lucky to be alive.
Who is he?
He's a child murderer that some parents
from around here burned alive.
- Then he came back.
- Oh, shit.
Back for revenge in our nightmares.
- Funny no one ever told us about it.
- Okay, thank you.
You want some free advice? Coffee.
Make friends with it.
Mark. That's enough.
You're scaring her.
Will?
I thought you might be in trouble, so--
Lori. Oh, my God, Lori.
Lori, honey, wake up.
Someone get help, please.
Someone just get me--
- Someone get some help.
- Will, the principal.
- Get me some help.
- Bro, let's go.
Are you okay?
Please, somebody help her. Lori.
How much longer is it gonna take?
Is she okay or what?
For nose jobs, what kind of anesthesia
do the doctor's use?
They put you all the way under, right?
Got your nose.
Ah!
Strong work, man.
I came to make sure she's okay,
and you put her in the infirmary.
- And you're facilitating?
- Exactly, we'll go back to my office.
What were you thinking about
telling her all that stuff, man?
We're not in groups.
I'm thinking for the first time in my life
that maybe I'm not crazy.
That my brother wasn't crazy.
She had the same dream, Will.
Will Rollins. Mark Davis.
This doesn't make any sense.
There's nothing on Krueger.
Not his arrest, his death,
not even a birth certificate.
Whole sections of the records are gone.
Look at all these blacked-out obituaries.
January 18th.
That's the day
my brother committed suicide.
Why isn't that in here?
I don't know.
But I'm sure there's a good reason.
Remember in group when they told us
not to jump to conclusions?
Listen to yourself.
You're holding on to that psychobabble...
...like it's some kind of security blanket,
man.
Let it go. They covered him up, Will.
They never told us about Freddy.
That's how they decided to beat him.
They treated him
like he was a fucking disease.
They locked up kids who made contact
with him so they wouldn't infect the others.
- That's crazy.
- Is it?
How come we were never allowed
to call any of our friends, man?
How come none of our friends
ever called us?
We were in a fucking quarantine, man.
That's what Westin Hills was for.
Well, even if all you're saying is true,
then why didn't Freddy kill Lori?
Maybe he's not strong enough yet.
My brother said it's our fear
that gives him his power.
Yeah, well, you sure as hell
spread enough fear today at school.
Holy shit.
You're right, they wanted to forget Freddy
so they wouldn't fear him, that's--
- What if I screwed up the town's plan?
- No.
Fuck. This fucker's gonna spread
like the plague, man.
Kids are gonna start falling asleep.
It's go--
- Let's leave, let's leave.
- No, I can't leave.
- Why not?
- I gotta go talk to Lori.
- I gotta see if she's okay.
- Is she worth dying for?
Because if you sleep,
you ain't waking up.
Yeah, well, if that's the case,
how come you're not dead?
Or any of the freaks at Westin, huh?
When's the last time you had a nightmare?
I don't know.
I can't remember my dreams anymore.
Look, just give me one night, okay?
Just let me find Lori,
and then we're out of here.
I swear.
All right, but if your ass isn't back here
by dawn, I'm gone. We clear on that?
This baby's my brother's pride and joy,
so be careful.
- Oh, shit.
- Linderman.
Shack, I don't drink.
Hi, Lori.
I didn't think I'd see you here.
Can I get you something to drink?
Oh, smooth opening, but you know,
we're already taken care of.
What happened to your clothes?
Oh, this?
I was playing a drinking game
with some of the lower primates.
I guess I'm penalized for my ability
to read above a fourth-grade level.
Linderman, you know, I always pictured you
as a straight-up bed-wetter.
You know what, Kia?
I used to think you hated me...
...because I wasn't good enough for Lori.
But that's not it.
You tear me down to make yourself feel
better because you hate yourself.
Which is pathetic when you stop
and think about it.
Assuming, of course, you can think with
all that makeup weighing down your head.
Cops said Blake committed suicide.
Apparently, it was grief over Trey.
No, that's bullshit.
I heard some guy Krueger killed them both.
I said his name to my parents,
they almost shit.
Yeah, I heard that Freddy freak
used to live here.
Fucking gutted Trey
like a goddamn turkey, man.
Like, I heard his intestines and shit
were just on the floor.
Oh, shit. Yeah, I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Look who's here. Look who's here.
What are you looking at?
Come on, come on, let's dance.
Come on, Linderman, let's go.
Where have you been, Will?
- Didn't you get my letters?
- What letters?
They must have never even mailed them.
Who?
The doctors at Westin Hills.
I've been in a psychiatric hospital.
Mark was with me there,
and some other kids too.
I don't understand.
Well, I saw on news the other night,
that kid that was killed at your house, I'm--
I needed to know that you were safe.
What happened?
I don't know, I don't know. Nobody knows.
Nobody saw what happened.
And the police have been acting really weird
like they know something.
And I heard them mention some name.
Some....
Freddy. Freddy Krueger.
Where was your dad?
- Out of town.
- Are you sure?
- What is going on, Will?
- Look, four years ago, I thought I--
Enough with this bullshit talk. Let's go
shake our ass on the dance floor. Come on.
I'm dead one day, and you're already out
getting shitfaced? Same old Gibb.
Trey, I-- I cannot believe you--
Come on. Let's go.
Babe, don't make me
ask you twice, okay?
Now!
Trey?
Trey.
Where's the door? Where's the do--?
Ah!
Help me.
No. No. No.
Ah!
You're the one that killed Trey!
Don't worry about my little errand boy.
The only thing to fear is fear himself.
Ah!
Oh.
No!
She's mine. Mine. Mine!
This Everclear is kicking my ass.
Check out this fucking guy.
Well, hey, Jethro.
This is a rave, not a Halloween party.
Why don't you go find yourself
a pig to fuck?
Yeah, invite only, cornpoke.
And you weren't invi--
Son of a bitch.
Yeah. Burn, motherfucker.
No.
Run!
Ah!
Big stupid mother--
Gibb! Oh, my God!
- Oh, Gibb, no!
- Come on, let's go.
Let's just go, come on!
Was that him?
The guy you were talking about?
- Freddy Krueger?
- No. That wasn't the guy in my dream.
That was somebody else.
Who cares about some fucking
dream guy, okay?
- That psycho in the hockey mask was real.
- That goalie was pissed about something.
- We need to find the police, y'all.
- No, no, fuck the police.
Just take me home, Will.
Gibb, I ca--
I can't believe she--
I know. I know.
Look, call me later, okay? Please.
- Just to check in.
- Okay.
Bye, Will.
Be careful.
Well, I'm gonna go inside now.
No, I think that's the last thing
you should do right now.
Please, after everything that's happened,
I just wanna go home.
No, there's more to it than that.
Look, I tried to tell you this earlier.
The reason I was sent to Westin...
...is because I saw your dad
kill your mom.
Will, my mom died in a car accident.
No, that's what he wanted you to believe,
but I was there, Lori.
I was sneaking up to your room
like I used to do.
Only you weren't there.
I saw him kill her.
- Dad.
- Get out of the van.
- Get out of the van!
- Dad, what are you doing?
- I've been looking all over for you.
- Stop it.
- Get away from her.
- You're in a hell of a lot of trouble.
- Yeah, like I give a shit anymore.
- Get in the house.
- I'm taking you back to Westin.
- No, no way. You can't trust him, Lori.
- Whatever you do, don't go home with him.
- Will, what--?
No, listen to me, Lori.
He was the one who had me committed.
You didn't understand, you still don't.
You were confused.
- Stop it, both of you, stop it!
Get-- Lori--
Damn it, Will. I am not gonna let you
endanger my daughter again.
- Stop it!
- Not after everything that's happened.
Stop it! Stop it! Fuck!
Lori. Lori.
Lori, Lori.
Did Mom die in a car accident?
- Yes. Of course she did.
- Prove it.
Show me a death certificate.
Show me an autopsy report.
Lori, I don't think now is the right time--
Really, Dad?
Because I think it's the perfect time.
Why didn't you tell me about Westin Hills?
You work there?
Because I thought
you were a general practitioner.
Yes, I--
I do some consulting there now,
but it isn't what you think.
Oh, my God.
So you knew about Will this whole time?
Lori, listen to me.
You're upset. We both are.
Now, I think what you need now
more than anything is to get some rest.
Why don't I give you some pills?
That'll help you sleep.
And then we'll talk about it
in the morning.
I don't wanna sleep, Dad. I wanna know
why you've been lying to me.
We'll talk about it in the morning.
Now do what I say.
Lori. Lori.
Lori.
Open this door. Open this door.
- Go away.
- Damn it, Lori, let me in.
Lori.
Goddamn it.
- Ah!
- It's okay. It's me, it's me. Shh. Shh.
Okay? Okay, it's me, it's just me.
Come on, it's me, okay?
I don't know how your father's connected
to all this. But I think Mark was right.
There's some kind of cover-up
going on here with Krueger.
We can't trust the police.
We can't trust any of the adults.
So, what do we do?
We gotta get to Mark.
He's the expert in all this.
He'll know what's going on.
You always looked out for me, bro.
Hey, Mark.
I gotta stay awake.
Shit.
Hey, Mark.
- You didn't forget about me, did you?
- Oh, God.
Oh, that's right. Everyone forgot.
- That's why they weren't afraid.
- I'm dreaming.
That's why I needed Jason to kill for me
to get them to remember.
But now he just won't stop.
That hockey puck.
This isn't real.
Somebody please wake me up!
Please!
Mark. Mark, wake up!
I need you to send a little message
for me, that's all. Just a little message.
I'm not gonna do it.
I won't do it!
No?
I won't do it.
I'll have to pass that message myself,
won't I?
Ah!
Oh, my God!
Wake up!
- Help me.
- Mark.
Pass on a little message for me, will you?
Sheriff, look, I've been compiling info
based on eye-witness reports...
- ...of the hockey-mask killer--
- We already know who did this.
Sheriff, we closed down the school
and set up a curfew for anyone under 18.
Good. I want 24-hour roadblocks set up.
Nobody leaves town, nobody gets in.
Contain the son of a bitch
before he spreads any further.
Yes, sir.
- Sir, shouldn't we have the FBI come in--?
- No outsiders, Stubbs.
We can handle this.
We've stopped him before.
Okay, I'm a little lost here.
Stopped who before?
We don't say his name out loud.
You're not from here,
I don't expect you to understand.
With all respect,
I think we have a copycat...
...of the Jason Voorhees
Crystal Lake killer on our--
You listen to me. We do things around here
a certain way for a reason.
And that's given us four years of peace.
So either do your job
and keep your mouth shut...
...or so help me God, I will lock you up.
Do you understand me?
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Why don't we all just leave?
No, even if we leave,
Freddy can still get us.
I mean, we all know about him.
We're all afraid of him.
It was our fear that gave him his power.
And we're marked now.
Man, screw that clown.
I mean, what kind of pussy
comes after you in your dreams, anyway?
Now, that big-ass motherfucker
back at the cornfield...
...that's who we should be afraid of.
Tell me who the fuck that was.
His name was Jason Voorhees.
Shit, man.
How'd you know we were here?
Nothing personal, but the Scooby van
out back wasn't exactly subtle.
And never keep your keys in the door.
Great. So now we're completely fucked.
No, you're not. I'm here to help you.
Now, this Jason Voorhees
supposedly drowned...
...at Camp Crystal Lake back in 1957
when he was 11 years old.
The counselors weren't watching him.
Then they made the mistake
of killing his mother.
And the legend has it, is that Jason
kept returning from his grave...
...to punish whoever returned
to the camp.
- I think we're dealing with a copycat here.
- No, no, no.
He's not a copycat. I've seen
what he can do. He's the real Jason.
That's impossible, Linderman.
Jason is dead.
Yeah, well, you better start thinking
outside your little box, dude.
Because somebody's definitely breaking
the fucking reality rules, okay?
It makes sense in a way. I mean,
what if Freddy brought Jason back...
...because he was too weak to go after us
on his own, so he used Jason.
I mean, he knew that we'd think it was him,
that we'd spread the fear again.
And now that it's working,
it's like he can't shut Jason back down.
Wait a minute.
Freddy died by fire, Jason by water.
How can we use that?
I think we should concentrate
on Jason first.
I thought we decided
that Freddy was the one pulling the strings.
Shouldn't we go after him first?
I don't know, maybe what we need to do
is to offer Freddy a sacrifice.
Yeah. Yeah, totally.
Like a virgin, right? Someone pure.
Dude, don't look at me.
Even if you pay for it, it still counts.
Oh, come on.
Look, we all know who real virgin is here.
- Kia.
- Oh, come on, Lori.
I know you never made it with Will.
Why would he want to,
when he can fuck somebody like me?
Let's tie the bitch up.
What?
Don't worry, angel, you've still got me.
Come on, give daddy a kiss.
Ah!
Your eyes say, "No, no."
But my mouth says, "Yes, yes."
Ah!
- Lori, you all right?
- Lori.
You fell asleep. God.
Oh, shit.
I pulled that out of my dream.
- All right, how is that possible?
- Anything is possible now.
God, you just don't get it.
Oh, God, y'all, two killers.
We're not safe awake or asleep.
It's not sleep that's killing us,
it's our dreams.
At Westin, Mark and I never had dreams.
Were you on any drugs?
Yeah. But there's something
called Hypnocil.
They never told us what it was for
but everyone there was taking it.
"Hypnocil. Experimental drug...."
- Not even approved yet by the FDA.
- Oh, shit.
"Used for the suppression of dreams."
We need those pills. Enough for all of us.
Can you get us back to Westin Hills?
All right, this isn't it, guys.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, dude, dude, dude.
Let's take a little J break, huh?
- No, man. He's a cop.
- Come on, what is he gonna do? Arrest me?
Yeah. Hold up--
Hang on a sec. Fuck.
Oh, that's better.
Where's Freeburg?
Come on. Come on.
This is D wing. These are the ones
who wouldn't stop dreaming.
Are they dead?
They're in a coma.
Says they were given too much Hypnocil.
Who would do this to people?
Your dad's name is at the bottom
of both of these charts.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
Nice.
Hold up, man.
What?
What do you want?
No. I don't know
where the Hypnocil is, okay?
I can't pour these down the drain.
We need this stuff.
Ah!
Freeburg!
Freeburg. Freeburg, what are you doing?
We need those drugs.
Dude, no. Dude-- Ah!
Go on! Get out of here, go!
Ah!
What was that?
Let's go check it out. Let's go.
Die! Shit! Help!
Fucker! Help me!
- Shit, they're all empty.
- We gotta keep looking.
- Maybe there's some down here.
- Damn, there's gotta be here somewhere.
- Freeburg, come on. Come on.
- Come on.
What are you waiting for? Come on.
Freeburg, time to go.
We gotta go. Now! Come on!
Let me handle this, bitch.
What?
Come on. Come on, man. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Will, wait, wait. Look.
Come to Freddy.
These are my children, Jason.
Go back where you belong.
Oh, God.
Fuck you.
Linderman.
These are my children, Jason.
Go back where you belong.
Jason.
Jason, my special, special boy.
I'm disappointed in you, Jason.
You disobeyed me.
You were supposed to come back home.
Just kill a few of them.
But I blame myself. I should have known
you wouldn't be able to stop killing.
You are like a big stupid dog
who can't stop eating...
...even though your master said
you've had enough!
Now, it's time
to put this bad dog to sleep.
For good.
Ha!
Not my arm.
Welcome to my nightmare.
Penny for your thoughts, chief.
Oh, scary.
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
Oh.
Tilt.
Why won't you die?
Come on. Come on.
Ah.
So you are afraid of something
after all, huh?
How in the fuck did I let
y'all talk me into this?
Why don't we try and do it here?
Why go all the way to Crystal Lake?
Best-case scenario, Jason wins.
He'll already be home,
back where he belongs.
- I mean, why follow us anymore?
- And if Freddy wins?
At least Jason has home-field advantage.
Aw.
How sweet.
You ugly little shit.
Now, there's a face
only a mother could love.
Yeah. Now we're getting somewhere.
Let's see what really scares you.
Oh.
And dig a little deeper.
I'm dying to see what skeletons
are hidden in your closet.
We're seriously running out of tranq here.
I got maybe one dose, plus enough for Lori.
We're almost there.
- Then I better get going.
- No, no, no. Just....
- I don't want you to go.
- I'm coming back.
Just give me 15 minutes,
then wake me up.
I'll bring that bastard Freddy
back through.
Just make sure Jason's waiting for him.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
Get him.
Freak show, freak show, freak show.
Bulls'-eye.
I want him out of here.
Get him out of here.
Freak show, freak show, freak show.
Try this on.
Stop it.
Aren't you gonna help the kid?
Can't you see I'm busy here?
You mean you're not coming?
It's not my fault
this bitch is dead on her feet.
- It's been five minutes.
- That was the last of the tranq. We're out.
Calm down, okay? Just relax.
Help!
Wait! Give me your hand!
Give me your hand!
- Help!
- Jason?
Ah!
Jason Voorhees!
Y'all? Y'all? Something's wrong.
- It's like he's drowning.
- Shit.
- Freddy must be killing him.
- We need him alive!
Dude, what do you want me to do?
Give him mouth-to-mouth or something?
Hell, no. Why you--?
No. No, I'm not gonna do that, no.
Kia, I would do it myself,
but I've had asthma since I was 6.
I don't have the lung power.
Kia, he has asthma.
Oh...
Look, you can do this, okay?
You can do this. You just--
Shut up. You're not the one
that has to do this.
- I know, but I--
- Shut up.
Ah!
Oh, my God. I don't wanna do this.
- You can do this.
- Oh, God.
Oh, man.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
- You.
- Ah!
What's wrong, Lori?
Miss your wake-up call?
Wake me up! I got him! I got him!
No!
- Come on, wake up. Wake up.
- Lori.
- Look.
Guys, look.
We're almost there.
Let's go. Come on. Help me get her up.
- All right.
- Come on. Start running. Let's go.
Wake me up!
Daddy, don't!
Daddy! No, Daddy, don't!
Freddy. It was you.
I've always had a thing for the whores
that live in this house.
Ah!
Lori, wake up!
Oh, shit.
- It's him. He's here.
- Lori, come on, you gotta wake up.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no. Come on. Lori, wake up!
Lori, please, wake up!
Lori, please. Lori, please.
Go, go, go.
Ah!
Lori.
Oh, you fucking asshole. Goddamn it.
Welcome to my world, bitch.
I should warn you, princess.
The first time tends to get a little messy.
Ah!
Get away from her!
Linderman.
Oh, no.
Die, you little bitch.
Oh!
Ah!
Jesus, Linderman, you're really hurt.
No, no, no. Don't worry about me.
It's just a scratch. Just go get help, okay?
- What?
- I'm just gonna rest here a minute--
- But Linderman--
- I'm fine, Kia.
- Really. Now, get out of here. Go get help.
- But you-- You--
Just go.
Okay, okay. But I'm gonna
be back as soon as I can.
- Lori.
- Think you're so smart, huh, bitch?
Freddy!
How sweet, dark meat.
- No! Kia!
- Let's go. Now.
No!
So you're the one
everyone's afraid of?
Tell me something.
What kind of faggot runs around
in a Christmas sweater?
I mean, come on, get real.
You're not even scary.
And let's talk about the butter knives.
What is with the butter knives?
You trying to compensate
for something?
Maybe coming up a little short there
between the legs, Mr. Krueger?
I mean, you got
these teensy-weensy little things...
...and Jason has got
this big old thing and like--
Oh.
Kia!
Come on.
- Let's go, we can't help her anymore.
- No, I'm staying.
Are you crazy? You got what you wanted,
you pulled Freddy out. He's fighting Jason.
- Come on, what more do you want?
- He killed my mother, Will.
It was Freddy.
My dad covered it up to protect me.
- He didn't do it.
- Oh, my God.
Look, he has taken everything from us.
He has ruined both of our pasts.
And I am not leaving until
I see him die.
Man the torpedoes.
Hey, asshole.
Up here.
Aha.
Yeah.
Oh, give me a break.
Ah!
Oh, no. Oh, no!
Lori, get the tanks.
You can dish it out,
but you can't take it.
Freddy!
Go to hell!
Ah!
It's okay. It's okay.
You--
Ah!
Welcome to my world, bitch!