Oh, this is great.
Wow!
That's incredible.
There's got to be
7 or 8 feet up there.
And 80 years of dust.
Look at all this height.
With our bedroom upstairs,
we'd have all this space.
For what?
Just space.
1 ...
2...
3!
And 4?
And 5?
Watch it. Watch it.
God, this place
is huge.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
God!
You guys, it's
absolutely incredible.
Incredible.
A little paint,
you could sell this tomorrow
and double your money.
Carl, you're obsessed.
A little bit.
Whoa, look!
Hey, it's
an Indian head penny.
1 898.
It's a good omen.
You're the good omen.
Oh, it's so great.
I had Rose
move your 3:00 to 4:00.
Gary Allen called
late yesterday.
He has to see you
about the final painting bids
for the loft.
3:00 is the only time
he can make it.
Sam?
Huh? Oh, I'm sorry.
Relax. This isn't brain surgery
you're going into.
Pitching these Japanese guys
makes me so nervous.
Sam...
you're going
to be great, OK?
What am I
supposed to say?
I can't tell them
my Swedish pompom girl joke,
you know.
Those are great.
Where'd you get those?
Nice, huh? Molly.
What do you think?
Are they me?
Man, look at that.
A Testarossa.
Whoa.
Ouch.
Pay off
your Mustang first.
How are you feeling?
What did
the doctor say?
He said
it was contagious,
that it was really...
No.
He said I shouldn't
be coming in today.
What about the rash?
The rash?
Mm-hmm.
The rash is, um...
also incredibly
contagious.
He said they've
both been spreading.
No.
On your genitals
again?
Yeah.
Yeah, right on
the genitals.
Basically everywhere.
He said that I
shouldn't touch anyone.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
You're sick.
I know.
Morning, Paul.
Morning,
Carl, Sam.
Hey, Paul.
Morning, Mr. Wheat.
Morning, Susan.
You're looking good.
Sam?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here it is.
Thanks.
Morning, Sam.
Morning. Listen,
the Kobiashi people--
They're already here.
They're early.
I know.
Come here. How long
have they been here?
About 10 minutes.
Andy Dillon called
and says he needs $900,000
transferred to Albany by 1 0:00.
By 1 0:00?
Yes.
Carl?
Yeah?
Dillon needs 900,000
in Albany by 1 0:00.
Can you transfer it
to his payroll account?
I'll need your Mac code.
OK.
Discretion, right?
Got it.
You bet.
I'll do it right now.
Bill, I'll call you back.
OK, OK, that's fine.
That's fine.
That's fine!
Aw, man,
it's too far out.
Can you
get this, man?
Where
are you guys from,
the New York City Ballet?
Almost.
Oh!
Saved your life!
You shit.
You scared me to death.
Why'd you do that?
It's better than seeing
this gorgeous body
splattered
all over the place.
Look out.
Sam? Molly?
You guys home?
Did you invite Carl?
Slave labor.
-Carl?
-What?
Hurry. Help.
Oh, my God.
Grab the bottom.
Want this down here?
Right here?
Watch your toes.
Where do you want this?
Uh, in the bedroom.
God, this place
looks great.
Yeah.
You like it, huh?
Like is hardly
the word.
I didn't know it would be
this beautiful.
Molly, what about her?
Leave her there
until we get the rest in.
What are these?
Oh, let me show you.
Help me
lift this up.
Here?
Voila!
Wow.
What do you think?
It's fantastic.
I love it.
Sam, what's
this chair doing here?
What do you mean?
I love that chair.
I know, but we
discussed this...
I've had it forever.
When I watch TV,
I sit in it.
This chair is ugly.
So?
And it doesn't go
with anything.
It goes with me.
You're right.
It does.
We'll paint it.
We'll what?
Are you OK?
Mm-hmm. I'm fine.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You worried
about the promotion?
No, not really.
Then what?
Is it moving in
together?
No.
I don't know.
It's...
a lot of things.
I just don't want
the bubble to burst.
Seems like, uh...
whenever anything good
in my life happens,
I'm just afraid
I'm going to lose it.
I love you.
I really love you.
Ditto.
The pilot
first reported trouble
when the number two
engine blew,
the one in the tail
of the plane...
Oh, Jesus,
another one?
Oh, don't watch that.
I should cancel
my L. A. trip.
These things always
happen in threes.
Sam, get serious.
Besides, you lead
a charmed life.
Oh, yeah?
So did they.
It's amazing.
Just like that.
Blackout.
Oh
My love
My darling
I've hungered for...
What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep.
A long
Lonely time
I must
have passed out.
What time is it?
It's 2 a.m.
And time
Goes by
So slowly
Any time
Can do so much
Are you
Still mine
Oh, no.
I hope it wasn't
a masterpiece.
It's not now.
Can I help?
Yeah.
Put your hands here
and get them wet.
Just let the clay
slide between your fingers.
God speed your love
To me
Lonely rivers Flow
To the sea
To the open arms
Of the sea
Yeah
Lonely rivers sigh
Wait for me
I'll be coming home
Oh
My love
My darling
I've hungered
Hungered for your touch
A long
Lonely time
And time
Goes by
So slowly
Any time
Can do so much
Are you
Still mine
I need
Your love
I
I need your love
God speed your love
To me
Oh, no.
What's the matter?
A glitch.
What's up?
The Greenberg and White accounts--
I can't get in.
The Mac code
isn't working.
Oh, I changed it.
Why?
Nothing. I want to
nose around a bit.
Is something wrong?
Can you keep a secret?
Yeah, sure.
What's up?
There's too much money
in these accounts.
Too much money?
That's impossible.
Sam, this is going
to take you hours.
Let me do this.
It's already
taken me hours.
Let me figure it out.
No, that's OK.
It's like
a vendetta now.
Thanks, though.
I appreciate it.
OK.
If you start to go blind,
give a shout.
OK. Adios.
Listen, what are you
and Moll doing tonight?
We're going to the theater
to see Macbeth.
She likes
the guys in tights.
You want to go?
No, thanks.
I want a full
report, though.
Later.
Yeah.
Well, I loved it.
I was spellbound
the whole time.
I could tell.
So could
everyone else
with that resonating
snore of yours.
Did I tell you
what Melissa said?
Yeah, about six times.
It wasn't six times.
Quit being
so blase about this.
This is really
important.
I'll have two pieces
in her gallery.
The New York Times
reviews her gallery all the time.
Molly,
The New York Times
is just some
frustrated little critic
with pimples on his ass
who flunked art school.
Who cares what they think?
About eight million
readers, that's who.
Nah, they're just
reading the sports page.
Your work
is really beautiful.
It really is.
Thanks.
It shouldn't matter
what anyone else thinks,
just what I think.
I want
to marry you, Sam.
What?
Yep.
I've been
thinking about it.
I've been thinking
about it a lot,
and I think we
should just do it.
You're serious.
Yeah.
What's that look for?
You never wanted
to talk about it.
Do you love me, Sam?
Well, what do you think?
Why don't you
ever say it?
What do you mean?
I say it all the time.
No, you say ""ditto,""
and that's
not the same.
People say I love you
all the time,
and it doesn't
mean anything.
You know, sometimes
you need to hear it.
I need to hear it.
Let's go.
What should we do?
Let me handle it.
What do you want?
Your wallet--
give it to me!
Sam, just give it to him.
OK, just take the money.
Just leave--
No, Sam--
You son of a bitch!
Sam, don't!
Somebody help us!
Jesus Christ, Sam!
Just get off him.
Somebody!
Somebody help us!
Sam, just let...
Sam, stop it.
Stop it, Sam!
Molly?
Molly, he got--
Sam...
Baby, hold on.
You're going
to be OK.
Somebody?
Somebody help us!
Oh, Sam.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Sam, come on.
Hold on, baby.
Someone's going to come.
You're going to be OK.
Somebody!
Somebody help me!
Please, anybody!
Help me. Please help me.
Take it easy, all right?
We'll help you, OK?
Molly? Molly?
Molly?
OK.
All right.
Molly?
What should we do?
Aah!
What's happening?
What's...
Is he breathing?
I don't know
if he's breathing.
Don't die, Sam.
Hold on.
Hold on, baby.
Oh, my God.
Come on, man.
All right.
Here we go.
1 ...
Come on, baby.
Sam, don't you leave me.
Sam, hold on!
Sam...
Oh, Sam...
Jesus...
Miss Jensen, if you'll just step
this way, please.
So, what happened
to you?
What?
You're new, huh?
I could tell.
Are you talking to me?
Relax. It ain't
like before.
It's a whole new
ball of wax.
Who are you?
I'm waiting
for my wife.
She's in the cardiac wing.
She's fighting it.
Shot, huh?
That'll do it every time.
Poor bastard.
You may as well
get used to it.
You could be here
for a long while.
Come here.
I'll tell you a secret.
Doors ain't so bad.
Zip, zap--
they ain't nothing.
You'll see.
You'll catch on.
This patient's fibrillating.
Let's move it.
Give me
the paddles.
He ain't
going to make it.
I've seen it
a million times.
He's a goner.
He's still
fibrillating.
Clear.
You see?
Here they come.
Lucky bastard.
It could have been
the other ones.
You never know.
Who are--
No!
Aah!
God help me.
Oh, God...
help me.
""I am sunk
in the abysmal swamp
where there is no foothold.
I have reached
the watery depths.
The flood overwhelms me.
I am wearied with calling.''
As we say farewell
to our friend Sam Wheat,
we are reminded
of his kindness...
his generosity,
his buoyancy of spirit.
All that we treasure--
our loved ones,
our friends,
our body,
our mind--
are but on loan to us.
We must
surrender them all.
We are all travelers
on the same road,
which leads
to the same end.
As our loved one
enters eternal life,
let us remember
that love, too, is eternal.
That although
we will miss him,
our love
will light the void
and dispel the darkness.
I picked up
your shirts today.
I don't know why.
Mr. Reynolds told me
to tell you hello.
I broke into tears.
It's like I think
about you every minute.
It's like
I can still feel you.
I'm here, Moll.
Floyd, what's
the matter, kitty?
What's the matter?
Crazy cat.
Sam?
That's really
stupid.
I love this picture.
It's great.
Office.
Let me see that.
It's, um...
Sam's address book.
Right.
Dave Brubeck.
Newport, '88.
Should I toss
them?
No.
No? Molly, we hated
that concert.
Hey.
Oh. You wanted
to save those?
Rolaids?
Molly, what
are you doing?
I just miss him,
Carl.
Me, too.
Carl?
Yeah?
Wait a minute.
Wait.
What?
Not that one.
Which? Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to put
that on there.
That's OK.
Hey, Moll,
why don't you come?
It's like summer
outside.
No, I'm really
not up for it.
Just for a walk.
I don't want to.
You can't stay in
all day.
It's not healthy.
Carl, I can't do it!
Molly, you're not
the one who died.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Shit.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe
just a short one.
That a girl.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Molly!
What are you
doing here?
You bastard.
You son of a bitch!
What do you want?
-Molly?
Molly, get out!
Oh, my God.
No, Molly! Look,
no, no, please!
Molly!
Molly,
he's got a gun!
Hi, kitty. Hi.
You hurt her--
Aah!
Shit!
Is somebody there?
Hello?
Oh, my God!
Let go!
What are you doing?
Aah!
Like trains?
Stay out! This is mine!
Shit.
It's me.
I couldn't get it.
She came home.
Give me a couple
of days, man.
I'll go back.
Relax.
I'll get it.
Get what?
Who are you?
What do you
want from us?
No.
You stay away
from her.
Do you hear me?
Stay away from her!
And...
teddy bear, teddy bear,
turn around,
teddy bear,
touch
the ground.
Rosa Santiago?
Please
be seated.
Our sister will be
with us soon.
Sister Oda Mae,
grant us the gift of
your all-seeing presence.
Appear before us
now.
Mrs. Santiago?
Buenos dias.
I'm Oda Mae Brown.
I understand you wish
to contact your husband.
Si.
I believe
he'll be with us today.
Thank you.
But you know,
Mrs. Santiago,
there's no telling
about that other world,
so you've got to be
a believer, Mrs. Santiago.
Are you a believer?
Si. Si, I believe.
I believe.
Then let us begin.
I can't.
It's too difficult.
I can't make contact.
I don't feel his vi--
No, wait!
I'm feeling something.
Did he know someone
by the name of Anna?
Consuelo?
Lucita?
Julietta?
Josefina? Linda?
Maria?
I Si! His mama!
She is Maria!
Yes! Praise God, I knew
he was with his mama.
Oh, my God.
It's too difficult.
It's two of them.
I'm not sure
I can do that.
It's so trying.
Oh, I pay more.
How much?
$20.
Way to go. Milk her
for every penny.
Huh. Yes, I...I believe
we can start again.
- Praise the Lord.
- Thank you, Jesus.
Welcome, Mrs. Santiago.
You're fortunate today.
The spirits are churning.
My husband?
Have mercy!
Oh, yeah? Where?
Julio?
Yes!
I feel his vibration.
Ooh!
I see him!
How is he?
How does he look?
Oh, he's a handsome man.
Handsome?
Mrs. Santiago,
in Our Father's kingdom,
we're all handsome.
Oh, Julio.
Julio's
coming towards us.
I see him! He's coming!
He's there!
He's dressed
in a black suit.
Black suit?
It could be blue.
What a crock of shit.
Who is that?
Julio! Where are you?
Julio? Julio?
Did you hear it?
Damn!
Where are you?
Julio?
Who are you?
Whoa!
You can hear me?
Don't you hear him?
I don't believe this.
Hey, you,
my name's Sam Wheat.
Can you hear me?
Sam Wheat. Say my name.
Leave me alone!
Say it! Sam Wheat!
Talk to me, Oda Mae.
Say something!
Sam Wheat!
Jesus.
- Sam Wheat?
I swear,
no more cheating.
I'll do anything.
I'll do penance,
but make that guy
go away!
No way.
Aah!
It's OK.
All right, sister.
Thank you.
Yeah, you're
all right.
My mother
and my mother's mother
both had the gift.
They always said I had it,
but I never did.
I never had it.
They told me
all about it.
But now that I got it,
I don't think I want it.
Go away.
Find somebody else.
Somebody else?
You're out of your mind.
I'm getting there fast.
She hit her head
harder than we think.
She was talking to nobody
before she hit her head.
Sister can do that.
Where exactly are you?
Standing
right beside you.
Oh, you're standing
right beside me?
Well, honey,
we're right here.
Are you white?
What?
White?
You're white,
aren't you?
Know what I think?
I'll call the doctor
right now.
I knew it.
A white guy. Why me?
Listen, damn it.
You're going to help me.
There's a woman
named Molly Jensen.
She's in terrible danger.
The man who killed me
broke into our apartment,
and he's going
to go back.
You've got
to warn her.
What makes you think
she'll listen to me?
It's just a phone call.
Look...
you're all I've got.
Now, I'm not leaving
until you help me.
I don't care
how long it takes,
'cause I can talk
forever.
Hello?
Uh, hi. Is this
Molly Jensen?
Yes.
My name's
Oda Mae Brown.
I'm a spiritual reader
and advisor.
A friend of yours gave me
a message for you.
I know this sounds crazy,
but it's not.
You got to believe me.
Just don't be afraid.
Who is this?
I got a message
from Sam.
What?
Sam Wheat?
He asked me to call.
I told you.
Go there.
Forget it.
I'm not going anywhere.
I don't care
what you do.
Second verse
Same as the first
I'm 'En-er-y the Eighth
I am
'En-er-y the Eighth
I am, I am
I got married
to the widow next door
She's been married
seven times before
And every one
was an 'En-er-y
'En-er-y
Wouldn't have
a Willy or a Sam
No, sir
I'm her eighth old man
I'm 'En-er-y
'En-er-y the Eighth
I am, I am
I am
Second verse
Same as the first
I'm 'En-er-y the Eighth
I am
'En-er-y the Eighth
I am, I am
I got married
to the widow next door--
All right! All right!
Stop singing!
I'll go anywhere
you want to,
just don't sing anymore.
I can't believe this.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
What am I doing
down here?
I never come downtown.
I hate downtown.
She's probably
not even there.
Where are you?
Oh.
Woof.
Which building is it?
Uh, push 3.
See? Nobody's there.
She's there.
Just wait.
I did everything
I said I'd do.
I pressed
the button.
She's not there.
I'm going.
99 bottles of beer
on the wall
Take one down
Pass it around--
Don't sing, all right?
Hello?
Molly--
Shh! She can't hear you.
Hi, I'm Oda Mae.
I called you about
your friend Sam Wheat?
I told you.
Hey, Molly!
Molly Jensen.
I know you're up there.
I know you hear me.
I'm down here.
Sam wants to talk to you.
This is for real.
Remember the starfish
in Montego Bay?
How would I know that
if he wasn't here?
Hey, Molly, I know
about the green underwear
that you wrote
your name on.
I'd never get over that,
I tell you that.
I know about
the picture in Reno.
Hey, Molly!
Ask her about the sweater
she knitted in the closet
that's too big.
He asked me to remind you
of the sweater in the closet
that you knitted
that's too big.
Four sizes.
Hey, you hear me
talking to you?
I hear you.
Shut up. Nobody's
talking to you.
Ever hear of a phone?
Want to kiss my butt?
I'm not staying
down here all day.
Thank God.
Aw, man, shut up.
Molly! I'm going
to count to 3,
and I'm out of here.
1 , 2, 3.
No, Oda, wait.
No.
It's Molly.
Molly?
I'm Oda Mae Brown.
I don't know you or Sam,
but let me tell you
what he did.
He kept me up all night
singing I'm Henry
The Eighth, I Am.
That's how he got me
to go out with him.
Look, I'm sorry.
I just--
I just don't believe
in this life
after death stuff.
Well, tell her
she's wrong.
He says
you're wrong.
You're talking to him
right now?
He just asked me to tell you
that you're wrong.
So where is he?
I can't see him.
I can only hear him.
I'm right here.
That doesn't help,
Sam.
I'm holding
her hand.
He says he's
holding your hand.
What are you doing?
What do you think
you're doing to me?
If you think I'm here for
my health, you're crazy.
Sam's dead, OK?
He's dead.
Tell her
I love her.
He says
he loves you.
Sam would
never say that.
Say ditto.
What the hell
is ditto?
Ditto!
To tell you
the truth,
I don't know how
I'm doing this.
Confidentially,
nothing like this
has ever happened
to me before.
I mean, nothing.
Now I can't
turn it off.
Is this him?
Is this you?
- Yeah.
Huh. Cute.
White,
but cute.
What I don't
understand is,
why did he come back?
I don't know.
Why is he
still here?
He's stuck,
that's what it is.
He's in between
worlds.
You know,
it happens sometimes
that the spirit gets
yanked out so quick
that the essence
still feels
it has work to do.
Would you stop rambling?
I'm just answering
her question.
He's got
an attitude now.
I don't have an attitude.
Yes, you do
have an attitude.
We're having
a little discussion.
If you didn't have
a attitude,
you wouldn't have
raised your voice.
God damn it,
Oda Mae--
Don't you god damn me.
Don't you take
the Lord's name in vain.
Would you relax?
You relax.
You're the dead guy.
Want me to help?
You apologize.
Jesus Christ!
I'm leaving.
Nobody talks to me like that,
you understand?
Now, you better
apologize.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
OK?
Now, would you
sit down?
Please?
He's apologized.
I need you to tell
Molly what I'm saying,
but you have to tell her
word for word.
Yes. He wants me to tell you
what he's saying
word for word.
Molly, you're in danger.
You can't just
blurt it out like that.
And quit moving around,
will you?
You're making me dizzy.
I'll just tell her
in my own way.
Molly, you in danger,
girl.
What are you
talking about?
I know the man
who killed me.
He knows
who killed him.
His name's Willy Lopez.
I know where he lives.
He's a Puerto Rican,
Willy Lopez.
He knows
where he lives.
Write it down.
You write it down.
I ain't no
damn secretary.
Just do it!
Argh!
He's so testy.
What is it you
want me to write?
It's 303 Prospect Place,
apartment 4-D.
303 Prospect Place?
Yeah.
That's my
neighborhood.
Molly, he's got
my wallet,
he's got my key,
and he was
in here.
He's got his wallet
and key and was here.
Yesterday after your
walk with Carl,
you talked to Floyd,
took off your clothes--
All right,
all right.
When you came in
after your walk with Carl,
he saw
everything.
Go to the police.
It was a setup.
I was murdered.
He says go to the police.
He was murdered.
There's somebody
else involved--
I don't want no more
to do with this.
Where are you going?
I'm leaving, I did everything
I said I'd do.
And don't be
following me.
I'm finished.
I mean it.
Have a nice life.
Have a nice death.
Goodbye.
Molly, there is no one
on earth besides you
who wants this
to be true more than me,
but you got to be
rational about this.
Sam is no more
in this room than--
Look, I understand the
need to hang on to him,
I really do,
but this is absurd.
I know this seems absurd,
but it had to be real.
You believed some
fortune-teller from Brooklyn
who shows up
at your door?
I watched her have
a conversation with him.
I don't buy it, Moll,
not for a minute.
What about the things
she knew?
What things?
The photo Sam took of me
on our trip to Reno.
Carl, we were alone.
And the green underwear
that I wrote my name in.
She said Sam knew
who killed him.
Yeah, that he
was set up.
This is getting
deranged.
We're off
the deep end.
She had a name
and an address--
Willy Lopez.
303 Prospect Place,
apartment 4-D.
This is sick.
Oh, Carl.
This is really sick.
Oh, God.
Molly, I don't
understand
how you could--
you could...
swallow this crap.
I mean...
this guy
may not even exist.
Maybe she's just
trying to use you
to set someone up.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
That's what
I got to find out.
What do you mean,
find out?
She said Sam wants me
to go to the police.
Sam wants you to
go to the police?
Jesus, Moll. Are you
out of your mind?
What are you going
to tell the police?
That some
storefront psychic
has been communing
with the dead?
Do you know what
that sounds like?
You're talking ghosts here,
for Christ's sake.
I'm sorry.
This stuff just really
gets to me,
you know?
It's OK if you
don't believe me.
I'm trying to, Molly.
Look...
if it'll make you
feel any better,
I'll go check
this out, OK?
I want you to try
and get some sleep.
OK?
All right.
I'll call you
in the morning.
OK.
Be careful.
Carl.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Who you been
talking to, Willy?
""Talking to""?
What the hell do you mean?
Some woman knows
all about you, everything.
Where's she
getting it from?
I haven't said
a word to anybody.
She knows your name
and where you live.
A lot of women
know where I live.
This is not a joke.
She knows
about the murder.
I want you
to find this bitch,
whoever she is,
and I want you to--
Just get rid
of her, OK?
I've got $4 million stuck
in a god damn computer.
If I don't get
those codes,
if that money is not
transferred soon...
I'm...
dead.
We're both dead.
Why not tell them
you only launder money
the first of the month?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Is everything a joke?
You killed a man.
You were supposed
to steal his wallet.
-Was that a joke?
-I did you a favor.
That was a freebie.
Look, these are
drug dealers, OK?
Just don't blow this
for me.
I've risked my job.
I could go to jail.
$80,000 of that money
is mine.
Look, just...
let me have the key
to Sam's apartment.
I'll get the address book
myself, OK?
You god damn bastard!
Why?
Why? You were
my friend!
I had a life,
god damn you.
I had a life!
Look, I don't even believe
in this stuff myself.
But she was real.
You think I'd come down here
if it wasn't real?
You know,
you told me if I had
any new information
that I should come.
So here I am.
I know
how this sounds.
I hear myself
saying it,
and I want
to cringe.
But this woman knew things
she couldn't have known.
Things Sam
only said to me.
OK, according to this
psychic lady,
there are ghosts and spirits
all over the place
watching us
all the time?
Huh?
Hell, I'm never going
to get undressed again.
Excuse me.
I got more
important things to do.
The guy's name
is Willy Lopez.
All I'm asking you to do
is check it out.
OK. Wait here.
Let me see if the guy's
got a record, all right?
Great.
What are you doing?
Where's the file
on Willy Lopez?
There isn't one.
He was probably
some old boyfriend
she was trying
to get even with.
This psychic woman's
got a record
that goes back
a long way.
1967,
Shreveport,
forgery...
selling false I.D.
Served one year, 1971 .
Baton Rouge,
arrested for fraud.
Numbers racketeering,
served 10 months, 1974.
Look,
this is impossible.
It goes on and on.
She knew things,
private things.
Now, how could she
have known all that?
A lot of times
they read the obits.
She just had to see
the word ""banker""--boom.
Hell, they even go
through your...garbage
to find things
they can use--
letters, old papers.
It doesn't take much.
No.
It was real.
She knew about a...
a sweater I knitted.
And songs we sang.
Our trip
to Montego Bay.
I'm sorry.
I know this is hard.
People want so much
to believe.
They're grieving,
they're vulnerable...
and they will
give anything
for one last moment.
Believe me.
These people know
what they're doing.
I know
how you must feel,
but you know
you can press charges.
No.
Thank you.