Wait for it.
- Can I turn on the radio?
- No.
Jane, you can't keep doing this.
The last seventeen occurrences,
had been predictable
- to the second.
- Jane...
You're an astrophysicist
not some storm chaser.
I'm telling you,
there's a connection,
between these atmosphere
disturbances and my research.
Erik, I...
I wouldn't have asked you
to fly out here,
if I wasn't absolutely sure.
Jane?
I think you wanna see this.
What is that?
God!
I thought you said,
it was a subtle aurora.
Go!
Help me get down!
- Get closer.
- Yeah, right! Good one!
Go!
What are you doing?
I'm not dying
for six college credits!
I think that was legally
your fault.
Get the first aid kit.
Do me a favor
and don’t be dead! Please!
Where did he come from?
Once...
mankind accepted
a simple truth,
that they were not alone
in this universe.
Some worlds, man believed
to be home to their gods.
Others, they knew to fear.
From a Realm
of cold and darkness,
came the Frost Giants.
Threatening to plunge
the mortal world,
into a new ice age.
But humanity, would not face
this threat alone.
Our armies drove
the Frost Giants,
back into the heart
of their own world.
The cost was great.
In the end,
their king fell.
And the source of their power,
was taken from them.
With the last great war ended,
we withdrew
from the other worlds,
and returned home,
to the realm eternal...
Asgard.
And here, we remain
as the beacon of hope.
Shining out across the stars.
And though we have fallen
into man's myths and legends,
it was Asgard,
and its warriors,
that brought peace...
to the universe.
But the day will come,
when one of you,
will have to defend that peace.
Do the Frost Giants
still live?
When I'm a king...
I'll hunt the monsters down,
and slay them all!
Just as you did, Father.
A wise king,
never seeks out war, but...
he must always
be ready for it.
- I'm ready, Father.
- So am I.
Only one of you
can ascend to the throne.
But both of you,
were born to be kings.
Oh, please.
Yes!
Thor Odinson,
my heir,
my first-born.
So long entrusted with
the mighty hammer, Mjolnir.
Forged in the heart of
a dying star.
It's power has no equal!
as a weapon to destroy,
or as a tool to build.
It is a fit companion
for a King.
I have defended Asgard,
and the lives of the innocent
across the Nine Realms,
in the time
of the Great Beginning.
And though the day has
come for a new King...
Do you swear to guard
the Nine Realms?
I swear.
And do you swear
to preserve the peace?
I swear.
Do you swear,
to cast aside
all selfish ambition,
and to pledge yourself only
to the good of the realms?
I swear!
Then on this day,
I, Odin Allfather,
will proclaim you...
The Frost Giants...
The Jotuns must pay for what
they’ve done!
They have paid
with their lives.
The Destroyer did it's work,
the Casket is safe,
and all is well.
All is well?
They broke
into the Weapons Vault!
If the Frost Giants had stolen
even one of these relics...
- But they didn’t.
- Well, I want to know why?
I have a truce with Laufey,
King of the Jotun.
He just broke your truce!
They know you're vulnerable.
What action would you take?
March into Jotunheim
as you once did,
teach them a lesson,
break their spirits
so they’ll never dare--
try to cross our borders again!
You’re thinking only
as a warrior!
- This was an act of war!
- It was the act of but a few,
- doomed to fail.
- Look how far they got!
We will find the breach in our
defenses, and it will be sealed.
- As King of Asgard...
- But you're not King!
Not yet.
It’s unwise to be in my company
right now, brother.
This was to be
my day of triumph.
It will come.
In time.
What’s this?
If it’s any consolation,
I think you’re right.
About the Frost Giants,
about Laufey, about everything.
If they found a way to penetrate
the Asgard defenses once,
who’s to say they won’t try again.
Next time with an army.
- Exactly!
- There’s nothing you can do,
without defying Father.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
I know that look!
It’s the only way to ensure
the safety of our borders.
- Thor, It’s madness.
- Madness?
What sort of madness?
We’re going to Jotunheim.
What?
This isn’t like a journey to Earth,
where you summon
a little lightning and thunder,
and the mortals worship
you as a god.
This is Jotunheim.
My father fought his way
into Jotunheim,
defeated their armies,
and took their Casket.
We would just
be looking for answers.
It is forbidden!
My friends, have you forgotten
all that we’ve done together?
Fandral, Hogun?
Who led you into
the most glorious of battles?
You did.
And Volstagg,
to delicacies so succulent,
you thought you’d died
and gone to Valhalla?
- You did.
- Yes.
And who proved wrong all who
scoffed at the idea that--
a young maiden could be one
of the fiercest warriors,
this Realm has ever known?
- I did.
- True. But I supported you, Sif.
My friends,
We’re going to Jotunheim.
Leave this to me.
Good Heimdall...
You're not dressed
warmly enough.
I'm sorry?
Do you think that
you can deceive me?
- You must be mistaken...
- Enough!
Heimdall, may we pass?
Never has an enemy
slipped my watch, until this day.
I wish to know
how that happened.
Then tell no one
where we’ve gone,
until we’ve returned.
Understand?
What happened?
Your silver tongue turn to lead?
Be warned.
I will honor my sworn oath,
to protect this Realm
as its Gatekeeper.
If your return threatens
the safety of Asgard,
Bifrost will remain
closed to you.
And you’ll be left to die
in the cold wastes of Jotunheim.
Couldn’t you just leave
the bridge open for us?
To leave the bridge open,
would unleash
the full power of the Bifrost,
and destroy Jotunheim
with you upon it.
- I have no plans to die today.
- None do.
We shouldn’t be here.
Let's move.
Where are they?
Hiding. As cowards always do.
You've come a long way
to die Asgardians.
I am Thor Odinson.
We know who you are.
How did your people
get into Asgard?
The house of Odin
is full of traitors.
Do not dishonor
my father’s name with your lies!
Your father is a murderer
and a thief.
And why have you come here?
To make peace?
You long for battle.
You crave it!
You're nothing but a boy,
trying to prove himself a man.
This boy has grown tired
of your mockery.
Thor, stop and think.
Look around you.
We are outnumbered.
Know your place, brother...
You know not what your actions
would unleash.
I do.
Go now, while I still allow it.
We will accept
your most gracious offer.
Come on, brother.
Run back home, little princess.
Damn!
Next!
At least make it
a challenge for me!
That’s more like it!
Don’t let them touch you!
Thor!
- We must go!
- Then go!
Run!
Thor!
Heimdall! Open the bridge!
Father!
We’ll finish them together!
Silence!
Allfather.
You look weary.
Laufey. End this now.
Your boy sought this out.
You’re right.
These are
the actions of a boy.
Treat them as such.
You and I can end this,
here and now.
before there’s further bloodshed.
We are beyond diplomacy now,
Allfather.
He’ll get what he came for...
war and death.
So be it.
Why did you bring us back?
Do you realize what you’ve done?
What you’ve started?
I was protecting my home.
You cannot protect
your friends.
How can you hope
to protect a kingdom?
Get him to the healing room!
Now!
There won’t be a kingdom
to protect,
if you’re afraid to act!
The Jotuns must learn
to fear me,
just as they once
feared you.
That’s pride and vanity talking,
Not leadership!
Have you forgotten
everything I’ve taught you?
- What of a warrior’s patience?
- While you wait and be patient,
the Nine Realms laugh at us.
The old ways are done.
You’d stand giving
speeches while Asgard falls!
You’re a vain, greedy,
cruel boy!
And you are an old man
and a fool!
Yes. I was a fool,
to think you were ready.
- Father.
- Nay!
Thor Odinson...
You have betrayed the express
command of your King.
Through your arrogance and
stupidity,
you've opened these
peaceful Realms,
and innocent lives to the horror
and desolation of war!
You are...
unworthy of these Realms!
unworthy of your title!
You're unworthy...
of the loved ones,
you have betrayed.
I now take from you,
your power!
In the name of my father!
And his father before!
I, Odin Allfather,
cast you out!
Whosoever holds
of this hammer,
if he be worthy, shall possess
the power of Thor.
I think that was legally
your fault.
Get the first aid kit.
Do me a favor
and don’t be dead.
Wow. Does he need CPR?
Because I totally know CPR.
Where did he come from?
- You all right?
- Hammer! Hammer!
Yeah, we can tell you’re hammered.
That’s pretty obvious.
Oh, my God!
Erik, look at this.
We’ve got to move quickly
before this all changes.
Jane, we have to take him to
the hospital.
- Father!
- He’s fine, look at him.
Heimdall!
I know you can hear me!
Open the Bifrost!
Hospital.
You go, I'll stay.
You! What Realm is this?
Alfheim? Nornheim?
New Mexico!
You dare threaten me,
Thor, with so puny a weapon!
What?
He was freaking me out.
Next time you decide
to taser someone,
make sure
he's already in the car, okay?
Jane, come on.
- Name?
- He said it was "Thor".
T-H-O-R.
- And your relationship to him?
- I’ve never met him before.
- Until she hit him with the car.
- I grazed him.
- But she tasered him.
- Yes, I did.
Hi.
Just taking a little blood.
How dare you attack
the son of Odin!
- I need some help!
- You need help?
Call security!
Security to ER!
We need assistance!
You’re no match
for the mighty...
Huh.
You don’t think this was just
a magnetic storm, do you?
Look. The lensing around
these edges,
is characteristic
of an Einstein-Rosen Bridge.
A what?
I thought you were
a science major.
- Political Science.
- She was the only applicant.
An Einstein-Rosen Bridge
is a theoretical connection,
between two different points
of space-time.
It's a wormhole.
Erik, look...
What do you see?
- Stars.
- Yeah. But not our stars.
See, this is the star alignment,
for our quadrant,
this time of year.
And unless Ursa Minor
decided to take the day off...
these are someone
else’s constellations.
Hey, check this out.
No, it can't be.
I think I left something
at the hospital.
It’s not possible.
- Oh, what the hell happened?
- I don't wanna know.
I just lost my most important
piece of evidence. Typical.
- Now what?
- We find him.
Did you see what he did
in there?
I'm not sure finding him
is the best idea.
Well, our data can't tell us--
what it was like to be
inside that event,
and he can.
So, we're gonna find him.
Okay.
So you're gonna look
all over New Mexico, right?
Exactly.
Oh, what?
I’m so sorry. I swear
I’m not doing this on purpose!
# If you got a problem,
you don't care what it is #
# you'll need a hand,
I can assure you this. #
# I can help. #
# I got two strong arms,
I can help. #
# It would sure do me good #
# to do you good
Let me help #
Come on, pick it in now!
Did it work?
Sir...
we’ve found it.
You know, for a crazy,
homeless person, he's pretty cut.
Hey, sorry I tased you!
Excuse me, excuse me!
- Umm.
- What is this?
Oh...
My ex.
Good with patience
and bad with relationships.
Uh... They're the only clothes
I had that would fit you.
- They will suffice.
- You're welcome.
This mortal form
has grown weak.
I need sustenance!
We should never
have let him go.
There was no stopping him.
At least he’s only banished,
not dead.
Which is what we’d all be
if that guard,
hadn’t told Odin
where we’d gone.
How did the guard even know?
I told him.
What?
I told him to go to Odin
after we’d left.
He should be flogged
for taking so long.
We should have never
reached Jotunheim.
- You told the guard?
- I saved our lives.
And Thor’s.
I had no idea Father would
banish him for what he did.
Loki...
you must go to the Allfather,
and convince him
to change his mind!
And if I do, then what?
I love Thor more dearly
than any of you,
but you know what he is.
He’s arrogant, he’s reckless,
he’s dangerous!
You saw how he was today.
Is that what Asgard needs
from its King?
He may speak of
the good of Asgard,
but he’s always been
jealous of Thor.
We should be grateful to him.
He saved our lives.
Laufey said there were traitors
in the House of Odin.
A master of magic could bring
three Jotuns into Asgard.
Loki’s always been one for
mischief,
but you’re talking about
something else entirely.
Stop!
- Am I cursed?
- No.
What am I?
You’re my son.
What more than that?
The Casket
wasn’t the only thing,
you took from Jotunheim
that day, was it?
No.
In the aftermath of the battle,
I went into the Temple,
and I found a baby.
Small for a giant’s offspring,
abandoned, suffering,
left to die.
Laufey’s son.
Laufey’s son...
Yes.
Why? You were knee-deep
in Jotun blood.
Why would you take me?
- You were an innocent child.
- No.
You took me for a purpose,
what was it?
Tell me!
I thought we could unite
our kingdoms one day,
bring about an alliance,
bring about a permanent peace,
- ... through you.
- What?
But those plans
no longer matter.
So I am no more
than another stolen relic,
locked up here until you
might have use of me.
Why do you twist my words?
You could have told me
what I was from the beginning.
- Why didn’t you?
- You are my son.
I wanted only to protect you
from the truth.
What?
Because I...I...I...
I'm the monster that parents
tell their children about at night?
- Don’t...
- You know, it all makes sense now!
Why you favored Thor
all these years.
Because no matter how much
you claim to love me,
you could never have
a Frost Giant,
sitting on
the Throne of Asgard!
Guards!
Guards, please help!
How'd you get inside
that cloud?
Also how could you eat
an entire box of Pop Tarts,
and still be this hungry?
This drink, I like it.
- I know, it's great, right?
- Another!
Sorry, Izzy.
Little accident.
- What was that?
- It was delicious. I want another.
Well, you could have just
said so!
- I just did.
- No. I mean ask nicely.
I meant no disrespect.
All right.
Well, no more smashing. Deal?
- You have my word.
- Good.
The usual, please, Izzy.
You missed all the excitement
out at the crater.
They’re saying some kind of
satellite landed out in the desert.
Yeah, we were having
a good time with it,
Untill the Feds showed up.
Excuse me, did you say
there was a satellite crash?
Yeah.
Oh, my God! This is going
on Facebook. Smile!
What did it look like,
the satellite?
Well, I don’t know nothing
about satellites.
But it was heavy.
Heavy. Nobody could lift it.
They said it was radioactive.
I had my hands all over it.
- Which way?
- Oh. Fifty miles west of here.
But I wouldn't waste my time.
Looked like the whole Army
was coming in when we left!
- Where are you going?
- Fifty miles west of here.
- Why?
- To get what belongs to me.
- Oh, so you own a satellite now?
- It's not what they say it is.
Well, what ever it is,
the government seems to think
it's theirs.
So, you just intend
to go in there and take it?
Yes.
If you take me there now,
I’ll tell you everything
you wish to know.
- Everything?
- Yes.
All the answers you seek will be
yours, once I reclaim Mjolnir.
Myeu-muh?
What’s Myeu-muh?
Can I have a word, Jane?
Please don’t do this.
You saw what I saw last night.
This is no coincidence.
We have to find out
what's in that crater.
But I'm not talking about
the crater. I'm talking about him.
- But he's promising us answers.
- He’s delusional!
Listen to what he's saying.
He's talking about Mjolnir,
and Thor and Bifrost!
It's the stories
I grew up with as a child.
I'm just gonna drive him.
That's it!
He's dangerous, Jane.
I'm sorry.
But I can't take you.
Then this is where
we say goodbye.
Uh...
Thank you!
Jane Foster, Erik Selvig, Darcy.
Farewell.
Alright.
Back to work.
Hey!
That’s my stuff!
What the hell is going on here?
Ms. Foster, I’m Agent Coulson,
with SHIELD.
Is that suppose
to mean something to me?
- You can’t do this!
- Jane.
Jane. This is a lot more serious
than you realize. Let it go.
Let it go?
This is my life!
We’re here investigating
a security threat.
We need to appropriate
your records,
and all your atmospheric data.
By "appropriate"
you mean "steal"?
Here. This should more than
compensate you for your trouble.
I can’t just buy replacements
of RadioShack!
I made most of
this equipment myself!
Then I’m sure
you can do it again.
And I’m sure I can sue you,
for violating
my constitutional rights!
I'm sorry, Ms. Foster.
But we’re the good guys.
So are we!
I'm on the verge of understanding
something extraordinary.
And everything I know
about this phenomenon,
is either in this lab,
or in this book,
and you can't just
take this with...
- Hey!
- Jane! Easy! Easy!
Thank you
for your cooperation.
Years of research, gone.
They even took my iPod.
- What about the backups?
- They took our backups.
They took the backups
of our backups.
They were extremely thorough.
Just downloaded like
thirty songs onto there.
Could you please,
stop with your iPod!
Who are these people?
I knew this scientist.
a pioneer in gamma radiation.
SHIELD showed up,
and...
he wasn't heard from again.
They're not gonna do that
to us.
- I'm gonna get everything back.
- Come on, please!
Let me contact
one of my colleagues.
He's had some dealings
with these people before.
I’ll email him
and maybe he can help.
They took your laptop, too.
All-Father, we must
speak with you urgently!
My friends.
Where's Odin?
Father has fallen
into the Odinsleep.
Mother fears
he may never awaken again.
We would speak with her.
She has refused to leave
my father's bedside.
You can bring
your urgent matter to me.
Your King.
My King, we would ask
that you end Thor's banishment.
My first command can not be
to undo the Allfather’s last.
We’re on the brink of war
with Jotunheim.
Our people need
a sense of continuity,
in order to feel safe
in these difficult times.
All of us must stand together,
for the good of Asgard.
Yes, of course.
Good, then you await
for my word.
If I may,
beg the indulgence
of your majesty,
- to perhaps reconsider...
- We're done!
I need a horse!
We don't have horses.
Just dogs, cats, birds.
Then give me one of those,
large enough to ride.
Hey, you still need a lift?
I've never done
anything like this before.
Have you ever done
anything like this before?
Many times.
But you're brave to do it.
Well, they just stole
my entire life's work.
I don't really
have much left to lose.
- But you're clever.
- Thanks.
Far more clever than
anyone else on this Realm.
Realm? Realm?
- You think me strange?
- Yeah, I do.
Good strange, or bad strange?
I'm not quite sure yet.
I'm sorry.
But who are you?
Really?
You'll see soon enough.
You promised me answers.
What you seek, it's a bridge.
Like an Einstein-Rosen Bridge?
More like a rainbow bridge.
God, I hope you're not crazy.
I never get used
to seeing him like this.
But he’s put it off
for so long now. But I fear...
- How long will it last?
- I don't know.
This time, it's different.
We were unprepared.
So why did he lie?
He kept the truth
from you,
so that you would never
feel different.
You are our son, Loki.
And we your family.
We mustn't lose hope that
your father will return to us.
And your brother.
What hope is there for Thor?
There's always a purpose
to everything your father does.
This tube is a satellite crash?
If they would've hauled
the wreckage away,
they wouldn't built
a city around it.
- You’re going to need this.
- What?
Wait, why?
Now stay here.
Once I have Mjolnir,
I will return the items
they've stolen from you.
- Deal?
- No! Look what’s down there!
You think you're just
gonna walk in,
- grab our stuff, and walk out?
- No.
I'm gonna fly out.
Sir, feed from the keyhole.
Can barely penetrate
the cloud cover.
Tech’s barely working as it is,
with all the interference,
that thing’s giving off.
And we’ve got a commercial
aircraft coming in right over us,
Southwest Airlines
Flight 5434.
Reroute it,
like all the others.
Hold a sec...
we've got something
outside the fence, west side.
DeLancey, Jackson,
west side perimeter,
go check it out.
DeLancey, Jackson,
report.
Agent down!
We’ve got a perimeter breach!
You’ve reached Dr. Erik Selvig.
Please leave me a message.
Hi, Erik. It's me.
Don't worry, I'm fine. But...
just in case you don’t hear
from me in the next hour,
just come by the crater site
and try to find me, okay?
I did exactly
what you told me not to.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. Bye!
- You two, follow me!
- All the squad, move!
Open the gate!
He breached our tunnel!
Negative, negative!
Place is locked on!
I need eyes up high.
With a gun.
Pulling North!
So, what have we got?
There's a mass of electromagnetic
surge coming of that thing.
Systems are barely coping.
Barton. Talk to me.
Do you want me
to slow him down, sir?
Or you're sending in
more guys for him to beat up?
I'll let you know.
You’re big.
Fought bigger.
You better call it Coulson,
cause I'm starting to root
for this guy.
- Last chance, sir!
- No, wait! I wanna see this.
Why?!
Alright, show’s over.
Ground units, move in.
He committed a crime!
He's in jail!
- I can't just leave him there!
- Why?
- You didn't see what I saw!
- Look! Look! It's Myeu-muh.
- Where'd you find this?
- The children's section.
I just wanted to show you
how silly his story was.
But you're the one
who's always pushing me,
to chase down every possibility,
every alternative!
I'm talking about science,
not magic!
Well magic's just science
that we don't understand yet,
- Arthur C. Clarke.
- Who wrote science fiction.
- A precursor to science fact!
- In some cases, yes.
Well, if there is
an Einstein-Rosen Bridge,
then there's something
on the other side.
And advanced beings
could have crossed it!
Oh, Jane...
A primitive culture like the vikings ...
might have worshiped them as deities.
Yes, yes, exactly!
Thank you!
You made my men,
some of the most highly trained
professionals in the world,
look like a bunch of
minimum wage mall cops.
That's hurtful.
In my experience,
it takes someone
who's received similar training,
to do what you did to them.
Why don't you tell me,
where you received your training?
Pakistan? Chechnya?
Afghanistan?
You know, you strike me more
as the soldier of fortune type.
Where was it?
South Africa?
Certain groups pay very well
for a good mercenary like you.
Who are you?
One way or another we'll find out
what we need to know.
We're good at that.
Don't go anywhere.
Loki?
what are you doing here?
I had to see you.
What's happened?
Tell me? Is it Jotunheim?
Let me explain to father.
Father is dead.
What?
Your banishment.
The threat of a new war.
It was too much
for him to bear.
You mustn't blame yourself.
I know that you loved him.
I tried to tell him so,
but he wouldn't listen.
So cruel to put the hammer
within your reach,
knowing that
you could never lift it.
The burden of the throne
has fallen to me now.
Can I come home?
The truce with Jotunheim
is conditional upon your exile.
Yes, but...
couldn't we find a way to...
Your mother,
has forbidden your return.
This is goodbye, brother.
I'm so sorry.
No.
I am sorry.
Thank you for coming here.
Farewell.
Goodbye.
Goodbye?
I just got back.
Sir...
he’s got a visitor.
- His name is Donald Blake?
- Doctor Donald Blake.
You have dangerous
co-workers, Doctor Selvig.
He was distraught
when he found out,
that you'd taken
all of our research.
That was years of his life, gone!
You can understand how a man
can go off like that.
A big faceless organization
like yours,
coming in with their
jack-booted thugs and...
That's how he put it.
That still doesn't explain,
how he managed
to tear through our security.
Steroids!
He's a bit if a fitness nut.
Sir?
It says here
that he was an M.D.
Well, he is!
Or he was.
He switched careers
and became a physicist.
A brilliant physicist.
He's a... he's a wonderful man.
He's a man in pain.
Oh, Donny, Donny, Donny!
There you are!
It’s gonna be all right,
I’m taking you home, now.
Doctor Selvig?
Just keep him away
from the bars.
I will.
- Where are we going?
- To get a drink.
Follow them.
You know,
I had it all backwards.
I had it all wrong.
Was that a bad thing, finding out
that you don't have all the answers?
You start asking
the right questions.
For the first time in...
in my life,
I have no idea
what I'm supposed to do.
Anyone who's ever going
to find his way in this world,
has to start by admitting,
he doesn't know
where the hell he is.
Thank you,
for what you've done.
No, don't thank me.
I only did it for Jane.
Her father and I
taught at University together.
He was a good man.
He never listened.
Neither did I.
My father was trying
to teach me something.
But I was too stupid to see it.
I don't know
if you're delusional,
or if you're putting
some kind of con. I don't care.
I just care about her.
I've seen the way
she looks at you.
I swear to you,
I mean her no harm.
Good. In that case,
I'll buy you another round.
And you'll leave town tonight.
Two boilermakers!
Kill him.
After all I've done for you?
So you're the one who showed us
the way into Asgard.
That was just a bit of fun really.
To ruin my brother's big day.
And to protect the realm from
his idiotic rule for a while longer.
I will hear you.
I will conceal you
and a handful of your soldiers,
lead you into Odin's chambers
and you can slay him where he lies.
Why not kill him yourself?
I suspect that the Asgardians
would not take kindly to a King,
who had murdered
his predecessor.
Once Odin is dead,
I will return the casket to you.
And you can return Jotunheim
to all it's uh...
glory.
I...
accept.
What troubles you, Gatekeeper?
I turned my gaze upon you
in Jotunheim,
but could neither see you
or hear you.
You were shrouded from me,
like the Frost Giants
had entered this Realm.
Perhaps your senses
have weakened,
after your many years
of service.
Or perhaps someone
has found a way to hide,
that which he does not
wish me to see.
You have great power,
Heimdall.
Did Odin ever fear you?
- No.
- And why is that?
Because he is my King.
And I'm sworn to obey him.
He was your King.
And you are sworn
to obey me now.
Yes?
Yes.
Then you'll open the Bifrost
to no one.
Until I have repaired the damage
that my brother has done.
Oh, my God!
Is he okay?
He’s fine.
Not injured at all.
- I'm Sorry, my friend.
- What happened?
We drank. We fought.
He made his ancestors proud.
Put him on the bed.
Oh, I still don’t think
you’re the God of Thunder.
But you ought to be.
Are these your chambers?
Uh... it’s more of
a temporary living situation.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don’t usually have guests.
Actually...
We never had guests.
That's not the right place
for it.
I'm so sorry.
- Can we go outside?
- Yes, of course.
I come up here sometimes
when I can't sleep,
or when I'm trying to reconcile
particle data,
or when
Darcy's driving me crazy.
I come up here a lot actually,
now that I think about it.
I'm really glad you're safe.
You've been very kind to me.
I have been far less grateful
than you deserve.
Well, I hit you with my car
a couple times,
so I think
that kind of even things out.
Perhaps I had it coming.
Oh, my God!
- I don't believe it!
- It was all I could get back.
I'm sorry,
it's not as much as I promised.
No! No! This is great!
This is...
I don't have to start
from the scratch now.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
SHIELD, whatever they are.
They're going to do everything
in their power,
to make sure this research
never sees the light of day.
No, Jane. Listen to me,
you must not give up.
You must finish
what you started.
- Why?
- Because you're right.
Here, look.
You're ancestors called it magic,
and you call it science.
Well, I come form a place,
where they're one
and the same thing.
What is that?
My father,
explained it to me like this,
that your world is one of
the Nine Realms of the cosmos.
Linked to each other
by the branches of Yggdrasil.
The worlds tree.
Now you see it everyday
without realizing.
The images glimpsed through,
what did you call it? This...
this hooble telescope.
- Hubble.
- Hubble telescope.
Tell me more.
So, the Nine Realms.
Now there is Midgard,
which is earth.
There's Alfheim, Vanaheim,
Jotunheim and Asgard.
And that's were I come from.
Thank you, Jane.
Our dearest friend banished,
Loki on the throne,
Asgard on the brink of war,
Yet you've managed
to consume,
four wild boar, six pheasant,
a side of beef
and two casks of ale!
Shame on you!
Don't you care!
Do not mistake
my appetite for apathy!
Stop it! Both of you!
Stop.
We all know
what we have to do.
We must go.
We must find Thor.
- It's treason.
- To hell with treason. It's suicide.
Thor would do the same for us.
Now, shh!
Heimdall might be watching.
Heimdall demands
your presence.
We’re doomed.
You would defy the commands
of Loki, our King,
Break every oath
you have taken as warriors,
and commit treason
to bring Thor back?
- Yes.
- Good!
So you'll help us?
I am bound by honor
to our King.
I cannot open the bridge
to you.
- Complicated fellow, isn't he?
- Now what do we do?
Look!
What the hell was that?
I don’t know, sir. We got massive
energy readings out of nowhere,
and then they just disappeared.
Fifteen miles due northwest.
Let’s go take a look.
- Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Base to team two, we've got
activity outside the town.
Stay on your target.
Ensure my brother
does not return!
Destroy everything!
Mom?
Is there a Renaissance Faire
in town?
- Call it in.
- Yeah.
Base, we've got... Xena,
Jackie Chan, and Robin Hood
It's a beautiful theory, Jane.
You won't be able
to convince...
the scientific community
of any of it.
Not without hard evidence.
Found you!
My friends!
This is good!
- I don't believe it!
- Oh, excuse me.
Lady Sif,
and the warriors three.
My friends,
I have never been happier
to see anyone.
But you should not have come.
We're here to take you home!
You know I can't go home.
My father is...
dead because of me.
I must remain in exile.
Thor...
your father still lives.
Tell me, Loki, how did you get
the Jotuns into Asgard?
You think the Bifrost is the only
way in and out of this realm?
There are secret paths
between the worlds,
to which even you
with all your gifts are blind.
But I have need of them
no longer, now that I am king.
And I say,
for your act of treason,
you are relieved of your duties
as Gatekeeper.
And no longer
citizen of Asgard.
Then I need no longer
obey you.
Get somebody
from Linguistics down here.
Was somebody else coming?
- Is that one of Stark’s?
- I don't know.
That guy never tells me
anything.
Hello!
You’re using unregistered
weapons technology.
Identify yourself.
Here we go.
Incoming!
Jane, you have to leave.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm staying here.
Thor is gonna fight with us.
My friends,
I'm just a man.
I'll only be in the way,
or worse get one of you killed.
But I can help
get these people to safety.
Well, if you're staying,
then so am I.
- We'll need some time.
- You'll have it.
Okay, move it people!
Everybody, out!
Use the backdoor!
Go, hurry!
You can eat later!
Keep it distracted.
For Asgard!!
Fall back!
Go, now! Run!
Sif, you've done all you can.
No! I will die a warrior's death.
Stories will be told of this day.
Live, and tell those stories
yourself.
Now, go!
You must return to Asgard.
You have to stop Loki.
What about you?
Don’t worry, my friends.
I have a plan.
Come on.
We need to fall back.
Come on!
Come on.
Wait!
What's he doing?
Brother, whatever
I have done to wrong you,
whatever I have done
to lead you to do this,
I am truly sorry.
But these people are innocent.
Taking their lives
will gain you nothing.
So take mine...
and end this.
No!
- It's over.
- No. It's not over.
- I mean, you're safe.
- We're safe.
It's over.
No.
Whosoever holds
of this hammer,
if he be worthy,
shall possess
the power of Thor.
Jane!
- No. No.
- Let's go! Now!
No!
Oh. My. God.
So is this
how you normally look?
More or less.
It's a good look.
We must go to the Bifrost site.
I would have a word
with my brother.
Excuse me!
Donald,
I don't think you've been
completely honest with me.
Know this, son of Coul.
You and I,
we fight for the same cause,
the protection of this world.
From this day forward
you can count me as your ally,
if, you return the items
you have taken from Jane.
- Stolen!
- Borrowed.
Of course you can have
your equipment back.
You're gonna need it
to continue your research.
Would you like to see
the bridge we spoke of?
Uh... sure.
Wait!
I need to debrief you!
Welcome to Asgard.
Heimdall! Open the Bifrost!
Heimdall.
He doesn't answer.
Then we’re stranded.
Heimdall! If you can hear me,
we need you now!
Heimdall!
I must go back to Asgard.
But I give you my word,
I will return for you.
Deal?
Deal.
Get him to the healing room!
Leave my brother to me.
It's said,
you can still hear and see
what transpires around you.
I hope it's true.
So that you may know,
your death came
at the hand...
of Laufey.
And your death came
by the son of Odin.
Loki,
you saved him.
I swear to you mother,
that they will pay
for what they have done today.
Loki!
Thor!
I knew you'd return to us.
Why don't you tell her?
How you sent the Destroyer
to kill our friends!
- To kill me!
- What?
Well, I must have been enforcing
father's last command.
You're a talented lier, brother.
Always have been.
It's good to have you back.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to destroy Jotunheim.
You can't stop it.
The Bifrost will build
until it rips Jotunheim apart.
Jane?
Why have you done this?
To prove to father,
that I am a worthy son!
When he wakes,
I will have saved his life.
I will have destroyed
that race of monsters.
And I will be true heir
to the throne!
You can't kill an entire race!
Why not?
And what is this newfound love
for the Frost Giants?
You? who could have killed
them all with your bear hands.
- I've changed.
- So have I.
Now, fight me.
I never wanted the throne!
I only ever wanted to be
your equal.
I will not fight you, brother!
I'm not your brother.
- I never was!
- Loki, this is madness!
Is it madness?
Is it?
Come on, what happened to you
on earth that turned you so soft?
Don't tell me it was that woman?
Oh! It was!
Well, maybe
when we're finished here,
I'll pay here a visit myself!
Thor!
Brother, please!
Enough!
Look at you.
The mighty Thor!
With all your strength!
And what good
does it do you now?
Do you hear me, brother?
There's nothing you can do!
What are you doing?
If you destroy the bridge,
you’ll never see her again!
Forgive me, Jane.
I could have done it, father!
I could have done it!
For you!
For all of us!
No, Loki.
Loki, no!
No.
It's gone.
And then,
with a mighty bellow,
I flew into the giant metal beast
and laid it low...
Is that another way of saying
you fell on your huge...
As a matter of fact,
falling down was a tactic.
My Queen,
I'm so sorry for your loss.
How is he?
He mourns for his brother.
And...
he misses her.
The mortal.
You'll be a wise king.
There will never be
a wiser king than you.
Or a better father.
I have much to learn.
I know that now.
But some day, perhaps,
I shall make you proud.
You’ve already
made me proud.
So, earth is lost to us?
No.
There is always hope.
Can you see her?
Yes.
I have the particle detectors.
Darcy, do you have
the SHIELD's satellite codes?
Yeah.
Have you seen my taser?
How is she?
In the car.
Come on, Jane.
She searches for you.
Doctor Selvig?
So, you're the man
behind all this?
It's quite a labyrinth.
I was thinking, they're taking me
down here to kill me.
I've been hearing about
the New Mexico situation.
Your work has impressed
a lot of people
who are much smarter
than I am.
I have a lot to work with.
The Forster theory,
a gate to another dimension.
It's unprecedented.
Isn't it?
Legend tells us one thing,
history another.
But every now and then, we find
something that belongs to both.
What is it?
Power, doctor.
If we can figure out
how to tap it,
maybe unlimited power.
Well, I guess
that's worth a look.
www.moviesubtitles.org