I had a vision in Amityville.
I had a premonition of your death.
We have both seen the same inhuman spirit.
Mom, who is that?
The demon in your painting is real.
The following occurred in 1952
Abbey of St Carta, Romania.
GOD ENDS HERE
Are you certain we're
making the right decision?
We have no other choice.
Will the relic truly save us?
Have faith, sister.
Our father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
Thy Kingdom come, thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven...
Give us this day our daily bread...
And forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those who
trespass against us.
Take it!
This evil needs a vessel to escape.
It will come after you next.
Don't let it have you.
- You know what you must do.
- I can't.
Then, not even God...
Forgive me, father, for the sin
that I'm about to commit.
Forgive me, Lord.
Oh God!
VATICAN CITY
Father Burke?
Bishop.
So, last time you were here was what night?
Six.. seven years ago?
After my time as a chaplain
ended in the war, Yes.
We appreciate you coming again,
under such short notice.
Father Burke.
Sit.
We have received news that a
nun has taken her own life...
at an Abbey in the mountains of Romania.
Suicide is a terrible, a terrible sin.
But it doesn't strike me as a strong
enough reason for our reunion.
But the news of it would
not boast our arguments
to keep with the
faith and the church...
You are not telling me something.
- Why do you say that?
- Because we are in the Vatican.
Let me put it this way, father.
In this, orbeat rare instance...
We do not believe we are
the ones with the secret.
Those are your travel documents...
and contact information on the
man who discovered the nun.
He lives near the Abbey in a
small village called Biertan.
You will want to talk to him first.
Also in the file is the
name of a postulant...
who can help assist you in your inquiries.
Since it is a cloister at convent
and your access will be limited.
She is also familiar
with the territory.
VINCENT HOSPITAL,
London, England.
I have survived many
terrifying encounters,
but nothing could have
ever prepared me for this.
My only hope now is that the
beast could not smell me.
But then, the wind changed and...
Run!
Run for your lives!
Mother superior says that
dinosaurs were never really alive.
God just put their bones
here, to test our faith.
That seems like a pretty
dirty trick, don't you think?
Wait, they are not in the Bible.
Well... do you believe in
penguins and koala bears?
- Yes.
- They aren't in the Bible either.
The Bible is God's love letter to us...
but, it doesn't mean that he doesn't
want us to ask questions...
about the wonders of his creation.
But Mother Superior says...
Wait a minute, you've got a little
something on your nose.
There.
- The Vatican?
- I'm as surprised as you.
- I haven't yet taken my vows yet.
- Oh! He's aware of that.
He is waiting for you in the garden.
And change in to your habit.
This is an official visit.
It shouldn't take more
than few days at most.
You were recommended for
the journey because
of your familiarity
with the territory.
The territory?
Yes. Romania.
I've never been in that part of the world.
- Really?
- There must have been some mistake.
I apologize if you coming here
was a waste of your time.
No apologies are necessary.
Every decision that Vatican
makes, is with purpose.
I'm sure they had their
reasons for selecting you.
BIERTAN, ROMANIA.
What is it?
Mr Theriault?
Hi.
Jealous husband or angry father?
I'm sorry, what?
Usually it's one of the two...
when an older man and
a young, beautiful...
not so innocent girl, show up in the
doors at this hour of the morning.
I beg your pardon, Mr. Theriault,
but you and I have never met.
Then perhaps time we do.
Call Me Frenchy,
everyone does.
Mr. Theriault, we are here because
of the nun you found at the abbey.
How do you ...?
Oh you priest?
And she's a nun.
Forgive me for my impure thoughts, Sister.
I had no idea. Never seen
a nun out of a vestments.
Not that I am opposed to.
Excuse me.
Mr. Theriault...
The Abbey, is it far?
Not of distance, no. But
takes time to get to.
If I may ask, why were you there?
I was delivering the quarterly supplies.
Apparently, the Abbey
has had some kind of
arrangement with the
village for centuries.
Do you think you could take
us there sometime soon?
Don't think so, Father.
Is there someone else in the village then?
Everyone in this village pretend
like the Abbey does not exists.
Even talking about it
might get you in trouble.
It's settled then.
You will take us.
- With all due respect, Father...
- Please, Frenchy.
Hey, go home.
You took a plane from Rome,
a bus from Bucharest...
And now, my friends, you
are in the dark ages.
In the backwoods of Romania.
Now you travel by horse.
Where are your things?
The postman's charge, 10 letters with an L.
Deliveries.
Yeah, but not for this, Sister.
What brings a Frenchmen to
the countryside of Romania?
Actually I'm French Canadian,
but don't tell anyone.
Doesn't sound as romantic.
I came here looking for gold, but
when I met the people here...
I just knew this was the place I was meant
to be. Wanted to help them. Anyway I could.
That's very noble of you.
I know.
Tell me sister... How
long have you been a nun?
I'm not a nun yet,
I'm still just a novice.
You still haven't taken
your temporary vows?
Temporary?
I didn't think there was anything
temporary about being a nun.
Temporary vows would help prepare me
for a life of total consecration.
Would sister, or will?
What happened?
Everything alright?
We walk the rest of the way.
The horse won't go any further.
Maybe you should get a new horse.
It's not the horse, Father,
it's what lies ahead.
He is scared.
Locals say it's a cursed place.
And the horse agrees.
If I may ask, Father, why is it the
church sends you on such tasks?
The Church reaches out to me when they need
some investigation into unusual phenomenon.
Associated with Catholicism.
Unofficially they call
it "miracle hunting."
I thought we were here
because of a suicide.
We are, but it's only part
of our investigation.
I also have orders from the Vatican to
determine if the grounds are still...
Holy.
But I can give you my opinion
on that now, Father.
Result of the war?
Bombing raids, yes.
I heard stories of how the ground
shook for days after them.
I've tried to find more information
on the castle itself...
But there is no record
of it in the village.
And the locals only spit
when it's mentioned.
- Spit?
- Yeah, to ward off evil.
It is an old and silly superstition.
And if you asked me, these crosses
that surround the Abbey...
They keep evil in, not out.
You tried to contact someone
inside when you found the nun?
I did, no one responded.
Then again in the two years
I've been delivering supplies,
She was the first nun I'd seen.
Frenchy, when you found
the nun, what did you do?
I moved it to protect the
body from the elements.
- Where did you move it to, son?
- The ice house.
That's where I leave my deliveries.
When I found the Sister, I thought...
might be, moving her in here
would help preserve her.
After You.
I should tell you one more thing, Father.
- What?
- That's not how I left her.
What do you mean?
She was laying down when I left her here.
Not like that sitting up.
There have been cases
of bodies twitching...
or sitting up, not long after death.
Yeah, but Father, who knows how long
she was dead when I found her.
- You are not helping.
- Sorry.
- Father, what is it?
- Seems to be a key of some kind.
DELIVERIES
That's the door the nuns would
enter from to choose supplies.
So they wouldn't have to leave the castle.
We should give her a proper burial.
In the name of the Father and
of the Son, and Holy Spirit.
Amen.
It's common practice during the plague,
when people feared to be buried alive.
If you were unfortunate
enough for it to happen...
You could ring the bell,
to let those above
ground know, they
have made a mistake.
I think being here is a mistake.
That's where I found her.
How is that possible? It's been weeks.
I told you. This place is...
What is the opposite
of a miracle, Father?
Hello?
Please excuse us for unannounced arrival.
What is it you want?
I'm Father Anthony Burke.
This is Sister Irene.
- Are you the Reverend Mother?
- I am.
You haven’t taken your vows yet.
No.
Why are you here, Father?
We come on behalf of Rome, to inquire
about the recent death in your convent.
Recent death?
One of your nuns.
I found her outside,
hang from her neck.
Is that so?
And you saw fit to bury her?
Would you allow us for a moment?
Please.
You should leave with him.
Are you saying you weren't aware
of the risk passing of the nun?
Rome is concerned about safety
and well-being of your closer.
I would like to speak with your sister, so
I can offer my assurances to the church.
I can offer the assurance you seek.
I'm afraid that won't suffice.
They will just send more, and perhaps
less diplomatic church officials.
Yes, Father.
However the gate will be closing shortly as
we are about to take out vespers..
Followed by the Great Silence
which ends near to morning.
Come back tomorrow and you will find
the answers you seek.
There is lodging in the convent,
you may stay there.
Thank you.
Why could you not talk to the sisters now?
Why must we wait til morning?
The sisters took the vow of silence from
sunset to sunrise. That must be respected.
You should begin heading back yourself.
You might didn't wanna be caught
on the relics when night falls.
Better roads than here, Father.
We'll be fine son.
Come back in a few days.
That should give us enough
time to get what we need.
Yes, Father.
Hello?
Hey... Hey!
I'll take.....that.
OK... alright.
- Father?
- Hmm?
You mentioned miracle hunting before.
Is that...
Is that a roll you sought up..
No. God, no.
I'm part of a...
small select field that church
relies on to...
look in to their more...
Unusual matters..
So you knew Bishop Forne?
- How do you...
- Because he helped me when I was younger.
I had a series of visions
when I was a girl.
My father believed
I was mentally unstable.
Or worse, a liar.
But word of my vision reached the church..
Cardinal Conroy, specifically, and
he sent Bishop Forne to meet with me.
What were your visions?
There were many, never
the same one repeated.
But, after each one ended.
The same thought would be stuck in my head.
Which was....what?
Mary points the way.
What is it, Father?
I was, thinking of a similar incident I
encountered in France. During the war..
I was stationed there, near Lyon.
I was told to investigate
a boy with visions.
But unlike your case...
after what I believe
with careful evaluation...
I made the judgment he was possessed...
I'm persuaded to act accordingly
within the laws of the church.
My God. Daniel...
What have they done to you?
Was it a success?
The church thought so.
They believed the evil was cast out.
But not you.
The most glorious Prince,
of the Heavenly Armies...
Saint Michael, the archangel...
Help me, Father.
Come to the assistance of Daniel.
The God and may in, his likeness.
- Behold the cross of Lord.
- Why don't you help me?
Begone, you evil forces.
Daniel sustained severe injuries
during the exorcism.
Ones from which he couldn't recover.
Daniel, I'm so sorry.
He died, days later.
I often wonder, if I was too eager
with my determination.
That is a puzzle.
Father.
Daniel?
Wait. No.
Help.
No.
Somebody.
Help.
Sister Irene. Help.
Father?
Help.
Help me.
- Father?
- Sister?
- Sister Irene.
- Father, I can hear you.
Over here.
Thank God. Thank you.
Hurry!!
Thank you, Thank you sister.
How did you get in there?
The ground was covered.
There's some powerful evil
presence in this place.
Maybe those books will help
shine a light on our answer.
There's more of it,
how's that possible?
Another puzzle.
Abbess?
As requested,
we're here to speak with the nuns.
It seems like not so much as an invitation
as we get. - I'll go find the Abbess.
Take this.
See what that you can find out about it.
It was obviously important to the desist.
Sister, be careful please.
I will, Father.
Hello?
Wait.
Plena, Dominus tecum.
Benedicta Tu in mulieribus, et benedictus
fructus ventris tui nobis peccatoribus...
nunc, et in hora mortis nostrae. Amen.
Ave Maria, gratia plena, Dominus tecum.
Benedicta Tu in mulieribus,
et Benedict fructus ventris tui, lesus.
Maria, Mater Dei, Ora pro nobis
peccatoribus, nunc, et in hor...
Ave Maria, gratia plena...
- benetus fructus ventris tui, lesus.
- Sister?
Ave Maria, gratia plena, Dominus tecum.
Benedicta Tu in mulieribus...
ventris tui, lesus.
Sancta Maria, Mater Dei,
Ora pro nobis peccatoribus...
nunc, et in hora mortis nostrae. Amen.
Ave Maria, gratia plena, Dominus tecum.
Benedicta Tu in mulieribus...
Sister.
We mustn't stop praying,
even for a second. This
convent has had perpetual
etheration for centuries.
This sisters prayers seems to maintain
the constant rituals.
I'm so sorry to have disturbed her.
Sister Ruth has listed more than just
someone sneaking up behind her.
I'm Sister Oana.
We were told you were coming.
Please, follow me.
Benedicta Tu in mulieribus,
et Benedict fructus ventris tui, lesus.
What?
Another round.
I told Luca it was on the house.
- Why did you cover the mirror?
- It's tradition here when someone dies.
You cover the mirror so
the deceased doesn't
see their reflection
and become a ghost.
- Someone died?
- You didn't hear?
Luca's daughter committed suicide.
I can't believe it.
She was just a kid.
12 years old.
Hang herself in his barn.
Hanged herself?
Why?
Why the Addi Constantine's
crop turn to dust?
Why little Stefan struck blind?
It's that place. The abbey.
Whatever evil is up there, it's
leaking out, poisoning us.
And that couple that you took up there
yesterday.
- Who were they?
- A priest and a nun.
Are they still up there?
Yeah, pick them up tomorrow.
You recently
discovered the body up
- there..didn't you?
- Yeah Grigore, yeah.
Well, I believe you are
about to discover two more.
An out of the ground, formed
every beast of the field...
To every bird of the sky.
Forever the man called the demon creature
at last, it's name.
Valak.
The defiler.
The Profane.
The Marquis of Snakes.
Sister.
Sister Irene.
Sister Victoria's death
was a terrible tragedy for the convent...
but we still feel her presence.
She was the most devoted out of any of us.
Excuse me, sister.
Sister Vic...
Forgive us.
We are highly protective of our privacy.
Some other sisters would prefer to not
speak to you, at all.
We appreciate your willingness
to do so.
Sister Oana, can you tell me
about the history of this abbey?
It was built by a duke
in the Dark Ages.
The Duke of St. Carta.
He wrote countless texts
on witchcraft and rituals...
in which to call
upon the forces of hell.
Hell used him to open a gateway, so that
an unspeakable evil would walk amongst us.
But the church stormed the castle.
They sealed the gateway,
using an ancient relic...
Containing the blood of Jesus Christ.
The church claimed the
castle for their own...
and our perpetual praying began, to
secure the abbey and contain the evil.
For centuries it worked,
and evil was keep at bay...
until the bombs of war
shook the abbey...
and evil found another way
to open the gateway.
Sister Oana,
last night in the chapel I saw a nun.
She was, she felt anything but holy.
Did you see her too?
I've seen her stalking
the hallways at night.
We all have.
She looks like us,
but she's not one of us.
It's something unholy.
It takes on different forms to deceive us
and prey on our weaknesses.
It appears as a nun so it could hide among
our clothes until it can corrupt us all.
I fear her presence means
the portal has opened again.
It means, Sister Victoria
commit the ultimate sin.
Sister Oana.
Sister Ruth is nearly finished
with her prayers.
- It's time you turn to yours.
- Yes sister.
- You haven't taken your vows yet?
- No.
Then, this is not a place for you.
You need to leave, now.
She can't.
The gates have closed.
You must stay until they open again.
- When do they open?
- Sunrise, you must stay the night.
Sister Irene.
Good night, sister.
- Sister, wait.
- Yes.
Sister Victoria had this
in her possession when
she died. Do you happen
to know what it's for?
No.
Now please, I must go pray.
Where are you?
You wont find another way in, Father.
Abbess?
What is it that concerns you?
I'm afraid..there is something very
wrong with this place, Abbess.
Like many places in this world,
the abbey has a long history.
Not all good, but we repent.
That nun..I found her, clutching
the key in her hands.
What does it open, Abbess?
It's too late, Father.
Sister Irene is lost.
Abbess?
Sister Irene.
Mary points the way.
Who are you?
God save you.
Sister please, come.
Sister Oana?
Oh God.
Quiet.
The evil grows stronger.
Get your things and meet
me in the chapel, sister.
Only prayer would get
us through the night.
Go, leave.
Now.
Santa María, Madre de
Dios, ruega por nosotros
pecadores, ahora y en la
hora de nuestra muerte.
Hello?
Dios Te salve, Maria. Llena eres
de gracia: El Senor es contigo.
Santa María, Madre de Dios,
ruega por nosotros pecadores,
ahora y en la hora de nuestra muerte.
Santa María, Madre de Dios,
ruega por nosotros pecadores,
blessed among women
and the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
The Mother of God Pray for us...
ahora y en la hora de nuestra muerte..
now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with you.
Blessed among women
and the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
The Mother of God Pray for us ..
Now and at the hour of our death.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee
Sister Oana?
The Mother of God Pray for us...
now and at the hour of our death
Hail Mary, full of grace...
How long have I been dead, Father?
How long?
Daniel?
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you help me?
Mother of God Pray for us...
now and at the hour of our death.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee..
Blessed among women
and the fruit of your womb.
The Mother of God Pray for us...
now and at the hour of our death.
We need to pray, now!
And what ever happens,
what ever you may see or
hear keep your eyes forward
and don't stop praying.
Hail Mary, full of grace;
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed among women
and the fruit of your womb.
The Mother of God Pray for us...
now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
The Mother of God...
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with you.
Blessed among women...
DELIVERIES
"That's the door the nuns would enter
from to retrieve their supplies".
"So they wouldn't have
to leave the castle".
Holy Mother of God.
Frenchy.
Thought you could use some help.
Thank you.
But please, by all means.
Next time, do use the shotgun.
I'm saving that for emergencies, Father.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with you.
Blessed among women.
The Mother of God...
now and in
now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with you.
Among women
and the fruit of your womb.
The Mother of God...
The Mother of God, pray for us.
Ave Maria
full of grace, the Lord is with thee.
Among women because the fruit.
The Mother of God Pray for us...
now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with you.
Benedicta Tu in mulieribus.
Sister.
Sister Irene.
Father Burke.
It's Father Burke.
He will help us.
Sister.
Sister Irene.
- Thank God, Father.
- Are you all right, sister?
Frenchy?
What happened?
We've been praying, all of us together.
Perpetual etheration, it's the only thing
that's been holding back the evil.
Who's been praying?
All of us. The other nuns.
They were here.
They were praying with me,
when we're attacked.
The nuns tried to warn me.
- Visions.
- It felt so real.
There's no one left.
We have our answer, Father.
As if there was any doubt,
before this place is no longer holy.
Our Father.
Father, what do we do?
Get my bag, sister.
Holy cross.
Put some holy water on this.
- Here.
- Hurry! Please father, hurry.
Put her down.
Cover its face.
The Gods out, the demon in you...
In the name of the God, and the Father all
vanity and the power of the Holy Spirit.
I ask this in the name
forefather, Jesus Christ.
Which is the Judge
all the living and the dead...
and the world of fire.
That felt like an emergency.
We're too late.
The evil is free.
No.
For demon to enter our world,
it must possess a human soul.
Sister Victoria must have been the last nun
in this Cloistered.
- You know what you must do.
- I can't.
Then not even God...
It wasn't suicide.
It was a sacrifice...
so the evil wouldn't take her soul.
I did not understand what you just
said, but I ahh...
Sounds like your investigation is complete.
So let's get out the here.
- We can't just leave.
- Oh come on, why the hell not?
We have to seal the gateway,
to contain the evil.
The gateways is in the catacombs.
But we can't close it,
without the relic, the blood of Christ.
'Christ.' Jesus Christ?
Did the sisters tell you where it is?
The Abbess was found dead
in the tunnel to the catacombs.
I think I know where that tunnel is.
Good, then that's where we look first.
But Father, before we do...
I'd like to take my vows.
Are you certain?
My visions.
I now know they are miracle of God and
I am ready to commit my life to him.
That sister is a noble act.
It's a shame, but...
By the authority entrusted to me,
and in the name of the church...
I receive the vows you have taken.
I earnestly commend you to God.
That your gift of self is made one,
with the sacrifice of the Eucharist...
And might be brought to perfection.
May the love of God,
unite you forever and ever.
In nomine Patris et Filii
et Spiritus Sancti.
Amen.
There's nothing here.
There has to be.
They told me this key unlocked
the doors to the relic.
That could be anywhere in the castle.
It is here, don't you see, sister?
What?
Mary points the way.
The blood of Christ.
Holy SHIT.
The Holys'.
Only a true bride of Christ
can wield something so sacred.
Wait.
What is it?
Shouldn't we say a prayer or
something first?
There's a time for prayer,
and a time for action, son.
Now is the time for action.
Also still feels like a time for prayer
as well, Father.
"Finit hic, Deo."
"God ends here."
We need to search everywhere
to find the gateway.
Sister Irene. This way.
Hello?
Sister Irene.
Sister.
Irene.
Lord Jesus, in the holy name...
I bind all evil spirits to this fire.
Protect us from evil
with your holy light.
Frenchy, help me.
Of course.
Notre Père qui es aux cieux
Que ton nom soit sanctifi
Que ton r gne vienne
Que ta volont soit faite sur la terre
comme Au ciel
Amen.
You failed.
Just u failed everyone in your life.
Tomorrow, a village will
be missing, you idiot.
You should have kept dreaming
when you had the chance, Frenchman.
I am French-Canadian.
Run.
Frenchy!
No!
Sister... Sister Irene.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Come on.
I hope you don’t mind,
is called the 'kiss of life'.
Just call that way.
It's just, it's not really...
Frenchy, what's your real name?
Maurice.
Thank you for saving my life, Maurice.
You're welcome.
We should get going.
At your hands O'Lord, we humbly
deliver your servance...
the nuns of St. Carta.
They served You in this life
with strength and faith.
Deliver them now from every evil.
And let them live with you
in perfect grace forever.
Amen.
I thought this ground
wasn't holy anymore.
It is now.
Will you stay on in Biertan?
I think I have live feel of Romania.
My father was a tomato farmer.
Maybe I'll try that for while.
Sounds little boring for a
world traveler like you.
Certainly hope so.
20 YEARS LATER
An exorcism can be very dangerous not only
for the victim, but for anyone in the room.
Take Maurice Theriault.
His friends called him Frenchy.
He was a French Canadian farmer.
Nothing more than a third grade education.
After he was possessed...
He spoke some of the best
Latin I had ever heard.
And like that, an upside down cross
started to appear from within his body.
Which brings me to the three stages
of demonic activities.
Infestation...
Oppression...
Possession.