Gangland enforcers broke the arms
of an elderly news dealer
this afternoon,
when he refused to share
his week's receipts with them.
Stacks of newspapers
were tossed in the gutter,
as the thugs wrecked the business
and made their getaway.
Lunchtime crowds were paralyzed
by the suddenness of the crime.
Not a hand was raised in protest.
Organized crime is their name.
What appeared to be organized hoods
shattered the kneecaps
of the beloved operator
of a shoeshine parlor today,
as horrified customers looked on.
The bootblack would not
give up his receipts,
and paid dearly for his failure
to surrender to gang demands.
A mother offour,
unable to pay a gambling debt,
lies dead tonight.
Gangland thugs left her
to expire in a pool of blood,
as they helped themselves
to the contents of a cash register
in her son's luncheonette.
I was talkin' to them
at the station house,
and it was the darnedest thing
I ever saw...
Five, no help. King, no help.
- Aces and eights.
- Twenty.
Okay, I'm callin' it.
Deuce, still possible. Six, no help.
Pair of aces, pair of eights.
Okay, the ace bets.
- Hey! Little Face!
- What's the trouble?
Come on, let's go!
Ace bets five.
I call.
- Six.
- See ya.
What's that?
Cat.
Aw, a little kitty.
Hi, little fella!
Let's go.
- Ace bets five.
- I'm callin'.
I'm in.
Six.
You got a possible straight.
Queen. Eight. Pair of eights.
Nine, no help. Jack, no help.
King, no help.
Well, Little Face?
See what you can find.
I wanna leave a little message here.
Calling Dick Tracy. Calling Dick Tracy.
- Come in, Pat. This is Tracy.
- What is that?
We got five dead men
at the Seventh Street Garage,
and nobody knows who they are.
You better get over here right away.
I'm on my way.
I'll be back.
I wanna know how it comes out.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
- Ow!
- Sorry.
- Hello, boys.
- Tracy!
Tracy, are we glad to see you.
Tracy, whoever they are,
they're all dead.
Five dead men, Tracy.
And we don't even know who they are.
Whoever did it took their identification.
- But they didn't take a dime.
- Big Boy Caprice.
Everything all right, Tracy?
Fine, fine.
Just a little trouble downtown.
Tracy,
they're saying that Big Boy's
got the city out of control.
What about this rumor
they're movin' you up to chief of police?
We've already got an excellent
chief of police, Bert.
Why don't you shave off
that silly moustache?
How 'bout runnin' for mayor, Tracy?
I'm a cop, Charlie.
I don't want to take a demotion.
Hey, McNally,
I want a copy of that shot.
You got it, Tess.
They're sayin' Big Boy's got
the city out of control!
Still can't get anything on him, huh?
Don't let them get to you, Tracy.
You'll get Big Boy.
Big Boy's on the street and they want
to stick me behind a desk?
They believe in you, Tracy.
They think if you're chief of police,
the city'll be safe!
Tess, there's about as much chance
of me gettin' behind a desk
as there is of me gettin' a new girlfriend.
Sooner or later you're gonna decide.
Sooner or later there's nowhere to hide.
Baby, it's time
So why waste it in chatter?
Let's settle.
The matter.
Baby, you're mine on a platter
I always get my man
I'm gonna love you
like nothin' you've known
and you all alone.
Sooner is better than later
But lover
I'll hover
I'll plan.
This time I'm not only getting
I'm holding.
My man.
Bad news on the garage, Lips.
They've bumped them all off.
Our men are getting very nervous.
- Champagne, Miss Mahoney?
- Breathless,
that was beautiful, as always.
I'm so happy you liked it.
- You mind if I leave?
- Why?
I get sick when you eat.
You didn't used to.
You didn't used to be a zeppelin.
- Your devotion is touching.
- Lips!
Lips! It's a raid! It's the cops!
Lips Manlis, you're under arrest,
for owning and operating
a gambling establishment.
- Yeah? Where's your warrant?
- Right here. Let's go.
- You, too, Breathless.
- I wasn't gamblin', I was singin'.
- Get in the car.
- Flattop.
- These ain't cops!
- Who are they?
Hiya, Lips. Hiya, Breathless. Let's go.
Even Chief Brandon says
you'd make a wonderful chief of police.
It's a desk job.
What's so bad
about a desk job, anyway?
You think if you sit at a desk,
you're playin' it safe.
If you weren't out in the street
every night, risking your neck,
you could have a wife. I mean a life!
Nobody's gonna put Big Boy Caprice
behind bars sittin' behind a desk.
Tracy, you said you were going
to take a day off tomorrow.
Hmm?
Come on.
- Tracy, did you say you were gonna...
- Sure...
Hey, kid. What's your hurry?
Where are ya goin'?
- Stop him! Hey, stop!
- Take it easy.
- He stole my watch!
- Hey, kid?
- Stop that boy! Stop that boy.
- Hey, hey, kid!
Come here!
Did you steal this man's watch?
Hi, Tess.
The rest of my party should
be arriving any minute.
Come on, kid. You're makin' a mistake.
It's only a watch! You don't wanna
get yourself in this kind of trouble!
Hey! What are ya tryin' to do?
You're gonna get hurt, kid!
Be careful! You're gonna get hurt!
- What did you get?
- Didn't save me no chicken.
Things is tough.
- That's all?
- Yeah.
Hey, tough guy. Want to try that
on somebody your own size?
Maybe we should step outside.
Okay, tough guy. Now do you want
to give the kid a piece of chicken?
We got a place for people
who beat up kids.
- This cockroach your old man?
- Go suck an egg.
Look what you did
to your pretty tuxedo.
- Big Boy, ain't we pals?
- No pals in this business, Lips.
You taught me that. Sign it.
- The deed to the Club Ritz!
- That's right.
I'm goin' into show business now.
You're dirty, Lips. You need a bath.
Not the bath! Not the bath!
Big Boy, not the bath!
- Hey. You got a name?
- Kid.
- Kid?
What's the name your mother
and father gave ya?
What mother and father?
- Who takes care of you?
This is Moriarty.
I'm at the Southside Warehouse.
- Do you read me?
- Repeat, Moriarty.
- You're at the Southside Warehouse?
- Right.
I don't know who they are,
and I can't see what goin' on inside.
The car was unmarked...
Big Boy, we're friends! Not the bath!
Not the bath! We're friends!
I know, and I'm gonna miss ya.
But, "All's fair in love and business."
Benjamin Franklin.
Big Boy. Big Boy, Big Boy.
Think about it.
How could you do this to me?
- You.
- Me?
- How do you want it?
- Want it?
Allow me. If a woman don't wear mink,
she don't wear nothin'.
Well, I look good both ways.
Mumbles! Wipe it off.
All right! Put the word out!
Lips' territory is my territory now.
Everyone who worked for him
is workin' for me!
Everything he owned, I own!
Let's get outta here.
Cover that trapdoor!
You are my lucky charm.
With you here on my arm.
Well, we gotta call
the Welfare Society. Hey, Mike.
Wait. The what?
The boy's home. Mike?
You got any ice cream?
- Hey!
- Let me go!
Hey, where are you goin'?
What are you doing?
You ain't stickin' me in no orphanage.
I've been there!
Hey, come on. Sit down. Sit down.
I'm very sorry, pal.
It's the law. Sit down.
Look, Kid, if you don't have
a home with a mother and a father,
you go to the orphanage, it's the law!
Hey, Mike. You got any ice cream?
Calling Dick Tracy. Calling Dick Tracy.
Bring the Kid some ice cream.
Come in, Sam.
Southside Warehouse,
on the river, Tracy.
Somethin's goin' on.
You better get down here.
I'm on my way.
Hey, Tracy,
what about the eating machine?
Huh? Oh.
Can you watch him or somethin'?
Watch him do what?
Uh...
Well,
take him to my place.
I'll tell Pat to call the orphanage.
- You two married?
- No.
Would you like a broken arm?
- I don't like dames.
- Good. Me neither.
- Walnuts!
- Walnuts?
Tracy, there's a widow to whom a few
words need to be said in bereavement.
Pat, bring in Flattop and Itchy.
Sam, get these fingerprinted.
- Flattop and Itchy? For what?
- I wanna find Lips Manlis fast.
- With a handful of walnuts?
- Yeah, with a handful of walnuts?
Walnuts?
All right, all right, all right.
Hello, gentlemen.
- Where's Lips Manlis?
- Who's Lips Manlis?
Yeah, who's Lips Manlis?
We get to make one phone call,
that's the law.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Gimme the phone.
There's the phone. Be my guest.
Make a note, Pat.
They waived their right to a phone call.
- Right, Tracy.
- Hey, copper.
Maybe you ought to look before
you leap, huh? We got rights.
Take the bad men away.
They scare me.
- Up and at 'em. Get outta here.
- We got rights, too, you know?
- Take your story walkin', Itchy.
- See you around, Tracy, huh?
- Come on!
- All right, all right.
- Get your mitts off me.
- Can't do this, Tracy.
The D.A.'ll say
you're badgering witnesses.
Get me Mumbles.
You have no right to do that.
Hello, Mumbles.
- Where's Lips Manlis?
- I don't know...
Where's Lips Manlis?
Got my diamonds, got my yacht.
Yacht!
Got a guy I adore.
"A guy I adore!"
Let's hear it! Let's hear it!
I'm so happy with what I got.
Come on! Let's go.
I want more!
Stretch it, stretch it!
"More!" They want, "More!"
Count your blessings.
"Count your blessings!"
One, two, three
I just hate keeping score
"I hate keeping score," let's show it!
Move it, touch it! Touch it, I want it!
Any number is fine with me.
Grab it! More!
As long as it's more.
More! Let's go!
Come on! More! Good!
More! More!
If you've got a little, why not a lot?
Add a bit and it'll get to be a oodle.
Everyjot and tittle adds to the pot.
Gotta pick it up!
Soon you've got the kit
as well as the caboodle.
More!
Up! Up!
Come on, up! More! Higher!
More!
Let's go!
Never say when
Never stop at plenty
lf it's gonna rain, let it pour.
Happy with ten
Happier with twenty
lf you like a penny
Wouldn't you like many much more?
"Would you like a penny much more?"
Or does that sound too greedy?
That's not greed, no indeedy.
That's just stocking the store.
Give it to me!
Hmm.
Mumbles? Where's Lips Manlis?
That's what's soothing about excess.
Kick it up! Kick it up!
Come on. Down in front!
Never settle for something less.
Something's better than nothing, yes!
But nothing's better than more.
More.
More! More! More! More!
More! More! More!
No! No! It's wrong!
It's off, it's wrong! It doesn't work!
- It's not good. What?
- Boss! Boss!
I'm sorry. These girls are tired.
Yeah, we been doin' it all night.
It's 2:00 a.m.
It's 2:00 a.m.?
I'm about to turn this dump
into the birthplace
of a new era in entertainment!
You're tellin' me it's 2:00 a.m.?
Play the piano!
Hey! That was a silly thing to do.
He's the best piano player in town.
Shut up!
Come here.
Next time I take his fingers,
and I turn them into pretzels.
I just might do
the same thing to your face.
See? He's playin' better already.
Let's go.
From the toppy-top!
From the top!
Care for some water? I'm thirsty.
Where's Lips Manlis?
You heard it, Mrs. Green.
That's his testimony.
- Okay, boys. Get his out of here.
- His what?
Hey, hey! Wrong way, Mumbles.
That's coercion, Tracy.
Even if you get anything, it's illegal.
Just tell those boys in the lab.
Fingerprint those walnuts
by 8:00 in the morning,
'cause I'm gonna bring
Big Boy in tonight.
You what?
- That's the fifth time!
- It's a gamble, if you can't make it stick.
Let me tell you what the gamble is,
leavin' Big Boy on the street.
Let's go get him.
No indeedy
That's just stocking...
Hello, Big Boy.
I brought your garbage.
- Tracy!
- We meet again, huh?
- Where's Lips?
- This is a private club, copper.
- You got a membership card? I own it!
- Do you?
- Since when?
- Today.
- I made a deal with Lips.
- Lips!
- Where is he?
- I don't know. Must have left town.
Well, that's a coincidence.
My new girl, Breathless Mahoney,
meet Dick Tracy.
A servant of the people. Like me.
- You like walnuts, don't you, Big Boy?
- I love them!
A lot of people like walnuts.
They're good for the liver.
Yeah. But they're bad for the brain.
You're sloppy, Big Boy.
You're under arrest.
Get him outta here, boys.
We got a nice place for him to sleep,
- where they don't serve walnuts.
- Half hour, boss.
You'll be back
before the opening number, boss.
This ain't no break!
Keep rehearsin'! Get the lawyer.
- See ya in a half hour, boss.
- Tell him this flatfoot is at it again.
He's got no case.
Hello?
You're breaking
and entering, you know.
- Sorry.
- Sit down.
Aren't you gonna arrest me?
If I were gonna arrest you,
I'd have done it by now.
Then what are you up to, honey?
I think Lips Manlis is dead.
And I want you to tell me who killed him.
Or maybe you weren't on his side.
- Whose side are you on?
- The side I'm always on.
- Mine.
- No grief for Lips?
I'm wearing black underwear.
You know, it's legal for me
to take you down to the station
and sweat it out of you under the lights.
I sweat a lot better in the dark.
I know how you feel. You don't know
if you want to hit me or kiss me.
- I get a lot of that.
- Look, you're safe. Big Boy's in jail.
You're the one that can keep him there.
Give me a call.
You can do a little two-step
I'll go anywhere that you step to.
'Cause now I'm followin' you.
My feet might be falling out of rhythm.
Don't know what
I'm doin' with them, but...
My gosh! What time is it?
It's 6:30.
I have to get to the greenhouse.
Got those delphiniums comin' in.
Pat says he's gonna call
the orphanage today.
- Tracy, you might try waterin' those.
- Tess!
Mmm-hmm?
Thanks for watchin' the Kid.
- 'Night, Tracy.
- And Tess?
You know you're one in a million?
Romance is in the picture too
Now I'm followin' you
Tracy, good night.
By the way, Tracy. Have a good sleep.
Rompin', rompin'
Stompin', I'm rompin'
Rompin', stompin'
I'm rompin'
Rompin', stompin' all day.
- Tried the iodine transfer?
- Yes, Tracy.
- The silver nitrate?
- Twice.
Big Boy Caprice's fingerprints
are not on those walnuts, Tracy.
Well, I had to take the gamble.
What is it, Sam?
Tess is waiting. Boy's Department,
Marshall and Bradbury.
She says she's not going to go for
a drive in the country with that Kid
if he's wearin' the clothes he has on.
They stink.
Police brutality, boys.
And this is the fifth time.
Lucky for me, I don't bruise easily.
Mr. Caprice, do you intend to take legal
action against the city for false arrest?
Why should I blame the city
for something one man is doing?
This Tracy character is unstable.
The city should get rid of him.
You mean,
if you don't get rid of him first.
Who said that?
Hey, there's Fletcher!
"Law without order is as great
a danger to the people
"as order without law." Jefferson.
How can I support
a maverick police detective
who keeps making false arrests
of private citizens
and throwing them in jail?
Tracy, I am District Attorney.
Tracy, Tess can't get the Kid
- to take off these smelly clothes.
- Chief!
I am a candidate for mayor.
If you can't control Detective Tracy,
you'll just have to take him off duty.
Or I'll have to prosecute him,
and take you off duty.
Tracy, Tess is havin' a terrible
time with this Kid. What should I do?
Hey, hey, hey.
Come here! Come on!
You don't have to wear
what Tess tells you to wear.
Come here.
Where are you goin'?
What are you runnin' away from?
I don't need no suit.
- A suit's for school.
- School?
You can't fool me.
That means the orphanage.
I ain't wearin' no suit.
Kid, your clothes don't smell
very good, okay?
If you don't want to wear a suit, just go
back in there and say you don't want to.
Otherwise, pick the suit you like.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Just we two, flyin' high and hidin'
Up in a tree
Live alone and like it.
That's the answer for me
Don't come out of that tree.
Get your mitts off of me.
I can do it myself!
Young man! Ow!
Get outta here.
The young man will be out in a moment.
All right. When do we eat?
Live alone and like it
Free as the birds in the trees.
When do we eat?
High above the briars
Live alone and like it
I do whatever I please.
When do we eat?
When my heart desires
Free to hang around or fly.
At any old time.
When do we eat?
No equivocation
Most of all, no guarantees.
That's my only motto
Free of obligations.
Only the murmuring breeze.
When do we eat?
As an obbligato
Live alone and like it.
Why is that such a crime?
Free to call the tune.
Free to say if I'm gonna work or play
I can have the moon.
But I don't have to have it
Night and day.
Anyway
What I like is gliding.
Where the wind takes me to
Flyin' high and hidin'
Up in a tree
Live alone and like it.
That's the answer for me.
Don't come out of that tree.
Nice day.
Yeah.
What?
- I been thinkin', Tess.
- What about?
- Well, you livin' alone...
- I like living alone.
- Huh?
- You know that. I'm not the lonely type.
Well,
that's something we got in common.
Yup, we have that in common.
Well, don't you think that
since we have so much in common,
it might be a good idea if we just
- went ahead and...
- Yes?
Well...
Look, I wasn't thinkin'
about you livin' alone,
as much as I was thinkin'
about me livin' alone.
- I mean...
- Hey, Tracy, watch out!
- Tracy, wait!
- You all right, Kid?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- Thanks for the tip.
- Who was it, Tracy?
- I don't know, Kid.
- I thought we was goners.
- They're just tryin' to scare us.
- Jeez, this is incredible!
What are we waitin' for? Let's get them!
Let's get them! Come on, let's go.
We can still get them!
They took a right, I saw them!
I'm sorry.
This is amazing, Tracy.
Come on! Let's go!
Tracy,
when you play in the street,
it's part of the game, I know that.
Just don't ask me to like it.
Come on! Let's go!
They headed up towards Main Street.
Who was it, Tracy?
I don't know, boys. Do me a favor.
Stick around here, will ya?
Sure, Tracy.
...police have been so wrong
in their search for the perpetrators
and the citizens of the peace-abiding
neighborhood are up in arms
over the clash of gunfire
that shattered the night.
Thanks for calling.
I was beginning to wonder
what a girl had to do to get arrested.
Well, wearin' that dress
is a step in the right direction.
Are you gonna make a move,
or do I have to do everything?
- I'm on duty.
- What's your day off?
Sunday.
It's a big world.
It must be Sunday somewhere.
Seem hot to you?
Hot?
Why did you call me here?
You know that car?
What I'm looking for is a driver.
Preferably one with some mileage.
Yeah?
I called you here 'cause I want
to know if you're ready to testify.
No?
You're right, Tracy.
Why would you get mixed up with me?
I'm a cheap floozy to you.
I'll be lucky if I get
through the week alive.
They probably followed me here.
It isn't easy, Tracy.
You want to throw me in jail?
Go ahead.
Let's dance.
Watch the Kid.
You can do a little two-step
I'll go anywhere that you step to.
'Cause now I'm followin' you.
My feet might be falling out of rhythm.
Don't know what I'm doin' with them.
But I know I'm followin' you.
I remember all of ya
from when I was nothin'.
Pruneface, you tossed a firebomb
in my car one night,
give me a lot of trouble, but I forgive ya.
Mocca, you put three slugs
into me, but I lived.
I forgive you, too. I owe everybody
at this table a little something.
But I forgive all of you. Why?
Because I put the past in the past.
However, a boss
who cannot see the future
becomes a liability
to everyone concerned.
What are ya, a fortune teller?
What do you mean, the future?
Pruneface, what I mean
is the future is me.
Pat, Sam, come in. This is Tracy.
I followed her to the Club Ritz.
It looks like we got every hood in town
in one room.
Pruneface, Flattop, Johnny Ramm...
- Those guys hate each other!
- Better get over here, fast.
- L gotta find out why they're together.
- All right, let's go.
Baby, you're mine on a platter
I always.
Get my...
We got a problem with
organization. We're all split up.
That's bad business.
While we're divided,
the cops can keep us under control.
But use your imaginations.
We form this big company, see?
Each of us here at the table
are on the board of directors.
- I'm Chairman of the Board.
- Why you?
Because I have a vision.
A big boss must have a vision.
We got a town with thousands
of small stores and businesses.
People who are working real hard.
I think they should be workin' real hard.
For us.
Because we are for the people.
"And if you ain't for the people,
"you can't buy the people."
Lincoln.
We will become
the people's silent partner.
Every time some citizen buys a pound
of hamburger, we get a nickel.
Every time some guy gets a haircut,
we get a dime.
We'll dress like bankers.
Join the Rotary Club.
- Together, we will own this town.
- Why you?
- Excuse me.
- Hey!
When do we kill Dick Tracy?
As you know,
if anything happens to Tracy,
I'm the prime suspect.
- Leave Dick Tracy to me.
- I say we kill Tracy now.
- You say?
- I say.
I say you say nothing. I say,
you get behind me, we all profit.
You challenge me, we all go down!
There was one Napoleon,
one Washington, one me!
I'm out.
It only works if we're all in.
Then it don't work.
I got a good business.
I'll take my chances alone.
Let him go, let him go.
It's still a free country.
Maybe he'll have a change of heart.
Sam, I'm worried about Tracy.
What would it take to make you
go off your trolley?
Not me. I'm not the type.
Tracy, you crazy?
You don't have a search warrant.
If you don't get off that ledge,
do you have any idea
what the D.A. will do to you?
- This is Pat. Come on down.
- Just be ready to get me out of here.
Who's that? Spaldoni?
I think that's Spaldoni leaving.
If any of those bums find you,
the chief'll never forgive ya.
Come on, Tracy, get off that building.
If they catch ya,
they got a perfect right
to do whatever they...
- Great Scot!
Very upsetting.
Go, Sam. Get him!
Peppermint. Try some.
You know, Tracy, for a tough guy,
you do a lot of pansy things.
Is that right?
- Who is it?
- Mr. Tracy?
- I'm Mrs. Skaff.
- I'm from the Welfare Department.
- The Welfare Department?
I'm afraid we're going
to have to take
the little boy to the orphanage.
Well, just give me
one minute, Mrs. Skaff.
I hope you understand,
Mr. Tracy. As a single man,
you can't just pick up a child
from the streets and take him home.
- He belongs in an orphanage.
- Mrs. Skaff, let's discuss this.
It's the law. Then he has to be
processed through proper channels.
- And then we have to...
- Mrs. Skaff, if you'll leave
this situation to me, I think you'll...
- We don't want no kid, copper.
- Yeah, we don't want no kid, copper.
Get dressed.
Come on. Get in there or I'll plug you.
Yeah, come on.
Glad you could join us, Tracy.
We thought you'd be
much more comfortable
meeting us here in the basement
of your girlfriend's apartment building,
while she's away at work.
You know, Dick...
You mind if I call you Dick?
My associates here
would very much like to see you
have a little accident.
But I tell them, "No."
"I'll take care of Tracy myself,"
I tell them.
You know why?
I want you on my side!
And let me tell you what my side is.
My side is a lifetime of action
and adventure, with no clock to punch.
It's treating that gal of yours 100%.
She should be treated like a princess,
protected like a baby.
You gonna put
all that money down there?
Fifteen thousand clams.
- It's a deal.
- Fifteen thousand clams.
Welcome to new orders, Dick.
We're gonna run one hell of a ship
with you aboard.
There's a big world out there,
and it's up for sale!
All of it. All we gotta do
is to make sure that the people know
I'm the one big enough to run it.
And that you are guilty of attempting
to bribe an officer of the law.
- Hey, hey!
- Not so fast, copper.
- You dumb dick!
- Let's give it to him!
Okay, boys. Do it!
You have just said good-bye
to oxygen!
You silly, stupid cop.
You refused me.
I offer you the keys to a kingdom,
and you tell me you're
an officer of the law!
I am the law! Me!
Boys, you guarantee me that this
is going to look like an accident.
Don't disappoint me. So long, sucker.
You should have made the deal.
Yeah. You're gonna have
one terrible accident, Tracy.
I don't even think
they're gonna find your body.
- Dumb dick.
- I didn't think Tracy'd take a bribe.
Ouch! This accident's been waitin'
to happen all day, Tracy.
You sure you don't want
to change your mind?
I guess
that's the end of Dick.
Thirty seconds, no more Dick.
Thirty seconds, no more Dick!
Hey, Tracy!
Kid! Get outta there!
Get away from there!
The furnace is gonna explode!
Get outta here, Kid. Get outta here.
Sit tight, Tracy. I'll get you out of here!
Hit the dirt!
Jeez, Tracy, that was a lot of dough.
You're all right, Kid.
"For action
in the face of grave danger,
"the Kid," whose name will be
filled in when he thinks of one,
"is awarded this Honorary Detective
certificate, with badge."
- Congratulations, pal.
- The best-lookin' officer on the force.
- With or without a name.
- But this is just a temporary certificate,
- till you pick a name for yourself.
- What's the matter with "Kid"?
Nothin'. This means no more
jumpin' on the back of cars.
- Got it?
- Tracy.
When does this
become permanent?
I got a badge for you.
- When he picks a name.
- What do you mean?
Look in your top drawer.
You already got the makings
of a detective.
Chief, it's temporary
till he picks a name, huh?
Sure, he'll pick a name.
Couple of years, this Kid'll be drivin'.
Maybe I'll make him my partner.
Sam, that's somethin'.
How'd ya like to pick your own name?
- Put her there, Detective.
- Know what I'd pick? I'd pick Sam.
What's that matter?
We're not paying you enough money?
Don't tell me about my boys
messin' up the Tracy rubout,
they were being tested, they flunked!
Now, they're just flunkies. Like you.
I don't care if Tracy
puts one and one together.
Don't matter to me.
You're still workin' for me!
You're on my side. You're not out.
You're not out.
When you are dead, then you are out.
You are mine. I own you.
Tracy, we've got 14 witnesses,
they all insist Big Boy
spent the entire morning
- at a dance lesson.
- Uh-huh.
I am sorry!
Be just a second, Tess.
- What kind of ice cream did you get?
- Fresh peach.
Better eat it right away.
It's starting to run a little.
What are you doin' here?
Aren't you gonna frisk me?
You're so good with names.
What's a name that you like?
I don't know.
Herbert. Horace. Thomas. Edgar.
Anything's better than "Kid." Hold this.
- Well, I like "Kid."
- If you want that detective certificate
to be permanent,
you gotta pick a name.
Gimme.
- She's pretty.
- She's a lot more than that.
Look, if I testify against Big Boy,
he'll have me bumped off.
He'd have to bump me off first.
Why?
Because, I'd be protecting you,
24 hours a day.
- You would?
- Yeah. That's my job.
Do you always put so much
of yourself in yourjob?
You're not gonna know that
till you testify.
You're a good man, Tracy.
And I want to do the right thing.
Come here.
Hey! What's the hurry?
Where's the fire?
Throwin' a ball in a trash can,
is that supposed to be some big...
Tess, this is...
I know who she is.
Hello, Miss Mahoney.
You must be Miss Trueheart.
Tracy's told me so much about you.
Oh?
He doesn't know
so awfully much about me.
Yeah, well, thanks for comin' by.
- We'll be in touch, Tracy.
- Right.
Miss Trueheart.
What a cute little boy.
I'll bet she does some
nifty undercover work.
Well, we're makin' our move
on the Club Ritz tonight.
Is this pistachio?
Now, that's what I call a dame.
What was she doin' here?
She knows something.
I'm tryin' to get her to testify.
You know what, Tracy?
You ought to let me talk to her.
Is this 88 Keys?
I got a deal for you. Meet me at
the city car barn in one hour.
That's right. One hour.
Up here, 88.
Open the suitcase.
Do you wanna know why I called you?
Five thousand. Your first payment.
- For what?
- You work for Big Boy now.
You want to make a lot
of money helpin' him?
- Yes or no?
- Yeah.
Give that letter to Big Boy,
tell him you found it under your door.
Who do I tell him you are?
You don't, because you never saw me.
And don't try to find me, I'll call you.
Make the deal.
"If you kill Dick Tracy,
you will be the prime suspect,
"and the city will mobilize against you.
"But for 10% of your business,
we guarantee.
"Dick Tracy will not be
a problem for you anymore,
"and you will not be
suspected of anything."
What can you lose?
If they don't deliver, you don't pay.
You're a piano player.
What do you want to be? A radish?
Don't bring me a deal
from someone you never saw,
you don't know how to get to.
Get him out of here.
Go ahead. Play the piano.
Okay, what's this?
I think I got this figured out.
Hey! Got a match?
- What was that all about?
- My income tax.
Hey!
- Come here.
- You want me to follow him?
Where? To the piano?
That was none of your business.
Come here. I'm your business.
Okay, Numbers,
let's see your numbers.
We get the same percentage
from the laundries...
Where do you think you're goin'?
Come on, Tracy. Take me with ya.
Get back in there and brush your teeth.
Go on. And wish me luck tonight.
I'll see you later.
Move in, and take your positions.
Sooner or later you're gonna be mine.
Sooner or later you're gonna be fine.
Baby, it's time that you face it
I always get my man.
I have to hand it to you, Big Boy,
you got the best broads in town!
Top drawer!
...you're gonna decide.
Sooner or later there's nowhere to hide.
- Come in, Tracy.
- This is Tracy, Sam.
We made it.
...why waste it in chatter?
Careful, Tracy.
The waiters carry guns.
Baby, you're mine on a platter
I always get...
All right, Tracy. You all set?
Okay, boys. Let's go.
All right! I got it under control.
Relax! Please! Everybody?
It's okay. Please! Please. Okay!
No, no! I got it under control!
Everybody! No! Everything's under...
Just sit down, everything...
Relax. It's easy.
Get this thing taken care of.
It's okay. No, everything's all right.
Okay, Bill, that side of the room.
Frank, cover the bar.
Hello, Big Boy. The gang's all here.
- What is it, a class reunion?
- This is a private party, mister.
- Invitation only.
- Here's my invitation.
Search warrant.
And no one I've kissed, babe.
Ever fights me again.
- No gambling, no nothing, Tracy.
- What?
You mean,
you thought we had gambling?
I wouldn't be caught dead
in a place that permitted gambling!
I'll be back, Big Boy.
Listen, tell me when you're coming.
I'll have a big party waitin' for ya.
- Let's go, boys.
- Right, Tracy.
Then, baby, amen.
I thought you was gonna
take care of Tracy.
- He didn't look around. Did you notice?
- Yeah.
I don't get it.
He's just trying
to louse up the party.
- How'd it go?
- Clockwork.
Let's hope Big Boy thinks I'm too stupid
to look under the top of a table.
Pat, I am gonna get him.
It's just a question of when.
Sooner or later you're gonna be fine.
Baby, it's time that you faced it
I always get my man.
Get over to 132 Broad Street.
132 Broad Street.
- Okay, 132 Broad Street.
- Right, Bug.
The challenge delights me.
The more you resist, babe.
The more it excites me.
Dick Tracy has struck tonight,
and he has struck hard,
right at the heart
of the gang lord's empire.
No one I've kissed, babe
ever fights me again
lf you're on my list.
It's just a question of when.
When I get a yen.
Then, baby, Amen
I'm counting to ten
I'm gonna love you
like nothing you've known
and you all alone.
Sooner is better than later
But lover
I'll hover
I'll plan.
This time I'm not only getting
I'm holding.
My.
Man
Tracy, Tracy, Tracy, Tracy!
Everywhere I turn,
it's Tracy, Tracy, Tracy!
It's like he's reading my mind.
Texie Garcia,
Ribs Mocca, Johnny Ramm
and now DeSanto. I don't get it.
How could he catch them so fast?
I don't understand.
He knows what we're doing,
before we do it.
You said you had a way
of taking care of Tracy,
"Leave it to me," you said.
Well, let me tell you somethin'.
I'm taking this bum out of the headlines.
I'm rubbin' him out!
You kill Tracy, they point
the finger at me. This bum...
We're being bugged.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Hey, Mike, what'd you put in
this chili, melted rubber?
Sometimes I wonder why I slave over
a hot stove for you, Tracy.
Okay, Freddy. Get down
to the Southside Warehouse.
Big payoff!
Tracy, I'm leaving.
I used to be afraid that maybe you'd
never take some time and settle down,
and now I know it.
I knew you'd never
want a desk job, Tracy.
Calling Dick Tracy. Calling Dick Tracy.
Do you read me, Tracy?
You got Big Boy on the run now,
and that's good.
Calling Dick Tracy.
Tracy, good luck.
Come in, Tracy. This is Bug Bailey.
Do you read me?
What is it, Bug?
There's something going on
at the Southside Warehouse.
- It sounds big, really big.
- Go on.
Tracy, come in.
Go on.
Tracy, are you there?
Better get over there, Tracy.
I'm on my way.
I'll be back, Tess.
Reload.
All right! All right, that's enough!
I want them dead! Both of them.
I want this no-face dead
and I want Tracy dead.
What's the matter?
You bums forgot how to kill people?
Doesn't your work mean
anything to you anymore?
Have you no sense
of pride in what you do?
No sense of duty? No sense of destiny?
I'm lookin' for generals!
What do I got? Foot soldiers!
I want Dick Tracy dead!
Don't get me wrong, Tracy.
If you say there was a man with no face,
I'll bet the mortgage there was.
- But who's he working for?
- Yeah, who's he workin' for?
I don't know, boys,
but I didn't dream him up.
Would you get my suit cleaned?
We need a witness who'll testify.
- A man with no face?
- A man with no face.
What can you lose, Big Boy?
What can you lose?
I don't know, Big Boy. It seems they
want to get rid of Tracy as much as you.
It'll only cost you 10%.
What can you lose?
Okay, piano player.
You got a deal.
Mike, give the Kid a donut.
- Hi, Tracy.
- Which one?
- Where's Tess?
- Out of town.
She asked me and the boys
to take care of the Kid
till they take him to the orphanage.
- There's no jelly in that donut.
- Tess went out of town, huh?
Sorry, Tracy, I thought you knew.
Want me to take the Kid
back to the precinct?
- No, Chief. Thanks a lot for fillin' in.
- Okay. Good night.
Good night.
Tracy. Want a donut?
Yeah, thanks.
Mike, let me have a coffee, will ya?
- Coffee.
- One for me, too.
What can you lose?
Maybe it shows.
She's had clues.
Which she chose to ignore.
Maybe, though, she knows.
And just wants to go on as before.
As a friend, nothing more.
So she closes the door.
Well, if she does.
Those are the dues.
- Once the words are spoken.
- Something may be broken.
- Still you love her.
- What can you lose?
But what ifshe goes?
At least now you have part of her.
- What if she had to choose?
Leave it alone.
Hold it all in.
- Better a bone.
- Don't even begin.
- With so much to win.
- There's too much.
- To lose.
Cheer up, Tracy. I'm the one in danger.
I shouldn't be talking to a cop.
- You know what I want.
- I want to hear you say it.
I don't want you to be hurt.
Don't tell me what you don't want.
Tell me what you do want.
You want me.
Don't you?
You're right, I do want you. In court,
- where you can tell the truth.
- You're lying.
You want me the same way
that I want you.
You want me to take a risk?
I want you to take a risk.
I told you I'd protect you if you testify.
- Protect me?
- It's my job.
I don't know about yourjob.
I only know what I feel.
If you can't tell me how you feel,
Tracy, then I can't trust you.
Wait a minute.
What do you want me to admit?
That I think about you? Okay, I admit it.
- Testify.
- You want my testimony?
Tell me you want me. If you do that,
I'll do anything you say.
How bad do you want Big Boy?
It's up to you.
Tell me you want me.
Tell me you want it all, but tell me now.
If I say that, I'm gonna hurt
somebody I don't wanna hurt.
You trust her.
I love her.
He could be
President of the United States,
and he'd call it a desk job.
Dick Tracy's awfully tough on himself.
He's torn, Tess.
He's torn between love and duty.
If you get too close to a man like that,
you probably won't be
treated much better
than he treats himself.
It takes a lot of understanding
to love a man like that.
What did you say, Mother?
I said, it takes a lot of understanding
to love a man like that.
He'll never take a desk job.
Yeah?
Sit down, will ya?
Sam, Mrs. Trueheart said
Tess left there a long time ago.
Has somebody checked out
Route 3 for accidents?
Right, Tracy.
We gotta talk about
this orphanage business.
- What?
- Tracy, did you get the sketch?
Yes, I got the sketch.
I got both sketches.
They're both the same sketch.
Forget the sketch!
Check Route 3 for accidents!
- We're working on it, Tracy.
- Don't work on it, do it!
- Right.
I hope she comes back to him.
I've never seen him like this.
The Welfare Office called again.
I'm not supposed to keep you
out of the orphanage.
Yes, and then send
a letter to District Attorney Fletcher.
- Can you do it?
- Ah.
I can do anyone's handwriting.
All right. Tracy's handwriting, write this,
"District Attorney Fletcher,
I have evidence that will destroy you.
"Bring $10,000 to room 429,
Midway Hotel."
Bring $10,000
to room 429, Midway Hotel.
If you want to stay alive,
you'll do what Big Boy says.
That's not it! That's not it! Does
Paddy O'Brien know she's missing?
- Yeah. That's not him?
- Was he the one?
That's not it! That's not it! What's that?
- It's for you.
- Open it.
Pat, what about that guy
from up north?
You hear anything about him?
What's his name? Louie?
- Yeah, Louie the Louse.
- Yeah, where is he?
- He's in the pen, I think.
- I can't do it, Kid. It's the law.
- Six months.
- Flowers.
This is cold!
Hey, who's on the coffee
out there, Rip Van Winkle?
- You can't get a decent cup...
- I don't know why it'd be cold.
Tess wants to talk. Watch the Kid, boys.
Sure thing, Tracy.
Tracy, you got lilies.
Want me to put them in water?
Tracy? Tracy?
I'm here to pick up a child, case 38196.
I don't want to wait.
I want the child now.
You're from the orphanage,
ma'am?
Last night we had a date
We stayed out late
I bought round after round.
Just for you
I played the fool.
Yes, I was quite the clown
Tess, where are you?
Words were spoken
Hearts were broken.
But now I hope you see
lt was the whiskey talkin'
Not me.
I had myself a little splash...
Tess?
Tess! Tess.
Relax, Tracy.
Just smell the flowers, and go to sleep.
It won't kill you. It won't even hurt you.
But your big career is over.
Hey!
Close the darn door.
Tracy, you're late. Wait a minute.
Who are you?
Mayor Tracy,
Senator Tracy, Governor Tracy.
High political offices
are being coupled with Tracy's name.
- Now?
- Now.
"You can't blackmail me, Dick Tracy.
"Nobody does that to me!
Nobody blackmails me!
"You put that gun away!
"Who do you think you're dealing with?
If I go to jail, you go to jail!
"I don't have to pay you!
I don't have to give you a dime!
"I don't have to give
you a nickel, Dick Tracy!
"You're nothin' but a punk,
Tracy, that's all you are!"
Police? Better send someone over
here right away. The Midway Hotel.
"Put it away! Put the gun away, Tracy!"
Out.
Go around back!
Yes, there's bad news tonight.
It's worse than bad. It's heartbreaking.
Dick Tracy is in disgrace tonight.
Charges of blackmail and murder
fill the hushed air.
And in the void, once more, is heard
the rattle of chips, as the wheel spins...
This is beautiful.
I want to hang this on my wall.
I've gotta hand it to ya, 88!
Your people did it!
They got Tracy out of the way.
Keep him out of the way.
Boys, we're back in business!
Maybe I'll run for mayor myself.
Yesterday it seemed
the world was about to end.
Didn't it?
Looked as though
we wouldn't last out the year.
Yesterday disaster
waited around the bend.
Well, my friend.
Spring is here.
Back in business and ain't it grand?
Let the good times roll.
Yesterday things were out of hand.
Now they're under control.
Bye-bye, blues
So long, adversity.
Happiness, hello.
Hello, hello.
Keep the status quo.
Permanently so.
Back again like a boomerang.
Same old stand
Same old gang.
Back in business with a bang.
Let the good times roll.
Back in business.
And ain't it grand?
Let the good times roll.
Back to normal
Back to usual.
Let the fun resume.
No more doom and gloom.
No more bust, just boom.
Back in business and overnight.
In demand
Well, all right.
Business is just dynamite.
Let the good times roll
Tracy didn't do it, Chief.
I know he didn't do it.
You did the right thing to call me, Kid.
Tracy's in real bad shape about Tess.
She's still missing,
and we haven't a clue.
It looks like a kidnapping,
but nobody's asked for ransom.
Tracy's the only one
who can find her.
- Judge said no bail.
- He didn't do it, Chief.
He didn't do it.
Why would somebody kidnap Tess
and not even ask for a ransom?
If I could just get back on that street...
I'll leave the two of you alone
for a minute. It'll be anytime now.
The state police will be coming
to transfer you
to the county jail in a little while.
How's the food?
Good.
How's the food at the orphanage?
It's good.
- It'll be anytime now.
- All right, Chief.
What a New Year's Eve, huh?
I got my permanent certificate.
But... I thought you had to pick a name.
I did.
If it's all right with you?
It's all right with me.
It is.
Tess, I hope
you like being alone with me.
Happy new year.
- Here, let me get that.
- Okay. It's okay.
Sorry, Tracy.
- Happy new year, Tracy.
- What are you two doing here?
It's a long trip to county jail.
I'd say it would take at least eight hours
to get there.
All right, boys, call headquarters.
Get them to send a car
to 38th and Central,
and tell them there's something
I want them to bring.
Hello, Mumbles! Who set me up? Huh?
Talk! Talk, you cockroach! Talk!
Huh? Huh?
Okay, Pat.
Care for some water, Mumbles? Huh?
This is Brandon speaking.
Who's calling?
Do you want to put Big Boy in jail?
- Yes?
- He's kidnapped Tess Trueheart.
- Go to 38th and Grand.
- Now wait a minute.
- Who is this? Hello? Hello?
- Wait for a call.
38th and Grand. That's the Club Ritz.
- Joe! Get my car.
- Yes, sir?
- Keep an eye on the Kid till I get back.
- Right, Chief.
You don't want to tell me
who set me up, huh?
You want Big Boy to hear that?
Ah.
What do you think, Mumbles?
Big Boy did it. Big Boy did it.
Okay, Sam. Let's take this
and play it for Big Boy.
Wait. Wait.
88 Keys, the piano man, set you up.
Big Boy paid him
to get you out of the way.
Why would somebody kidnap
Tess and not even ask for a ransom?
So what do we do? Grab 88 Keys,
or go straight for Big Boy?
Yeah, Tracy, what do we do? Grab
88 Keys, or go straight for Big Boy?
Is the enemy of my enemy my friend,
- or the enemy of my friend my enemy?
- What?
- Or the enemy of my enemy my enemy?
- What did he say?
The enemy of my enemy is my enemy.
He said the enemy
of his enemy is his enemy.
Oh.
Caprice speaking. Who is this?
How long since you took
a look in your attic, Big Boy?
Who is this?
Better take a look around upstairs.
Something's fishy.
Okay, Sam, you take the front.
We're going to the roof.
Tracy, why are we going to the roof?
I don't know. It seems like
a good place to hide.
Can you get through to Chief Brandon?
Big Boy. I think you ought
to come with me, quick.
Tracy, why we going to the roof?
This is Chief Brandon.
Jumpin' Jimminy, Tracy. That's Tess!
- Break that lock.
- Okay, Tracy, okay. Let me just...
- What's she doing here?
- It won't budge, Tracy.
- What is this?
- It's Tracy's dame!
What is she doing here?
How'd she get in here?
Tracy!
Untie her! Come on!
We gotta get outta here!
Untie her! Let's go! Get her outta here!
- Don't shoot.
- A frame!
It's a frame-up!
Somebody tried to make it
look like we kidnapped her!
It's a federal offense!
Come on! Come on!
I'm okay, Tracy!
That's kidnapping, Big Boy!
It's a federal offense!
Things are not always what they seem.
You're gonna pay for this!
- Easy!
- Anybody shoots, I shoot you,
sweet pea! Come on!
Tracy, what's goin' on?
Did you hurt yourself?
Gotta figure a way out of here, Pat.
Tracy, are you okay?
Got my diamonds.
Got my yacht.
Got a guy I adore
I'm so happy with what I got.
I want more.
There's no way out
of this place.
You can't find a trapdoor or a panel
that moves or something?
I'm looking, Pat.
The ceiling must be 20 feet high.
Mathematician.
All I know is addition.
What are you doing down there?
Tracy, what are you doing down there?
Boss! Why are we surrounded by cops?
- Cops?
- A billion of them!
This is it! Burn the records!
Lock all the doors. This is your fault.
They're forcing me to use you
as a hostage. Break out the guns!
Jeez, boss. Tracy's girl?
Someone set us up. They're gonna
get us on a kidnapping rap.
All of us! We've gotta get out of here.
- Get out of my...
- Get out of my way!
I like Tracy. I had a meeting
with him once. Did he tell you?
Let me tell you. I may just put
a bullet through your head!
Let's go!
What do you weigh, Pat?
I don't know. About 195, 196.
Somethin' like that.
- How much?
- 210.
L find counting a bore.
Keep the number mounting
Your accountant does the counting.
More! More!
The only way to get into this joint,
Chief, is to bust our way in.
- Jump.
- What?
- Jump?
- Keep your mouth shut, woman!
- You don't say nothin' to nobody.
You may think they got us surrounded,
but I'm getting out of this.
Watch it! Move it, woman!
Now, however, I own the view.
Come on. Just jump.
Come out with your
hands over your head.
Them coppers are never gonna take me
alive. We're making a break for it.
Come out with your hands over
your heads. This is it.
The jig is up!
One is fun, why not two?
And if you like two
might as well have four.
And if you like four why not a few.
Why not a slew more?
Come on! Let's go! In the
car, in the car! Now, listen, you guys!
When I hit my horn,
that's the signal to go.
Okay, Big Boy!
Let's give it to them, boys!
You gotta tell them everything.
They crave leadership.
- You're under arrest. If you...
- Chief.
- Look at him. What's he doin' up there?
- Tracy!
If you've got a little, why not a lot?
Add a bit and it'll get to be an oodle.
Everyjot and tittle adds to the pot.
Soon you've got the kit
as well as the caboodle.
More!
He does have Tess,
but he won't bring her out of there.
- We gotta go in.
- Go in?
Give me that tommy gun, Sam.
Okay, hit your horn.
You bring your men...
...for something less.
Something's better than nothing, yes!
This may get messy. You make a wrong
move inside here, I blow your head off!
Big Boy!
Come on! Yeah!
You know, sometimes I wonder
why I try to improve things.
Nobody seems to care.
Pain can be valuable, Miss Trueheart.
We learn from pain.
We learn... Don't make me push you!
This is awkward. This is so awkward.
Here.
Let's go, men. Big Boy's inside.
He's got Tess with him.
I knew he wouldn't
have the guts to come out.
Right, Tracy.
They say I kidnapped you.
I didn't kidnap you.
But I'm kidnapping you now.
- Does life imitate art?
- Mr. Caprice!
So many questions, so few answers.
What a way to usher in the new year.
He took her through there,
the wine room.
Tracy.
You don't trust me.
Tracy?
Good luck.
Thanks.
It was very stupid of you to have
been lured into this scheme.
- Oh!
- A big mistake.
Get them up, Keys.
It's not so much that I have to hurt
someone, it's just don't make me do it!
Ya louse!
Believe me, this is not
the way I wanted it to be.
There it is! The city!
They'll never find me.
Can you hear its beat?
The rhythm. Happy new year, city!
Jump! We can make it!
No, no, don't jump! We can't make it.
You'll pay for this.
You're gonna pay for this.
Don't move!
Not if you want to stay alive.
A woman! A woman! A woman!
I've been humiliated by a woman.
The way I see it,
and Plato agrees with me,
is that there is what is,
and then there is
what we would like it to be.
Well, that's not important.
What's important is the future,
is planning ahead.
"A man without a plan is not a man."
Nietzsche.
Wait a minute.
Wait. I'm having a thought.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
I'm gonna have a thought. It's coming.
It's gone.
Let's rise above the tide.
Take that journey,
that journey into that faraway land,
a land that just waits.
It waits by the track,
where the train of destiny must run,
run into the future
breaking the shackles of the past.
Forget the past. Forget the...
Our limitations are our shackles.
Put them behind you forever.
Put them behind you forever, Tess.
Can't you see I love you?
Wait! What's that?
Hands up, copper! We gotta talk.
I did not kidnap this woman.
Drop that gun!
Or my next bullet's got her name on it!
Don't do it, Dick!
Good. Good, Tracy.
What's that?
Tracy!
Tracy? Tracy?
Where are ya? Where'd ya go?
What, are you playin' hide-and-seek?
You're hidin' from me?
That's not fair. No way to be, Dick.
Come out, Tracy.
These gears are turnin'.
You want this dumb dame's head
to be smashed like a walnut?
Tracy, I did not kidnap this girl.
Somebody's trying to frame me!
Where are you? Come on. Just let me
see ya. I just wanna see your face.
I just wanna talk some sense. I wanna...
I just wanna take your head,
and I wanna crack it like an egg!
No, no! I didn't mean that!
No, Tracy, listen to me.
Tracy, you hear that?
What's happening to that can
is gonna be happening
to her head in a few seconds.
There's not going to be anymore
beautiful hair to fondle, huh?
No ears to nuzzle.
You're gonna have
chopped sweetheart, Tracy.
See those gears?
Those gears are like a clock.
Every notch, tick tock.
Tracy!
Drop it, Big Boy.
Get your hands up, Tracy.
Don't move, either one of you.
I outsmarted you, Big Boy.
I knew you'd panic.
I brought you down with kidnapping,
the only crime you didn't commit.
Whoever you are,
I know we can make a deal.
A deal?
I'm making my deal with Tracy.
Tracy, with Big Boy out of the way,
we can own this town.
Pick up that pipe and kill him.
Pick it up!
Pick up that pipe.
Tracy, no!
Drop that gun!
I'll do it, Kid!
Don't move your head, Tess. I got it.
It's okay. Don't turn your head.
Hey, Tracy, look.
Is he still alive?
Will you look at that?
Tess, call an ambulance.
I'll call, Tess. I'll go get it.
You were right, Tracy.
I couldn't pull the trigger.
It was a good plan, Breathless.
You almost pulled it off.
- The city would have been yours.
- Yeah.
You were my only mistake.
Tell me the truth.
Could it ever have
happened between us?
That's how we got him to confess
that Breathless killed Fletcher.
- He was her piano player.
- Not bad.
Right. Mmm-hmm.
You know, you're probably much
too smart to need this,
but I think I'm gonna
give it to you anyway.
Gee!
Tracy! This...
Thank you. Wow!
Tastes different, Mike.
What did you do? Wash the bowl?
Don't listen to him, Mike. It's just grand.
Except for the guy she goes
out with, this lady's got real taste.
- Tess.
- What?
- I've been thinking.
- What about?
Well, you living alone, and...
I like living alone.
Uh-huh.
We have that in common, I guess.
Well, don't we?
Well, I just think
when two people have
so much in common,
they ought to do something about it.
Would...
Uh-oh.
Shut up, Kid.
And...
Don't...
Yes?
Don't you think we'd
be happier if we just...
What?
What do you think?
Dick Tracy, are you asking me to...
Calling Dick Tracy.
Pat Patton to Dick Tracy.
Robbery in progress, Tracy.
Metropolitan Bank.
Hot diggity dog!
Come on! Let's go!
Come on, Tracy! Let's go! Come on!
Come on, Tracy!
Well, what are you waitin' for?
A nice, safe desk?
Tess,
you're one in a million.
This is amazing, Tracy!
What are you waitin' for?
Come on. Let's go!
Come on. Metropolitan Bank.
Come on. Step on it!
You know somethin', Tracy?
I kinda like that dame.
Once upon a time
I had plenty of nothin'
Which was fine with me.
Because I had rhythm, music, love.
The sun, the stars
and the moon above.
Had the clear blue sky
and the deep blue sea.
That was when the best things
in life were free.
Then time went by
and now I get plenty of plenty.
Which is fine with me.
'Cause I still got love
I still got rhythm.
But look at what
I got to go with 'em.
"Who could ask for anything more?"
I hear you query.
Who could ask for anything more?
Well, let me tell you.
Dearie.
Got my diamonds.
Got my yacht.
Got a guy I adore
I'm so happy with what I got
I want more.
Count your blessings.
One, two, three
I just hate keeping score.
Any number is fine with me.
As long as it's more.
As long as it's more!
I'm no mathematician.
All I know is addition
I find counting a bore.
Keep the number mounting
Your accountant does the counting.
More!
L got rhythm.
Music, too.
Just as much as before.
Got my guy and my sky of blue.
Now, however, I own the view.
More is better than nothing, true.
But nothing's better than
more, more, more.
Nothing's better than more.
One is fun, why not two?
And if you like two
might as well have four.
And if you like four why not a few.
Why not a slew more?
If you've got a little, why not a lot?
Add a bit and it'll get to be an oodle.
Everyjot and tittle adds to the pot.
Soon you've got the kit
as well as the caboodle.
More!
Never say when
Never stop at plenty
lf it's gonna rain, let it pour.
Happy with ten
Happier with twenty
lf you like a penny
Wouldn't you like many much more?
Or does that sound too greedy?
That's not greed, no indeedy.
That's just stocking the store.
Gotta fill your cupboard
Remember Mother Hubbard.
More!
Each possession you possess.
Helps your spirits to soar.
That's what's soothing about excess.
Something's better than nothing, yes!
But nothing's better than
more, more, more.
Except all, all, all.
Except once you have it all.
Have it all.
You may find all else above.
Else above.
That though things.
Are bliss.
There's one thing you miss.
And.
That's.
More!
More! More! More! More!
More! More! More!