Oh, my God!
Frank, thank God! I'm dead.
I'm dead.
Frank, I'm sorry. I got lost.
This town is so confusing.
It's Connecticut,
Vermon, Massachusetts
Man, What a day.
My wife had to work early.
So I took my kid to his new
school, we wont stop crying.
He said he wants to
move back to Chicago.
- It broke my heart, Frank.
- Any more excuses?
No.
Good. When you work with
me, you be punctual.
- You got it?
- I'm sorry Frank. It won't happen again.
- Frank, how are you doing?
- It's good to see you again.
Hi, Marty. Sorry we're late.
Al, could go downstairs and
help out Jimmy and Raul.
Yeah, sure. Appreciate it.
This is his.
- You don't trust me?
- I live in a crappy neighbourhood.
- You got that funny money?
- Yeah. Right here.
It looks good. Looks real good.
- Now we're in business.
- Excellent.
There's just one problem.
Know this guy Al. ...
He keeps asking all these
questions about my counterfeiter.
- Really?
- Yeah he asked me too many question
Now, my instinct usually tells me
when something's wrong.
And there's something wrong here.
So I had him followed.
He's a fucking Secret
Service agent, Frank.
What do you think I
ought to do, Frank?
Make sure the body doesn't
wash up on shore.
I want you to pop him for me, okay?
- I think maybe you're with him.
- Look, you came to me, remember?
- So pop him. Show me I'm an asshole.
- I'm just a businessman.
So pop him...
...and let's do some business.
Yes, Frank, that's what I'm looking for.
Come on, let's go
get an omelette.
You like omelette Frank?
I know a good place
Let me get my pistol.
My gun?
You're under arrest.
You're under arrest, too.
Secret Service.
You knew the gun
was empty, right?
You knew from the weight of the gun
that the chamber was empty, am I right?
Well there could have
been one bullet there.
Oh my god.
Hey, Frank.
Frank, do you think we can go
someplace and talk about this?
You killed guys before, Frank?
Does it get to you?
It gets to you.
I don't think I cut out for
this undercover stuff.
Man, I was so scared.
You know I joined
the Secret Service because. . .
...I've always wanted
to protect people.
The idea of throwing
yourself in front of a gun?
Hoping like hell that
the bullet hit you
instead of the guy you're protecting?
You find that appealing?
I don't know. Maybe I'm....
- Maybe I'm just wrong for the job.
- You're a good man, Al.
You'll make a good agent.
How do you know? This the longest
conversation we ever had
I know things about people.
Come on, let's go get
something to eat.
Nah. I want to got home,
hug my wife and kid
You know when I got into
town, a lot of guys
warned me you were
a pain in the ass.
And they were right
- I'lI see you in the office.
- Oh damn! The office.
Monroe wants us to
check out some wacko
I'lI take care of it.
I'lI go with you.
No. You go home, hug
your wife and kid.
I am not a nosy lady. I don't snoop,
but the smoke alarm was going off.
I get scared.
I got more scared when
I see what is there inside.
The smoke was from crumbs
in the oven he left on.
Thirty-one years
Iim in this country.
I love the United States.
I go to White House.
Only United States can just anybody go
to the house of the President to visit.
So when I see this,
these killing things.. .
... I called the police. They said,
they called the Secret Service.
But two days you don't come.
Well the President gets
1,400 threats a year ma'am.
We've got to check them all.
You say his name's McCauley?
Joseph McCrawley, from
Colorado, Denver.
I still remember it like yesterday.
I cried and cried.
- Joseph McCrawley, Denver. Right?
- That's right
Died over 30 years ago, age 11 .
Your guy must've got himself
a duplicate birth certificate. . .
...then used it to get a driver's licence.
- Thanks, Jack.
- See you.
Federal Agents. Open up!
Oh, my God! That's you.
- Yeah?
- Frank Horrigan?
- The Secret Service agent?
- Yeah. What did I win?
- My God, it's really you?
- Who the hell is this?
- That was you in my apartment last night.
- McCrawley?
- Why not call me Booth?
- Why not Oswald?
- Booth had flair and panache.
He leap to the stage
after he shot Lincoln.
- Where are you?
- Closer than you'd imagine.
It's very exciting to talk to you.
I feel like I know you.
How's that?
I've read about you and seen photos.
You were JFK's favourite agent.
The best and the brightest
But that was a long time ago.
What kept you in the game all these years?
Why don't we get together and
have a drink, we can talk about that.
I'd love to but I think the less
you know about me, the better.
Why?
Because I'm planning
to kill the President.
Now you shouldn't
go and said that.
It's a federal offence
to threat the President
you could go to jail even
if you don't mean it.
I mean it all.
JFK once said, all someone
needs is willingness
to trade his life for
the President's, right?
- That's right.
- I'm willing.
and going up against you, this raises
the game to a much higher level.
Fate has brought us together, Frank.
- I just can't get over the irony.
- What irony?
You being intimate involvement with
the assassinations of two presidents.
Hang on a second will you.
I've got something on the stove.
He was owning the bulding
for three weeks.
He came and left about
and hour afterward
What's really weird is that
other tenants notice him,
they pass him oin the stairs
but never really saw him.
I mean depending on who you're
talking to, he is between 5'8" and 6'2".
Between 165 and 180 pounds.
- Age?
- Between 28 and 45.
Before an election, panic is what
you've got on a good day. I think...
- They're been waiting for you.
- Hey, Frank.
Sam.
It's been a long time since anyone
seeing you in this part of the building.
Well, I hear the new
director isn't much fun.
I've been the director
for almost two years.
Yeah
Al D'Andrea. Director.
Frank, you know Matt Wilder.
- Yeah. Matt
- Frank
He still owes me $20 from Super
Bowl 21. He always like Denver
This is agent-in-charge,
Bill Watts.
- Bill
- and LilIy Raines.
- Hello
- Lilly
Secretary's getting prettier
and prettier around here
And field agents
get old and older
Lilly's an agent Frank.
I know that, I just wanted to see
if she had a sense of humour.
Have a seat.
Let's talk about this guy.
I guess we're calling
him Booth for now.
Yeah
- Alright. What do you know about him?
- Well, he's dangerous.
- How do you know?
- I know things about people Lily
Might I ask why didn't
you take appropriate
steps to know more
that first night?
- Well we had a busy day Bill
- Too busy to investigate properly?
Your report said, you were
only in the room 10 minutes
I didn't have a warrant.
Given your reputation for
undercover work, I wont take...
What reputation are you
talking about Bill?
Alright, let's get
back on track.
I like to know what
reputation he's referring to?
Let's drop it!
Am I being paranoid,
or is he busting my balIs?
Probably a little of both.
You know Bill, there was a time around here
when I was almost as arrogant as you.
I don't have time for this. I've got
to pull 75 agents out of Miami.
Keep me posted, Sam, will you?
- So what do we do with this guy?
- We keep investigating.
Mean while if you can
have my phone tap
What makes you think
he call again?
- He'll call again. He's got panache.
- Panache?
- Yes, it means flamboyance.
- I know what it means.
- Really? I had to look it up.
- All right, we'll tap your phone.
By the way Frank,
Watts no where near
as arrogant as you were
when you had Kenedy's rear.
Just what reputation was Watts
referring to, Sam?
You know damn well
Is it because I'm considered
a borderline burn-out...
...with questionable social skills?
So what do you want to talk to me
about, besides your reputation?
I want to be assigned
to the President.
- Protection?
- That's right
After all these years?
Frank, Christ, you're a dinosaur.
This guy's gonna make a try
and I got to be there.
Watts will fight me to the nail
Then fight him back. You owe it to me
after 30 years doing you favours.
If you knew how many times
I protected your job.
I've got to come back Sam
Do you really want to stand
post again Frank? At your age?
Yeah, I've got at least
one pair of good
shoes in the back of
the closet somewhere.
All post, from Watts. We're stopping.
Traveller wants to work the ropes.
The French President's going with him.
Get a security man up here.
God damn it! Get back.
- What's going on here?
- Horrigan had a heart attack.
- Hey pal, are you okay?
- Get the hell out of here.
- What's the hell is going on?
- I had a call about a cardiac case.
- Are you all right, Frank?
- I'm on my break here.
I get it, you bastards.
Who's the wise guy?
Okay, everybody, back to work.
All right, who was the joker
who called those guys?
It may not have been a joke.
You were looking a
bit peaked today.
Well if I find it who it is,
I'lI pay him back in spades.
How can you be sure it was a him?
- Hey, you've missed my street, Al.
- Oh Frank, why don't you have a car?
I lived in New York a lot of years.
I like public transportation.
You like buses, that's great Frank,
why make me go out of my way?
I like your company.
- He's a weird-looking guy. Isn't he?
- lf he still looks like that.
PulI up over here. Will you?
The President's political
troubles were hardly
apparent around restaurant road
downtown at noon time today.
The motorcade with the
French President stopped
twice so the man could greet
the enthusiastic crowds.
It remain to be seen whether
the Senate would react as
favourly due to the new trade
agreement of the two leader side.
Mean while the French embassador
will host a formal dinner
at the embassy to resuficate
for the President function.
and the Presidential political
advisors are said to be very pleased...
...with the French willing
to make a point in thanking
the President so publicity
in an election year.
It's a weird sub-culture, Al.
I like you to send some field
agents to check this things
Ask about some wackos.
Yeah. Sure first thing in the morning.
I'll check them Frank.
I'll talk to Jack about it.
Hang on, I've got
the other line.
- Yeah?
- Frank.
- Booth? How are you doing?
- I'm fine, thanks.
Hang on a second let me
get rid of the other call
You got it?
We got it, Frank, keep him on
the line while we get the ANI.
- Yeah?
- Trying to trace me Frank?
Why didn't I think of that?
You did or you're not an
adversary I hoped for
Speaking of which how are you?
I was worried about you today.
Why?
In the motorcade, I thought
you were going to pass out.
You should get in shape
for that kind of duty.
- Yeah, maybe you're right.
- By the way, I'm watching your movie.
- Movie?
- November '63. Kennedy's last days.
The arrival in Texas.
It must have been exciting
for you Fank.
Dallas. That morning at Love Field.
You all look so radiant.
JFK, Jackie and you.
You look so young and able, Frank.
What did happen to you that day?
Only one agent reacted to the gun fire
and you were closer to Kennedy than he was.
You must have looked
up at that window,
the Texas book depository
but you didn't react.
Later at night when the demons come...
...do you see the rifle
coming out of that window,
or did you see Kennedy's
head being blown apart?
If you'd reacted to
that first shot,
Could you got there in time
to stop the big bullet?
and If you had, that could've been
your head that being blown apart.
Do you wish you'd succeeded, Frank?
or is life too precious?
What's done is done, Booth.
I have that Esquire article
on the tenth anniversary. . .
...about you and the other
agents over there that day.
So sad how your wife left you
and took your little daughter.
and you were so forthright
about your drinking problem.
And the fact that you weren't
easy to live with.
I was so moved by your honesty.
The worId can be a cruel place
to an honest man. Frank
What about you, Booth?
What's your story?
It's an epic saga.
I'll talk to you again soon.
It's nice to have a friend.
- Did you get him?
- We got him.
He could have a device
manipulates the ANI
and fake the caller ID make he seem
like he's calling from another number
This device, where
would he get it?
He could build one if he has
knowledgable in digital circuitory
But you can't you
trace the call?
We could run a comparity check.
If he was online with digital switches.
You mean, you can
trace the call?
Not if he's on an old
twisted para-analog line, no.
Damn it, Jack will you
give me a straight answer,
or I'm going to have my partner
to shoot off his foot.
Okay. If he calls again,
you keep him on the line.
We'll see what we can do.
Right Tony?
I suggested that the police
don't go knocking down any more doors.
I have that Esquire magazine
article on the 10th anniversary
about you and the other agents
that were there that day.
So sad how your wife left you
and took your little daughter.
and you were so forthright
about your drinking problem.
the fact that you weren't
easy to live with.
I was so moved by your honesty.
I'm intrigue but why
play it for me?
We like you to consider canceling the
President's dinner tomorrow night.
The state dinner, at
the French Embassy?
You have any idea how
long it took to line
up this trip for this
cIose to the election?
This guy manipulated the phone system.
If he has knowledge of explosives,
there could be a problem.
If you guys do your job and
there wont be any problems.
It's not that hard to smuggle
weapons inside an embassy.
You think the French want
to knock off the President?
Are you nuts? They love him.
Why is it every chief of staff--
You have no reason to believe
that this guy is anymore
dangerous than thousand of other
people who makes idle treat.
But you want me to order
the itinerary of the world
most powerful man and risk
offending 40 million Frenchman?
Now isn't possible
that this guy's push the
buttons in you and that make
you overreacting just a little.
I'm trying to protect
your boss damn it.
Well so am l.
We're trailing 12
points in the polls,
if he's doesn't get out there
he's out of the job in six weeks.
- He's got to be seen.
- Even if it kills him?
Next order of business?
How could being down 12 points down
look like good news?
The President was even worse off
weeks ago.
He's aids now to keep up with
the voters as much they can,
especially in the Midwest and then the all
important swing from California.
Ladies and gentleman, The President
and First Lady of the United States.
and His Excellency, the
President of France and his wife.
Agent Raines, you do
look devastating tonight.
- Thank you.
- Good enough to eat, I might add...
...if you'll pardon the expression.
You know everytime I try
to be sympathise with you,
you say something
really annoys me.
Why sympathise?
The tape of that phone call.
When he mentioned your wife.
- Ex-wife.
- At any rate, I'm sorry.
It strange that
the only sympathy
I get nowaday is a would-be assassin
or a woman I attend to annoy.
- Would you care to dance?
- Perhaps some other time.
I get off in a couple of hours.
What are you looking at?
I was just wondering where
do you hide your firearm?
Don't tell me, let me guess.
We're on our final approach to L.A.
the temperature is above 76 degrees.
It's a beautiful day out there.
Thanks for flying with us and we're
looking foward to see you again.
I like to deposit this
in the new account.
Okay and I'll need to see
your appropriate resolutions
"Microspan Corporation."
What kind of business are you in?
- Software.
- Up in San Jose?
Yes
I'm based there,
but I'm opening an office here in L.A.
- I like San Jose. Are you from there?
- No
Where are you from?
- Minneapolis.
- You're kidding! So am l.
Well, it's a small world.
I hated the winters.
Nine months of the year
winter I stayed indoors
in pig out
I moved here and lost 30 pounds so far.
What high school did you go to?
New Brighton High School.
- There isn't any New Brighton High School.
- There was when I was there.
Well, maybe I'm just confused.
It happens a lot.
What was the name of that high school
one on third just across from--
I'm sorry but I'm very late for
a meeting, will this take long?
Not at all, just another minute.
Thank you.
- You have a very pleasant way about you.
- Thank you, Mr. Carney.
Agent Raines, how would you like
to give a colleague a ride home?
- Why do you keep flirting with me?
- Am I flirting with you?
You know I can't possibly go
anywhere so why keep doing it.
Maybe because I know I can't
possibly go anywhere.
Come on, give me a lift and
I'll go buy you an ice cream.
No further obligations.
Oh, boy.
I never worked with a female agent before.
How many are there?
About 125.
- Pure window dressing.
- Excuse me?
Window dressing.
125 out of a little over 2,000.
They have you all around
so that the President
can looks good to his
feminist voters.
Do you make an effort to be
obnoxious or is it a gift?
It's a gift.
Let's face it, half the thing
we do are window dressing.
Take that along side running
with the limousine.
It'd take an anti-tank missile
to put a dent in that damn thing.
There we are out for show,
trying to make the President
look more presidential.
If I'm here for the feminist vote,
what demographics do you represent?
Let's see.
White, piano-playing,
heterosexuals over the age of 50.
There ain't a lot of us,
but we do have a powerful lobby.
Well time flies when
you're being annoyed.
Where are you going?
- I have a date.
- With whom?
That's none of your business.
- You want a ride?
- I don't think so.
I like it here this time of day.
I think I'll hang out.
Okay, well thanks for the ice cream.
- See you.
- You're welcome.
If she looks back,
that means she's interested.
Come on now, give me a lttle
look a little glance back.
Give me a smug look
and be on your way.
Well, Abe... . Damn, I wish
I could've been there for you pal
Hi, baby, how are you doing?
Yes, I missed you too.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to startle you.
- Mr Carney?
I got your address
from the phone book.
- But I'm not listed.
- Well, It best I better come clean.
I followed you. I'm sorry,
I'm not very good at this.
I'm new in town. I was wondering
if you'd care to join me for dinner tonight.
That's sweet, but.. . .
and I also wanted to apologise
for lying to you this afternoon,
we both know that I'm
not from Minneapolis.
I shouldn't ask so many questions.
Did you mention our conversation
to anyone at the bank this afternoon?
- No!
- May I?
Rory, settle down!
- Pam, what's going on? Oh, hi.
- This is my roommate.
- Sally, this is Mr. Carney.
- Jim. Call me Jim. Happy to meet you.
Nice to meet you
I was just on my way out.
I'm sorry, but I can't
let you ladies leave.
What?
You shouldn't have been
from Minneapolis.
Look Mr Carney I don't know
what you want, but. . . .
- Hi, this is Sally
and this is Pam.
Ethier we're out having
fun or we asleep.
- Leave your name and number.
- And we'll call you back. Bye.
Frank, I hope you don't mind
me calling you at the office.
I was in the neighbourhood
- No, why don't you drop by?
- I'd love to Frank.
Let me take some time to welcome
those who are joining us late.
I'd love to drop by. I like to.
We've got so much in common.
We do? Like what?
We're both willing to trade
our lives for the President's.
We're both honest
and capable and we
were both betrayed by
people we trusted.
- I wasn't betrayed, Booth.
- Sure you were, Frank.
The Warren Commission report,
they call your procedure
as seriously deficient.
They criticised you
and the other agents
who're out drinking
late the night before.
As if Kennedy would be
alive today if you'd
been in bed by 10 p.m
it's ludachrist
Maybe they were right.
No, as the matter of fact,
they weren't right.
You wanted to stationed agents
on his bumpers and sideboard .
He refused.
and do you know why
I think he refused?
I think he refused because
he had a death wish.
He talked all the time
about being assassinated.
His favourite poem was
"l Have a Rendezvous with Death"...
...which is not a good poem, Frank.
I think he wanted to die.
And I think he didn't care that
his death would ruin your life.
I think he was a selfish bastard
But what do you think, Frank?
Frank?
What about you, Booth?
Who betrayed you?
I don't think he's
scrambling it.
Some of the same people,
but I'm going to get even.
I'll have my day in the sun.
The question is, will you have yours?
I think you're in
for a lot more pain.
How much of this shit
do I have to listen to?
Jesus
He's right across the street.
LaFayette Park. Keep him on.
Booth!
Did you see somebody over there?
I told you to get in shape, Frank.
Is this your current address?
And you didn't see anybody suspicious
hanging around that phone booth?
That's him! Al, that's him!
Secret Service! I'm impounding
this car. He put his hand on here.
- We got fingerprints.
- Are you all right, Frank?
Hey Tony, have a look at this.
- The print from Secret Service?
- Yeah, it's something strange here.
Shit! This is C-12.
We can't tell them.
Horrigan, I'm afraid
we've drawn a blank.
You're sure?
We ran that print against
everything we got
So what do we do now?
Well I'm meeting with the
President in the morning.
You keep investigating.
What should I do?
You're an adult human being aren't you?
Think of something.
You know, you're a real pain in the ass
when things don't go your way Frank.
Well your friends warned
you about that.
The President hit the
campaign trail today, he
left form Andrew Air
Force Base on world tour
that will take him the 12
states over the next 6-days.
With just over a month to
go before the election,
The President is trailing his
apponent by 10 points.
To close that gap, he'll concentrate
his campaign effort in the Midwest,
where he's sagging in the polls.
The campaign will wind up in
Chicago with a big rally.
The President's campaign staff
is hopeful by that time...
Reservations. May I help you?
Yes I'm calling to find
out when you have
a flight on Tuesday from
Washington to L.A.?
Alright
and if possible I'd like
an open-ended ticket
because I may have to make some
stops in the mid-west on my return.
Okay checking
To command post, C-5 agent, we'll
off-load the choppers first.
Who's our route agent?
C-5 agent, check.
That'll be Jacqueline King.
Denver Command post, Watts,
we have arrival at 13:15.
King C-5 agent, where will
we keeping the cars secured?
Denver PD has a
defense area for us.
Security room, Watts, we're ten
minutes out. Situation report..
Here in Denver we gather today
in the shadow of giants.
Brave pioneers who
overcame counterfying
obstacles to carve a new
nation from the wilderness
Today we are asked
to match our vision to their vision.
And to pass that legacy on.
- ls sector three secure?
- Sector three is secure.
The President campaigning
today today in Denver.
Mean while here in Washington..
We are living in a time
of global economic transition.
We need compassion and vision
to create a future...
...of peace and progress
for each and everyone...
That was The President
stumbling in Nebraska today,
he's due to arrive here in L.A.
later in the month.
to compete in the California's
crucial 54 electoral votes.
Hi, Sandy Riggs calling
for James Carney.
James, if you're serious
about trying to
catch a rally while you're in
the Midwest, you'd best call me.
The President's schedule change hour by hour.
and an answer to
your other question,
just send a cheque to
the party headquarters.
Thanks again.
I'm looking foward to meeting you.
Ladies and gentlemen
of Holly, Michigan. . .
...the President of the United States.
We've gone a long way toward achieving
that goal but there's a lot left to do....
Watts, Flynn we've got some
trouble on track up ahead.
You better notify the White House staff.
Milwaukee will be easy tomorrow.
We only got one side later.
May I have your
attention please,
Flight 318 to Milwaukee is
now boarding at Gate 21 .
Please have your
boarding passes ready.
All passangers should proceed
to the boarding area now.
Checking.
Hey, pal, found any bombs today?
- Hello Agent Raines.
- Agent Horrigan
How the First Lady,
she ask about me?
Have you gotten
to know them yet?
I normally preferred not to
know the people I'm protecting.
Oh yeah? Why is that?
Well you never know, you might decide
they're not worth taking a bullet for.
Here comes my replacement.
Care to join me in the bar?
We can't drink on the road.
Of course not. But they
have a hell of a piano player.
I've played for presidents
and I've with presidents.
Nixon and I once did
a decent duet of "Moonglow."
I heard he didn't like you.
That's not true.
We got on all right.
It was his Chief of Staff, now
that was another matter
We were once rally up to a bar,
he ordered me to get rid of
some anti-war protesters.
and I said I couldn't do that.
I said that Freedom of
speech, that kind of stuff
He said, look when I'm talking to you,
I am the President.
I said, The President?
You Iook like a sack of shit
in a cheap suit to me, sir!
Well I like the "sir"
.It was a classy touch.
I thought so.
So Hoorigan how come you never wear
shades when you're standing post?
I like the wackos
to see the whites of my eyes.
A good glare can be just as effective as a gun.
Know what I mean?
Oh yeah
You know what I mean?
Oh you got me.
You'd better stick to the shades,
sweetheart.
Agent Raines what are you afraid of?
I'm afraid of making a big mistake.
Good night.
Good, we've got some updates
on Milwaukee.
Thanks.
- Don't answer it.
- No. Oh, shit.
- Raines.
- Watts
Okay, I'Il be right down.
Well Traveller's losing ground in
Georgia so Milwaukee's out tomorrow.
And they're staging a rally
somewhere outside Atlanta.
Damn!
What am I doing?
Oh, Lilly... .
Damn I've got to put all that shit
back on, god damn it!
You don't know how glad I am to see you all
out here in the rain with me today.
You know I've been going around saying,
"Don't just vote for me, join me."
And today you certainly have.
You know, we may get a tad damp today.
But guess who's gonna be all wet
on Election Day?
How about the watch list?
I got twenty-three crazies
under surveillance
and Chicago intelligence
handling that morgue
The hospital?
Saint Ann an extra units of
Traveller's blood type are on hand.
Accessible to the
alternate route as well.
ETA Chicago 10 minutes
- Under the weather?
- Sick as a dog, Lilly.
What's this? "Psychological
Profile of John Booth."
- So did you make a mistake?
- What?
You said in the bar you were afraid
of making a big mistake.
Well I mean this job, let's be realistic.
It's not like we work in a bank.
So you had an affair with an
agent that it came out deadly?
He wasn't an agent.
But he left you because you
wouldn't quit your job?
You were broken-hearted
I left him Frank because
I wouldn't quit my job for him.
and I did brake my heart.
You vowed never again to let a man
come between you and your career.
Except now you're in love with me and
it scares you a little, doesn't it?
- Blow your nose. Here.
- Sorry.
What would happen
if I gave up my job for you?
Why would you do that?
Well maybe I vowed to
never again let my
career come between
me and a woman.
Frank.. . .
- Hey, be careful, will you?
- Yeah?
This whole event's been advertised
in advance. Just be alert.
Watts, this is Horrigan,
it's a zoo here.
It's not very secure, we gotta
take Traveller underground.
All post, Watts. We are using the
alternate arrival site. Underground.
Horrigan to Watts, I think
Booth may be here.
I thought you couldn't
identify him.
I can't. Just call it a hunch.
We all do respect to your psychic abilities
but we sticking to the game plan.
All posts take your positions.
- You've got a fever, Frank.
- You stay alert in there, will you?
One quality above all
marks this President.
and It has earned him
the affection of every
working man and woman
of this country.
and that quality is courage.
The question is, will we stand
by the man who has stood by us?
- Post check, stage right?
- Stage right, all clear.
- Stage left?
- Stage left, clear.
- Stage centre?
- Stage centre, clear.
The President of the United States
and the First Lady!
- Gun!
- Get down!
Security room, follow up,
what the hell's going on in there?
All clear.
False alarm.
Traveller's secure.
All post resume positions.
- Are you hurt, Mr. President?
- I'm Okay. I'm all right.
Everything's all right, folks.
Everything's going to be just fine.
We had a little
false alarm there.
That was exciting, wasn't it?
Take your seat, please.
Security room, Raines.
It was just a balloon popping.
All clear.
Traveller wants to continue.
Do you have any idea how many
votes you cost us last night?
The President came off  looking
like a coward on national television.
I thought he came off all right.
You were the one who came off
looking like a damn coward.
- Is this just a joke to you?
- No, you're a joke to me Harry.
You have no idea what
we do around here
That's enough Horrigan!
You call me Harry one more time.
You'll be busting
counterfeiters in Alaska!
You keep him away from The President,
away from the White House
and you sure as hell
keep him away from me!
The man's a disgrace
to the sacred..
You can't talk to The White
House Chief of Staff like that.
I don't work for him.
No. You work for me. At least
you did. You're off my detail.
My Super Bowl debt. ln case
I don't see you after this trip.
You know, Frank.. .
...if you just acknowledge that
it was an unfortunate situation--
I'm not going to apologise
for doing my job.
I'm not saying you should.
- But the President was humiliated.
- He's alive didn't he?
Well yeah we here to safe
guard his dignity as well
I'm not paid for that.
What about the time when Kennedy's
girlfriend caught in the
white house and you
said she was with you.
Don't you go believe every
rumors someone tells you
Frank Wilder told
me the whole story.
About how you were suspended
for a month without pay
I say that was safe
guarding his dignity.
- That was different. He was different.
- Maybe you were different.
I was different.
The whole damn country was different.
Everything would be different
right now too if I'd
been half as paranoid
as I am today. Fuck
Frank.. . .
Why not just retire, Frank? Live off
your pension. What's the point?
Somebody else asked me that
not long ago.
You don't spend any money on anything,
except on jazz records.
I want to stay
on the Booth case, Sam.
All right, but as for
protective detail--
I understand.
That thing in Chicago... .
I've never been on the wrong side
of a judgement call like that.
You had the flu for Christ sake!
That's been known can
impair your judgement.
Face it, Frank.
You're too old for this shit.
Hello.
What happened
in the Windy City, Frank?
Booth?
- Did the balloon get you a little panicky?
- You were there.
Yes, yes.
Watching The President, I
couldn't help wondering
why you'd risk your life
to save a man like that.
You have such a strange job. I can't
decide if it's heroic or absurd.
Now, why would a man
like you risk want
to risk his life to
kill a man like that?
Don't you have a psychological
profile on me yet?.
I don't put a lot
of stock in them
Nor do I . A man's actions don't equal
the sum of his psychological parts.
- It doesn't work that way.
- Just how does it work?
It doesn't work, Frank.
God doesn't punish the wicked
and reward the righteous.
Everyone dies.
Some die because they deserve to.
Others die simpley because
they come from Minneapolis.
lt's random and meaningless.
If none of this means anything then
why kill the President?
To punctuate the dreariness.
It's sounds to me like you
need to get yourself laid Booth.
You're the same as me Frank.
Name one thing in your
life that has any meaning.
- I play the piano.
- That's not enough.
How do you know? Do you play?
I've seen you in your bar alone.
There's no cause worth fighting for Frank.
All we have is the game.
- I'm on offence and you're on defence.
- When do we start playing the game?
The clock's ticking, Frank.
Take care.
Wait. Wait, Booth.
Frank, he scrambled it again.
I missed him.
Fuck!
Fucker.
Jesus, Frank.
I've been calling for hours.
I thought something happened to you.
You okay?
No I'm not Okay, I'm sick, I'm tired
and I'm armed, too. So be careful.
You're also maybe a genius.
Not to be recognised
in this lifetime.
Tell me, you listen to
the tapes, the call?
Yeah Frank, remember you said--?
Call the field office in Minneapolis.
See what you can find
about accidental deaths.
Frank!
Will you listen to me, please?
Spit it out, god damn it!
You said to have field agents
checking the model builders right?
There is a professor at
The Art Center College
of Design in Pasadena
California Frank.
I think we've got something.
Like I told your collegue,
I met him at a design conference
in New Orleans about a year ago.
We ordered a few rounds of
drinks at the hotel bar.
He seemed like a
nice enough guy.
But when talked in term of politics
he took on a real nasty edge.
He said he felt betrayed
by the government,
that he wanted to exact
some measure of revenge.
I mean the way he said it
scared the shit out of me.
So I Okay said, Nice talking to you.
And I got the hell out of there.
But for the life of me
I cannot remember his name.
But I'm pretty sure
he said he was from Phoenix.
You know who you guys
ought to talk to,
a guy in Phoenix named
Walter Wickland.
He know everybody down there
Why don't you book us
on a first flight to Phoenix.
Hey how about we get a police artist
together with the professor here
Have a composite
sketch faxed to us.
You figured that one
out by yourself, Al?
- Kiss my ass, will you, Frank.
- I told you you'd make a good agent.
Well it doesn't look much like him,
but it's got to be Mitch, Mitch Leary.
- I haven't seen him in over a year.
- What do you know about the guy?
You see this wheelchair?
Mitch bought it for me.
It cost over $1 ,000.
- You see this?
- Take it easy now.
This is in case he ever comes back.
He accused me of ripping
off one of his model design.
He said my penalty for
disloyalty was death.
If you put him away,
I'll sleep better.
Have you had any idea
where can we find him?
Yeah I think I might've got
his address somewhere.
Don't move.
Drop it!
- Let him go, Horrigan.
- I got him.
It's okay. We're on the same team. Okay?
- Hands, motherfucker!
- I'm getting my identification, okay?
- Give it to me.
- David Coppinger. ClA.
- And who's this asshole?
- He's with me.
- Goddamn it!
- Who're you here for, Leary or me?
Mr. Leary used to be
one of our operatives.
Did you know he's threatened
to kill the President.
We didn't think he was serious
until you turn up that finger print
- But you knew. You and the FBI.
- I understand your frustration.
You understand my frustration?
You pompous son of a bitch!
What the fuck did Leary
do for you anyway?
Run coke ? Sell arms to Iran?
It's a C-12 matter,
so this is off the record.
If asked, I'm going to deny it.
Leary's what we nowadays
call a wet boy.
What's a wet boy, Frank?
Leary's an assassin.
In Leary case, that's a bit too gently.
He's more like a predator.
- Was that you shooting?
- Yes.
- What the hell kind of gun is that?
- Something I made.
You made it?
That beats paying for it.
- Can I see it?
- Yeah.
- It's light. What's it made of?
- It's composite. Like plastic.
Pretty neat! You mind if
I give her a little dance?
- Not at all.
- Go for it.
That is great! That is really great!
You won't be interested
in sell it, do you?
No, I need it.
- For what?
- To assassinate the President.
- Why would you want to do that for?
- Why did you kill that bird, asshole?
Mike Leary was one of our
most effective contractors,
but times changed.
Cutbacks had to be made.
Leary didn't take it too well,
couldn't adjust to civilian life
We've not been able to
locate him for sometime now.
Maybe you folks and
FBI had more luck.
If we can work together
if that a possiblity
Wouldn't that be refreshing?
We have his fingerprints and
we have numerous photograph.
What makes you think he
look loke any of these.
These things got to be
at least 15 years old.
Man in his line stay
out of the camera eye.
They're worthless, he'll
be in disguise, anyway.
I think we need photo
alterations, Sam.
Gentleman, what I'm about to
show you is highly classified.
This is a former colleague
of Leary's. A close friend.
He went by Leary's
home in Phoenix try
pursuade him to accept
counselling and retrainning
This is how Leary
treats his friends.
We need every possible variable.
Facial hair, skin colorization,
glasses, weight changes.
and keep in mind
he's 15 years older now.
As good as they are, they aren't
much good. The eyes are dead.
You can always tell a man
by his eyes.
Look tomorrow morning
I'd like you to--
I'm resigning tomorrow Frank
What?
What for, just because you
were scared down in Phoenix?
Hell I was scared too.
You did your job
I have nightmares Frank about that
boat with the bag over my head.
I can't breathe.
Phoenix just clinched it.
The service has
counsellors for this
I've been to counsellors Frank
Look I need you Al.
We can get this guy.
I can't do it!
Stop this cockamamie shit. Will you?
Come on, pal, I need you.
Please.
Okay, Frank.
Cockamamie. That's a word
your generation hasn't embraced yet.
Maybe you ought to use
it once in a while
just kinda keep
it alive you know
- Cockamamie!
- Yeah.
Oh, God!
Well, it made you
laugh for Christ sake
You kill me, Frank.
Hello.
Hello, Frank.
Let me take a second to give a hearty
welcome to all of you joinning
our program in progress
I know who you are, Leary.
I'm glad Frank. Friends should be able
to call each other by name.
- We're not friends.
- Sure, we are.
I've seen what you do to friends.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You slit your friend's throat.
- You talked to Coppinger, Frank?
- Yeah that's right.
Did you de-louse?
The man's a professional liar.
I saw the photos.
No, you saw what
he wanted you to see Frank.
I saw a picture of your friend
lying on the floor with his throat cut.
What you didn't see Frank, what
you couldn't possibly know is
that they sent my best friend...my
comrade in arms to my home to kill me
- Your voice is shaking.
I never lied to you,
Frank and I never will
Why is it everyone who ever knew you
said that you're a sick son-of-bitch.
- Your colleagues. Your wife.
- What does your wife say about you Frank?
We're not talking about me.
Frank, you of all people,
I want you to understand.
Because we both used to think that
this country was a very special place.
You don't know what I--
But you know about me,
do you have any idea what I've
done for God and country?
Some pretty fucking horrible things!
I don't even remember who I was
before they sunk their claws into me.
They made you into
a real monster.
That's right.
And now they want to destroy me because
we can't have monsters roaming the
quiet country side now can we.
What do you see when you're in
the dark and the demons come?
I see you, Frank.
I see you standing over
the grave of another
dead President.
That's not gonna happen.
I'm on to you
Fuck you, Frank.
I'm willing to trade
my life for his.
I am smart and I am willing,
that's all it takes.
That President is coming home
from California in a fucking box.
- Where in California?
- The address?
Come on Frank.
I'll keep you in the game,
but I'm not gonna
throw it for you.
- I want you to give yourself up.
- Sorry to live a long and fruitful life?
Well we can work something out
Frank, don't fucking lying to me.
I have a rendezvous with death.
So does the President.
And so do you Frank,
if you get too close to me.
You have a rendezvous
with my ass, motherfucker!
Frank, do you know how
easily I could kill you, Frank?
You know how many times
I've watched you go in and
out of that apartment
You are alive because
I have allowed you to live.
so you show me some god damn respect!
St. Francis Hotel,
Florida Avenue on North-east.
Frank.
Take my hand, Frank.
Take it. If you don't, you'll die.
Take it.
You're gonna shoot me Frank
after I saved your life?
Shit.
The only way to save the President
is to shoot me.
Are you willing to do that
to trade your life for his...
...or is life too precious?
Leary, don't fucking move!
Frank, I got him!
Al?
There's nothing here.
Frank, you've got a phone call.
Yeah?
Frank, you looked so sad on the bus.
I'm sorry, it was self-defence.
Tell me about Skellum.
You're barking up the wrong tree
Frank, Skellum is worthless.
Are you gonna meet him in L.A.?
It's late in the game and
you're way behind Frank.
I'm way ahead. Look Leary I know what you
look like. I've seen your eyes.
My eyes might look
different next time.
Not what's behind them wont
You better pray I don't
find you, you prick
Pray? Don't you want
to kill me, Frank?
That's right.
The irony's so thick here so
thich you could choak on it
There is no fucking irony Mitch!
Think Frank, the same government
that trained me to kilI,
trained you to protect.
and  now you want to kill me.
Up on that roof I protected you.
They'll write books about us.
- I'm tired of your bullshit!, Mitch
- Don't be a poor sport.
You could have taken me out, but
you chose to save your ass,
don't cry about it now. Okay?
You know, It does make
me wonder about Dallas though.
Did you really do all you could,
or did you make a choice there too?
Do you really have the guts
to take a bullet Frank?
I'll be thinking about that
when I'm pissing on your grave.
There's no one named Skellum
in all of Los Angeles?
I ran 5 different counties
- What about Louisiana?
- Hang on.
Frank, no Skellums. Sorry.
Oh shit! Damn it!
The election's in three weeks and you're
asking me to commit political suicide.
I'm asking you to stay
out of California.
If this guy's so smart,
he's not gonna tell you where
he'll going to make an attempt.
I don't think he'd lie to me.
Ain't that sweet, you've become
that close, have you?
Look people, California is the key
to the whole damn race.
We narrow the gap to 5 points.
We can't let up now.
We have to change our procedure.
Move around in unmarked cars
Frisk people within 50 yards.
Frisk people going in
at $10,000 dinners?
You're overreacting
again Horrigan.
If I don't overreact then
The President's dead.
Why is he even here?
I told you to keep him away from me
Frank's heading
this investigation.
Then let him investigate,
as long as he doesn't within
sight of The President.
If you'lI excuse me, I'm in the
middle of a campaign here.
- Frank. Hi.
- Hi.
Up late?
We'll advance to L.A.
It's will be a lot of work.
- What's up?
- I've got a request.
I'd like you to talk to Watts.
Get me on your advance team.
- He thinks you'll overreact.
- What do you think?
I think maybe you're too
close to all this Frank.
That's why I've got
to be there Lily.
I can spot him.
I can anticipate him.
You really think he'll
be in California?
Why would he tip
you off like that?
He wants to keep the game close.
He'll be there
This has nothing to do with
you and me. Strictly professional.
But that son of a bitch
killed my partner. My friend.
I know. I'm sorry.
You're looking at a living legend Lily
The only active agent
who ever lost a President.
Please.
Mr. Horrigan, welcome to Los Angeles.
Can the President
close the remaining
distance in the little
time he has left?
He has in California they say,
The President will appear
for a rally at the Bonaventure
Hotel in Los Angelos.
Field office, the advance team
is at the Bonaventure, stick with them
- Any problems?
- No.
Security room, TST, We've swept the
western end of the motorcade route.
Manholes are secured.
Mailboxes removed.
Abandoned vehicles towed,
bridges checks out.
We're moving to Sector 3
We'll need sharpshooters
on both those towers there.
We need sharpshooters
to cover those restricted areas.
Other polls today had the President
three points behind and still gaining.
But here in the nation capital,
he'll have to close that
margin in California.
Welcome to Los Angeles
International Airport.
Raines this is Horrigan,
double-checking those exits?
Yes, Frank this is the
third time now.
Watch list Paul Reubiac yellow,
section five.
Secret Service.
- Robert Stermer.
- He's a bellboy. He's been cleared.
- Robert, have a nice day.
- No questions.
Come on, pack it up. Let's go.
Come on. Pack it up and move
Mr. Carney, all set.
Finally we meet!
You are James Carney?
You must be Sandy Riggs.
I was starting to wonder
if you really existed,
maybe you're an angle send
down to help the party.
I'm very much human.
Well good then let's
have a drink,
you know they got the bar on top of
this place, it's beautiful what a view
When does the President arrive?
Tomorrow evening just in time
for dinner, which remind me,
Here's an invitation.
Don't lose it, will you James.
The Secret Service have been
driving me bunkers over this thing
I've got a you great seat,
just a stone throw across
from the President himself
So tell me James what is Microspan
Corporation all about?
I just came to meet the
President Mr Riggs
I wouldn't presume of
bore you with business.
I don't blame you. One thing I
don't understand is high-tech.
I can't wait to introduce you.
Look at this beautiful view.
Yes, very pretty.
Give me the list of dinner guests.
and who this fat cat organiser?
Sanford Riggs, The Chairman of
California Victory Fund.
Call LAPD and make sure
they have no uniforms missing.
It's been taken care of.
and call the hospital see if
they lay down supply of B+
Your average American businessman
who looks at product marketing...
He sees the length
and width of it.
The Japanese see the depth,
the long term effect
We look at the next
fiscal quater.
The Japanese look at
quarter of the century.
Try to get our people
understand that.
Mr. Riggs, can I talk
to you for a moment?
Excume me fellas
- Who's that?
- Secret Service agent.
Do you know everyone who's
attending this dinner personally?
I sure do.
How about these pictures here,
any of them look familiar
Look I went through this with
another agent yesterday.
I'll cooperate, but this is
bordering on harassment.
I'm a harassing kind of guy.
No, no, no, no.
I'll be right back, Mr. Carney.
Bill he did what anyone of us would.
- He beat up a bellboy on television.
- No I was there
I'd say he was a little overwrought.
Well we're all a little overwrought knowing
Leary's out there someplace.
- You don't think he's a liability?
- No I don't think he's a liability.
Well, you're in the minority.
I want him gone before Traveller's arrival.
Send him on to San Diego
first thing in the morning.
By whose order, Harry Sargent?
Traveller.
Do you want to tell him or should l?
Miss Raines, somebody's
approaching Traveller's suite.
-Hi.
What are you doing
up here Frank?
I was just seeing
anything more I can do.
You know, between LAPD,
the FBI and the rest of us...
...there are 229 people
protecting Traveller tomorrow.
A lot of guns.
If Leary gets off a shot, You and I
could be killed in the crossfire.
Frank.
- Bill Watts just called.
- Heard about the bellman?
So did Traveller.
They want you to go to San Diego
and assist in the advance tomorrow.
Just like that.
Frank, it's not just you against Leary.
Have some faith in the rest of us.
You know something?
For years I've been listening
to all these idiots on bars...
...with all their pet theories on Dallas.
It was the Cubans, or the CIA.
The white supremacists, or the mob.
Whether it was one weapon
or whether it was five.
None of that meant too much to me.
But Leary....
He questioned whether I had the guts
to take that fatal bullet.
God, that was a beautiful day.
The sun was out.
It had been raining all morning.
The first shot
sounded like a firecracker.
I looked over and I saw him.
I could tell he was hit.
I don't know why I didn't react.
I should've reacted.
I should've been running flat out.
I just couldn't believe it.
If only I'd reacted,
I could've taken that shot.
It would've been alright with me.
- What's the number in San Diego office?
- 619 ukulele.
Ukulele?
That's how I remember it you
know, 7 numbers 7 letters.
You just push U-K-E-L-E-L-E, easy
What a minute, isn't
Ukulele spelled U-K-U?
I don't know.
But the phone number is U-K-E-L-E-L-E.
U-K-E-L. Wait a second.
Jesus.
We have an arrival. Chopper standing
by to take Travell's to site one.
- Southwest Savings, may I help you?
- Southwest?
- Yes. May I help you? Hello?
- What's your address?
Taxi!
Raines to Lobby agent, post check.
Post 3?
Roger, in place.
- Post 6?
- Roger in place.
- Post 12?
- Roger, in place.
Wait right here.
I'm sorry there's no
Mitchel Leary or Joseph
McCrawley in our accounts.
Try to imagine him in disguise.
A hat, wigs, mustache, that sort of thing.
I haven't seen him but I've only
been here a couple of weeks
Who was in charge of new
accounts before you?
- Pam Magnus.
- Where can I find her?
She's dead. She was murdered.
Lily, she was murdered and
she was from Minneapolis
They won't cancel.
You know what Sargent said.
At least make the arrival underground.
Don't give Leary a target
They want a big show.
They said unless we have
proof that leary's here
The proof may just have
been a dead president?
I'm pulling up all the accounts
open by Pam the last 6 months.
The problem is we don't log it
by the date they're entered.
It's going to take time to compile
Fax me the list as soon as
you get them. Will you please
All agents in position.
- Please step back sir.
- Would you please empty your pockets.
Thank you.
You're from Texas though, right?
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the United States.
I'm sorry?
Frank! What're you doing here? Watts
is gonna shit if he sees you!
Have you got a fax for me?
Yeah, just now, what is it?
What's this about?
What the hell is going on, Frank?
James Carney.
Carney, Mr. James.
- Jesus.
- Frank!
- What the hell is he doing here?
- I don't know.
- Who the hell gave you permission--
- He's here. His name is Jim Carney.
- I want the damn seating chart.
- Give him the chart.
Gun!
Stop! Put the gun down!
Get down!
Don't shoot!
Get him in the car!
Raines to shooter. Hold your fire!
Get out of his way!
He's got a hostage!
Raines to shooters.
If you have a shot, take it.
Nice view.
- What's the plan, captain?
- It's your man up there. You tell me.
All post hold radio traffic,
get me sharpshooters on the
north and west towers.
Take the subject out.
You had the guts.
You took the bullet.
- I broke my damn ribs.
- Sorry, I wasn't aiming at you.
Where the hell are the shooters?
West tower in place. No lights.
No light in sight, shit! No shot
from the north. We can't see inside
Wearing a bullet-proof vest Frank?
That's a bit of a cheat don't you think?
- Otherwise, you played a good game.
- It's no game, Leary.
I was doing my job.
What going to do now?
Do you believe
in the nobility of suicide?
No.
But if you want to blow your head off,
go ahead, be my guest.
Nicely put Frank,
except you see.
I don't want to leave this
miserable world alone.
- West tower, do you have a shot?
- Negative, too dark. Target unclear.
It's better to die with a
friend don't you think Frank?
Friend? You're a damn killer!
You sick bastard!
Don't talk to me like that,
I saved your life. You owe me.
- I don't owe you shit.
- I was always honest and fair with you.
- Go ahead and shoot.
- It's Frank. Quiet!
- Come on damn it.
- Frank, are you talking to me?
- Well what are you waiting for?
- What am I waiting for?
I'm waiting for you to show me
some god damn gratitude.
Without me, you're just be another
sad-eyed, piano-playing drunk.
I brought you into this game.
I let you keep up with me.
- I made you a god damn hero today.
- You didn't make me anything.
I redeemed your pathetic shitty life.
I just did my job. You're the one
with fucking the pathetic life.
Go ahead and shoot! Damn it!
They can't see inside.
lf they fire you'Il be hit.
- I want you to thank me first, Frank.
- Shut up and shoot.
All right, Frank.
Shooters stand by to fire.
Wait for my command.
- Sleep well, my friend.
- Just one thing, aim high.
- What?
- Aim high!
- Now!
- You bastard!
Take my hand.
If you don't, you'Il die.
You want to save me, Frank?
To be honest and fair with you, no.
But it's my job.
Take it.
- Are you okay?
- Stand back please.
We've been working with Agent
Horrigan for quite some time.
Yes, Frank exemplifies
courage and self-sacrifice. Frank!
I guess I overreacted again, Harry.
Agent Horrigan, why are you
retiring from the Secret Service?
Well because I hate desk work
and I'm too old for running
along side limousine
And thanks to you people
pestering my pictures
up everwhere I'm no good
for undercover work.
- How are you, Frank?
- Sam
Frank, The President sent
his limo for you.
- Well that's the least he could do.
- Good. I love public transportation.
Come on in.
Make yourself at home.
- So, what do you think?
- I like it.
Hello, Frank. By the time
you hear this, it'll be over.
The President is most likely dead
and so am l.
I wonder Frank, did you kill me? Who won
our game? Not going to matters.
For among friends, like you and me,
it's not wether you win or lose
it's how you play the game.
and now the game's done.
It's time to get on with your life.
But I worry that you have
no life to get on with Frank
You're a good man.
and good men, like you and me,
are destined to travel a lonely road.
Goodbye and good luck.
I bet you that brown pigeon down
there flies off before the white one.
How do you know?
I know things about pigeons, Lilly.
Sub synced and edited by: PEEAN91