You've got a client.
I don't want to.
What?
Can't you get someone else?
He wants you.
But this customer is a pig.
He's waiting outside.
What did you do, huh?
What did you do to that customer?
Slavi, he hit me.
Understand.
Let's talk about you
not answering my calls.
Bitch!
Should we give him a card?
Don't be shy... Make the call.
Understand.
Why is that piece of shit
in my parking space?
- Are they upstairs?
- Yes.
Tevi. You collect
from that fuck, Dmitri?
Yes.
He asked for forgiveness.
Forgiveness?
I told him.
What am I, Jesus Christ?
You lost, dedushka?
- How the fuck did he get up here?
- I don't know.
Should I get rid of him?
No.
Can you believe this guy?
You know amerikantsy.
Be ready for business.
Of course, don't worry.
Good.
- Understand?
- It will all be well.
Keep digging-
We've searched the city.
No sign of him.
McCall has disappeared.
Mr. Pushkin has been notified.
You're out of time.
It Will all be Well.
Go fuck yourself.
He's close. Get ready.
Here comes the bus.
The bus is empty.
Kill one.
Kill one of them.
You wanna be first?
Guards, guards!