I start with a question,
as a filmmaker and a storyteller,
how should this story tell itself?
Because there's different strategies
that are available.
And what attracted me
to Stuart Beattie's screenplay
was the notion that it all happens
in a very short time frame,
meaning that it's like the third act
of a traditional drama
and you're making a whole
motion picture about only the third act.
One of the big reasons
I wanted to make the film
was that we're seeing fractions,
or fractals...
We're seeing a fraction
that represents the whole,
and only what you need to know
is what you're seeing.
And it doesn't go backward in time
or give you exposition
about other parts of their lives.
They don't really talk
about themselves that much.
So in the beginning,
I wanted to enter this scene,
or enter these activities,
with kind of a torn edge.
So we just see Vincent in LAX.
We hear a plane land, Vincent's in LAX.
He meets somebody who's foreign
and that's all you need to know
is that he's foreign.
He's got a South London,
working-class accent.
This accidental bumping
into each other, you realise,
if I've done my job correctly,
is not really accidental.
It's premeditated,
and a briefcase has been exchanged,
so that whatever it is
that Vincent's here to do,
you know only the few things
you need to know,
which is that there was
a premeditated plan to it,
it's secretive,
and it involves people
from foreign places.
And then we enter the domain of Max,
but we don't know what it is.
First, there's abstract pieces
of things, and then we realise
those abstract pieces of things
are, in fact, cars
and that the cars are cabs and that
there's drivers waiting to go on a shift.
And what I'm trying to direct
the attention to is that Max
IS very obsessive
about making this environment
of the interior of his cab
clean and perfect
and that he has a picture
that has some significance to him,
'cause he very carefully
mounts it on his visor,
and that he closes out chaos,
makes chaos go away.
This mural that we put outside the cab
comes from Estrada Courts,
which is in East LA,
and there's a spectacular tradition
in Los Angeles of mural painting
that's Hispanic, derives from Mexico.
And this is... It was painted in '74.
The painter's anonymous,
and he never finished it.
The vaquero doesn't have a head,
and for some reason
that I can't put my finger on,
it just really felt like it fit
into the vision of here's Max
launching out of the cab depot
onto the streets of Los Angeles
in late afternoon, on a shift
that probably began about 4:00.
Cab driver described to me as
folks who get in the back seat
are kind of like a radio
with a random wonder bar.
You never know what station
you're gonna land on,
and so you never know
who's gonna wind up in the back seat.
There's a lot of aerial shots
in the picture,
and they're shot with a Wescam
mount, which is amazingly steady.
This is a gas station just off
the Santa Monica Freeway
after the sun has set, and the light
in LA has this amazing red quality,
red-yellow quality to it.
And the mural of the products for sale
in the tienda is taken off
a tienda in East LA.
The fractions of LA
and how diverse LA is,
and diverse not in...
I grew up in Chicago.
Not in a Chicago or East Coast
or New York way,
but diverse in a Pac-Rim, Hispanic,
Los Angeles way
are part of the intent of,
again, the opening of the film,
Max's world,
and the world of Los Angeles.
Now, this guy here, his real name,
the actor's name is Manny Urrego,
and he was a limo driver.
In working out every detail,
the most important details
of Max's life as a cab driver
and the work we did
in preproduction with Jamie,
one of the key things we did
was make complete
Max's business plan
for having a limo company,
and consequently,
Manny provided spreadsheets,
a whole business plan, complete
with depreciation, overhead, salaries.
Annie is played by Jada Pinkett Smith,
who I worked with in Al
When Jada gets in the cab...
This is one of the first sequences
we shot,
and we were using the Sony F900
high-definition video camera.
If we were shooting film,
you wouldn't see any definition
of the images behind them.
And you wouldn't have this feeling
of the low light levels that make me
feel that we're actually in a cab.
The picture was originally written
for New York City.
And my interest in shooting
a motion picture that took place at night
in Los Angeles
in a compressed period of time
predates my getting my hands
on the Collateral script,
which was given to me
by Walter Parkes at DreamWorks.
And it's written by Stuart Beattie.
It's an excellent script,
but it was written about
the Russian Mafia and New York City.
And my interest was immediately
to transpose all of that
into not just LA as a location, but LA
with its unique, diverse population.
And the way it seems to be organized,
where there are almost, like,
sites or domains
that you travel to. The ethnic richness
and the sense of place in LA
is not immediately apparent
off the freeways.
You have to go to it.
And then in putting together the film,
again, as the storyteller,
the first thing I'm looking for is,
who are these people?
Who is Max? Who is Vincent?
Who are these characters?
What's their history?
Where did Vincent come from?
How did Vincent get made into
the Vincent who shows up in LA,
late afternoon
on this one day?
Where did Max come from?
Some of the answers to this
that, as the director,
that I build in building the characters
and in working with the actors
in preproduction
and in forming the character
of Vincent with Tom
and Max with Jamie had to do with
their histories, where they came from.
In fact, the back-story
of Tom and the film
was that in the offshore world
of narco-trafficking cartels,
they have the budgets
to buy the best, and they do.
Particularly since the end
of the Cold War went on,
that labour market has become available.
People who are ex-KGB, ex-Stasi,
as well as Brits and Americans
from special forces, Israelis.
And these cartels also have
the best of computer technicians,
signal-intercept capabilities
to run sophisticated counter-intel,
as well as attorneys
and private investigators to discover
if there's any operations
against them or whether or not
there's a Department of Justice
investigation or a DEA investigation
or any indictments pending
against them in the United States.
And that's exactly what's happened here.
The group that's hired Vincent
has found out
that there are pending indictments
and that an assistant U.S. attorney,
played by Jada, is, in fact, about
to indict, in a grand-jury hearing
that's supposed to begin
tomorrow morning, certain figures.
And they have had
private investigators working,
and they've discovered the identities
of five key witnesses
and have spent the last three
or four months working up
an operation to kill these witnesses.
And tonight's the night.
Max and Annie, who have just met
in this cab, Max doesn't even know
she's a prosecutor yet,
are completely unaware of this.
I wanted to form characters who were
absolute strangers to each other
and constituted opposites to each other
in every conceivable way that I could,
because they're about to be
thrown together into this cab.
One of the big things
that appealed to me about this film
is to tell a story the way
this story tells itself,
which is that since we're only
in these 10 hours,
we're only seeing
a small fraction of a whole life.
And since we're only in the 10 hours,
the challenge is,
"Can I design those fractions
so that they become glimpses,
“ "that you kind of sense the person?"
To do that, one has to invent
the history of Vincent,
the history of Max,
and then choose those details
to put into the 10 hours of tonight.
The way Max dresses or the kind of
self-deceptive attitude he has
when he talks about a limo company.
The film doesn't do
what a life experience of these 10 hours
also would not do,
which is to have exposition
or to travel backwards in time
via flashbacks or any of those
other devices,
but instead just to keep us
immediate into this present,
and yet to have a greater degree
of knowingness about their lives.
Max is averse to impulsive action.
He has planned to perfection
this business plan, in which
he's gonna set up a limo company.
He's been doing it for 12 years.
Now, one of the hardest things
for an actor to play is indecision.
That in-between state means that...
That's exactly what Max is.
He's a man who has big dreams
and has realised none of them.
So for Jamie to play this,
it means that he must generate
the object of Max's desire,
really experience it and feel it,
and then invent what impedes him
from actualising it so that he exists
in that kind of twilight zone
of potential and frustration.
And in this case,
it all becomes personified by Annie,
with whom he has this stunning rapport,
as played out by Jada
and Jamie right here.
But he can't bring himself
to actually ask her out,
and the way Jamie plays it
and the way Jada plays I,
I, for one, feel Jamie melt
when Jada's eyes look up
at the moment that just passed.
There's this kind of instant regret
at his having failed himself.
And as she's leaving,
she realizes she has no way
to ever have contact with this guy again.
She could take cabs in LA
for the next 15 years
and might not run into him.
So she responds to her impulse
and she gives him her card,
and then the contact is made.
Feeling that she's just been
in this cab with this man
who has other plans in life
beyond driving a cab
but just understood her
and was so generous
about giving up something that's his
because he recognised she needed it.
And it's kind of the rapport and intimacy
that can be struck up
only between strangers,
because you believe
there's no consequence,
"cause you're never gonna
see each other again.
So you can be open.
Vincent is somebody who is decisive
and who's embraced force
as a way of controlling
his environment, as a way of...
And I don't think Vincent is
actually actively aware of this,
but as a way of
controlling the environment
so that bad things don't happen to him.
He, consequently, is somebody
who can be improvisational.
He's highly trained, he takes action,
he has opinions.
Max is exactly the opposite.
Vincent chooses public transportation,
and the thought behind that
is the same thought
that's behind Vincent's suit.
It serves two purposes.
One is to be indistinguishable,
to be anonymous,
so that if somebody witnesses Vincent
do an illegal act and are later
questioned by the police
and they're trying to describe him,
it's a guy with grey hair,
kind of average-sized, grey suit,
white shirt, there's nothing there.
So that choice is,
in the first instance,
simply really good tradecraft,
to be inconspicuous by being anonymous.
And that's one of the reasons that
he also picks public transportation.
In his mind,
and according to his plan for tonight,
the cab driver who's driving him around
will not, in fact, know what he's doing
at each of the stops he has to make.
This is an interesting shot.
I'm gonna digress here because, again,
this is something only possible
with high-definition video.
It became a whole strategy
about how to see the world
that Vincent and Max
are gonna traverse this night.
I viewed the first scene between Max
and Vincent in the cab as casting.
Vincent is being
provocative intentionally,
saying things about Los Angeles,
"Nobody knows each other,"
to see what Max's reaction is gonna be.
And if Max was aggressively defensive,
Vincent might just have changed cabs.
And when Tom and I
were working in preproduction,
I thought that it was likely
that Vincent, in fact, had a cab
that took him from the airport,
and he didn't like that cab driver
for whatever reason,
and so he switched out
when he went to reconnoitre
Annie's building,
and that Max is, in fact,
his second cab of the night.
Vincent would've been one of these
guys who would've been recruited
in the private sector.
He probably lives offshore.
He has a domicile that's maybe
in Uttahorn Province in Thailand
or Songkhla in Thailand,
some place where...
A Buddhist country where people
leave everybody else alone a lot.
Max comes from a middle-class family,
Ladera Heights in Los Angeles,
and he has a plan, a business plan
to set up a limo company,
so that driving a cab is only temporary.
It's only a means to an end.
We're about to find out
that temporary's been about 12 years.
The other aspect
about Vincent's appearance is,
again, in building the character
and how to make these two characters
be oppositional,
what Vincent's chosen to wear,
it tells us things.
I believe that audiences
are much brighter
than they are aware of.
There's a lot of information they take in
on a feeling level.
There's a cut to his suit that says
perhaps it was custom-tailored,
but not in Milan or London or New York.
In my mind, it was in Kowloon.
The thing about his hair, the scars
on his hands, scars on his face...
In effect, he's kind of rough trade
in a good suit,
prematurely grey,
kind of a steely aspect to him.
Those are design issues
that are designed to tell us,
tell the audience, tell you things
about who he is on a feeling level,
not on anything
that is didactic or spoken to you.
It was tricky to arrive
to some of these looks
and some of these issues because...
And this was also
the challenge of the film
that made it very exciting for me
to do it and want to do it,
which is that when you compress
the time frame of a narrative,
and it's down to under two hours,
and you're just in one locale
for one night,
it also means there's gonna be one suit
and one wardrobe change,
so everything becomes
inordinately important.
It's kind of like driving a race car,
where a small input in steering
has a very radical effect.
So the slightest change,
because it's cumulative,
becomes a big deal.
Now, this location is an alley off of...
In Pico Union.
That's downtown Los Angeles
in the background.
It's about two miles away.
You couldn't see this, again,
without using digital video.
The building Vincent's walking up in
is at 1839 South Union.
When you're working on a film
during preproduction,
you find yourself moving through
different neighborhoods
as you're looking for your locations,
and you often times get glimpses
into lives and people's residences,
and you see fragments
of working folks and their conditions,
and sometimes these fragments
can speak about
a whole life or a whole existence
that's not really part of the story,
yet it is really part of the environment.
And I find that very powerful,
and sometimes
I'll try to build that
into the environment
as something that maybe
is glimpsed in passing
and maybe something that we don't take in
except on kind of a sensory level.
And so it's a small detail, but the
idea of these two guys in this room,
with a line that they run across the room
where they hang their six
or seven good shirts
that they brought up from Mexico,
that was a particularly unique facet
of something we saw,
and so I reproduced it here.
The local gang,
which is the 18th Street gang,
provided the graffiti
which is on the walls here.
Vincent did not expect Ramone
to fall out the window.
That's an accident.
His first instinct is to look around him
to see if he's picked up
any surveillance.
Has anybody... Are there neighbours
looking out the window?
Has somebody dialled 9117?
Are there police coming in?
And this is ironic here.
And Tom's ironic timing,
I think, is both subtle and masterful.
And in analyzing I, how irony is achieved
is by Tom playing it
as if he's as oblivious
to what's self-evident as Max is.
Max says, "You killed him."
Tom's response is,
"No, I shot him.
The bullets and the fall killed him."
And I'm an admirer of Billy Wilder,
who used irony a lot,
kind of a Berliner wit from Weimar.
And so I spent a lot of time studying
Cary Grant's work in Front Page
in preparation for Vincent's
use of irony, his droll wit
and his facile nihilism.
And so there's a kind of homage
to Billy Wilder
way back in the preparation
I did for these aspects
of Tom's character,
and then Tom just nails it.
Jamie's comedic timing is spectacular
just as it was in the last scene.
He doesn't need any help from anybody.
But I think underlying that is actually
his native talent as an actor.
Jamie trained not as a comedian,
he trained as a musician.
And then when he wasn't getting work
as a musician,
he saw people getting work
doing stand-up comedy,
so he acted like a stand-up comic.
Whatever the origins were,
his timing and gestures
and attitude and hesitation
and stuttering...
Just experiencing it, it's great,
and if you look at it analytically,
it all hits in a certain perfect rhythm.
Here's Mark Ruffalo,
the fine, fine actor, playing Fanning
to a piece of score by Tom Rothrock
called Rollin' Crumblin',
kind of a blues concert thing.
I had Ruffalo spend a lot of time
with a guy named Q,
who's an undercover narc in LA.
And we borrowed liberally
from Q's appearance,
in the way he holsters his gun
and the way he has these little clips
that hold the magazines on his belt,
designed to be...
If you just look at him,
you don't realise he's carrying.
And if you saw Q,
you would never guess
that he was, in fact, a detective
by both his carriage and attitude,
as well as by his appearance.
This apartment is in, really,
the same building,
and the decor in this apartment is,
in fact, what's there in real life.
It was one of those places
where you happen upon it
and it's so evocative of a mood,
of a kind of working-class
Hispanic apartment
in this section of the city.
It's so representative of that, that other
than putting in a big-screen television,
we changed nothing. So the fish tank,
and on the opposite wall
that we're looking at right now,
this backlit, strange
aqua art object of a ship
is also...
Belongs to the guys, two guys,
who actually live here.
What this launches is the sub-story
of a quest by Fanning,
who has very solid procedure,
an unorthodox appearance
belying a very orthodox
and sound procedure.
And it's gonna lead Fanning to be
the only man who's gonna realise that
A, witnesses are being killed
and B, that Vincent is not in fact Max,
but in fact is Vincent.
He'll be the sole person who has
what happened here correctly
as the events of the night unfold.
As the events of the night unfold.
We're now entering a long scene,
and what's interesting to...
What may or may not be interesting
to people who aspire to direct
or want to know
how films are made is that,
for myself, I have to know
exactly what a scene is trying to do,
and I believe that
I should be able to distill that
into one simple set of words,
called "the action."
And in this case, it's, "What is Vincent
doing? What does Vincent want?"
And it usually has to be expressed in
the infinitive, and it is that Vincent...
It is "to manage."
Vincent needs to manage Max.
Now, there's many other layers
and many other things
that are happening here.
Max has just experienced a dead body.
He's never seen
this kind of violence before.
If there was an adrenaline rush
that kept him functioning in the alley,
now that he's driving,
the adrenaline's worn off.
He's on the precipice of falling into
shock or going into a fugue state.
So one of the things he's doing
is throwing out
some really provocative thoughts
that are also part of Vincent's themes,
but nevertheless,
they're being used to provoke Max.
And that's keeping Max sharp.
Vincent's saying that, "What difference
does it make if one fat guy falls?
"There's six billion people on the planet,
Max, what are you worried about?"
He's giving him justifications using
everything from social Darwinism
to the I Ching to advise Max
in a therapeutic way,
how Max ought to think about
the events that have just happened.
And Max is confounded.
By being confounded,
he's also preoccupied.
And, in fact, he is still driving
'cause Vincent, from his point of view,
has a number of jobs to do.
He's got to watch out for...
See if they picked up surveillance.
You'll see him throw looks from
time to time out the side of the car.
Secondly, he's working on his PC,
because he has to go
to target number two.
And number three,
he's got to keep Max functioning.
And what he does next is
put Max into this impossible situation,
that Max has to
talk his way out of a ticket,
or Vincent is gonna Kill
both of these two cops.
Or Vincent is gonna Kill
The officer on the left
is played by Jamie McBride,
who is, in fact, an actual LAPD officer.
He's ex-CRASH unit.
I've used him as an actor before
in Robbery Homicide Division.
And the actor on the right
is an extremely fine actor
named Richard T. Jones
who's a regular on Judging Amy,
which stars Amy Brenneman,
who I worked with in Heat.
But getting back to Jamie McBride,
it's really interesting
for a director to work with people
who have some native ability to act.
The most difficult thing
for them to do, by the way,
is to play a character
that's close to them in life.
It's much more easy,
for example, for Jamie McBride
to be playing a villain
than for him to be playing a cop.
But in working with them,
it would be a mistake for me
to expect them to have
the kind of technique
that comes from years
and years of training.
As a director, I have to find the means,
maybe through subtle suggestion
or whatever,
to help Jamie McBride lose himself
in the moment of what he's doing,
because it will be really good
and spontaneous only the one time.
And what Jamie McBride is doing here
is not playing, he's doing.
And even though it's something
as routine as a traffic stop,
nevertheless, there's a 120-man
film crew all around Jamie McBride,
and for him to be unselfconscious
about that process is the objective.
And to just do what he, in fact,
does at a normal traffic stop.
You can see how good
Richard T. Jones is there.
I've had people ask me if both these
guys were, in fact, real LAPD.
There's a certain fatalistic attitude that
Jamie has as he sits back in the cab,
as if he's just been condemned
to get back behind the wheel
and be in his seat and ride this cab.
This is an alley right off of Wilshire
Boulevard on the edge of Koreatown.
And Max is... A lot of Max's character
is built around this inability to confront
and the evasion and avoidance of
doing what, in fact, he wants to do.
And that's when there's the... We have
the impulses to do things in life.
We want to do things,
we enact them or chart a course
that takes us to
a certain outcome, a certain goal.
And Max has these things, and he has
a lot of latent power as an individual,
but it all exists behind a wall of
repression that he can't break through.
And one of the interesting constructions
of the picture,
viewed as the big picture,
is the collision of these two guys
in this situation
in which, at the end,
Vincent actually becomes an agent
for the liberation, in a way, of Max
and enables Max to manifest
his individuality and, in fact, act.
And reciprocally, Max,
towards the end of the film,
provides us and Vincent
with an illumination into Vincent.
There's a moment in time,
later in the film,
when Max sees beyond
the end of Vincent's gun
and sees Vincent for who Vincent is,
which is damaged goods.
And at that point in the film,
Max's judgment
to Vincent is devastating to Vincent,
and he's truly impacted upon.
The Teflon coating, the impervious Armour
that Vincent,
in this part of the film has, is gone.
And one of the designs
in the evolution of his character,
of Vincent's character,
through the film that I hoped to get
was the glimpse of fractures
in Vincent's Armour,
the realization that
he's not this machine-like presence,
that, in fact, there's something wrong
with Vincent tonight.
And it begins in the scene
that happens later,
with the paroxysm of remorse
that Vincent does after he shoots
somebody named Daniel.
And some other small subtleties
that I designed into our understanding
of Vincent's character,
hoping to try and communicate those
to an audience almost subliminally,
almost things that you sense about him
without even being aware
that you're sensing them.
And that sensing lays a foundation
for actual overt reactions
when Vincent has them
much, much later in the film.
That's all working backwards
from the end about the necessity,
I believe, to know the man,
to have characters
that are three-dimensional,
meaning that he can commit heinous acts
and is responsible for his actions,
and there should be
consequence to those actions.
At the same time,
you glimpse something wounded
behind those actions
and come to whatever conclusion
you would like to come to.
One of those conclusions might be
that, given different circumstances,
Vincent might have been
somebody else in life.
Understanding Vincent
doesn't let him off the hook.
Even having positive emotional feelings
for him
does not let Vincent off the hook
for the judgment
that we render upon his actions,
because I believe that
you're responsible for what you do,
and your intent is something that
we all maybe sympathize with,
but that's got nothing to do
with responsibility for your actions.
But it's dimensional to have
both be there.
That's what makes characters
fascinating to me,
and I wanted to try and fuel that.
So to do that, I built backwards
towards the front of the film
the sense that there's something
going on with Vincent that we...
That he's not just machine-like.
Tom trained for about three months
with live ammunition
under extremely rigorous, safe conditions
on the LA County Sheriff's
combat shooting ranges.
And Tom had not fired live rounds
through a handgun before,
so for him it was a new experience,
and it's a whole different deal
when you're doing it for real
than when you're firing blanks.
And the true lethal potential
of a firearm is...
And your managing of it becomes a
very strong dynamic in a performance,
particularly when your skills...
And Tom is extraordinarily skilled
at everything athletic that he tries.
Particularly when the skills
become so schooled in him
that they become truly second nature.
But the real sign of how
integrated Tom was able to become
with the skills that Vincent,
in fact, would have,
is the expression
that's on Vincent's face
after he shoots these guys
and when he's holstering his gun.
He's not thinking about holstering
the gun. He can do that in his sleep.
And immediately after
he's fired that last round,
his attention gets focused
on Wilshire Boulevard,
down at the end of the alley.
"Is anybody coming at us from there?
Did anybody hear these gunshots?
"What's Max doing?"
He immediately switches over
to the next task,
and that's absolutely perfect craft.
And it's exactly what somebody
who had a lot of trigger time,
who had been in the kinds of conflicts
in various places in the world
that we imagine Vincent had been in,
that's exactly what he'd be doing.
He wouldn't be worrying
about how he holsters his gun.
So that is a beautiful little movement,
and it's a testament
to the commitment of Tom
to the work of
turning himself into Vincent
and having deeper
and deeper understandings,
as well as acquiring
all the physical skills.
There's no cutting in it, and Tom draws
and fires five rounds in 1.4 seconds.
And we did that on the range.
And we did that with dummies
and with plates and stuff
and with live ammunition. And it's hard.
As well as a lot of close-quarter combat,
a lot of hand-to-hand combat,
of a very brutal, short, efficient nature.
Not martial arts.
And all the other tradecraft
that Vincent would have,
a lot of which doesn't even appear
in the text of the film.
But it's a whole package
and it had to do with
reconnoitring each of these people.
But the deeper work that goes into
this kind of thing is, in fact,
how did Vincent become Vincent?
And Tom and I did a lot of work
in trying to understand
where this guy came from.
If he was in a foster home
for part of his time,
if he had an institutionalized childhood,
and he was back in
the public school system at age 11,
that would have been
sometime in the '70s.
He would have been dressed
very awkwardly.
He would've probably been ostracized
"cause he'd have looked odd,
and the kind of brutality of, you know,
preteens and early adolescence.
Probably which... We postulated
an alcoholic, abusive father
who was culturally very progressive.
He was probably part of Ed Sadlowski's
Steelworkers Local in Gary.
He was a Vietnam veteran.
He had friends who were African-American,
the south side of Chicago,
the Checkerboard Lounge
is 30 minutes away on the Calumet Skyway.
So the father,
probably in the '60s and early '70s,
was probably an aficionado of jazz.
There was a great jazz scene
on the south side of Chicago,
Modern Jazz Quartet.
But it's almost as if
the father blamed the son, i.e. Vincent,
for what happened to the mother,
and the father drank
as Gary was being reduced into...
You know, looked like Dresden
at the end of the Second World War.
The father never tutored the boy in jazz,
but the boy extolled the virtue
of knowing about jazz
'cause he heard his father talk about
jazz, not to him, but to other people.
And that's why he knew about jazz.
And that's why he learned about jazz.
His father, Vincent's father,
never tutored Vincent about jazz
because he had rejected
his son and ignored him.
It was something
that got constructed as back-story
in the work I did with Tom
during preproduction
and understanding every aspect
of the character, of who Vincent was,
much more than appears
in the text of the film.
So that the fractions of Vincent-ness
that we have in the text of the film,
within these 10 hours, could
resonate with the totality of a life
the same as they would
with anybody you met, you know.
We all bring our whole history with us
into any moment of the present.
This is my pal, Pete Berg,
who's an extremely talented director,
as well as being a fine actor,
playing Weidner,
who's Fanning's careerist partner
on this crime scene.
Who's Fanning's careerist partner
And we segue to a jazz club.
And this is Barry Shabaka Henley,
who also played Herbert Muhammad in Ali.
Max doesn't like jazz,
and I got the idea
that Max didn't like jazz
because Muhammad Ali doesn't like jazz,
and Muhammad Ali doesn't like blues.
Muhammad Ali only likes soul.
But Vincent knows all about jazz
and has just explained it.
And in a way, that's kind of related.
And that is not a direct metaphor
for what's happening in the film,
but it's very closely associated.
It's almost an analogue, rather than
a metaphor, about improvisation,
about having a theme, having a structure,
but then being able to improvise.
And so Vincent here is starting
to verbalize the themes that are...
He sees into Max, he really reads Max.
That's part of Vincent's job,
that's part of his craft, is to read Max.
So Vincent already knows
all that we know about Max,
which is that Max is not improvisational.
And he also knows that Max
is along on a ride
in which Max has no idea
what's gonna happen to him
10 minutes from now.
So it's really the first articulation
of two of the central themes
each of these guys personify.
They're in opposition to each other.
The music that we just heard
is Spanish Key by Miles Davis.
We cut down the 17-minute length,
which is on Bitches Brew,
to a little over three-and-a-half minutes.
And Shabaka,
playing the character of Daniel,
relates an incident in which Miles Davis
came to South Central
after recording at Columbia
and sat in on a session
in one of the great jazz clubs
that came out of South Central.
This is after the flowering
of West Coast bebop,
which, in part, came out of graduates
of Jefferson High School in Los Angeles.
Dexter Gordon, Lester Young.
Just a whole slew of jazz musicians
came out of it, and then they were
very much part of that scene in the '50s,
along with other West Coast
jazz regulars,
which would have included, say,
Charlie Mingus, Wardell Gray,
Thelonious Monk, Chet Baker, like that.
The anecdote that Daniel's relating
here is an actual event
from Miles Davis' life.
Miles Davis played a guest-starring role
in two episodes I did
on two television series.
He played a character for me
in Miami Vice
and a more profound role
in one episode of Crime Story,
in which we were telling the story
as a two-parter of the Moulin Rouge,
which was an African-American casino
in segregated Las Vegas.
He played in that one as well.
And so I had some contact with him.
The anecdote that's related here
is interesting,
because it talks about
the violent reaction that you will have
if you're somebody whose concentration
is so totally focused.
Daniel talks about Miles' head
IS in a musical head space, you know,
his reaction to being pulled out of it
was fierce.
And that is what you feel
when you are concentrated,
if you're an actor
concentrating on a scene,
while they're resetting lights
and somebody disturbs you.
It's a violence. And it's not personal,
but it comes from high, high order
of focus and concentration,
and the irritation sometimes
almost is in direct proportion
to your ability to focus.
And there's nothing I can imagine
requiring focus more
than doing the art
that Miles Davis did, so...
There's a stillness to the depth
of which Tom is into the moment
in this particular scene right now
that always I admire.
He is so economically,
completely in the moment.
He knows what he's gonna do.
He just has that sideways glance
to see if the waitress,
who he heard leave, has, in fact, left.
And she has.
This is where, I think,
great acting resides.
There's a pure economy of motion.
There's immobility
when there should be immobility.
You don't program this kind of work.
It's there or it's not there.
And there's a paroxysm of regret.
That's the first anomaly to the perfect,
machine-like presentation
we've had from Vincent.
And it's designed to be an anomaly.
It's designed to be a deviation
from the way we have seen him
up to this moment.
And Max can't take it
and wanders off on this broken course
without much navigation.
And the way he walks across the sidewalk,
he heads towards the parking meter,
then to the left.
And Vincent, who has repressed regret
and is right back in business,
back on the case,
reminds Max he's not playing.
Max provokes a theme,
"If you were playing him,
"what would you have done
if he'd gotten the answer right?"
And I wanted that question
to remain unanswered.
I want it posed, but not answered.
So I then interrupt it with
Lenny the dispatcher, who returns.
Now, the voice of Lenny
is the voice of Michael Waxman,
who was my first assistant director.
He's a dear friend, and we've done
many movies together, so...
He just was reading these lines
so that we could shoot them,
'cause Lenny was always to be off camera.
He was always to be off-screen.
So we were gonna find a voice later on.
We tried to cast some other voices,
but we couldn't find a voice
that was as wonderfully kind of annoying
as Michael's voice, in fact, can be.
Now, this is another use
of high-definition video.
I wanted to see the world
that they're moving through,
and this is nothing you would see
in normal motion picture film.
You can see the clouds in the sky
behind Vincent,
and you also are able to see
the colonnade of trees behind Max
disappearing in the distance.
You normally wouldn't be able to see
any of that.
Now, Vincent is about to deliver
a second anomaly.
The first was the regret that he felt.
It became kind of a paroxysm
and then he repressed,
and the second one is gonna be right now.
When he says to Max,
"She carried you in her womb
for nine months,"
as if there's a special consciousness
of the significance of mothers
that Vincent possesses.
This sentiment will continue
in the scene with Ida
and provoke almost a sibling rivalry
for the affections of Ida
between Vincent and Ida's son Max,
which Vincent wins.
We're gonna find out later on
that Vincent never had a mother.
It's an accumulation of small anomalies
to indicate that something
subterranean is going on with Vincent.
That something is fracturing
with this man.
And the coincidence,
which is part of the wonderful structure
of the piece.
Stuart Beattie's narrative construction
is unchanged.
It's as if you take a screenplay
and throw it in an X-ray or an MR,
and you see
the underlying engineering of it.
And that's what's so brilliant
about what Stuart Beattie did.
These two vectors
of Fanning going some place...
We don't know where it is. We're gonna
find out later he's going to the morgue.
So it's as if
the hospital is Martin Luther King,
which would also have the morgue in it.
And Max and Vincent
going to visit Max's mother,
"cause Max does this nightly.
He has a complex relationship
with his mother.
One can almost imagine
that there's three older brothers
whose wives have made them
move out of Los Angeles,
to Houston, some place,
to get away from the mother.
Now, she says to Vincent,
"They're beautiful."
And Vincent's struck by that.
And Jamie's playing in this scene
of betrayal is, I think, profound.
And then Vincent is charmed
and gets seductive.
But the hurt in Jamie's eyes,
I just thought he just did
a wonderful job right here.
And then the picture...
Another thing I liked about this picture,
one of the reasons I did it,
is that it had a multiplicity of forms,
of different kinds of narrative
all contained in the same picture.
And this becomes ordinary sitcom.
Irma Hall started as a schoolteacher
in rural Texas,
from a town that's next door
to the town of 8,000 people
that Jamie Foxx grew up in.
And so they were comparing notes
when we were shooting here this day,
and they both knew some of
the same officials in the school system.
And Jamie went to graduate
from his high school after studying...
Being both on the football team
and studying piano,
and got a scholarship into university
in classical piano.
This is the first time Max is
gonna manifest an impulsive act
that is completely irrational,
which is to steal Vincent's briefcase,
and run where? Do what with it?
It's an illogical, irrational act.
But it's provoked by Vincent winning
the affection of Max's mother.
And this puts us out of the hospital
and across a footbridge
Over the 5 Freeway in a
neighbourhood known as City Terrace.
It's just east of downtown,
and what we're looking at right now
is westbound on the 5 towards
downtown LA in the distance.
This is a very hotly-contested turf
between two gangs
on opposite sides of the freeway,
and so this night
we had elaborate security precautions.
The question that gets asked
later in the film,
in the scene after the shootout at Fever,
actually relates to this moment in time.
It's when Max says to Vincent,
"And why haven't you killed me yet?"
Because by everything we know
about Vincent,
that's exactly what should happen
right now.
And we start to wonder...
And it's a question whose origin
is in this moment,
and in the continuing relationship
that starts to become
almost the relationship of two brothers
who are violently quarreling,
but nevertheless two brothers.
Although Vincent will,
in a kind of schizoid way,
have those relations with Max,
but then he'll go back
to being on the job.
The question is,
what is Vincent seeking from Max?
What does Vincent want from Max?
Why, as they get closer
and strike a rapport
and begin to talk about things familiar
and then from familiar to intimate,
what's going on? And it's something
that I hoped, and do hope,
is occurring subtly within the audience,
almost subconsciously.
I'd prefer it to be they're not actually
aware that this question's being asked,
but that it produces a state of openness
to wondering what's gonna happen
with these two men.
Because the wondering
what's gonna happen is actually not
whether or not Max is gonna live or die
or Vincent's gonna live or die.
It's about, "What is this relationship?"
Fanning has linked the victims together,
SO we have a situation
in which Fanning, that is, the LAPD,
knows there's linkage among victims.
Meanwhile, we cut back
to Max and Vincent.
And this is the first time Vincent
will digress with Max into familiarity,
as if these are two guys in a bar
who've known each other
for a couple of months.
And they're talking about their father.
And Max talks about his mother.
This is a design by which this subtext
of the two men impacting on each other
actually begins to take over
and start to drive the story.
And for it to do that,
it has to begin early on,
where you start to see
there's certain anomalies
in Vincent's behaviour.
Where he's not
the machine-like presence he was
at the beginning of the film,
but that there's deviations
that are happening.
So you get the sense something else
is going on with this guy tonight.
Now, this is the truth,
but Vincent doesn't play it for truth.
And, again, this is a moment that I think,
I believe, that Tom just absolutely hits
a very difficult thing to nail,
which is that Vincent is brilliant
and he knows how easily shocked
is petit bourgeois Max
and that he says things
to absolutely horrify and appall Max.
And when Max delivers the reaction,
Vincent laughs it off
and says he's kidding.
And now they're talking
about Island Limos
and the rationalizations Max has
about why it hasn't been started yet.
So Max has evolved
and refined this ideation
of this exalted, ephemeral state
of riding in a limo, in Island Limos,
to such an elevated experience
that it's not only impractical,
it's never gonna happen.
And all this was shot
in the refineries of Wilmington,
which is near the Port of Los Angeles.
In Wilmington, there are clubs like this.
Why anybody would want to locate
a club there, I don't know.
The El Rodeo disco
that the following scene is shot in
is not in, actually, Wilmington.
It's in Pico Rivera,
and we did nothing to this place.
And the difficulty
in scenes like this sometimes,
and in which Jamie does a wonderful job,
Is to maintain,
sometimes three months after
the beginning of principal photography,
that pure line of exactly his character,
of what
the character's circumstances are.
Because the night, in fiction,
is only two hours old,
and the circumstances are
that he's being asked to do
some preposterously outrageous,
difficult task,
which is to go into this club
and pretend that he's Vincent
and impersonate Vincent.
And the perplexed confusion, as Jamie...
As Max has to try and process a task
of which he's completely incapable.
Those circumstances, keeping those alive
and keeping those present
after you've been playing Max,
and we shoot all the scenes
out of order anyway,
so it may be, you know, two months later,
not two hours into the evening,
is what Jamie's achieving here
and what he's able to do.
And it's an innocent look in his eyes
as he turns and looks at Vincent.
We're about to see Klea Scott,
who was a regular
on Robbery Homicide Division.
She's a fine actress who trained
at the North Carolina School
of Performing Arts.
And Bruce McGill,
who I've worked with a couple of times.
He was terrific playing the attorney,
Ron Motley, in The Insider
and did a well-remembered episode
of Miami Vice
called
"Out Where the Buses Don't Run."
What you're seeing
is exactly what appears,
including the security guards
in the front,
who are the real security guards
at the real El Rodeo,
and really nice performances.
Particularly by this guy, Cosme,
who's gonna be the guy
on the left with the bald head.
And most everybody in the place
are regulars.
It's a Nortefo disco,
the people are from northern Mexico,
the music has got
a heavy polka influence.
And we substituted Calexico
and a couple of other bands.
And Max doesn't know
what he's getting into.
One of the things that intrigued me
about Stuart Beattie's script
was the way the storylines intersect.
They're held in a very disciplined way.
Discrete, each in its own channel.
And we're about to see
two of them collide,
as the shadowy,
silhouetted figures we established
coming into the FBI surveillance
are, in fact,
revealed to be Fanning and Weidner,
who have information
that is specifically, is and only is,
that there's a linkage between victims.
Not who the victims are
or how they network together,
or who's responsible for killing them.
And somebody told Pedrosa,
played by Bruce McGill,
to cooperate with these guys
and talk to them,
and he's totally reluctant to
and is stiffing them.
But Fanning spotted the cab
and noticed it was the cab
described in the alley behind Ramone's
and launches them
on a voyage of discovery
that's gonna result in the convergence
of these two vectors.
And what's nice about Beattie's script
is the way,
once we know the vectors
are going to converge, he leaps ahead,
and the next time we go back
to the surveillance location,
Beattie leaps ahead
to the convergence already happened
and just takes us
right into the important part of it,
which is the conclusion.
And there's a great poster
for LA's famous Que Buena Radio.
And El Rodeo on the interior is black-lit,
and these are the actual murals
on their walls.
And these are some
of the actual security guards there.
A couple other of these guys
playing security guards
are some folks we got
on a work-release programme
from LA County Jail.
Here's Javier Bardem playing Felix,
and it's a case of a brilliant actor
who invests himself totally in a role
even though it was two days' shooting.
Javier is Spanish,
and he spent two or three weeks
learning how to speak English
with a Mexican,
as opposed to a Spanish, accent.
And the two story tracks
between the LAPD and the FBI
have converged, and now their information
is actually revealed to us,
'cause we have not known,
up to this point,
who these people are
who are being killed,
which is very unusual
when you think about it.
We're engaged in a picture
in which Vincent is killing people,
and he's taken captive Max,
who's compelled to go along with him.
And we don't know
why the people who are being killed
are being killed.
They're obviously crimes of dispassion.
Vincent is indifferent.
And we're gonna discover later
that Vincent isn't even sure
why they're being killed.
So the way the information is marshalled,
the way it's moved around,
and where it's revealed
is fascinating to me, and it enhances,
for me, the sense of immediacy,
because when you are immediately
in the moment of something,
you don't know the back-story.
You don't know the context.
You don't know everything
about where people came from.
You're just occupied
with the "right now" of it.
And that's what appealed to me
about doing this film was that,
"Could I make a motion picture
in which I can engage the audience
"in the 'right now' of it
without a lot of history,
"without a lot of exposition,
so that it kind of, in a way,
"almost simulates our experience
of the present
"when we're put in a context
we don't know?"
We don't know the circumstance,
we don't know exactly where we are.
The landscape may be
somewhat foreign to us.
And so we have less answers
than we have answers.
And as that...
The impressions impact upon us,
one after the other, in sequence,
some of that experience,
that's what I wanted to...
That's what attracted me
to tell this story, because it did that.
It had that immediacy to it.
I found that very exciting.
The degree of difficulty of this scene
for an actor is rather high,
because what Jamie has to do is
he has to pull off that he is Max
and he, playing Max,
has to have Max play that Max is Vincent,
and with believability,
so that you believe that it's
credible enough for Felix to buy.
And that's hard to do.
Behind all that, and why this is pivotal
in the realization of Max's character,
it has to do
with this massive compression
of Max's life to this single point,
this single fine point in time
in which Max believes he's gonna die.
And there's the moment of truth for Max.
And faced with mortality,
what emerges is,
in fact, the power, the skill,
the improvisational ability
to speak his mind, to take action.
It's okay that it manifests itself
in mimicry. He's imitating Vincent.
And that's okay, 'cause that's actually
how our learning process...
As human beings, that's how we learn.
We mimic something,
and then we make it our own.
And that's exactly what the idea
of this was.
But he had to have that experience
as his jumping-off point,
as a catalyst of, "He's gonna die."
And it comes from Felix
telling this anecdote
he probably just made up
about Black Peter.
Felix is surrounded by a ring
of security people around him,
and he is also surrounded
by sharply-pointed plants,
and it was... I wasn't happy with the set,
and we couldn't really change anything
on the walls,
and so we just improvised
and brought in a bunch of plants.
This is an interesting scene to me,
in terms of audience reactions,
because for some reason,
some audiences get
that Max is offering Felix a big discount
on Vincent's fees.
That he's giving away
a whole bunch of Vincent's money.
And some audiences think
this is actually hilarious.
And for some reason, other audiences,
it just goes right past them
and it doesn't get any kind of a reaction.
The colour right here
is just something that happened.
Just the composition, the light.
This is actually shot on film, this piece.
And we just managed to preserve it.
What's happened here
was very challenging for me
from a storytelling point of view,
or actually the plot point of view.
Because the information deficit
that each discrete track had,
i.e. the FBI knew nothing,
the LAPD knew that bodies were dropping
and they were linked,
and then, also, we're about to generate
Paco and Rubio,
have all come together
in the FBI surveillance scene.
And the FBI and the LAPD now know
that the bodies are dropping,
are all linked together,
and that, in fact,
they're the FBI's witnesses
who were about to come forward
in a federal grand jury
that's supposed to be convening tomorrow.
This was an abandoned Kmart,
and it was the largest...
I think it was the largest Kmart
in America,
and it was transformed into this set
by a very talented art director.
It was a very long night.
And we wound up working very fast,
and it was very late in the night.
And sometimes when you do that,
there's a real tremendous intensity.
And if you could keep that on a roll,
you get some of the best work because,
as an actor and also as a director,
it's just happening so fast,
there's a certain spontaneous intensity
to it.
And Mark Ruffalo, particularly,
I believe, really shined in this.
What's happening is that Klea Scott
is identifying for us
the origins of Vincent.
The FBI are poised
as kind of unguided missiles
or misguided missiles,
because they now have identified,
because of Vincent's ploy,
that they believe Max to be Vincent.
Fanning is skeptical.
This is Tom Rothrock's cue.
Most of the composing
is done by James Newton Howard,
who did excellent work,
particularly a very, very difficult piece
towards the end of the film,
which is alternately orchestral
and percussion.
But this particular piece
is composed by Rothrock,
whose strength
is this kind of blues mode,
which you're hearing right here.
He also did the cue that opens the movie.
And I view music
as telling different parts of the story,
so sometimes
just as you have multiple characters,
you should have different,
slightly different perspectives
on the music all fitting into a plan
about how the story ought to tell itself.
There's four story tracks
all heading to a disco named Fever.
Max and Vincent are heading there.
And there's kind of a sense of
destiny's gonna get worked out
in this confrontation,
and there's a prelude,
in which something
I found fascinating was to happen.
Vincent changes registers again,
and I wanted Vincent to just elevate
without any transition
into a state of mind
in which he was speaking to Max
as if they were brothers
or if they were pals
who've known each other for 15 years,
and they're in a bar
and Vincent's just saying
this most casual thing,
"Hey, why aren't you gonna ask
that girl out?"
With a familiarity that's schizophrenic,
that has no basis at all
in the circumstances
that Vincent has, in fact,
imposed upon Max.
It's a step aside from reality
into a parallel reality,
the reality that's going on
in Vincent's mind,
which is also the subtext of the film.
That Vincent's, in fact, cracking up.
That subtext is gonna wind up
hijacking the whole of the story
and drive us to the end.
And after he asks this question,
each man kind of retreats
into the solitude
of his own self-awareness.
And what they see is something
that I witnessed a couple of times in LA.
I was driving a babysitter home
and saw three coyotes
who were just walking diagonally
across the intersection
of Fairfax and Sunset Boulevard.
They seemed to have an attitude
like they still owned it,
this was still their real estate.
And this civilized layer
called the City of Los Angeles,
which has only been here for 80 years
was, in fact, something temporary.
Maybe here, maybe gone tomorrow.
And each man thinking his own thoughts
as he's heading into
what may be mortal combat.
When I heard this song by Audioslave
and the Chris Cornell vocal,
Shadow On The Sun,
I knew I wanted it
for this moment in the film.
As they travel through
the neon shopping malls of Koreatown,
the advantage of the video,
shooting in high-def, is the ability
to see these distant landscapes
and trees against the sky,
almost as if we're in
some kind of a dark afternoon.
The club is a club...
The real name of the club is Bliss.
It's on Sixth in Wilshire Central
in Koreatown.
We renamed it Fever.
And we actually enter the real location,
and we duplicated the decor
on a set that we built
that had to be seven times as large.
Seven or eight times
as large as the actual club
to fit the 800 or 900 Korean extras
we brought in.
What's happening
is that all the discrete storylines
are heading towards a collision,
and we, the audience, are aware of it.
Vincent, the hunter, is not aware
that he's, in fact, being hunted.
The challenge of shooting I,
and the excitement about shooting it,
was to set up each character
moving through this field of 800 dancers
in a way so that we were with each group
as they're moving through it
and knowing where we are at the same time
and keeping all three stories alive.
The music is Ready Steady Go
by Paul Oakenfold.
It's a great piece.
It was perfect for this scene.
But to make it be less familiar,
we translated Ready Steady Go
into Korean,
soO, what they're saying in Korean
IS, "Ready, steady, go."
Koreatown has the largest population
of Koreans outside of Seoul.
And as a community,
it's particularly vibrant and unified
and has a great depth of culture,
which is kind of typical of Los Angeles
and ethnic communities in Los Angeles,
where there seems to be
a lot less assimilation.
So that in going to a Korean club,
you're gonna see music videos from Seoul.
You're not gonna see music videos
from MTV.
The way I thought about this whole scene,
in terms of scene analysis, like,
"How does the scene work internally?"
Is that, it's a conflict between
our characters, Max and Vincent,
and then also Pedrosa,
when we're tracking with Pedrosa.
And what he's in conflict with is,
in fact, chaos.
And it's the chaos
that Vincent has to work against
to achieve his objective.
Which is, of course,
completely pathological,
which is to murder a Korean gangster
named Peter Lim.
A lot of the close-quarter combat
that Vincent is doing, again,
took three to four months of training.
And we did a much broader variety of it
than what we're seeing here.
But Tom was very fast and very strong,
very skilled with this.
And the instructor I used is Mick Gould,
who was one of the two instructors I had
for all the close-quarter combat
that we did.
And the other guy was Andy McNab,
who was also the author
of a book called Bravo Two Zero,
which is highly recommended reading
on the first Iraq war,
that he was in
and was captured by the Iraqis.
Lim has an outer ring of protection,
which is exactly
the way security would behave.
And then he's got
some closer people around him.
There were two classes of security,
one with bodyguards, trained bodyguards,
and then some Korean gangsters
who didn't speak English.
And why they don't speak English
is something that's gonna be
seen in a moment.
The Korean gangsters behind Lim
now mistake the FBI,
who are, in fact,
coming to bring Lim to safety.
They mistake it as an assault on Lim.
They don't speak English.
Pedrosa gets shot.
That instantly initiates panic and chaos,
and now Vincent is not just having
to move through a field of dancers
to get closer to Lim,
he now has to move through, in fact,
a gunfight and the chaos and the panic
and a mob stampeding to get away.
We had an admirable group
of Korean extras
recruited from Koreatown, from UCLA,
from all kinds of places,
who managed to work themselves up
into a state of panic
for about 12 to 14 hours a day
for about five days straight.
Vincent, in reality,
would be really focused
on what's happening.
Almost like a fugue state.
And then it's gonna get interrupted
by a threat to Max,
and as Vincent deals with it,
I wanted Tom to have,
and he absolutely has,
a kind of look on his face,
almost as if he's irritated
because Max has been so inconsiderate
to allow himself
to have his life jeopardised,
and Vincent's had to intervene
to save him.
The only guy who is headed right,
because he, in fact,
has really proper procedure
as a detective and investigator,
is Fanning.
And he's finally able to rescue Max.
He sets up the unexpected.
Vincent, right here in this scene,
is disarmed,
and it's actually his weakest moment
in the film.
He rises to the occasion
and continues doing what he does.
But the point was that Vincent had
a moment of confusion.
And it's one of the other subtle glimpses
into what's going on
below the surface of Vincent's activity.
And in my mind, and this is strictly
from the director's perspective,
meaning that the audience
didn't necessarily
get impacted upon these things.
In my mind, it was that...
It's almost as if Vincent's 11 years old
for an instant,
for a fraction of a second,
and he's confused by bad things
that are happening to him.
And he responds by reassembling
his perspective in reacting
and acting out with violent aggression.
Now, the audience may or may not only
get a moment of weakness from him,
but it was fundamental to me
in my understanding of Vincent's history
and his character that this, in fact, is
something that's repeated into his life.
Now, what Jamie was supposed to do was...
His door was open,
and he was supposed to be
so distracted by the seemingly eternal
situation he finds himself in,
meaning that regardless of what happens,
he winds up back behind the wheel
on the seat of that cab,
that he just accelerated forward
without closing the door,
and the door is to bang
into the parked car.
That didn't happen. The door closed,
and Jamie just headed for the car.
We're into something called "Scene 86"
and it's the big, pivotal scene
in the construction of the story.
Max has been changed
by a number of things that happen,
starting with the compression of his life,
facing death in the form of Felix.
My direction to Jamie
for that scene was that,
"You have to feel like you're gonna die.
You're gonna die right now."
And Max manifested individual action
for the first time,
which was always there.
It had been latent instead of manifest.
And in the scene with Felix,
it took the form
of actually mimicking Vincent's style
when he talks about / Ching, Darwin.
But between then, with Felix,
and right now, Max is changed.
And right now, Max sees
beyond the end of Vincent's gun
to the man who is there.
Vincent's repeating a pattern,
and he again delivers
the kind of facile nihilism
about the purposelessness of the cosmos.
"Nothing means anything,
so what difference does it make
"how many bodies are dropped tonight?"
This is the third time
we've heard this from Vincent,
and so there's almost
a kind of a self-directed cynicism.
He calls it "crap."”
But this time, Max doesn't buy it.
And Max sees through it.
Every film seems to have
its pivotal scenes,
and this is the pivotal scene
of this motion picture.
Max, for the first time,
is seeing beyond the end of the gun
and is seeing Vincent for who Vincent is,
which is damaged goods.
He experiences a feeling
of an understanding for Vincent,
and he struggles to put it into words.
And that struggle is something
I very much wanted Jamie to live through,
and that is Vincent's sociopathy,
that even if you put a gun
to his head and told Vincent,
"Il have to shoot you
unless you can tell me
"what somebody over there is feeling,"
Vincent can't do it.
He isn't capable of empathy.
He's literally incapable of it,
as if he were handicapped.
So Max renders a negative judgment
on Vincent.
He says,
"You are low, my brother. Way low."
Vincent is actually not impervious,
he's not the Teflon man
we saw landing at LAX.
He's injured by this.
And he assaults Max reactively.
And it's very personal,
and his intent is to devastate Max
with a prediction of the purposelessness
of what Max's life will be,
almost as if Vincent
is the Ghost of Christmas Future,
and telling him
that Max's evasion is chronic,
and he'll never achieve
any of his dreams.
In this scene right here, I can't fail
but to have a director's appreciation
for actors,
"cause fine acting is fine acting,
and it's not something
directors really do,
except notable exceptions
like John Huston.
But we have the highest, at least,
I have the highest regard for it,
because it is that projection
out onto the end of the limb.
Or on the wire without a net.
It's, you know,
going through that ineffable place
where you're simultaneously in control
and completely uncontrolled,
living, breathing
and being in the moment.
And I think that's what Jamie Foxx
and Tom Cruise are doing right here.
And it never ceases
to be marvelous to me.
Max has taken what Vincent said earlier
and stood it on its head,
which is to say that
if existence has no inherent meaning,
and it's meaningless,
then, in fact, the individual is free
to put meaning into his life
by his actions.
And Max takes action.
Max rebels,
and he's about to destroy what, in fact,
has imprisoned him for the last 12 years.
In flipping the cab, I designed the shot
and how many times I wanted the cab
to flip and how I wanted it to end up.
And the physics of it
are pretty interesting.
You weight the cab in certain parts,
and you lift the back of the cab
with kind of an air mortar.
And you just actually run the left front
of the cab into a piece of concrete,
and physics do the rest.
Joel Kramer, the stunt coordinator,
and the stuntmen who worked on this
are pretty much able to dump the cab
exactly where we want,
and we went out to an abandoned airstrip
and set up this course
with exactly the right distances.
And the cab dropped
where it was supposed to that day,
and it also dropped
where it was supposed to this day.
There were about nine cameras there,
but the key camera is the last one,
the camera in which the cab
actually comes to a stop,
after it lifts the front
end of this Pontiac.
And this is take one.
They just hit it, and they nailed it.
I've reviewed it on the monitors,
and because of the higher contrast
on the monitors,
it made it seem as if the crash
was actually more kinetic than it was.
And I thought it was too violent.
So we re-shot it, I think, two more times.
Didn't need any of it. The first take,
with the multiple cameras,
is the one we used.
This is Bob Deamer.
Bob Deamer is an officer in the LAPD.
And I've gone on a number
of ride-alongs with him,
in which we've had various adventures.
And contrary to his appearance here,
he's a very tough cop.
Jamie's so weary of life with Vincent
that being taken to LA County Jail
sounds like a good idea.
This begins a music cue
by James Newton Howard
that's going to alternate
between orchestral,
with the horns and low strings,
meaning cellos, violas,
double bass
and a horn section and percussion.
And it begins here,
and it's an extremely long cue.
Goes for almost 16 or 17 minutes,
taken in total.
It was written and composed
as a unified cue.
And that was
some of the fascinating dynamics
of the construction of this narrative
for those of us who made the film.
Of the construction of this narrative
Because it's immediate
and because it takes place in 10 hours,
that means you examine
smaller pieces of time
under a very powerful microscope,
which means that events
which normally, in a normal film,
might occupy two and a half minutes,
in this film occupy five minutes,
because we examine them
much more closely.
And so, consequently, music cues
that would be two or three minutes,
which are more conventional,
become five and six minute cues
or, in this case, a long cue
becomes a hugely long cue.
The visualization that you're seeing
in some of these shots of Jamie
on the rooftop are interesting,
because they would not be possible
with motion-picture film.
Those buildings are not lit.
There's, I think,
one parking-structure light
that's on Jamie, and that's about it.
If I had shot
on 35 mm motion-picture film,
I would have had to use
a lot of very powerful lights,
and then it wouldn't have had
a realistic look.
It would have looked like
it was, in fact, lit.
So it was... Cityscapes like this
are one of the key reasons
I wanted to shoot in high-def video,
because it revealed the whole world
of the city at night.
That's also apparent in the scene
when Vincent kicks in the door,
and you're seeing the detail
of the exterior and the depth of field,
meaning things in the foreground
are in focus
and things in the deep background
are also in focus,
including the distant lights.
Here's more of the lights
that we're seeing
only as a courtesy
of high-definition video.
This shot would also have been
impossible in motion-picture film.
Max would either be not exposed at all,
and/or he would not be able
to carry the focus.
This rooftop that Max is on
was a very, very difficult...
Probably the most difficult location
for us to get permission to shoot on
in the city, because it's controlled
by the Secret Service.
And they use it to park vehicles on
from time to time,
and they don't want anybody
even remotely near the rooftop.
And it took a lot of convincing
and us willing to work
under mass restrictions,
meaning we shot all of Max's work
in about two hours.
That's the only way we were able
to get permission to be on this rooftop.
It's the only exposed
rooftop quite like it
in downtown Los Angeles,
which was why I needed it.
The drums were originally heard
in Mozambique.
In Maputo, Mozambique on AIL.
When I heard them in Maputo,
I recorded them,
and then we got Ghanaian drummers,
who happened to be in Los Angeles,
to go into the third level
of my parking garage.
It's got a lot of echo in it.
And we repeated the drumming pattern
I had heard in East Africa
with drummers
who were mostly from West Africa.
We call them Ghanaian drums.
In fact, they're Mozambican drums,
if you like.
And we sampled those.
We also repeated it
and did them mostly live.
This scene,
without being able to use digital video,
would not even have been able
to have been written, much less shot,
because you wouldn't even conceive
of a scene in which characters
are moving around with no lights
and, in fact, it's only their silhouettes
against the city lights
and a little bit of bounce that's coming
from the city lights themselves
that enables you to see them.
It just would've been
physically impossible to capture it.
The cameras are seeing more
than the naked eye.
When we finished some of these shots,
and I said, "Cut,"
everybody had to stay where they were
until the lights were turned on
so that people didn't trip and fall
and hurt themselves.
Max grew up in Ladera Heights,
Which is a very middle-class section
of Los Angeles.
And he's never been exposed
to street violence, really, in his life,
except what he might have seen
as a cab driver.
So he doesn't know how to shoot
an H&K .45.
In doing some of the research
about what Vincent would've done
if he walked in a strange building,
he would have, first of all,
acclimated himself
to the ambient noise of the building.
Buildings heat up during the day
when the sun's out.
At night, they cool off and they contract,
and thousands of contractions
throughout the entire structure
give the building noise.
And if you're quiet in a building,
and you listen, you could listen to it.
And the point is
that what Vincent would've been doing
and what he does here
is that he stops, and he listens.
And he gets the ambient noise
that's supposed to be there.
Because what he's really listening for,
once he understands
what the ambient noise
that's supposed to be there is,
are the anomalous noises.
And the anomalous noises
are the sounds of his prey
and that's Annie.
And all he's doing when he's static here
is, in fact, listening.
And he's just almost kind of like a bat,
and he's listening for the sound.
What he hears are her stockings
scraping against the carpet
and her palms
scraping against the carpet,
and that's how he locates her.
It wasn't planned
that Vincent fall over the chair,
but when he did,
it's one of those accidents that I love.
But when he did,
I love it when something happens
that's unexpected.
It's kind of an anomaly.
I sometimes ask myself,
"What are the characteristics
of an event or an activity
"that are gonna make it simulate
something real
"or feel to me as if it's real?"
And it's the things
that don't go exactly according to plan.
I tend to be attracted to them.
I was attracted to this location
among all the different
MTA subway stations in Los Angeles,
particularly because of the amount
of steel.
I like the sense that they're running
into some place metallic,
almost like a metallic tube.
LA's got a pretty beautiful subway
and public-transportation system.
And when it travels on the surface
and hits some of the train stops,
many of them are one-offs.
They're individually architected.
Vincent is enraged.
He's impossibly formidable.
Max surprised Vincent
and actually pulled the trigger,
something that Vincent
thought Max incapable of doing.
In his clumsy way,
Max has been improvisational,
which brings it back to a theme
that's actually defined
in Stuart Beattie's script.
In the jazz club,
when Vincent talks about improvisation
and Max is acquiring
certain characteristics
through the agency now,
not of the advice of Vincent
but via his conflict with him.
I didn't desire to ameliorate in any way
Vincent's intent.
Vincent intends to kill Annie.
And it was something
that I questioned one or two times
and came to the conclusion
it has to be what happens.
This is a spectacular MTA station
right above...
Right amongst a conjunction
of three freeways.
It's the Harbor Station.
This is not a visual effect.
This is shot practically,
as is all these other shots
of pulling out of the Harbor Station.
There are some shots
that are gonna be coming up
in which I chose to shoot green screen,
meaning that I wanted to be able
to customize the backgrounds
that were outside the windows.
Like right here.
And the reason for it was because
I wanted the graphic pattern
of particularly those rectangles of light,
which are from parking structures,
and I wanted them to occur
right at this moment.
Max has closed his eyes
and simply pulled the trigger,
expecting to die
after he's forced himself,
impelled himself to confront Vincent.
There was a direction here,
the particular attitude
for Vincent to have as he sat down.
And the direction was to be irritated.
As if it was being irritated
at something pedestrian.
And he's irritated
at the absurd outcome of this gunfight,
at the whole of this night.
Particularly about the gunfight.
If Max hadn't closed his eyes
and just fired chaotically, he'd be dead.
Vincent's ironically repeated
the same line,
an anecdote about,
"A guy gets on the MTA, dies,
"think anybody will notice?"
But it's not a rhetorical question.
Vincent is asking,
"Will anybody note
that once upon a time I was here?"
And he's sincere.
All of Vincent's life, who he's been,
and all of Max's life,
it's all been collapsed
into this one moment.
Into the events of this one night.
And the night's over.