Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Mrs. Yepremian,
I would like you to meet
my new associate, Dr. Brooks.
-He's here for career day.
-Aw.
MRS. YEPREMIAN:
He's adorable.
DR. BROOKS: He wants to be a dentist
just like his dad.
All right, let's see
what's going on in there.
-Oh, boy.
-Ah!
-Dr. Brooks, is this gonna hurt?
-|‘m afraid just a little.
More than a tickle but way less
than paying your taxes.
That's right.
-All right, let's see.
Dr. Brooks!
I think I need a second opinion.
-Me?
-Mm-hmm.
Son, if you want to be
a great dentist,
never forget the personal touch.
Here.
MRS. YEPREMIAN: Ah...
Ah!
-Hello, ladies!
-Oh. Hi.
Beautiful day in Miami.
Whoo!
Good morning, fine ladies.
-Good morning.
-Busy day, doctor.
-Yeah, they all are.
We will be with you all in a while
and we promise to make you smile.
Now, if yourjaw still hurts tonight,
take two pills.
If it still hurts tomorrow, then...
you should probably find
a new dentist.
Huh?
"Find a..."
-|t's a little joke.
-Oh.
Anyway, just call us tomorrow,
let us know how you feel.
-Wow.
-Thank you.
-Sugar cookies.
-Hello, little darling. Hello, you.
-Mom... Hi.
-Teddy bear!
Hi. How are you?
Can I?
Excuse us for a second.
-Enjoy them.
-Come on, Mom.
Mom...
I love that you're involved
in my practice,
but you can't be giving
out sugar cookies in a dental office.
Your father always believed
in the personal touch.
And repeat business.
Hey, T. Got a surprise.
This guy says
he's an old buddy of yours.
I don't know this man.
Well, I'm Ernesto Julio Raphael Santisto.
-TED: Oh.
-And you've been served.
-Do you validate?
-Oh, no, you got to go.
-Hey, hey, stamp my ticket, man.
-Sure.
-|'m gonna stamp your head.
-Stamp my ticket!
-AMELIA: Ted?
Are you being sued?
Hey, if this is about
that Freeman kid,
he's lying.
I mean, okay, maybe I shouldn't have
been drilling left-handed
-but he dared me.
-Would you shut up?
It's about a will.
Phew.
But I definitely think they have
the wrong Theodore Brooks.
It's about some lady in Alaska,
a place called Tolketna.
-RUPERT: Alaska?
They definitely got
the wrong Ted Brooks.
See, they're looking
for the white Ted Brooks.
-Well, her name is Lucy Watkins...
Mom!
Rupert, get her something to drink!
Wait a minute, relax, relax.
Sit down. Breathe, breathe.
Here, rinse and spit.
Oh, Teddy Bear.
How can I?
-How do I?
-How do you what?
Ted...
Teddy...
You're adopted.
AMELIA:
We always meant to tell you
and then your father died...
This doesn't change anything.
I am your mother, no matter what.
You will always be
my teddy bear.
My love. My teddy bear.
My love. My teddy.
RUPERT: Ted!
Ted! Hey, Ted. Come on.
Don't trip on this.
All right?
A lot of people are adopted.
-Famous people.
You know, you got Webster
and Soon-Yi.
And those kids
from Different Strokes.
-They turned out okay.
-I should've known.
-Please.
-There were so many signs.
-Really?
-Yeah, |--
-Like what?
Well...
Like blue cheese!
I love blue cheese,
and they hate it.
Oh! Uncanny.
So how was it living
with strangers?
-Why am | a dentist, Rupert?
-Duh! 'Cause your daddy's a dentist.
Maybe I was meant
to do something different.
Be someone else.
I'm an Eskimo!
-RUPERT: All right, cuz.
-I got you everything you need
for your trip to Alaska.
I'm only going for a couple of days!
Yeah, well, I know you
just wanted a parka, but,
your credit card wanted more.
Oh, I got these shoes for myself.
Whoo! Yeah, ﬂy, right?
-What is all of this, Rupert?
-Okay.
For those cold Alaskan nights,
you know,
other than getting a little na-nooky.
I got you a personal, wearable
warm and cold system.
It's the ultimate climate
control accessory.
But wait, there's more.
There better not be more.
Well...
you're gonna receive a bill
for a massage chair.
-Out!
I like that co...
Shut up, Chester! I hate you!
When I bought this condo,
no one told me a little rat
like you lived next door!
I'm so sick
of your barking!
PILOT: Welcome to Anchorage.
We got a real scorcher today.
Expecting a high of three degrees.
WOMAN: As reigning champion,
what have you learned?
MAN: I know that nothing can
be left to chance.
In this race,
man and beast must move as one.
And when I cross the finish line,
nothing refreshes like Powerade,
the only drink on my sled.
MAN OVER P.A.:
Your attention, please.
Final boarding call
for ﬂight 522 to Tolketna.
-Oh! That's me!
- This is the ﬁnal ﬂight
-to Tolketna this month.
-Wait! Hold that plane!
-Wait! Wait! Wait!
-Sir, please! You can't go beyond...
Wait! Wait! Halt! No!
Flight 522!
Nonstop to Tolketna!
That's okay, l'll walk!
MAN OVER RADIO: George Murphy,
you're clear for takeoff,
so quit dawdling and move it!
George Murphy? You're the one
that sent me the summons?
Why, yes. At your service.
But, if you're the executor
of the estate
then why are you, uh?
I'm an attorney,
the justice of the peace
and the bush pilot.
A classic triple threat.
MAN OVER RADIO:
8-6-7—2—4-1-Queen, move it!
Or you're going to be
the hood ornament on a 737!
The captain has turned off
the seat belt sign.
You're free to move about the cabin.
-K|D: Right over here!
All right, all right,
over here!
-Who's that?
-Plane! It's George!
Come on!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
GEORGE:
Welcome to Tolketna International Airport.
The white zone is
for the loading and unloading
of passengers only.
Careful! Gets a little gusty up here!
TED: Help me!
GEORGE: There it is.
Downtown.
BARB: Hey, you guys,
I know you're starving.
Here's your sandwich.
All right, you roughnecks.
Give me back those knives.
These are for eating.
Nobody's going to order dinner,
if the silverware's been in the walls.
Come on, Barb,
we've all seen your food.
Nobody's going to order it, anyway.
Always a little high.
-MAN: Close the door!
-Whoo!
Whoo!
Hey, slick.
To your health, son.
Enjoy.
He looks just like her.
Ah! Excuse me.
Can I get a cup
of decaf latte, please?
Honey, you can get anything
your little heart desires.
Except a decaf latte.
How about a cup of regular?
Fresh brewed yesterday.
Sure, as long as it's hot.
-Coffee...
-Here you go.
A hot cuppa java.
So, how are you enjoying Tolketna?
Just trying to keep up
with the hustle and bustle.
Hey, Mister. We gotta talk.
I've been waiting a long time
for a dentist to come to town.
Yeah, I got a canker sore
in the back of my mouth.
And isn't that stench unbearable?
All right, quiet!
Now, pipe down!
Time to get started!
We got a will to read here!
George! Knock it off!
| just patched the last hole!
GEORGE: All right.
Now, we're here to read
the last will and testament
of Lucy Watkins.
So, here goes.
Oh. "First off, I'd like
to thank you all for coming.
I hope you got a good turnout.
Though, if there was a blizzard,
I understand.
Now, I don't want any crying.
People should enjoy themselves.
So, Barb, why don't you pour
a round of wild turkey on me."
Pass it around.
Here ya go.
What's with sasquatch?
Zip your lip.
That's Thunder Jack.
They call him that
'cause he got hit by thunder.
Twice!
You can't get hit by thunder.
GEORGE: Now, pay attention.
"Now, I led a simple life
so don't expect too many goodies
to be bequeathed.
First, to Peter Yellowbear,
my neighbor and fellow snow golfer,
-I leave my lucky putter."
-Yeah!
"But don't expect it
to improve your game."
"Next. To Barb,
my dear friend and boss,
I give my shearling coat."
"Which kept me warmer
than any man ever did."
You don't have to talk to it
in the morning.
"And...
to my son, Ted Brooks.
I'm sorry you never knew me...
but to you I leave the rest
of my worldly possessions.
| wish it were more."
Oh! "And to Thunder Jack...
I leave my outhouse
and all its contents."
"Now, in conclusion,
I just want to say thanks
to all you misfits, outcasts
and just plain weirdos.
You made living in this icebox fun.
lfl end up in heaven,
I'll put in a good word for ya.
And if! end up down below
well, at least it's warm."
-To Lucy!
-ALL: To Lucy!
-WOMAN: Great gal.
-To Lucy.
It's hard to breathe
at this altitude, huh?
Eh, you'll get used to it
after a week or so.
Oh, no, I'm not planning
on being here that long.
I'm just going to poke around,
get a feel for this Lucy,
maybe inventory her valuables.
Valuables?
You obviously didn't know her.
So, is that all you want?
Is to pawn off all her stuff?
Well, do I owe her more than that?
Huh! She pawned off her kid.
Don't talk about Lucy like that.
You don't know anything about her.
Is that my fault?
Never mind. Forget it.
Wow!
-Come on, I'll show you around.
-Oh, uh, no, thanks.
I think I want to go alone.
-Okay.
One ceramic lamp.
With a tacky shade.
One very dirty throw rug.
Yeah... And...
"Arctic Challenge third place."
Hey!
Where did you come from?
Nobody said anything
about Lucy having a dog.
Of course, no one said anything
about her having a son, either.
Oh, you're hungry, huh?
Well, go tell whoever it is
that feeds you.
Alright. Let's go see if we
can find you some chow.
Nope.
In here?
Where's the dog food?
Not in here.
No dog food.
Oh!
-Oh.
Oh, oh! Oh, oh!
Oh! Oh, oh!
Oh! Get back!
Back! Back! Ha, ha!
Back! Ah!
-Uh-oh.
-Oh, oh!
-Nice doggy.
Nice doggy.
Aah! Trouble. Aah!
Stop it!
-Let go! Let go!
-No, not the jacket!
-No, doggies!
-Hey, I come in peace!
Stop it!
Wait, that tickles.
Oh, no!
Okay, wait! Get off!
-Let me go! Stop that!
Give me the door!
Any more surprises?
-Huh?
Whoa! Whoa!
Where's those dogs?
-What?
-The dogs, where are they?
They're eating the house.
TED: Wait! Wait a minute!
Oh, you can't go in there!
This one dog is possessed.
He's dangerous.
Demon.
-TED: Wait!
Mr. Thunder?
Look out.
-Hey, whoa!
How you doing, demon, huh?
How's my boy?
-THUNDER: Oh! Looking good, kid.
How much you want
for these mutts?
Oh, uh. Well, I haven't
Checked the blue book yet.
-|'|| give you $200.
-Each?
-No, for the whole lot.
Well, that seems a little low.
I mean, even the puppies
in the mall cost...
You think I'm trying
to chisel you?
-No.
-You think I'm that kind of a man?
Why don't we just step outside
and settle this thing Eskimo style?
-Hey!
-Just you and me,
a rope and a knife.
And the last man breathing
gets the dogs.
-$200 is great.
-No, it's not.
You just stay out
of this, missy.
-You cheap chiseler.
You and I both know
that any of those dogs
is worth $500 and demon's
probably worth $1,000.
Really?
I'm not going to let you
take advantage of him
just because he's some
dumb city slicker.
You want to sell those dogs,
you look me up.
-Oh, what is this stuff?
-S|ump.
-S|ump?
-Mm-hmm.
Mostly the stuff
the butcher can't sell.
Hooves, lips, organs...
Slump.
In Miami, we call them hot dogs.
Oh!
So, why did Grizzly Adams
want these dogs, anyway?
Because the arctic challenge
is in two weeks.
These dogs are champions.
Except for Nana, of course.
Lucy just liked her company.
Arctic Challenge. What is that?
Well, next to the Iditarod,
it's the biggest dog race around.
Five days across 400 miles
of the most beautiful
and rugged terrain in the world.
Who'd be crazy enough to do that?
Your mother.
Oh.
I'm not being frisky.
I... I'm stuck.
That's what all the guys say.
-Oh!
Happens to everyone.
Up and at 'em.
You're all chapped.
Here.
-So, let me ask you something.
-What?
Did Lucy ever mention
about who my father was?
Sorry.
No one even knew you existed.
-Oh, right.
Well, there can't be
too many suspects.
How many black guys
are there around here?
Including you?
Let me see...
Two.
-Arthur?
-Oh, you must be Ted.
I've been waiting
so long for this.
-Would you like to come in?
-Of course. Thank you.
l was so worried that you wouldn't
have the time
to see me before you left.
l have felt this terrible pain
for so long.
Me, too.
So, should I sit on a Chair
or would you prefer me to lie down?
Uh, Chair's fine.
So, it's my left rear molar.
Filling fell out
a couple of years ago.
And now it's purple.
And there's this real rotten odor.
Maybe it's infected.
And you're telling me this because?
Aren't you a dentist?
Aren't you my father?
If I say yes,
do | get a discount?
Doesn't even look like me.
I, uh... categorized
all of Lucy's possessions.
These are the recommended prices.
This is what I'll settle for.
And you can keep ten percent
for yourself.
Oh, what about the dogs?
Give them to Johnny Lightning.
You mean Thunder Jack?
Sure, why not?
He wants them.
I haven't got any use for them.
-Thanks. This'll only take a second.
-Yeah, sure.
You‘re leaving?
I don't know
what I was looking for.
But I sure didn't find it.
Well, what were you expecting?
Maybe a little truth.
Find out about myself,
learn why she gave me up...
Hey, why don't you stick
around for a bit?
The arctic challenge is in two weeks.
There's hundreds of people.
TV crews come around.
-lt's going to be fun.
-Look, I like you.
If you're ever in Miami,
look me up.
My number's on all the buses.
Wait! Stop!
I know who your father is.
TED: Hold it, hold it.
GEORGE: What now?
His name is James Johnson.
Whoa-whoa!
Relax, relax.
You can do this.
Good.
Ow!
I hate the snow.
Well, well, lookie here.
Come to sell me them dogs?
You? You're James Johnson?
I don't much like
people calling me James.
What...
You're white.
Will you look at that?
-Do you know who I am?
-Yeah.
You're the fella that's going
to sell me those dogs.
No.
I'm your son.
Well, so, how much
you want for them?
You knew?
You knew the whole time,
and you didn't say anything?
I don't see any good coming
from dredging up ancient history.
Is that what I am?
Ancient history?
| tell you what I'm going to do.
I can go up to 300 dollars
for the lot.
The dogs?
-Don't you think of anything else?
-You got no business with them.
I mean, they're special animals.
They need to be taken care of.
-You're a real piece of work.
You know,
I don't believe we're related.
There must be some mistake
because you are definitely
not my father!
Well, tell you the truth,
I don't much give a hoot
one way or the other.
All I'm saying is that
you don't belong here.
I'm sure you've got a nice,
little condominium someplace
with a remote control color TV
and a nice electric blanket.
So, why don't you pack up
your big City butt
and go back there!
No.
I'm not going anywhere.
-You are a stubborn fool.
-No, you're the stubborn fool!
You must have something wrong
with that head.
No, you got something
wrong with your head!
No, you got something wrong
with your head!
in your head!
No, you got something wrong
with your head.
Oh, well,
you know what they say.
The apple doesn't fall far
from the tree, Jack.
Or should I call you father?
Or how about papa?
Or maybe even daddy-o.
TED: I don't belong here?
I'll show him.
I'll be a mush master.
-A regular sled doggy dog!
-Just watch me, Nana.
-Dr. Brooks speaking.
-AMEL|A: Ted.
I promised myself
I wasn‘t going to bother you
but we thought
you’d be home by now.
-|s everything all right?
-Everything's fine.
-So, how's Alaska?
Basically, everything's white.
Including my father!
TED: Ma? Are you still there?
-Are you sure?
-Sure, I'm sure.
Well, that explains
why you were always so crazy
about that Michael Bolton.
This has gone on long enough, Teddy.
I am coming up there.
TED: You're terriﬁed of ﬂying.
-Rupert! Get off the phone!
-I'm not on the phone!
When are you coming home? You know,
your mother's worried sick about you.
-Rupert, off!
-TED: Rupert, ofﬂ
Teddy, I‘ll be right there.
No, I don't need your help.
|'|| handle this by myself.
-I got to go. Slump's done.
Never, ever underestimate
Theodore Brooks.
DDS!
Bad dog! Bad dog! Get back!
Bad doggy!
Bad dog! Bad doggy!
Whoo!
Who made it in the tree, dog?
Who made it in the tree?
That's right! That's right!
You can't climb!
You don't know
what time it is!
Get over here! How you like that?
Oh, that's cold.
I hope your pee-pee freeze up.
Yeah, that's right, go inside!
-TED: This ain't over!
This is only round one!
Ooh! Ooh!
You having fun with that doggy?
You know what
your problem is?
See, Demon's got it in his head
that he‘s the alpha dog.
You've got to show him
who's boss!
Bite him in the ear!
I am not putting any part
of that dog in my mouth.
Suit yourself.
Any musher will tell you the same.
-Oh, you're a musher?
-Are you kidding?
I'm the only man ever
to win the arctic flame
three years running.
Congratulations.
Yeah, well, it is kind of
a strange award.
It goes to the person
who comes in last.
In Miami, three-time losers
go to prison.
BARB: Forget it!
Rest rooms are for customers only!
Out of my way, girlie!
-Hi.
-James Johnson.
Were you being coy, or is that
some sick Alaskan mind game?
-|'m sorry.
I swore to Lucy I wouldn't tell
a soul about Thunder Jack.
| just didn't want
to see you leave like that.
Bring it home!
Whoa, there. Come on, whoa!
Good boy.
Excuse me.
It's time for round two.
All right, Nana, if there's
any trouble, you back me up.
-MAN: Oh, Jack!
I got something for you.
Mr. Thunder?
Look, maybe we started off
on the wrong foot.
Huh.
Listen, I know this
can't be easy for you.
It's not for me.
I had to show up on your doorstep
after so many years
-and I got so many questions and...
-I can go to four.
Excuse me?
I can go to 400,
but that's it.
-See, it's mainly Demon that I want.
-This is not about the dogs!
MAN: Look, Jack!
Got in your new shipment
of blue cheese.
Oh! Danish, right?
Oh, yeah.
Nothing crumbles like Danish.
I never seen a man who could eat
as much Cheese as you do.
They ought to call you
Monterrey Jack.
Nobody can eat as much cheese
as I can.
Hey. Hey, no, hey.
-Mm...
-Hey, give me that Cheese.
I'll show you eating cheese!
Give me that Cheese.
Come on, give me that cheese
or somebody's going to get hurt.
All right.
Let's get down to business.
You are not equipped
to keep those dogs.
They're not city dogs.
They're athletes.
They have to run,
they have to get
those hearts pounding
othenNise, they go loco.
Loco?
So...
Show me how to run them.
-Yeah, we could teach each other.
I need to learn to mush,
and you need to learn to floss.
Come on, Jack.
-We need a father-and-son activity.
Father and what?
Sure!
Can't you see the resemblance?
Oh, yeah.
Yoo-hoo... Demon.
Ha... Oh!
You want a piece of me?
Huh? You want some of that?
What? What's my name?
You want a piece of me?
Come get it!
Come get it.
This was not a good idea!
Oh!
Who's the alpha dog now?
-Whoa!
Okay. "Place your feet on runners
keeping your weight centered."
Blah, blah, blah, all right.
Okay, just like a jet-ski with fur.
Hey!
Stop that. Hey!
Hey, knock it off.
Stop it.
Hey, how are you going to pull
if you're this way?
You got to look that...
Come on, buddy.
-BARB: Hey.
-Hi.
I thought we could go
for a picnic up on the mountain.
Sorry. Can't.
I'm mushing today.
See you.
You now, it's not something
you just learn overnight.
Hey, it's in my blood.
First off...
You have to step on the gang line
before you cross over.
-All right.
Okay, this is all wrong.
You have Mack next to Scoop.
That's a definite no-no.
Mack always runs best
when he's next to Diesel.
-Okay.
I know what your problem is.
Can you hold that?
Yeah. Hi, sweetie.
All right, that's good.
And Yodel and Sniff over there
are fine where you got them.
They're your wheel dogs.
They're not exactly
the sharpest tools in the shed
but they'll push or pull
anything you give them.
-Look! Twins. All right.
-Okay.
-What do we do with this guy?
-Girl. This is Duchess.
Scoop over there has got
the biggest crush on her.
The only way
to calm him down is to...
Put him with Duchess!
Good girl.
You two make a lovely couple.
Okay, and that just leaves
my evil half-brother, Demon.
-Oh.
No, he's an incredible animal.
-He was Lucy's pride.
-Yeah, with a lousy personality.
Nice doggy.
-Nice doggy, nice...
Maybe you should try
biting him on the ear.
What is it
with you people?
I'm cool. You cool?
-Sorry, Nana.
but, uh, big doggies only.
TED: Okay. Alright. Oh, just got
to program my GPS here.
Oh, well. I got
a great sense of direction.
Okay!
Ready, set, move!
Well, at least I don't have to worry
about you getting lost.
Let's see you try
to throw me this time.
No! No! Oh, stop!
Hey, Teddy!
-Want to drag?
TED: Oh! Ooh! Bad dog! Bad dog!
-Fore!
-Huh?
Whoa!
Sorry about that.
You know,
I never would have thought of it.
Thunder Jack. Wow!
Oh, I'm glad everybody's
having a great big laugh.
They are. The way you drive
that sled of yours.
That‘s pretty funny.
Whoa.
Hm.
Mush! Mush!
Nice day for a drive, huh, Nana?
Hi. Eat your heart out.
Oh.
Nana,
I finally understand sledding.
Hmm. What got into her?
No. Oh, no. No.
My eyes! My eyes!
Ah, no. Oh!
Ooh.
Oh, got yourself a skunk, huh?
Good eating.
You know, you're getting to be
an embarrassment to me.
Why didn't you just
tell them to stop?
Don't talk to me like I'm four.
You're not the boss of me.
Of course I shouted, "stop".
They wouldn't stop
if you shout, "stop".
You have to shout,
"break and hook".
Break and hook. Got it.
I want to go, I say mush.
Only in the movies
do they say mush.
Here you say, "hike".
If you want to go to the left,
you shout, “haw".
And if you want to go to the right,
you shout, "gee".
Why not just say right and left?
Why do they got to make things
so complicated?
Whew! Man, you really stink.
Whew!
What's that?
Don't worry, mountain man.
It'sjust me.
What are you doing here?
I thought it'd be nice
to walk the hill.
And it would be nicer
if you give me a ride back down.
Sure.
This is where l was going
to take you for that picnic.
-How did you know about it?
-I found Lucy's diary.
"It's quiet and perfect.
The one place | feel peaceful...
and can think
about the big questions."
This is the place all the folks
around here come for answers.
Oh, nothing but time
and places to think around here.
Great places, sure,
but, uh, no Starbucks.
No indoor plumbing.
Oh, yeah? You know what else
they don't have in this town?
Crime, traffic,
buses to put your face on.
If I could just get that old man
to sit down with me for an hour.
Just to find out
what happened.
It isn't like I want
anything from him.
I don't need a father.
I had a father and he's nothing
like my father was.
My dad was a great person.
Everyone looked up to him.
And your mom?
My mom?
She's amazing.
She does everything for me.
For everybody.
And her sugar cookies.
Oh! You haven't lived
till you had one
of my mom's sugar cookies.
Yeah, I miss her.
Maybe the answers for me
aren't even up here at all.
are hopping on the next plane
back to civilization.
You know, the thing about Lucy,
is she didn't always win the race...
but she never quit.
Maybe you need to finish
what you started, Mountain man.
Oh, that's cool.
-That's scary.
-You are such a city boy.
So...
how did you sleep?
-Oh. Oh.
That's beautiful. Oh, wow!
-Let's go!
Whoo-hoo!
Run, dogs, run!
Woohoo!
Oh. Oh. Oh, oh.
Oh, what are the words?
Duck and cover! Uh!
Cap and gown!
Stop!
-Oh!
Blink and hook.
Oh, stupid dogs.
I hate dogs. I hate 'em.
-I hate 'em. I hate 'em, I hate 'em.
Oh!
Oh, my goodness gracious!
-Hey, wait, let's all be cool.
Yeah, now, if we all stay calm,
there'll be no problems here today.
You know, I'm a big bear fan.
Sure. Uh, my man,
Smoky the bear. Yogi.
Uh, Walter Payton.
I can see the headlines:
"Miami dentist eaten by bear."
I'm alive!
-I'm alive!
I'm dead. I'm dead!
Mama!
Oh, help me, Lord!
This is insane!
I'm okay.
Got to get help.
-Got to get help.
Move it, keep moving.
Uh-oh.
Oh. 9-1-1.
OPERATOR: You are outside
your coverage area.
Should you like to expand
your service plan
please call back during
our business hours.
This is a recording.
Cold.
Ted, my main man,
you really stepped in it this time.
We tried to tell you
you didn't belong here.
I don't speak dog.
Tell me about it.
I like him.
Oh, sure, you'll roll over for anyone
who'll pour you a bowl of slump.
Hmph.
Scooper, you kill me.
AMELIA: Teddy.
-I made you a special treat.
-Mama?
It's your favorite.
Blue cheese cookies.
Ted, remember,
no matter what color you are
you can still have soul.
I mean, look at me.
Can I have one of those
blue cheese cookies, please?
Yeah.
BARB: Hey, city boy.
You've got to learn to relax.
Just sit back and listen
to the sounds of nature.
Relax.
Relax. Relax.
Where am I?
My, my, my.
Sleeping beauty's finally awake.
-Where are Lucy's dogs?
-They're back home where they belong.
I saw them coming
through town without you
so I figured that, uh...
What do you think you were doing
coming all the way out here?
l was mushing.
You should have seen me.
You silly greenhorn.
You could have been killed.
Don‘t you know that?
Well, if you would have told me
what I wanted to know,
I wouldn't be out here
in the first place.
Oh.
Ain't nothing to talk about.
-|t's not nothing.
-|t's nothing.
It's not nothing.
-|t's not nothing.
-Ted.
-What?
I'll make you a deal.
| tell you what I know,
I get the dogs?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Well...
It all happened
right here in this cave.
It was my second race.
l was out about three days
and this storm blew in.
And I should've, you know,
bunked down...
but I kept going,
thinking I could sneak up
a couple of spots, you know?
That's when it turned ugly.
The only thing that saved me
was finding this cave.
And Lucy was already here,
hunkered down with her dogs.
Now, I'd met her
a couple of times in town
but we weren't what you'd call
friends, you know?
But cold weather brings
people together in a strange way.
Well, you can guess the rest.
When I woke up in the morning,
Lucy and the dogs were already gone.
She finished ninth, that year.
I came in 19th.
After the race, I...
I tried to find her...
but she'd already gone.
That's it?
Afraid so. It's all I know.
Well, a bargain's a bargain.
I guess the dogs are yours.
Oh, well,
I'll take good care of them.
I guess I'd better be
getting on home.
Here you go.
Here, have some soup.
I thought you said this was soup!
Well, there's soup in it.
Kid, come on. I want to get airborne
before the winds pick up.
GEORGE: Final boarding call.
Hi, Chester.
Hi, buddy.
WOMAN: For the mushers and their dogs
nothing can match this moment.
We're here at the starting
line awaiting the signal
to begin the 112th
Arctic Challenge sled dog races.
And we'll be here bringing you
a bird's eye view of all
the color and excitement.
Back to you, Pete.
My people, I love you.
Will you look at that?
Now, Demon, look at me.
My hands are shot.
This is going to be
my last go around.
And probably yours, too.
So, what do you say,
we just give them something
to remember us by, huh?
Ah, that's my boy.
ANNOUNCER: There he goes
the Michael Jordan of dog sledding,
Olivier Trajean.
AMELIA: Teddy?
Oh, my Lord,
it's freezing in here!
You see that dog out front?
That‘s the lead dog.
Those two in back,
they're the wheel dogs
but it's the lead dog that
drives the team.
ANNOUNCER: He's ﬁnished dead last
three years in a row
and he believes...
-Why am | a dentist?
-You always wanted to be a dentist.
Except for that one year
you wanted to be
the Six Million Dollar Man.
You were always running
in slow motion.
We had to take ten extra
minutes just to get anywhere.
Oh, Teddy.
IS this Tolketna?
-Who's this?
-Oh, that's Barb.
She's just a friend.
Mm-hmm.
So this is...
She's pretty.
She looks just like you.
Oh, Teddy, I'm so sorry.
-|'|| get it cleaned up right now.
-Don't bother, I'll get a broom.
So, is this the father?
Who?
This white man with her and the baby.
Oh, look how cute you are, Teddy.
He lied to me.
Hello? Yes, I need your next flight
to Alaska.
REPORTER: A test of speed
and agility today,
at the Arctic challenge.
Here at the ﬁnish line,
the weather is ﬁne
but out on the course,
a massive Arctic storm
is blowing in tonight.
The lead teams are bunking
at the rusty knife checkpoint
hoping that morning
will bring relief.
Hey, girl. Good girl.
-How they look?
-Feet look good.
-Oh!
Old Demon never changes,
huh, Jack?
Been kind of ornery
ever since Victoria passed.
What kind of a man eats
before he feeds his dogs?
Don't worry, they already docked him
20 minutes for that one.
Uh, Jack, there's a storm
brewing out there.
Everybody's bunking in.
Come on.
I saved you a spot by the heater.
Yeah, thanks, Ernie.
-JACK: Hey!
Come on, Demon! Pick it up.
-Pick it up.
Pick it up, Demon.
-Whoa.
-Hey, hold up, there.
The old fool.
MAN OVER PA: Flight 1128 arriving
from Seattle and Miami at Gate B.
Hi.
George.
All right, let's go.
I got to find Jack.
Ted, there's something
you need to know.
Later. He lied to me.
Come on.
-Ted? Wait.
-What?
Jack's missing.
-GEORGE: He made the check-in
at Rusty Knife. Then the old fool headed
straight into a storm.
That's the last
anybody saw of him.
And the weather's gotten so bad
the rescue crews had to turn back.
I know where he is.
You think you know
where he is.
He could be anywhere
within a hundred square miles.
Come on.
BARB: You can't do this.
When I was lost,
he came looking for me.
I'm not going to let
him die out there.
-Ted, you don't even have a lead dog.
-Sure, I do.
There's my lead dog.
Hi, Nana.
-BARB: Nana?
-Nana's not a lead dog.
-Sure, she is.
If I can be a musher,
she can be a lead dog.
Atta girl, Nana.
Whoo!
Ted, please be careful.
-Ready up!
-Mush! Mush!
Get up there! Ha!
Ha! Mush!
Hey! Hey!
And it looks like our winner
is going to be, once again...
Hey!
Isn't that guy going the wrong way?
MAN: Hey, check out Ted.
-Go! Yeah, go!
Get up there!
-Olivier!
-Did you see him?
Whoo-hoo!
No more slump, boys!
It's milk bone for everyone!
Woo-hoo!
Olivier, you've won
the Arctic challenge.
-What are you going to do next?
-I'm going to Disneyland, Paris.
-O|ivier!
-Look what you've done.
We must run away.
I am so sorry
but all I've got is
American money.
Paging Dr. Te... Whoa!
-Here, let me help you.
Oh, thank you.
-You must be Ted's mother.
-Well, you must be Barb.
So, what did he tell you about me?
-He says you make amazing cookies.
-Oh!
Oh, that isjust like Ted.
He wouldn't say a bad thing
about anyone.
-Where is he?
That's it! That's it! Come on, guys.
Come on, come on.
Right, right, left, left,
right! Come on, come on!
Come on! Come on!
-Okay, okay.
Two-minute break.
Scooper,
what have you got now?
Sure, you can dig,
but you can't pull?
But wait a minute. Just wait.
Now, this is my son.
Aren't you supposed to send
a search party or a posse
or something?
Look, ma'am.
We're sorry, but there's simply
no way to go through the pass.
And it's too windy
to send up a chopper.
-|'m sorry.
Excuse me.
I couldn't help overhearing.
-Did you say your son is out there?
-Mm-hmm.
REPORTER: To the men and women
of the Arctic Challenge,
the Arctic flame is a symbol of hope.
It can't be extinguished
until the last musher has found
his way out of the wilderness
and crossed the finish line.
This year, that flame flickers
for one man lost out on the trail
old-time sledding legend,
Thunder Jack Johnson.
But we've now learned
of a startling unofﬁcial
rescue effort that's unden/I/ay.
- Ted Brooks.
-Yeah!
Get this!
A dentist from Miami, Florida
is bravely facing the storm
with his own team of dogs.
You go, Ted.
REPORTER: Tonight, somewhere
in the darkness,
a story as old
as time itself unfolds
as man and animal work together,
braving the elements
in what has become not a race
of winners and losers
but simply a race for survival.
Whoa, whoa, brake it off.
Jack?
-Jack?
Easy, Demon, easy.
Jack?
Okay. Good job, boys.
Okay, good, good boy. Good dog.
All right, good boy.
Good job.
Oh, Jack. Jack.
Jack.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Your leg's broke.
I'm splinting it.
Yeah. Well, how'd you get here?
Same way you did.
-Not bad for a greenhorn. huh?
Not bad at all.
So, what kind of crazy stunt
were you trying to pull out there?
Oh, I thought I could win
if I rode off into that storm.
But if I'd bunked in
like I should've,
I wouldn't have run into that tree,
and...
What...
-Ah-ah-ah!
It's the latest
in personal Climate control.
I guess I ought to thank you
for coming after me.
Because you didn't...
You didn't have to, you know.
It's payback.
Now we're even.
No, we're not even.
You know, I've always believed
that a man who don't tell it
like it is, is a liar.
And I hate liars.
Well, I lied to you, son.
l was at that hospital.
The night you were born...
Well, you were no bigger
than a loaf of bread.
I walked into that room,
and the doctorjust
placed you right in my hands,
just like that.
And in all my life,
I'd never seen anything like it.
But me and Lucy knew that we,
we had no business
trying to raise you.
You know, we were no good
for each other and we...
We race dogs.
But, uh, kids...
But Lucy...
wanted to bring you into this world.
But she knew that it would be better
if somebody else raised you.
So, now, you can't blame
everything on Lucy.
l was nowhere near ready
to be a father.
See...
we were independent spirits,
Lucy and me.
Oh, we'd see each other
from time to time and,
you know...
But I did love her.
Oh... Oh, I loved that woman.
I miss her.
Did she love you?
Well, she said so once.
And then she poked me
right in the face.
Yeah, but you turned out okay.
Look...
I bet Lucy would be proud of you.
I know I am.
Mrs. Brooks...
why don't you come inside?
They'll sound off the siren
when one of them comes in.
I'm not going to leave him.
I can't.
TED: All right, guys, let's go.
-Come on, let's go.
Okay, Demon,
let's get that harness on.
Oh, that dog's
not going anywhere.
Well, what's wrong with him?
He's, uh, gnawing at his harness,
won't eat.
He's just one unhappy dog.
Gnawing at his harness, huh?
Yeah.
All right, Demon, let's take
a look at your Chompers.
Oh!
-Okay, Demon.
-You leave me no choice.
Good, good boy.
Come.
I can't believe you actually
bit that dog on the ear.
But that's what everyone says
you're supposed to do.
Well, sure, but...
I never met a man dumb enough
to do it.
Okay.
Okay. All right.
Good boy. Open wide.
There we go.
Let's see what you got there.
-Here's the problem.
Oh, okay, all right.
All right, Demon.
Trust me,
I'm not going to hurt you.
Okay?
My, my, my.
Well, if you want to bite me now,
go ahead.
Mush!
There's a medic down
at Caribou Falls.
What do you want to do?
l have never not finished a race.
Well, I'm not going
to let you start now.
Hah!
Go ahead, Demon!
-Teddy, I'm slipping out. Whoa!
-Hang on, Jack! Hang on.
-Oh. Oh, yeah.
-Demon, get it, baby!
-Way to go, Demon!
Barb, l have a confession to make.
Are you Barb?
I never told Ted he was adopted.
I know.
There were so many times
when I could have told him.
It would have been
the right thing to do.
I know that now.
But from the first moment
I held him in my arms...
I couldn't have loved him more.
But I was afraid.
l was afraid if I told him the truth,
he wouldn't love us.
Not in the same way.
AMELIA: Barb, tell me he's going
to cross that finish line.
He's going to cross
the finish line.
Amelia, he's going to cross
Oh, I know, dear.
It's just a mother's worry.
-I keep thinking...
-|t's the siren. He's coming in.
That's it!
-MAN: Let's go!
-What's going on?
Oh...
Yeah!
-Oh, Barb!
Oh. Oh, wait!
Get me a close-up.
Oh, wow!
Let me help you, Jack.
Not bad for a dentist
from Miami, huh?
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Ted! Ted!
Let me through, please.
Ted!
You're here.
You came all the way here to Alaska.
I got on a plane and 14 hours
of prayer later, here I am.
Come here.
There's someone I want you to meet.
Jack... This...
This here's my mama.
Oh, baby. Oh, baby.
JACK: Well, it, uh...
It certainly is a pleasure
to meet you, ma'am.
You and your husband...
certainly did a fine job
with this guy.
Oh, Barb.
TED: He's an amazing guy.
He really is.
I'm so happy for you.
Barb, I...
Dr. Brooks,
the honor is yours.
Jack, I believe you earned this.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think we both should
blow it out together.
Okay, Ernie.
Dr. Brooks is ready
to see you now.
I haven't finished
reading about the crown
and the bridge yet.
-Come on.
-Oh, well...
Oh, here they are.
Avalanche. Little Aleutia.
And there's Chinook.
And my favorite, Demon Junior.
Good to see you, Ernie.
-Doctor, is this going to hurt?
-Oh, just a little.
More than a tickle
and less than paying your taxes.
Okay, open wide.