Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius (2001) (1CD Subtitle - 23,976fps - English)
you better have a look at this, sir.
- Commercial flight. - No. Too fast, sir.
- One of our own?. - Air Force has nothing scheduled.
We've got ourselves a bogie.
Orange Leader to Delta Group. Anticipate visual contact...
now.
Holy cow pie!.
Hi! Nice antiques.
Gotta blast!
Fusion mix stable, engine cycling at one million giga joules.
Cool! We didn't blow up.
Great! Jimmy, I think they want us to pull over.
Nope. No time for that, Carl. Stand by with the satellite.
Okay. What do I do again?.
you're the deployment system, Carl.
As soon as we clear the atmosphere, you just throw it.
- Right. - Prepare to leave the atmosphere!
Sorry about the toast, dear. I had to make it in the oven.
- I can't find our toaster anywhere. - Oh, looky!
Well, this oven toast is brilliant, sugar booger.
And your yolks are absolutely perfect too.
Oh, run away with me, my love.
We'll take my car. your transmission needs a new compression cuff.
Whatever. Ooh, this is a good one. Quack, quack.
Would you try calling Jimmy?. He's going to miss the bus again.
Jimmy! Breakfast! Time to come down!
Down. down. down. down. down. quackk Down. down. down. down. down. quackk
Up, up, up!
Engaging pulse rockets now!
- No! - Now?.
Is this supposed to happen?.
Come on. think. think. think!
Brain blast!
Give me your lunch!
Thanks, boy.
Don't try that at home.
Must engage stabilizers!
Now just a quick stop at my house.
I don't know, Jimmy. I gotta get to school on time. Besides, you pro--
- Right. Gotcha. - I didn't mean--
See you in homeroom!
Fasten your seat belt, Goddard. It's gonna be a bumpy ride!
Well, what do you know. The chimney fell off again.
That wasn't so bad, huh?.
James Isaac Neutron!
I see you up there.
How many times have we told you not to launch yourself off the roof?.
Probably nine. Exactly nine.
They say repetition is good for a developing brain.
Then just what do you think you’re doing?.
I received a message from space but it was garbled in the ionosphere...
so I had to launch a communications toaster-- I mean satellite.
Well, message from space?. Wow!
Don't encourage him, Hugh.
Jimmy, we've repeatedly told you not to talk to strangers.
Mom, I'm on the verge of contact with an advanced alien civilization.
I don't care how advanced they say they are, Jimmy.
If your father and I haven't met them, they're strangers, right?.
Well, except for policemen. They're there to help you.
Oh, you gotta admit that is pretty neat!
But very unsafe, honey. That's bad.
Deactivate pants!
Engage Gingivitis 2000.
Robo-Barber prototype, engage!
On-line.
Ta-da.
You rock.
You go. girl.
Shoe-bot!
- Oh. - Sorry.
Bye, Goddard!
- Wait! I'm here! - Good-bye, son! Have a good day!
Oh, Goddard! Not on the porch!
Hey! Hey, wait!
Seems like the perfect opportunity to try out the bubble gum mobile!
No, Jimmy, don't try it! It's too soon.
Nonsense! All great inventions need a test run.
All right!
- Right here! - Look! Neutron's got another one.
Nice invention, Nerdtron.
Too bad somebody already invented the bus.
Hey, guys! I've got it down this time.
Internal combustion is such old science.
Bubble travel is the way of the future!
I guess trees are, like, the brakes?.
Hello. Jimmy!
Oh, Carl.
Careful! Careful!
Thanks.
That's what I'm here for.
- What a day, huh?. - Look at the bright side, Carl:
The worst is behind us.
And my fossil-to-chromosome ratios clearly demonstrate...
that female dinosaurs, like this plesiosaurus...
were the stronger and smarter of their species.
But, so, what else is new?.
After class, I'll be happy to demonstrate how boy dinosaurs...
got their butts kicked by girl dinosaurs on a regular basis.
Excuse me, but the mandible crest of Cindy's alleged plesiosaur...
is actually that of a male megalosaur...
as defined by last week's World Congress of Palaeontologists.
Those findings were inconclusive, and you know it, Neutron!
Miss Fowl, what is the standard for research...
on these extra-credit reports?.
Um, yes, well, um--
Let's move along to show-and-tell now, shall we?.
This is Ultra Lord!
Sheen...
this is the seventh week in a row you've shown Ultra Lord in class.
Miss Fowl, this one is different.
This Purple Vengeance version with power fists and nuclear knees...
is in rare, never-been-seen condition...
making it highly collectible.
Never-been-seen, huh?. Then how do you know it's even in there?.
Hey, Jimmy. Wanna see a frog?.
That looks great!
Thanks. What are you drawing?.
FlyCycle modifications for Goddard, second prototype.
Prototype, huh?.
Oh, well, you know, that looks good too.
- Thanks, Carl. - Carl!
Would you please share with us your show-and-tell?.
Oh, okay.
This is my inhaler.
It provides fast-acting relief of bronchial swelling...
due to asthma or allergies.
One touch of the button, and--
I can't see!
Thank you, Carl.
All right, next we have--
Nick!
yes, Nick.
you are a tad tardy again!
Oh, my. Am I?.
It took me a while to copy my mom's handwriting for this late note.
your show-and-tell, please.
How's it going'?. you know, I don't really do show-and-tell.
Oh, oh, yes. That's right.
Thank you, Nick.
Did you drop this?.
yes, well, I, um-- My-- drop-- pencil.
We eagerly await another one of your...
interesting show-and-tells.
As a matter of fact, I brought my latest invention.
Behold the shrink ray!
What's the matter, Neutron-- aren't you short enough already?.
Funny, Cindy.
But this device is more suited to shrink something...
as vast as space itself like, say, your mouth.
Help me! Help me! I'm so tiny!
Just like Jimmy's brain!
So much for the Nobel Prize!
- Children, that's enough! - Better luck next time!
It worked this morning.
I like your useless shrink ray, Jimmy.
It's probably just
Oh, my!
Back, back, leviathan!
Come on, Jimmy. Some of the greatest inventors of all time...
started as complete, hopeless failures too.
Well, thank you, Carl. I feel better, I think.
- I'm glad. - That's good. Hey!
RetroLand Theme Park! Check it out!
Meet UltraLord live!
Look! It's the state-of-the-art, bone-warping gravity ride!
- I could hang out with UltraLord! - And there's a petting zoo!
- Well, look at this! - No! Meet UltraLord live!
Llamas and capybaras.
- Who cares?. Meet UltraLord live! - But I'm gonna touch a llama!
Guys, we have got to go to the grand opening tonight.
yeah!
yeah.
But my folks won't let me stay out after dark.
Well, it is a school night.
Pukin' Pluto, there's gotta be something we can do.
It's the grand opening!
- Sneak out. - What?.
you heard me, dweebs. Sneak out.
Well, yeah, but my parents sorta told me--
Parents?. What-- are you guys gonna be kids forever?.
What your parents don't know won't hurt 'em, right?.
But Nick, sneaking out is so, so barbaric!
Whatever, Neutron. But there's only one opening night...
and anybody who matters is gonna be there.
What do you think, Jimmy?.
Nick has a point. There is only one opening night.
Think, think, think.
Well, according to the Newville Journal of Medicine...
monkeys are easily influenced by positive reinforcement...
e.g., the giving of a banana.
And, since human and monkey DNA only differ by two percent...
the same principle should work on our parents.
My dad's allergic to bananas.
Oh, it's not the bananas, it's the principle!
It's called psychology. All you have to do is butter 'em up.
Give it a try. I'll call you guys later.
We go to RetroLand tonight!
Look out!
Slow down!
I know!
Excuse me! you through with that?. Thanks!
A few oysters.
One lump of coal coming up!
- Thanks, Gus! - Hi, Jimmy!
Excuse me!
Jimmy, is that you, dear?.
yeah, Mom! I'll be in, in a second!
DNA match confirmed. Welcome home. Jimmy.
Eliminate school smell.
Normal odour restored.
- Thank you, Vox. - You're welcome.
Warning. Entry tube closed for maintenance.
Here, Goddard. Here, boy!
Here, Goddard!
Hey, look what I brought ya-- aluminium!
Do you want it?. Do you want it, huh?.
Sit!
Roll over!
Play dead!
Mental note: Fix bug in obedience program.
Good boy!
Okay, Goddard, let's check the experiments.
The invisible hamsters are looking great.
I think.
Let's see how the girl-eating plant is doing.
Nice choice...
as usual.
The latest burping soda formula.
A guaranteed one burp per sip.
Excuse you.
There's still no reply to our satellite message.
Jeez, it's been a whole day.
you'd think we would have heard from an alien civilization by now, huh?.
Oh, well. Come on, Goddard.
Say ahh.
Add a little sand...
and in ya go!
I’m just an old lump of coal
But I'm gonna be a diamond some day Oh. yeah
Jimmy!
Hi, Mom!
Jimmy, you scared the bejeebers out of me!
Oh, sorry about your bejeebers, Mom.
- Might I add how lovely you look?. - I'm covered in transmission fluid.
Exactly! And might I say filth never looked so good?.
yes, well, how was show-and-tell today?.
It was okay. But first, happy birthday, Mom!
Jimmy, these are beautiful!
But, sweetie, it's not my birthday.
Oh, it's not?. Then whatever will I do...
with these lovely pearls and priceless earrings?.
These can't be real!
Oh, but they can, and they are!
And all these fabulous gifts and prizes could be yours...
if you know the correct answer to this question:
Please may I go to RetroLand tonight?.
- No, it's a school night. - Thank you and might I say--
- Did you just say no?. - yes.
- yes! - No.
- No?. - yes.
- yes! -Jimmy--
But-But-- all my friends are going...
and anybody who matters is going to be there, Mom!
I matter, and your father matters, and you matter.
But you're not going. Maybe we can go next weekend.
Wait. There must be something else in here to change your mind.
No, Jimmy, no! Look out! Look out, Jimmy! No!
Jimmy, be careful!
Mom, get me out! I'm starting to get a little--
I didn't do it!
Stop, drop and roll!
Goddard!
Okay, Jimmy. That's the last straw.
We have told you time and time again about playing with rockets.
But, Mom, it's technically not a rocket.
It's more of a jet-pack-type thing.
I don't care what type thing it is.
you just climb those stair-type things right now.
your father will have a few words to say to you when he gets home.
- It's not a rocket. - March!
yes!
The kingy loves his little orthgot. yes, he does.
yes, he does. yes, he does.
yes, he does.
Sire. My king. It appears to be some type of alien transmission device.
Tell me, when did it become acceptable...
to approach my royal throne unannounced?.
- Oh, yes, of course, my king-- - Space him!
Oh, wait!
Whoa!
Ooh! Oh, I missed it.
Can I-- Can I space another?.
- Oh, please, brother?. - I said no, Ooblar.
Oh, please, oh, please.
I would love for that to stop.
Oh, please!
What have we here?.
As the king's royal assistant...
I am the official checker of the new things to be checked.
It's all right! It's all right. I'll handle this.
Hello!
What galaxy are you from?.
- Ooblar. - Where is your leader?.
Ooblar, stop it. It's toast.
Hello, Toast!
I greatly admire your ship!
Beginning transmission from Earth.
Greetings from planet Earth.
I'm Jimmy Neutron. and you’re an alien life-form.
- Oh, what a bi g head. - I welcome...
the exchange of scientific knowledge and universal brotherhood.
This here is my dog. Goddard.
And this that you're looking at is my room. That's where I sleep.
And this is my mom and dad right here-- mom. dad.
Freeze that image!
They look delicious!
The search is over!
Dad, all my friends will be there!
I know, son.
But if all your friends were named Cliff, would you jump off them?.
I don't think you would. you see, Jimmy--
Jimmy. Jim, Jim, Jimmy. Jim, James. Son...
let me tell you a little about rockets.
Oh, they're big-people things, son.
And you just can't go around playing with big-people...
fiery, flying things.
Because that's what rockets are. Rockets are flying things.
Well, I hope this talk has helped.
Oh, and by the way, Mom says you're grounded. Sorry!
Oh! What good is it to be a genius...
if you can't even go out on a school night?.
Goddard, options.
Apologize. Your parents love you.
Next.
Create a time capsule. Escape to the future.
Oh. Take too long. Next.
Build Goddard a female poodle.
Goddard, this is serious!
Sneak out.
That's it! Barbaric problems call for barbaric solutions.
Phone, please.
Carl?. It's me.
you get permission?. Me neither.
It turns out parents don't understand psychology.
Tell Sheen to meet us at RetroLand in one hour.
We're sneakin' out.
Hold it right there!
- Flurp! - Take that!
Jimmy's awfully quiet up there. Do you think we were too tough?.
Oh, I don't think so, dear, no.
- Maybe I should check on him. - Oh, now, now.
I'm sure he's just reflecting on the error of his ways...
dealing with it in a mature, responsible manner.
Mom says you're grounded. Take that!
It's working now.
Okay, Goddard. you know what to do.
Good boy!
See ya later, Goddard!
Mmm! Jimmy's a big boy now.
- Don't you worry. - Oh, I suppose you're right.
yeah, sure. Look, I was a kid once. I remember being grounded a week...
and not being allowed to go to my best friend's bachelor party.
- What did you do?. - Actually, I snuck out.
you don't think that Jimmy--
Oh, no, no. Besides, how's he gonna sneak out?.
It's not like he can just walk right out the front door.
That's true.
RetroLand, here I come.
Libby, you're breaking my concentration.
Hey, I gotta choose a ring that fits my personality.
yeah, here we go! Here we go!
Tell me what it is you're supposed to be doing again?.
Tai Chi while drinking Purple Flurp.
Tai Chi promotes wellness, relaxes...
and rejuvenates the body, whereas Purple Flurp...
being 98% sugar, creates tension...
a temporary rush of energy and mood swings.
I figure if I do them together...
I achieve perfect balance.
Wow. It's better than the poster!
Gentlemen, this will be a night we shan't easily forget.
I don't know what shan't means, but let's go!
Do you promise to use your powers for good and not evil?.
yes, UltraLord.
Now, counterpart, take this UltraMask...
- I will! Give it to me! - and lead the fight for justice!
Is this kid with anyone?.
Go, Carl!
Wow! Now, that's what I call a ride!
Let's go!
This is way beyond awesome!
Just think: If you boneheaded dweebs had listened to your parents...
you'd be home in bed, instead of riding this monster.
Oh, man, this is great!
- I tell you, he's fine. - Just a quick peek, Hugh.
There. Now, what'd I tell you?.
- Jimmy, are you awake, dear?. - yes, Mother, I am awake.
Son, your mother and I just wanted to say good night.
yes, and to tell you that we love you.
Oh, honey, I know you're upset.
We don't like to punish you. you're such a special boy.
This says we should encourage Jimmy without overindulging him.
Okay. What does it say about rockets?.
Is there someone in the kitchen?.
Our kitchen?. I didn't hear anything.
Honey, did you leave the green light on?.
Jimmy?.
you're not Jimmy!
Hugh, are you all right?.
Was that so cool?.
- That was great. - Mind-bending!
yeah! Hey, my pants are almost dry.
Hey, Jimmy, I never thought I'd say it, but here goes:
you know what?. That Nick is not such a bad guy.
Are you kidding?. He's a genius!
- He's a genius! - No offence, Jimmy.
None taken!
Actually, his insights on dealing with parents are quite refreshing.
Wouldn't it be great if our folks all disappeared for a while?.
Oh, yeah. Oh, hey, a shooting star!
Cool! you get to make a wish. Lucky.
What should I wish for?.
I know what I'd wish for. I'd wish for no more parents.
That way, we could do whatever we wanted, whenever we wanted.
We'd be free! We could have fun all the time!
yeah!
Lift off in five. four. three. two--
We have lift off!
Abort mission. Abort mission!
Goddard, wake mode.
All right, come on, boy. Race ya to the kitchen!
Beat ya!
Hey, Mom, did you get any more Purple Flurp?.
Mom?.
Dear son/daughter--
We've gone to Florida for an extended vacation.
Love. your parents.
yeah. My parents went to Florida too.
That's weird.
From the look of it...
I'd say a lot of parents are gone.
- Did they all go to Florida?. - Maybe they went to get juice.
I don't digest pulp well. It makes me bloaty.
Goddard, scan for adult life-forms.
Just as I thought. There are no adults anywhere within radar.
They're gone. The whole city!
No parents.
No parents!
Excuse me!
I'm letting out the cold!
I'm peeing in the shower!
Llama, llama, llama!
I'm walking up the down escalator!
My clothes don't match. I'm out in public and my clothes don't match
I'm still doin' it! Go, go, go!
Welcome to the Candy Bar. Whoopee cushion or non-whoopee cushion?.
What'll it be, boys?.
We'll have what he's throwing.
Excellent choice!
Hang on!
No skiing in the halls!
Don't make me get the protractor!
Morning, Goddard. Oh, my head. What a night!
Oh, I'm stuffed now. I-I couldn't have anoth--
Okay, one more.
I'm gonna have one more, and then that'll be it.
What a battle. Are there any survivors?. Help me!
I remember my first time.
Shake it off, Neutron!
I gotta get home. Mom and Dad might be back by now.
Come on, Goddard.
We interrupt this program to bring you this special report.
Hey. knock it off. Arnie!
Trouble in paradise.
That's what some kids are saying in the aftermath of yesterday’s...
Mom and Dad are gone  celebrations.
Here's Courtney Tyler.
What started as an awesome day has become. like. a real bummer.
- Help us! - I don 't know how to make lunch!
Somebody hold me!
I was playing on the teeter-totter...
and the next thing I knew I was on the ground...
and my knee hurt!
Reports of tummy aches. owies and constipation...
have reached epidemic numbers over the past few hours...
with little indication of slowing down.
And so we were gonna see who could eat the most cotton candy...
and I won!
I want my mommy!
So. there you have it.
I want my mommy too!
Mom?. Dad?.
What kind of parents take off and leave their kid?.
And they didn't even say good-bye!
Son. your mother and I just wanted to say good night.
Yes. and to tell you that we love you.
We only do what we do because we love you.
Maybe we can all go to RetroLand next weekend. the three of us.
What about my fabulous dog. Goddard?
Sure. your fabulous dog. Goddard. too.
Well. good night. son.
Good night. Jimmy. Sweet dreams. We'll see you in the morning.
Okay, so they said good night.
In the morning?. Hey, wait a minute!
Play back the last part again, audio only.
Good night. Jimmy. Sweet dreams. We'll see you in the morning.
There! Why would she say that if they weren't gonna be here?.
Come on, Goddard. We're goin' to the lab.
It's just as I thought.
The serifs and kerning on this note...
don't match Mom and Dad's handwriting.
This note's a fake!
What is it, boy?.
The long-range space scanner-- it detected something!
Filtering out background radiation, and there it is!
Jumpin'Jupiter! The Earth's been visited by aliens!
Okay, so me, you and a dog...
are gonna battle an alien civilization, right, by ourselves?.
But he's a good dog. Aren't you, boy?.
The last time we tried this, Jim...
we couldn't even break free of the atmosphere.
I know. But I recalculated the thrust-to-fuel ratio...
and I've adjusted the engine accordingly.
- I can fix that. - Neutron!
- What is it?. - An angry mob!
In times of crises, intellectuals are always the first to go!
Well, they don't look angry.
They look like they're about to barf.
Let me go!
you are messing with powers beyond your mortal comprehension.
Okay, Neutron.
UltraFreak here says you really know what happened to all our parents.
Jimmy, how ya doin'?.
I didn't say nothing about our parents being abducted by aliens--
Where's my mom and dad?.
Tell us where they are!
Goddard, star map 72, please.
Right about there.
Sensors picked up ion trails indicating the departure route...
for whatever alien intelligence has abducted our parents.
They lead to the Orion star system three million light-years away.
So we'll need to leave by Friday.
Okay, that gives us about two days to collect the plutonium...
design and test our fusion engines and build our fleet of warships.
We'll also need to bring snacks. Any questions?.
Are you sure about this, Neutron?.
Well, the data seems to support this hypothesis.
Never argue with the data.
Okay, Neutron, here's the lowdown.
you get us to those kidnapping alien scuzballs...
and I'll take it from there.
We're getting our parents back.
Okay, Ben, that's good. Let it down slow.
Two more turns, Emma, not too tight.
yup. Tape adhesion is within operational limits.
Aw, what-- Cindy!
What did you do to that intergalactic starship?.
We thought that the deep recesses of space could use a feminine touch.
- What do you think, Jimmy?. - yeah, it's okay, I guess.
They kinda ruined it though.
Hey, Jimmy! Do these fusion reactors need fuel rods?.
Sheen, it's not rocket science. you just have to--
Actually, I guess it is rocket science.
- No fuel rods, Sheen! - Okay.
And for the final touch--
Good work, everybody.
We're ready for intergalactic travel.
-Neutron, this is gonna work, right?. -yeah, what if it doesn't work?.
It will work!
I'm 95% sure it will.
Ninety-five?. yeah?. And the other five percent?.
We blow up.
But just a little.
Look, a 95 is still an A.
yeah, I can deal with that. I never got a 95 in my life.
you heard the man. Stop suckin' your thumbs, and let's light this candle!
Goddard, initiate launch sequence.
Please make sure your seat belts are fastened...
and remember to keep hands and arms inside the vehicles at all times.
yeah!
Come on, everybody. Get in formation.
Carl, you're too low.
Come on, you stupid butterfly! Will you-- Whoa!
Go, counterparts, go!
Hang on. We're passing through the stratosphere.
Now the mesosphere.
Entering ionosphere.
Now I know why they all end in fear!
That's it, baby. Engaging pulse rockets now!
Come on, come on.
Look, Goddard, the wonders of the universe.
We're witnessing celestial events no person, or dog, has ever seen.
It's incredible!
Beautiful, isn't it, Nick?.
yeah, yeah. Wake me when we get there.
Hey, Jimmy!
Do you think we can rotate ships after a while?.
Hey, we'll switch!
Hey, this astronaut food isn't too bad.
That's toothpaste, Carl.
Oh. Minty.
Hey, what's happening?.
Meteor shower! Evasive action!
I do so relish these times of peril.
- That was close. - Look out!
We gotta find shelter!
Asteroid bearing two-thirty-six mark seven degrees.
Come on!
So these three filmmakers find all these sticks in the trees...
shaped like stick people...
and the girl filmmaker starts cryin'...
and her nose starts dripping, and they don't have any tissue at all.
None?.
None.
So then they start to hear...
really scary noises and voices coming from outside.
So they leave the tent.
Don't leave the tent! Don't leave the tent!
Oh, yeah, Carl, they leave the tent, and they follow the voices...
when from out of the darkness comes the--
That was so choice! you should have seen your faces.
Did they really leave the tent, Nick?.
There's a red giant! And that's a white dwarf!
you can relate, huh, Neutron?.
Hey, Jimmy, what's the matter?.
In case you haven't noticed, I'm not exactly the tallest guy around.
Shorty, squirt, small stuff, shrimp-- gets to you after a while.
And next year, there'll be dances.
Who wants to dance with a guy who looks like he should still be in Gymboree?.
I didn't think we liked girls yet.
Oh, we don't. No, not yet.
No. However, one day, Carl...
an influx of hormones that we can't control...
will overpower our better judgment...
and drive us to pursue the female species against our will.
Stop talking like that, Jimmy! you're gonna give me nightmares.
Listen, I wouldn't worry. Puberty is light-years away for you and me.
you know, we should've never wished on that star and...
I, I miss my folks.
My mom used to tuck me in bed every night...
before she was abducted by aliens.
Before my dad was abducted by aliens...
he would always read me to sleep.
And before my mom was inducted by aliens...
she would rub my tummy, and she'd sing--
- What?. - Nothing!
Come on, you guys. We gotta keep our heads.
We'll find 'em.
What is it, boy?.
Sensor sweeps reveal many advanced cities and ion energy signatures.
That's it!
We found it! I repeat, we found it!
Nick, we'll contact you as soon as we find the parents...
so you can kick some alien buttocks!
Piece of cake.
Okay, scouting party, follow me!
I'll be back, Nick!
Whoa, what is that?.
They've evolved beyond the need for mere conventional bodies.
They must be an advanced species millions of years ahead of us.
Wow! When I sneeze, it looks like an advanced species too.
Okay, they're this way.
Right this way, sire.
Ooblar, these humans look so scrawny.
Hardly very appetizing. Are you sure they're yummy?.
I assure you, my slimy sovereign, Poultra will be quite pleased.
Humans are mostly water, with a crunchy bony center.
Think nuts and chews.
- There they are. - What are they doing?.
What are those goofy-looking things on their heads?.
It looks like some kind of mind-control device.
Mom, Dad. Dad, it's me, Jimmy. Over here.
Jim, Jim, Jim, Jimmy’s, James, James, Jim.
Big fiery flying Jimmy. Hi, Jimmy.
Some dream, huh?. Attack of the Big Egg People.
- I think I've seen this one before. - No, Dad.
you're wearing a mind-control device. Take yours off. Hurry!
- Dad?. - Intruder alert! Intruder alert!
- Dad, no, no! No! - Intruder alert!
your dad's like a mind-controlled duck man.
Let's get outta here!
Come back! Join us, Jimmy!
Well, well!
If it isn't the littlest rescue party. How cute.
Hello, itty-bitty humans.
you let us go, you big ball of phlegm!
That's no way to talk to the king! He is the royal phlegm.
- Ooblar. - Sorry, sire.
It's only fair to warn you that if you don't release us in 24 hours...
an army of highly-trained combat specialists...
is poised to destroy your entire planet.
- Oh, really?. - Really.
Oh, my! Our entire planet! Whatever shall we do?.
Do you mean...
this army of highly-trained combat specialists?.
Hey, Nick!
Get your grubs off me, egghead!
Don't look so surprised. We're an advanced alien race.
- What did you expect?. - What do you want with our parents?.
It's not what I want. It's what Poultra wants.
- Who's Poultra?. - Poultra is our god...
the mightiest, most ferocious creature in all--
Oh, I get tired of answering this. Roll tape.
Hello and welcome to our special edition of Poultra: God of Wrath.
Brought to you by Goom--
Commercials! I hate them.
Welcome back.
If you’re watching this. chances are your friends and or relatives...
are about to be sacrificed to the mighty Poultra.
Which is a great honor indeed.
And very painful.
And this year’s human sacrifices feature something very special--
actual humans!
And it's all thanks to Jimmy Neutron.
Greetings from planet Earth!
I'm Jimmy Neutron. and you’re an alien life-form.
Without the coordinates you gave us...
we never would have found your puny little planet.
For such a tiny earthling, you've been a very big help, Jimmy Neutron.
Guards, throw these minuscule vermin into the dungeon...
until they're of worthier size.
And oh, give Mr. Neutron the presidential suite.
What?.
Ohh! Isn't this a funny-wunny little toy!
Get it off me!
Take this infernal thing to the lab and have it torn apart!
Oh, yes, great saliva-armed one.
Hold it! Move along.
- Goddard! - Move!
So, it was Neutron all along.
I mean, he got us into this.
Jimmy, didn't your parents ever tell you not to talk to strangers?.
That's rule number one.
Oh, come on, you guys! Give him a break.
Jimmy didn't mean to ruin our lives...
and get our parents eaten by a giant space monster!
She's right. We must ask ourselves, What would UltraLord do??'
Let's think about that, Sheen.
Maybe sit on a shelf, because he's a doll!
He's not a doll! He's an action figure! There's a difference.
Come on, Nick, let Sheen talk. Maybe he's onto something.
What would UltraLord do, Sheen?.
Well, in episode 224...
he fried the Zeebot's brain with his heat-seeking infra-thought.
It was cool!
Well, I'm convinced, folks.
That's pretty much the stupidest thing I've ever heard!
No, this is the stupidest thing you've ever heard!
- Oh, you're such a baby! - Why don't you leave me alone?.
you're picking on me because you're insecure!
Jimmy, you there?.
Look, don't listen to them. They're just scared.
Are you okay?.
yeah, I'm fine.
Don't be so hard on yourself. We'll get out of this.
Okay, so you made a mistake.
Beating yourself up isn't gonna fix anything.
you know, I was the smartest kid in school until you came along.
And I admit you know more about some things than I do.
But I know one thing that you don't seem to get...
and that's that we're never getting outta here without you.
So why don't you buck up, mister...
and put that big brain of yours back to work?.
Nick can handle the fighting stuff...
but first we have to get out of this cell.
Cindy?.
Why are you being so nice to me?.
'Cause there's a bunch of kids in here that need you...
and I do too.
I am never complaining about my parents again.
We didn't even get our one phone call.
That's it!
Libby, let me see your cell phone.
Okay, but I don't think my service plan...
covers anything outside our solar system.
- Who're you calling?. - A friend of mine.
All right, little Earth doggy.
Ooblar is going to take you apart into tiny little pieces.
All right?.
Hey! Give me that!
Fine! We'll use this one then.
No-no-no-no!
Would you stop that! Those are mine!
That's not funny. Stop it! And give me my thing!
Come on, boy, pick up.
Oh, good! Good. Perhaps we'll get somewhere.
Goddard, you're okay.
I miss you too, boy. Listen, what's your situation?.
Evil scientist, huh?.
Okay, I've got an idea. Put me on speaker, Goddard.
Danger! Danger!
You have initiated self-destruct sequence alpha.
That's my bad. Back in you go.
Self-destruct sequence is now engaged.
No-no-no! I put it back in. you understand me?.
This unit will yield a 50-megaton nuclear blast in ten seconds.
That's not good!
Please clear a 30-square mile area. Thank you. And have a nice day.
Ten. nine--
No! Bad dog! Mother!
Is he gone, boy?.
Great! Lock on to this signal and get here as fast as you can.
Halt! Who goes there?.
Oh, the guard!
By order of the most esteemed King Goobot...
it is my privilege and honor to mercilessly exterminate you.
Think, think. Goddard, play dead.
Good boy, Goddard, good boy!
Guess I'll make that bug a feature.
- Good dog, Goddard! - Way to go!
- Come on! Let's get the others! - Nice work, Jimmy.
Hey, Cindy, thanks.
If you ever tell anyone I was nice to you...
you'll wind up looking like that guy.
Let's go, Neutron! It's egg-scrambling time.
- Wait for me, Nick! - Come back!
Please?.
Bring out the humans!
It's show time.
Everybody out.
Kick it!
- Look, you guys, a football game! - I don't think so, Carl.
Goddard, binoscope mode!
What a lame halftime show.
They're making our parents dance so lame.
No, my dad really dances like that.
The festival is starting.
Our parents-- they'll be eaten!
Nobody eats my parents unless I say so! Come on!
Begin the incubation!
C'mon, Nick. Show them what you're made of!
Halt!
Hey, cool spear.
Oh, you really think so?. I guess so, because--
Mind if I try?.
No-no-no!
My hero!
Come on, everyone!
My hero?.
Okay, we need another plan.
Probably a Nick-less one.
Poultra! Poultra!
Citizens of yokus...
I, King Goobot V...
give you sacrifice!
That's a big chicken.
What do we do now?.
Think! Think!
Brain Blast!
Okay, everybody, listen up. We don't have much time.
I've got to make it to that control tower.
Cindy, Libby, keep the guards busy until Sheen arrives with the ship.
Okay, I heard the ship part, but was that, Sheen, get the ship?.
- yeah. - Ohh! Oh.
There's a transport ship big enough to carry us out of here.
I need you to get it here as fast as you can.
But I don't have a driver's license. I have no hand-eye coordination.
Ask yourself, what would UltraLord do?.
I accept this responsibility...
understanding the consequences you've bestowed against me.
Poultra, din-dins. yummy, yummy, foodie-woodie.
This is it, people. These crummy aliens stole our parents.
It's time to show them what we're made of.
We're tough, we're mean! Darn it, we're carbon-based life-forms!
Now, who's gonna kick buttocks?.
The carbonated  life-forms!
What?. What?. What is this?. Stop those kids!
After 'em!
Cindy, Purple Flurp!
Dragon whips her tail.
Let's dance!
yeah, Jimmy!
Come on, boy!
Jimmy!
Carl, show-and-tell!
Come here, you!
I can't see!
you want some?. you want a piece of me?.
I didn't think so!
Munchy, crunchy time. There you go!
- Fetch, boy! - Hey, hey, gimme' that!
- Come back here! - Everybody up.
Hey, nice party! Gotta blast!
Neutron!
Okay, let's move out.
Guards, vaporize the Earth brats!
Hurry! Head to the exit!
- Hey, where's Sheen?. - I don't know.
Stop them!
All right, Sheen!
your ship awaits, Captain Jimmy!
Ooblar, protect--
Oh, pooh!
Everybody to the ship!
Poultra, quickly! your dinner's getting away!
Okay, let's get outta here.
Come on!
We gotta do this quick! Launch positions.
Core temperature optimal. Engaging primary plasma coils.
- Jim, I think we better leave now. - Beginning countdown. Ten. Nine.
Eight--
One!
To the ships!
And could someone bring me a bucket?.
We made it!
Jimmy, here they come!
Time to discipline the naughty children. Open fire!
Okay, who wants fried chicken?.
So, Neutron, now it's just you and I.
All weapons on-line!
UltraLord is not afraid of chickens He is not afraid
Okay. he may be a little bit afraid of chickens
This thing's too slow. I can't outrun 'em!
- Incoming message. - On screen.
You see. Jimmy. you can't win.
All of your friends and family would be safe at home...
if it wasn't for one little problem-- you.
- Little?. - Now you all must die!
Little, huh?. I'll show you little.
Cindy, take over. C'mon, boy.
What are you doing?. Is this one of those macho things?.
We haven't field tested this feature yet, but we have no choice, buddy.
Goddard, FlyCycle!
Would you look at this?. I do believe he's going to ram us, Ooblar.
Remind me to clean the windshield later.
you steal my parents, you threaten my dog.
Itsy-bitsy Jimmy Neutron!
He does look a bit small and silly, doesn't he?.
you attack my friends, and you made fun of my size!
- Tiny, tiny. - So, so tiny!
Well, I may be small, but I've got a big brain!
- No! - Not tiny!
Can't we call this whole thing a mistake and go back to your plan...
rendezvous for universal brotherhood and what not?.
you've not seen the last of us...
Jimmy Neutron!
you look marvellous sunny-side up, sire.
That's no yolk.
All right, Jimmy!
Orbiting around Jimmy's big head.
Estimated time to ear, seven minutes.
So I guess I can't call you short anymore.
Don't worry. I'm sure there are other insults you can come up with.
Let me tell you, as soon as we get home...
we're going out dancing!
UltraDad!
UltraSon!
Dad?. Daddy!
Hey, Neutron...
nice job.
Thanks.
I've got that for you, dear.
Mom, Dad...
I should've listened to you when you said don't talk to strangers.
See, I guess I thought I was smart enough to do everything on my own...
that I didn't need you.
But I was wrong.
I love you guys.
We love you too, Jimmy.
Having a genius for a son may not always be easy...
but it's always interesting.
you make us so proud.
you sure do.
Not every family gets to ride in an alien spaceship...
hurtling at warp speeds, millions of miles from home.
We thank you for that.
Now you gotta admit, that is pretty neat.
There you are, gentlemen.
Freeze!
- It's okay, it's just breakfast. - I knew that.
I don't remember buying this brand of soda.
No, Mom--
Jimmy, it's just soda.
Mom, no!
Goodness! Excuse me!
Boy, it's a scorcher out there!
Thanks, honey.
At least it's coming out of the attic, not the basement!
James Isaac Neutron--
Onward, Mr. Wiggles. We reach the cafeteria by dawn!