Aah!
Show them the courage
of Allah.
Aah!
He says you stole the bread.
It's a lie.
I caught him stealing ours.
Cut off the infidel's hand.
No. I took the bread.
Wait.
That's not true.
They're not interested
in the truth.
But he's lying.
You're too weak, Peter.
You would not live.
As you wish.
Cut the other one's
hand off as well.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Robin.
Oh, God.
No, no, no!
This is English courage.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
That's for five years of hell.
Behind you!
Come on, Robin,
for God's sake.
Come on!
Wait!
Take us with you!
You cannot save
those people, Christian...
but you can save me.
They're coming, Robin.
Robin, come on.
Christian!
Why should I?
For pity's sake.
My sentence is death.
He's a Moor. Don't listen.
I will show you a way out.
Why should we?
If you do not,
we're dead.
No, Robin.
For God's sake.
Robin, they're coming!
I'm sorry.
Come, Christian.
Come.
This way.
Thanks. I misjudged you.
You are fast
with a sword, my friend.
Five years I've waited
to smell free air.
It makes a man fast.
Aah!
Peter!
It's mortal.
Leave me.
Give this ring
to my sister Marian...
and swear you'll
protect her for me.
His wound
is by the heart.
We cannot save him.
Swear it, Robin.
I swear it.
They're coming.
Tell Marian I died
a free Englishman.
Pe-Peter!
Peter!
For England!
No, no!
Come, my friend.
Make his sacrifice
an act of honor.
Come now.
Why did you cut me
free, Christian?
Whatever blood
is in your veins...
no man deserves
to die in there.
Farewell, friend.
God speed your way.
Our way lies together
with the speed of Allah.
What?
You have saved
my life, Christian.
I will stay with you
until I have saved yours.
Thanks, but I go
to England.
I relieve you
of your obligation.
Only Allah can do that.
What if I say no?
You have no choice.
I am Azeem Edin
Bashir Al Bakir.
You may call me Azeem.
Robin of Locksley.
Kindest sir...
"tis rumored you fought
in King Richard"s crusade...
with my beloved son Robin.
I fear you have
returned home...
to desperate times...
when dark forces plot
against our absent king.
I am anxious for word
of my son.
Were you present at
his capture nearJerusalem?
Do you know the name...
of the potentate
who holds him?
Does he still bear me ill will?
A little news, please, sir.
I would give all that I own
for his release.
I will see him, I tell you!
Get out of my way!
Stop there!
Help me, my lord!
You should have waited.
I'm sorry you were
disturbed, master.
Duncan, it's all right.
Let him go.
They've taken my Gwen,
my daughter.
Who's taken her?
Men on horses,
in masks.
We tried
to stop them, but...
my son, he's dead.
He's dead.
Master, stay.
There is an evil moon tonight.
Never fear, Duncan.
Good will overcome.
Trust in that.
I'm sorry, my lord.
I had no choice.
You!
Locksley.
The king
shall hear of this!
Join us.
Never.
Join us...
or die.
God and King Richard!
Yaah!
Oh, thank you, Lord.
I'm home.
I'm home!
You are strange, Christian.
Yes, but I'm free.
Now I beg you
to free yourself of your vow.
Return with the boat.
I know how it feels
to be so far...
from your home
and family.
Because I love them
so much...
I cannot dishonor them.
I thought
you would say that.
No man controls
my destiny...
especially not one
who attacks downwind...
and stinks of garlic.
Come, Azeem.
Our fighting days are done.
By nightfall, we'll celebrate
with my father.
You understand,
of course...
I had to try.
I would have succeeded.
Why must you walk
in back of me?
In your country,
am I not the infidel?
Ha ha ha.
It seems safer
to appear as your slave...
rather than your equal.
For an infidel, you have
uncommon clarity of thinking...
but you tell me
nothing of yourself.
For instance,
your name Azeem...
what does it mean?
Great one.
Great one, really?
Did you give yourself
this name?
It's... It's a joke.
Azeem the great one,
I am home!
Whoo!
Look.
Mistletoe.
Many a maid's lost
her resolve to me...
thanks to this little plant.
In my country,
we talk to our women.
We do not drug them
with plants.
What do you know of women?
Where I come from,
Christian...
there are women
of such beauty...
that they can possess
a man's mind so...
that he would be willing
to die for them.
Wait. Is that why
you were to be executed?
Because of a woman?
That's it, isn't it?
That's it!
It is close to sunset.
You painted old dog.
Who was she?
The mullah's daughter?
Huh?
Another man's wife?
What's her name?
Is there no sun
in this cursed country?
Which way is east?
- Her name.
- East!
Her name.
- Jasmina.
- That way.
You are sure?
I would know blindfolded.
I'm five miles from home.
Was she worth it?
Worth dying for.
We've got him now!
Ha ha ha.
You're dog's meat, son,
you know that.
Get down here!
You know that
you're doomed!
Come down here!
Down!
You're not playing
by the rules, boy.
Deer don't climb trees.
Perhaps he thinks
he's a game bird.
Ha ha ha!
Shall we
teach him to fly?
Yeah.
Get him down.
Hold!
I'm curious as to
what manner of creature...
is so fearsome that it
takes six men to attack it.
Stranger, this is
no affair of yours.
Well, have we treed
the devil himself?
Let me see.
A small boy...
a truly dangerous animal.
This boy killed one of
the sheriff of Nottingham's deer.
You starve us!
We needed the meat.
I advise you
to move on, pilgrim.
This is the sheriff s land.
Wrong.
This is my land and my tree.
Therefore, whatever is in it
also belongs to me.
Might I have
the pleasure of your name...
before I have you
run through?
Robin of Locksley.
Well, well. Locksley.
Welcome home.
Kill him!
Aah!
Azeem!
It's time
to redeem that vow!
Unleash the hounds!
Get off your damn knees!
Look out!
Yay!
Now, sir...
if you'd be so kind
as to give me your name...
before I run you through.
Guy of Gisborne,
the sheriff s cousin.
That little bastard
was poaching deer.
Poaching? Is it not
a greater crime to starve a family?
Go on, Locksley.
Go on.
I've seen enough blood spilt
to last two lifetimes.
Now get off my land.
And tell Nottingham
what happens to his scum...
when they
pick on small children.
You.
You traveled 10,000 miles
to save my life...
then leave me
to be butchered?
I fulfill my vows
when I choose.
Which does not
include prayer times...
or mealtimes or anytime
I'm outnumbered 6-to-1.
You whine like a mule.
You are still alive.
Have no fear.
Come down, boy.
Is it true, boy?
Did you kill a deer?
Hundreds of them.
You scared him.
Interesting place, this...
England.
Hold up, Sir Guy.
The sheriff s not
to be disturbed.
Cousin.
I trust you justify
your intrusion...
with news of profound value.
I met a hooded man today...
who bade me warn you
not to harm his people.
Who told you to cover up?
His name?
Robin of Locksley.
The prodigal son returns.
He's a whelp.
This girl could best him.
Put it there!
Yes, well, this whelp
bested four of my men.
Yes, well, your men
were probably drunk.
And yet you survived, cousin.
I barely survived.
Yes, yes. I'm sure
it would take an army...
to match these rogues.
I trust Locksley's
visited his manor...
and found the home fires
still burning.
Time for potence, cousin.
Mortianna?
Shut up!
You cold, madam?
Chit-chit-chit-chit-choo.
Ya, ya, ya.
What do you see?
The son of a dead man.
Locksley.
Does he affect us?
He precedes the lionheart.
King Richard returns
from the Crusades.
That could prove
a bit awkward.
It would soften the spines
of the barons.
Soon?
Make haste.
But my plan is still intact?
Aah!
What's wrong?
I have seen our death.
The painted man...
he haunts my dreams...
adorned with strange
foreign markings.
Ah! Locksley's companion.
Kill him!
Kill them both!
Father?
Father!
Is anyone here?
Duncan!
Father!
No!
No.
Who is it?
It's my father.
Who's there?
Master Robin?
Is that you?
Duncan?
Oh, praise be.
I thought God
had abandoned us.
Duncan, my father.
Oh, it's a miracle.
Why... Why didn't
you cut him down?
It's a miracle.
I never thought that...
Are you deaf?
Easy!
Look at him.
I would have done
if I could see.
Who did this to you,
Duncan?
Guy... Guy of Gisborne...
with the sheriff and
his witch looking on.
Why?
They say that the sheriff...
captured your father
worshiping the devil...
that he signed a confession...
before the bishop.
No.
That's not possible.
Nottingham declared
all Locksley lands forfeit.
Did you believe the charges?
Not even when
they took my eyes.
We must go.
He loved you till the end,
young master.
He never gave up hope
of your return.
I should have been here.
He called the Crusades
a foolish quest.
He said it was vanity
to force other men...
to our religion.
But you must flee now.
Head south to safety.
Gisborne will
surely seek revenge.
I hear you, Duncan.
You should go home.
My world's turned
upside down here.
I cannot ask you to
come where I am going.
Alone, Christian, you will
only get yourself killed.
Besides...
there is nothing left
for me to go home to.
I will not rest
until my father is avenged.
I swear it...
by my own blood.
What is this place?
Peter's home.
It's nearly six years
since we left together.
We'll find food and shelter here.
No more beggars.
Tell the mistress
of the house...
that Robin of Locksley
is at her door.
Her ladyship's not here.
Is the child Marian at home?
Maybe she is.
Maybe she isn't.
Aah!
Ohh!
The hospitality
in this country...
is as warm as the weather.
It's a joke.
Really?
Leave your weapons!
Just you.
Wait here.
Right here?
A curse on Moors
and Saracens.
Were it not for
their ungodly ways...
Master Robin would
never have left.
What manner of name
is Azeem...
Irish, Cornish?
Moorish.
Who are you?
Robin of Locksley.
You lie.
Robin is dead.
Step into the light.
Turn around.
Am I to dance next?
Who are you?
I am the maid Marian.
Well, then show
yourself, child...
for we knew
each other well.
The years have...
been kind.
Thank you.
With the king away...
we must guard against
villainous outlaws...
who would kidnap
a relative of his.
Surely you can see
I'm not one of those.
Perhaps.
Now remove yourself
from this house.
I would, my lady,
but I'm sworn to protect you.
Protect me?
Robin of Locksley
was nothing but a spoiled bully.
And besides...
as you can see...
we have enough protection.
Marian, wait.
You are truly courageous
against an unarmed man.
Aah!
Point me toward danger,
Azeem. I'm ready.
Stop! Stop!
Aah!
Ohh!
Hello, Marian.
His last thoughts were of you.
Oh, Peter.
Oh, God.
I'm sorry, Marian.
I'm sorry.
How do I know
you didn't abandon him...
to save your own skin?
No one feels his loss
more than I.
The next time I visit London...
I'll convey your condolences...
to my mother.
I would think,
for your safety...
that you would
join her there.
No. I have no interest
in life at court.
All that gossip mongering...
and currying favor.
But you're alone here.
Hardly.
These years have left us
many in need.
While you and my brother
were off playing boy heroes...
Nottingham has
plundered the shire.
I see you still
have your lands.
Because I give them
no excuse to take them.
I am the king's cousin.
It is my station
to look after these people...
until his return.
Marian.
My purpose in coming
was not to hurt you.
I swore...
I swore to your brother
that I would protect you.
You cannot replace
my brother.
I don't...
I don't want to replace him.
Marian, I've returned to my home
to find it destroyed...
and my father murdered.
And the only
explanations for it...
are the ramblings
of an old blind man.
All I remember of you...
is a spoiled bully
who used to burn my hair as a child.
Please allow that years
of war and prison...
may change a man.
Robin, whatever happened...
between you and your father...
you mustn't believe...
what they accused him of.
I don't.
Look.
How did your uneducated kind...
ever takeJerusalem?
God knows.
What is it?
It's Nottingham's soldiers.
Coming here?
Is this your protection?
I killed some
of the sheriff s men.
Oh, dear.
I fear I've placed
you in danger.
I can take care
of myself. Just go.
No. That's my horse.
A truly magnificent
animal, milady.
Go!
I said I'm sworn to protect you.
And I say no more
boyish gestures.
I'm not leaving.
Stop them!
They're stealing my horses!
You're so kind, Marian.
Ooh!
You've been sheltering
outlaws, Lady Marian?
They're thieves, you imbecile.
Lucky he didn't steal
your virtue as well.
A crown to the man
who brings me Locksley's head!
Milady. Hyah!
Have we lost them?
No.
My horse carries two.
Yours is lame.
We cannot outrun them.
Leave me, Master Robin.
I slow your escape.
We can lose them
in the forest.
Sherwood Forest
is haunted, master.
Either we take our chances
with the ghosts...
or become ghosts ourselves.
Come on, damn you!
There are only three of them!
It's not the men we fear.
It's the evil spirits.
Robin of the Hood...
son of a devil worshiper!
Your father died a coward...
cursing your name...
and squealing
like a stuck pig!
You will bring no justice
to your father...
by dying today.
Master Robin?
There are your
ghosts, Duncan...
wind chimes.
A child's toy
put to good use.
You scare easily,
my painted Moor.
This forest has eyes.
I swear it.
In my dreams alone...
have I imagined
such a place.
Then imagine
a way to cross it.
There's hope!
# There was a rich man
from Nottingham #
# Who tried
to cross the river #
# What a dope,
he tripped on a rope #
# Now look at him shiver ##
Beg for mercy, rich man!
I beg of no man.
Aah!
Well, this here
is our river...
and any man
who wishes to cross...
must pay a tax.
I will pay no tax.
As you can see...
I have nothing...
not even my sword.
Bollocks!
Any man who travels
with two servants...
and claims he's got
no bloody money...
is either a fool...
or a liar.
Yeah, he's a liar!
Who are you?
John Little...
best man of the woods.
- Yeah!
- Yay!
Well, best man,
do you lead this rabble?
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Yes, I do, mate.
And if you tosspots want to travel
through Sherwood Forest...
it's going to cost you...
that gold medallion.
This is sacred to me.
It's sacred to us,
too, matey.
That there will feed us
for a blooming month.
You'll have to
fight me for it.
Whoa! Whoa!
Love to, mate.
- Yeah!
Be careful, Father.
He walloped 12 of
the sheriff s men.
Is that so?
Reckon I'm going
to enjoy this.
Hey!
That's your father?
Come on, John!
Knock him over, John!
Ha ha ha ha!
Whoa!
He's drowning!
Lost something?
Thanks for the taxes.
Ha ha ha!
Looks like
the little rich boy...
is lost for words, eh?
Any great ideas?
Get up!
Move faster!
Move faster.
Great idea.
Watch it, John!
We're not through yet.
All right, my old cocker.
You want another
good walloping?
You shall have one.
Ohh!
Seems I've made it
past the gate, John Little.
Or should I call you
LittleJohn?
Hit him, Father! Wallop him!
Swimming time again,
old chum.
Ohh!
Where is he?
Do you see him?
It's a bloomin' shame.
He was a brave lad.
Ooh! Aah!
Help!
Do you yield?
I can't bloody swim!
Yes!
Good. Now put
your feet down.
I'll be buggered.
- The medallion.
- Give me your name first.
Robin of Locksley.
Well,
Robin of Locksley...
you got balls of solid rock.
Come on.
That's Much,
the Miller's son...
Harold Brownwell...
and that stumpy one there
is David of Doncaster...
but the lads
all calls him Bull.
'Cause you're short?
No. It's 'cause
I'm so long!
Yeah, look.
No, Bull.
Save it. Save it for the ladies.
Give the man some mead.
Very good, isn't it?
Now, I made that myself.
Has English hospitality
changed so much in six years...
that a friend of mine's
not welcome at this table?
But he's a savage, sire.
That he is.
But no more than you or I.
And don't call me sire.
With regret, I must decline.
Allah forbids it.
Your bloody loss, mate.
How is it there are
so many of you in hiding?
Well, we're all outlaws.
Got prices on our heads.
Even the young lad there.
He's a blasted sheriff.
He says we owes him taxes.
Well, you know,
your ghost...
will only keep the sheriff s men
at bay so long.
They've worked so far.
You have a better idea?
You can always fight back.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha ha.
I reckon I must have cracked
that noble head of yours.
These are all good lads here.
They got hearts of oak,
but they're farmers.
It'd be lambs
to the slaughter.
They say the sheriff
was raised by a witch.
Witch?
She knows
every man's thoughts.
You can see
right through her...
and she flies.
That's a load
of codswallop.
What does the rich son
of a devil worshiper care...
about outlaw peasants?
My lord was a kind
and generous man!
Who among you dares
believe him capable...
Duncan. My father was
no devil worshiper...
and I'll have words with any man
who says otherwise.
But he's right.
I was a rich man's son.
But when I killed
the sheriff s men...
I became an outlaw
like you.
You are nothing like us.
Well... that there's
Will Scarlett.
Don't take no note of him.
He's full of piss and wind.
Come on, lads, drink up.
Stop talking
so much bloody rubbish.
This here is the best
we simple men can expect.
Here we're safe.
Here...
we are kings.
Ha ha ha!
Aah!
Too much mead, old friend?
Oh, forgive me.
I oversleep.
No, no.
Rest yourself.
What day is it, Duncan?
Sunday, I think.
Do they still give alms
to the poor at mass?
That they do.
These days,
the need for mercy...
is greater than ever.
Well, my other god calls.
Oh, don't upset
yourself, Mortianna.
Appearances are important
to that lot.
Especially on a Sunday.
You know my true faith
lies in the old ways.
Although...
frankly sometimes...
I can't see much difference.
Did my parents truly tell you...
to instruct me in all this?
Their dying wish.
Come on.
We beseech thy blessing,
Lord...
on all your people...
but most especially...
on our noble sheriff
of Nottingham.
Grant him the wisdom...
to guide and protect
our glorious city.
Grant him also
the strength...
to bring to justice...
the lawless men who would
threaten its safety...
and prosperity...
and the judgment
to punish them...
in your name.
Amen.
- Amen.
Go in peace.
Alms, please, sir.
Please, madam.
- Sarah.
- Yes.
Thank you.
Ma'am.
That's all I have.
God bless you, mum.
Alms for a blind man, milady?
Mmm.
For one who cannot
see your beauty.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Searching my soul.
I do not wish to be seen
with an outlaw.
You prefer the company
of Nottingham?
There's a price
on your head.
How much?
100 gold pieces.
Is that all?
I'll have to annoy
the good sheriff more.
Soon it will be 1,000.
For 1,000, I would
turn you in myself.
Nottingham is
mounting an army.
He has every blacksmith
in the county...
in the castle,
making swords and armor.
What is he planning?
I don't know,
but there's no limit...
to the man's ambitions.
Go!
Thank you.
Quickly! Go!
Robin, do something for me.
What?
Take a bath.
Take a bath?
These are my private
chambers, my son.
I have priests
who would hear your confession.
- Gggt!
- Aah!
Shh!
I see the boy I knew
in the man before me.
Welcome home, Robin.
You shine like
the sun, milady.
You've been meeting
with Robin of Locksley.
My cousin tells me...
the knave deprived
you of some horses.
Oh... yes.
A most disagreeable
experience.
Yes, I know.
And for inflicting that upon you...
I'm going to hang him
from the walls by his own entrails.
I'd like to see that.
If you'd bring
your household...
within the city walls...
I could give your every need
my personal attention.
I do thank you,
but I prefer to stay...
in my family's home
for now.
Oh. Well, then, perhaps
you'd do me the honor...
of accepting
a small token...
of my undying devotion
to your safety.
Oh!
Why... King Richard
will be deeply moved...
to hear of your concern
for my welfare.
Yes, um...
I'm afraid the king
has many enemies...
both abroad
and at home.
I fear for his safe return.
Oh, no. Fear not,
dear sheriff.
He will return,
and when he does...
he will wish to reward
his faithful subjects.
I asked your father
three times...
if he worshiped
the dark one...
because his answer
vexed me so grievously.
He said...
he must meet God
with a clear conscience.
You lie.
On your souls...
do not shed blood
in the house of God!
You bastard!
In there!
Get him!
Locksley!
I'm going to cut
your heart out...
with a spoon!
Then it begins.
Aah!
He's taking
the sheriff s horse!
Close the gate!
The sheriffs horse!
He's stolen
the sheriff s horse!
Uhh!
What are you looking at?
There's a rider coming in!
Water!
Thank you.
For the animal.
How can I protect you,
Christian...
if I know not
where you go?
You've hardly raised
a finger...
when you do know...
great one.
I prefer to have
the choice.
Wonderful. You've stolen
the sheriff s horse?
You've stirred up
a bloody hornet's nest now!
Are you afraid, John?
Yeah, a little.
Well, so is the sheriff.
Today I gave him a sting
he'll not forget.
You fool!
You've started a war!
We're already at war.
Duncan...
bread.
And I say we strike back...
at the very man
who takes our homes...
and would
hunt our children.
We?
You planning to
join us then, matey?
No, to lead you.
Christian...
these are simple people.
They are not warriors.
Be careful
you do not do this...
for your own purposes.
You forget yourself, Azeem.
I do not ask for your company
or counsel.
Why a spoon, cousin?
Why not an ax
or something...
Because it's dull, you twit!
It'll hurt more!
I want this brigand found.
Starve them out!
Slaughter their...
No, take their livestock.
I want Locksley's own people
fighting to bring his head in.
Well, perhaps we could create
a name for him...
something to drive fear
into the hearts of the populace.
Maybe Locksley the Lethal
or Wreaking Robin or...
Whatever!
I want him dead
by the next full moon...
before the barons
come back.
Now sew...
and keep the stitches small!
He's not here, sir.
Where is your mate,
the man they call Little?
He died last winter.
Burn it down.
Light the other one.
Leave us the sow.
Her young will feed us.
Beware of
the Sherwood bandit.
Robin of the Hood?
Yes, sir.
Pray he's brought to us
before winter.
Ma!
Over here!
Oh, John!
Papa!
They burned it, all of it.
Where is this
Robin Hood now?
He's there.
Look! Look what
they've done!
If it's fame
you seek, Christian...
I think you have it.
You brought this misery
on us, Locksley.
It's Nottingham
trying to divide us.
We are divided, rich boy.
I'm not as blind
as that old man.
You're still trying to be
lord of the manor.
I heard today the sheriff
now values your neck...
at 500 gold pieces.
I say we take him in.
- Aye.
Do you think the sheriff
will return everything...
after I'm gone?
He'll give us the reward
and our pardons.
Wrong.
He'll stretch your
necks one by one.
What would you
have us do...
fight armored men
on horseback...
with rocks
and our bare hands?
If needs be.
But with
the one true weapon...
that escapes you, Will...
courage.
Look out!
Thank you, Wulf.
You wish to end this?
You wish to go home?
Then we must stop
fighting amongst ourselves...
and face that the price
for it may be dear.
I for one
would rather die...
than to spend my life
in hiding.
The sheriff calls us outlaws...
but I say we are free.
And one free man
defending his home...
is more powerful
than 10 hired soldiers.
The Crusades taught me that.
I will make you
no promises save one...
that if you truly believe
in your hearts...
that you are free...
then I say we can win.
They got armor.
Yeah! Right!
They got armor, Bull?
Even this boy
can be taught...
to find chinks
in every suit of armor.
We ain't got nothing to eat.
What do we need that
the forest cannot provide?
We have food,
wood for weapons.
We'll find safety
and solace in her trees.
Yeah, but
what about our kin?
Sheriff s taken
all they got, too.
Then, by God,
we take it back.
Ho!
Hyah!
What's the meaning of this?
Milady, a woman
of your beauty...
has no need for
such decorations.
How dare you!
Please don't take that.
Please, sir, those
belong to our lord.
Now they belong
to my lord sheriff!
- Yay!
- Ha ha!
Give it back.
Good.
Tell the sheriff...
for every harm he
does these people...
I will visit it
back on him tenfold.
Something vexes thee?
What the devil?
'Tis a hot day,
my friend...
to burden your horse
with a heavy purse.
The sheriff will hear of this.
I truly hope so.
Yeah!
There, luv.
Buy yourself
a new sow.
God bless you, Fanny...
and God bless Robin Hood.
We reckon he's nicked
three to four million...
in the last
five months, sire.
All right, fine.
Raise the bounty on his head.
25,000 crowns.
Begging your pardon, sire.
It won't do no good
how much you raise it.
Really, scribe?
And why is that?
Because, sire,
the poor, you see?
He gives them
what he takes...
and, well, sire,
they love him.
Just a minute.
Robin Hood steals money
from my pocket...
forcing me
to hurt the public...
and they love him for it?
Yes.
That's it, then!
Cancel the kitchen scraps
for lepers and orphans...
no more
merciful beheadings...
and call off Christmas.
The treasury is empty.
All day and all night,
people plague my door...
whining for tax relief...
and safe passage
through Sherwood Forest.
"We cannot pay thee...
what the highwayman
has taken. "
It's the shortest route
to London.
It's the only road to London,
you little ferret.
Sir Guy's patrols
have found nothing, sire.
No camp. Nothing.
This hooded viper
simply slithers into the forest.
You, my room,
10:30 tonight.
You, 10:45...
and bring a friend.
A tongue offends thee.
Whose?
One who rights all.
One who...
That horrible little scribe?
- His tongue?
- Cut it out.
# What's the pleasure
in this life #
# Laughter, love,
and drinking #
# Good King Richard,
bless his soul #
# Loves his wine
and warring #
# But for us
who stay at home #
# There's only beer
and whoring #
# Play your music,
dance the day #
# Think of not
tomorrow... #
How many?
20.
20?
How many?
Five.
They can't count anyway.
- Come on.
- Why scare them?
And they call me barbarian.
# Loves his wine
and warring #
# But for us
who stay at home #
# There's only beer
and whoring #
# Play the music,
dance the day... ##
Friar! You'll find
it difficult to sing...
with a sword
in your gullet.
Yes, my lord.
You pig.
Shut up about it!
Help me move this log!
Log? This is a tree!
You're supposed to help me!
I'm supposed to be
meeting a girl!
You men in front, after me.
You men in the rear,
stay with the wagon!
On to glory!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Bastards!
Come on, find them!
# Oh... ##
Go!
Hyah!
Welcome to Sherwood,
Friar. Giddyup!
Aagh!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Surrender your weapons!
Surrender your weapons
and I'll give you my word...
you shall go free!
Don't do that!
Aah! What are you...
Azeem! Aah!
Look at that!
Oh!
I'll be buggered.
This treasure had a purpose.
We must find out what.
Oh! Aah!
Good morning,
my reverend friend.
You travel
with poor company...
when you travel with
Nottingham soldiers.
Tax him!
- Tax him!
I'm Robin of Locksley...
and my men are thirsty.
- Aye!
- That's right.
Robin Hood!
Ha! Lord bless me.
I mistook you
for common thieves.
Kindly let me pass, huh?
Surely the lord
has the charity...
to spare a few barrels...
for good Christian men, yes?
We have much to celebrate.
Come on.
If you wish them to share
in the good lord's brew...
you must best me for it!
Hyah!
Confess, Robin Hood...
that Friar Tuck is a braver,
holier, and wiser man...
than thou art.
He giveth
and he taketh away.
Do you yield?
I'd rather roast in hell.
Aah!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
# Robin has his way #
# Whether you live
by night or day #
# Whether you're rich
or young or old #
# Whether you're noble,
meek, or bold #
# You will fall #
# Short or tall ##
Oh, I think the good friar's
taken us far enough.
Well done, Friar.
Thank you, Lord,
for teaching me humility.
Ohh.
Well, Tuck...
Thanks for the beer.
Are these not
the meek of the earth?
We're in need of an honest man
to minister to them.
What say you, Friar?
The Lord reveals himself
in mysterious ways.
I accept.
Good.
You will not regret it.
Aye, but you may!
We were ambushed, cousin.
Spanish steel.
Much stronger than
our native blades.
Ahem. Any losses?
Some.
In truth, all of them.
And the gold?
Taken.
Robin Hood?
They were woodsmen,
cousin.
Robin Hood.
I tried.
Cousin.
I tried. I tried.
Cousin, we must be strong.
We can't allow an outlaw
to make fools of us.
And I can't allow
a lieutenant...
to fail me.
Uhh!
Well, at least
I didn't use a spoon.
Ha ha.
It's good steel.
Much!
What?
Take the left one.
Which one's left?
Which one you taking?
What do you mean?
If you're taking the left,
I'm taking the right.
Which one's on the right?
The one next to...
Bollocks, we'll just
jump out and grab them.
- Now?
- Now!
A donation if you please.
Donation?
For what?
Bull?
Uh, for passage
through Sherwood.
Very well.
Come get it.
Huh?
You stunted shrub.
How dare you attack us?
It's me job, milady.
And who is your employer?
Robin Hood.
I insist on seeing him at once.
No!
I'm trying to stop her, Bull!
You cannot go down there!
Will you stop?
Don't rush.
You'll fall.
He's not expecting you!
My lady's intrusion
is simply tit for tat.
Out of the way,
you old traps!
You can't go down there!
Oh.
I told you,
not down there!
You've already had
the rough part of my hand.
You'll get it again.
Ooh! Oh, I say!
Cover your eyes.
Milady, don't.
You could have said.
Robin!
You got visitors!
Don't look at me like that.
It weren't my fault.
It was Much!
It weren't me!
Be careful.
It's slippery there.
Hello.
Well, what are you
doing here?
Taking a lady's advice.
What happened
to your eye, Bull?
It was set upon
by 10...
12!
15 large, big lads.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
You've been busy.
Ha ha ha!
We have guests!
Bring them down!
It works.
Kind of.
Of course it works.
Great shot!
A beauty!
All right, Wulf,
take your time, now.
- Yeah!
- All right!
That's good, Wulf...
but can you do it
amidst distraction?
Can you make the shot
when you must?
Show him, Wulf.
- Go on.
- You can do it.
- Oh!
- Hey!
Can you?
Well, go on, Robin.
It was a dirty trick.
Oh, he's serious.
Is his shirt
coming off at all?
Ha ha ha!
Well done.
This is grain...
which any fool can eat...
but for which
the Lord intended...
a more divine means
of consumption.
Let us give praise
to our maker...
and glory to his bounty...
by learning about...
beer.
- Ha ha!
- Ha ha ha!
Did you bring me
here to brag?
This is blood money, Marian.
It's intended to bribe
King Richard's enemies...
to unite against him.
We intercepted it.
But who would...
Nottingham.
No. Nottingham would not dare
challenge the king.
The king is not in England.
While he's away,
he may lose his country.
You thought...
You thought I was
keeping it all, didn't you?
Didn't you?
Well, here...
A contribution to your cause.
Keep it.
No. This dagger
would fetch a great price.
No! It's not
dear to me...
I mean, it...
it's not.
Oh, I'm saying
everything wrong.
Um...
cheers.
How do I get down?
Wait, wait.
Oh.
We don't go that way anymore.
I'm happy to hear that.
Grab on.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh!
We have a rule here.
Once someone has seen
the way to our camp...
that person cannot leave.
There's too many lives at stake.
That's why Sarah and I
asked to be blindfolded.
Oh.
Well, perhaps
you might join us for dinner.
Perhaps.
Salaam, little one.
Did God paint you?
Did God paint me?
For certain.
Why?
Because...
Allah loves
wondrous variety.
You see, that is why
your hair is brown.
Keep thy heathen words away
from ears of this innocent...
or you'll answer me.
You know nothing of our god.
Is not Allah the god of Abraham
as is your god?
Don't trick me with twist
of the devil's tongue!
Come! Come!
How is it that a once arrogant
young nobleman...
has found contentment
living rough...
with the salt of the earth?
I've seen
armored knights panic...
at the first hint of battle...
and I've seen the lowliest,
unarmed squire...
pull a spear
from his own body...
to defend a dying horse.
Nobility's not a birthright.
It's defined
by one's actions.
It's interesting
to hear you say that.
I didn't.
My father did.
Did the holy quest
erase your hatred of him?
I don't know.
All I know is...
that our last words
in this world were...
spoken in anger.
I was lost
after my mother died.
My father, too.
And for a short time,
he found comfort...
in the arms of another woman,
a peasant woman.
I thought he was betraying
my mother's memory.
So he gave her up?
For the love
of a 12-year-old boy...
who would never
forgive him.
Anyway, who...
who says I'm content?
I have my plans for the future.
No, a grander scheme
than this?
No. A simpler one.
A home, family...
love.
Oh, men speak
conveniently of love...
when it serves their purpose.
And when it doesn't...
'tis a burden to them.
Robin of the Hood,
prince of thieves...
is he capable of love?
Father!
It's mother.
She's dying.
Oh, God!
Aah!
Fanny, your baby
has not turned.
It cannot be born
without help.
Uhh!
He is the devil's seed...
sent to lead us astray.
Don't listen to him.
He will kill her!
If you do not
listen to me...
she will certainly
die... and the child.
No!
Aah!
The good friar's
done all he can.
I suggest you let
the Moor try.
Ohh!
So be it.
Then be it on your head.
I've warned you.
Marian.
Yes?
Get me needle,
thread, water.
And hurry.
Yes.
Come with me.
Come, John.
Ohh!
What are you going to do?
I have seen it
many times...
with horses.
With horses?
Bite down, bite down.
Yes.
Ohh!
Help me, Sadiq.
Give me your arms.
It will be all right.
Aah!
I tell you, John, the barbarian
is killing her.
No!
No, Father, no!
Out of the way, boy.
Quick, take him,
take him.
Oh...
ooh, what is it?
Your son, milady.
There you are.
You truly are a great one.
My son!
Look at that
lovely little baby.
Isn't he wonderful?
- Yay!
John, he's beautiful!
Today the Lord has taught me
a fine lesson.
And though I may
think I am godly...
I know I am not worldly.
Please, please.
Ha!
Come, my barbarian friend...
so you and I open
a barrel together...
and save each other's souls.
Alas, I am not permitted.
Well, fine, then.
You talk, I'll drink.
Well!
Milady!
Sarah!
May I have this dance?
Oh!
This lady is spoken for.
Why this way?
So you cannot
find the way back...
or be forced to tell
others the way.
It was good to see
you again, Marian.
It was good to be seen.
I have two favors to ask of you.
- One.
- Take Duncan with you.
I fear for his health
with what may lie ahead.
Besides, I grow tired
of his bellyaching.
You wish me to leave,
Master Robin?
Old friend,
listen to me.
Can you take Lady Marian
safely home?
I fear for her safety.
Of course, sire.
Good.
Bull.
And two?
Yes, two.
You're King Richard's cousin.
You can get word to him...
of Nottingham's plan.
He would believe you.
If the sheriff found out,
I could lose all that I have.
That's true...
but will you
do it for your king?
No.
I'll do it for you.
He fancies you, my lady.
I am blind, but some things
I can still see.
In 10 days' time,
the barons are coming.
Robin Hood has stolen what I was
to pay for their allegiance...
and I am surrounded by fools
who do not realize my obligations.
Tell me, Mortianna...
am I thwarted?
Aah.
Recruit the beasts
that share our god.
- Animals?
- From the north.
You mean Celts.
They drink the blood
of their dead.
Yoke their strengths.
Hired thugs.
Ahh. Brilliant.
Put thine own issue
on the throne.
- A child? How?
- Alive with royal blood.
Who?
It's a personal
matter, my lord...
but one of vital
importance.
I understand,
my dear lady.
This is my most
trusted emissary.
He must travel
to France immediately...
and put that directly
into the hands of the king.
My lady-in-waiting
shall accompany you.
My dear, I could not
vouch for her safety.
The journey is fraught
with danger.
I appreciate your
concern, my lord...
but Sarah is an
accomplished rider.
I insist that she go along.
As you wish.
What is wrong?
My horse is favoring
his foreleg.
What's this?
An appetizer.
You promised us
wagons of gold.
Well, there are
greater things than gold.
More land and power
than you've ever dreamed of.
When I rule this land...
it'll be divided between
just the seven of us in this room.
You get Cornwall,
you can have Wales...
and Scotland is all yours.
You recruit us to treason...
and yet you cannot even get gold
through your own forest.
My lords,
why risk life and limb...
for a man who can't even snare
the paltry bandit...
- who marked his pretty face?
- Why, indeed.
Good point, milord.
How can I control England...
when I cannot even control
my own county?
I bring in a little help.
Udrid!
By God.
You're to lie us
with the Celts?
What can these mercenaries
do that we cannot do?
Very impressive.
All right, milord sheriff...
but you must wed
royal kin before we act.
Then your claim
to the throne will be...
legitimate.
I'm as good as engaged.
Duncan, is that you?
Hello?
Rebecca.
Oh, God!
Nicodemus.
Go.
Find mice.
Ha ha!
Aah!
I've never seen the breasts
of a noblewoman.
Aah!
Back!
Oh, pardon, milady,
we couldn't hold him!
Someone wants
a word with you.
Aah!
Oh, no!
That's it, sir.
That's all of them.
Easy, easy.
Tonight I need your eyes,
old friend.
Robin!
Someone is in our home!
All is well.
It's Duncan!
What happened?
I found you, Robin.
Thank God I did it.
Nottingham's men
attacked us.
Marian?
They took her.
Ah...
What is it?
Over there! Look!
On the hill!
- Aah!
Celts. God help us.
Allah, be merciful.
To the trees!
Celts! They're coming!
Poor old fool
led them straight to us.
Get me prisoners.
Aah!
- Aah!
Children, come to me!
Grab the children!
Ha ha ha!
Daddy! Save me!
My God.
Aah!
Robin, save us!
Aah! Aah!
Come!
Hurry!
Aah!
Save yourselves!
We better go, Robin!
We better go now!
Run!
Robin!
Aah!
This way, my lambs!
Come on!
Hold thy fire.
It's gold! Gold!
Look! It's gold!
Fanny!
John!
Come on, now!
Aah! No!
Aah!
Fanny!
Go! Save yourself, John!
No, Fanny!
I won't leave you!
Go on, John!
Never!
Oh, God!
Oh, thank God.
John, you'll have to
catch her!
Come on!
Aah!
No!
I got you, girl!
You swine!
Come here!
Quick! Quick!
All right, now!
- Come on!
- Go on!
Don't wait for me!
John, go on!
Hurry!
Aah!
Corpus Christi.
Amen.
My lady Marian.
By what right do you
keep me prisoner?
You misunderstand
my intentions.
You've been brought here
for your own protection.
Protection from whom?
From yourself.
It seems you've been
consorting with outlaws.
No.
Where do you hear
such lies?
By your own hand, my lady.
I'm sorry, my child.
I feared you were
being led astray.
Come.
It's over.
Today I return justice...
to this land.
I shall have to hang
the ringleaders, of course...
but I would like
to be generous...
and give you the lives...
of the woodsmen
and their families...
The children!
And, of course...
of your traitorous
lady-in-waiting...
Get in there!
as a wedding gift.
And just who am I
supposed to marry?
Search your heart, my child.
Why not a union with
the House of Nottingham...
and heal the wounds
in our land?
There's only one man...
who can heal the wounds
of this land... Robin Hood.
I'm truly sorry, my lady.
He wasted his life.
How many more lives
would you waste?
What a beautiful child.
So young...
so alive...
so unaware of
how precarious life can be.
I had a very sad childhood.
I'll tell you
about it sometime.
I never knew my parents.
It's amazing I'm sane.
Marian...
our bonding would
allow these children...
to grow up as my allies.
You understand...
I cannot allow them
to grow up as my enemies.
I have no choice.
That's true.
No.
No!
Look.
Christian.
Aah!
Sorry to keep you
hanging about.
Would you prefer
pain or death?
Death.
Torture him.
What about you,
pain or death?
Uh, pain!
Torture him.
You see, it makes
no difference.
Spare me!
Will you keep the noise
down, please?
Now I have heard...
that Robin Hood
may still be alive.
Either tell me
where he may be hiding...
or you'll all be hanged
and we'll catch him anyway...
and do the same thing
to him.
- I'd love to kill him for you.
- Will, no!
So he is alive then.
I'm not really sure.
Then why would I need you?
Because if he is alive,
I can get close to him.
I'm one of his men.
He would never suspect me.
- He knows you always hated him, traitor!
- Shut up!
He's a trusting fool.
He'll believe me.
If he doesn't, he'll kill me.
Then you've lost nothing.
If you fail...
I will personally remove
your lying tongue.
And if I succeed...
I want my freedom
and the bounty on his head.
The lash, I think.
Sorry about that.
It'll make it more convincing.
My pride brought us to this.
No, Sadiq.
It was you who gave pride
to these people.
I was a fool.
I was a fool
to let them leave...
to believe I'd planned
it all so perfectly.
I once heard
a wise man say...
there are no perfect men
in this world...
only perfect intentions.
You were an honor
to your countrymen today, Azeem.
You fought better
than 20 English knights.
Will!
I thought you were taken.
I was.
How did you escape?
Traitor!
I'll wring your scrawny neck for you,
Will Scarlett!
You get in there!
No bugger escapes the sheriff...
not unless he's lining
his bloody pockets!
Now, get in!
Wait! Wait, John!
Let him betray us?
I'll have your guts for garters,
you little toad!
Aah!
- Bugger me.
- God.
Let him speak.
I bring a message...
from Nottingham.
Our men are to be hung
in the square...
- at high noon tomorrow.
- What about my boy?
The boy, too.
Ten men in all.
The hangings
are to be part...
of the celebration
for the sheriff s marriage.
Marriage? To who?
Lady Marian.
If he takes a bride
of royal blood...
Aye...
and with
King Richard gone...
he'll be after
the bloody throne.
You were to use this news
to get close to me...
and then kill me,
right, Will?
What are your intentions?
That depends on you, Locksley.
I've never trusted you,
that's no secret.
Are you going to finish
what you've started?
Are you going to
turn and run...
like the spoiled rich boy
I always took him for?
Did I wrong you in another life,
Will Scarlett?
Where does this intolerable hatred
for me come from?
From knowing that our...
our father loved you
more than me.
Our father?
We are brothers,
Robin of Locksley.
I am the son
of the woman...
who replaced your dead mother
for a time!
It was your anger
that drove them apart!
- It's a lie!
- It's not a lie!
You ruined my life!
I have more reason
to hate you than anyone...
but I found myself
daring to believe in you.
What I want
to know, brother...
is will you stay
with us...
and finish
what you've started?
I have a brother?
I have a brother.
I will make
my stand with you...
side by side...
to the end.
To the end!
We're all bloody in.
Daft buggers.
We finish this.
Overwhelmed with happiness.
Thank you for asking.
Yes, all is well.
I got all my money back,
Robin Hood's probably dead...
and I'm gonna be king,
all as predicted.
I want you to tell the hangman
I don't want to see...
any broken necks
in the morning.
I wanna see some dancing.
Don't touch that!
I can do that myself.
Thank you very much.
Have you been spying
on me, you little insect?
No!
Who else would
have made a ho...
Oh!
Where are you?
You come early.
The signs are not aligned yet.
You can stop all that,
you old fake!
I will try for thee anyway.
The union, the blood of the lion
and the House of Montague.
New power. New souls.
I found the hole!
You dare to spy on me!
I want the truth!
Why? Truth has never
served you before.
Truth didn't put Nottingham
where he is today.
- Mortianna did.
- You freak!
I despise you. After the wedding,
you're on the streets.
Without my protection, people will
rip out your black heart and burn it!
Without me, you're nothing.
You're a flea bite, a speck.
I birthed you
from this body.
I stole a babe
in this very castle and killed it...
so that you might rise
in its place.
You're my son.
You despise me?
You are me.
You know from your empty soul
it's the truth.
All my life...
I've been a freak.
When you stud
the lady Marian...
my grandchild
takes the throne.
My blood,
its twisted seed...
we're all through him.
We'll see who's freakish then.
Aah! What was that?
Truly you are a wizard!
The mystery is
in the black powder.
Surely the Lord will
grant us victory.
- Bull.
- Yeah?
Position by the gate
to cut off reinforcements.
John, sit on this wall
to protect our escape.
I will conceal myself here
below the scaffold...
to cut our men from their nooses
at the signal.
No. I'll do that.
You cover us with your bow.
It's too dangerous, Will.
So is your aim.
Ha ha ha.
Whatever Azeem
is concocting...
we must each be
in place for it.
Our success depends
on total concert.
We may be only six men...
Seven.
What are you doing, woman?
Where's the little ones?
Safe with me mother.
You gone bleeding cracked?
You'd get hurt.
I've had eight babies.
Don't talk to me
about getting hurt.
I won't sit here
and let one of them die.
You should be bloody well
minding the other seven.
Tell her, Rob.
Fanny...
you will take position here.
No blades, no bows.
You'll leave your weapons here.
Leave your weapons here.
No blades, no bows.
No blades.
What have you
got there, Father?
The lord's finest brew...
for the good sheriff s
fighting men.
It has a mighty kick, huh?
No blades, no bows.
Hey, who are you?
Hey!
Don't anger him.
He is a Celt.
Shh!
Psst.
John! John!
Hey, you.
Do I know you?
Please, sir, don't hurt me.
Oh, my God, you stink.
Pardon my blindness.
I'm always falling...
Get out of here!
Thank you
for noticing me, sir.
Careful, Friar.
What are you doing?
Ah, distributing libations
for the celebration...
of the sheriff s nuptials.
Why, is there
something amiss?
You are. Get this stuff
out of here.
Caesar has spoken,
my leprous friend.
We shall collect
our offerings and depart.
Is this your finger?
Leper? What?
Get this cart out of here.
Leaving bits and pieces
of himself all over England.
What are you doing here?
I ain't doing no harm.
I likes a good hanging.
- What's in this bundle?
- That's firewood.
- Psst.
- Hey!
Aah!
Hello, my lover.
Oyez, prepare
for the outdoor hanging.
Make way for
the Lord's work.
No fighting here.
Make way for
the Lord's work.
A simple benediction for these
poor bastards about to stretch.
God receive them
in thy mercy...
and show them the love
they so richly deserve...
even though they be
thieving sons of bitches.
Hey!
Nothing there
but trouble, boy.
That's a little inappropriate,
don't you think?
No more than
your wedding present.
Bring them out!
Oh, they're coming!
Get on. Get your
heads up in there.
Thief!
We're going to
get you vermin!
Patience!
Make way.
Traitor! Traitor!
Kill him!
Aah! Stop, stop!
What's going on?
Traitor!
Bring him here!
Kill him! Kill him!
What did I do?
Clear the way!
Stand still.
Oh, the turncoat.
Did you succeed?
Well, I... I found
his lair, but, uh...
he was already dead.
You sure?
You saw Hood's body?
No... I saw a grave.
We found this on him.
String him up
with the others.
Yay!
Put me down!
Let me go!
Leave him.
He's only a boy.
Shut up!
Bastard.
You all right?
Now, Robin?
My lord...
it appears
there's no more room.
I'm afraid I'll have
to respectfully decline.
Come on, you. Down.
Down!
Go on.
Hold your tongue!
There's always room
for one more.
Ha ha ha ha!
- No.
- My boy! John!
My boy!
Wulf!
Locksley.
Robin!
Wulf!
Get some troops in here!
Get on with it!
No!
I can't let go.
Help!
- Wulf!
- Father.
Oh, thank God.
Come on, you milksops!
- Fight your way free!
- Look out!
Aah!
This way!
To the wall!
My lord sheriff,
is this your idea of control?
Shut up, you twit!
- Come with me.
- Robin!
Marian.
Marian!
English!
Behold, Azeem Edin
Bashir Al Bakir.
I am not one of you...
but I fight.
I fight with Robin Hood.
I fight against a tyrant
who holds you under his boot.
If you would be free men...
then you must fight.
Join us now.
- Join Robin Hood.
- Freedom!
Come on, now!
Come on!
- Come on!
- Get back!
Help, Robin!
John!
Close the gate.
No!
Guard it with your life.
Bring the bishop to my chapel.
Push.
Right there.
Is she worth it?
Worth dying for?
Will!
- Aah!
Fuck me.
He cleared it.
Marian!
Aah!
We're doomed.
'Tis rebellion, my lord.
We must escape.
Marry us!
No!
I will never marry you!
Aah!
That's my wife, crone!
Get away!
Ah, she's ripe.
She will give us a son.
You must take her now.
I will not take her...
until we are properly wed!
For once in my life,
I will have something pure.
Will you stop interfering?
'Tis madness to delay.
- No!
- Aah!
Marry them or face me.
Aah!
Marian!
Where is she?
The lady Marian.
Up the stairs.
That way.
Aah! Aah!
Marian?
Aah!
Marian!
Robin!
Get on with it!
- Statue.
Do you, George,
sheriff of Nottingham...
take this woman to be
your lawful wedded wife?
To have and to hold...
in sickness and in health,
for better or for worse...
for richer, for poorer,
till death...
Yes, yes. Come on!
Make haste.
Do you, Marian,
of the House of Dubois...
take this man to be your
lawfully wedded husband...
No!
Yes, of course she does.
Aah!
Marian!
Damned English oak.
Robin!
Marian!
I'll try another way.
No! No! No! No!
What do you want?
Aah!
I can't do this
with all that racket!
How could you?
Yaaah!
Uhh! Uhh!
The painted man.
The witch.
I didn't know.
I didn't know it was you.
Please, sire, have pity.
Don't harm an old woman.
Aah!
You may take this body,
but it will not be me.
It will not be me!
Not again.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
In the name
of the Father...
the Son,
and the Holy Ghost.
Aah!
Robin.
Do you mind, Locksley?
We've just been married.
Uhh!
Recognize this?
It belonged to your father.
Appropriate,
don't you think...
that I now use it
to send you to meet him?
I shall never fear
my father's sword.
Really?
Aah!
Now we're even.
Robin!
If I must, I will take you
a piece at a time.
No!
I'll do the only taking today.
Aah!
No!
So...
you sold your soul
to Satan, your grace.
You accused innocent men
of witchcraft...
and let them die.
Brother friar,
you would not strike...
a fellow man of the cloth.
No. No, I wouldn't.
In fact, I'll help you
pack for your journey.
You're going
to need lots of gold...
to help you on your way.
You're a very rich man.
This, too, huh?
Enough?
Here's 30 pieces of silver...
to pay the devil
on your way to hell!
Aah!
Oh! Robin!
No!
Aah! Robin!
Robin!
Robin.
Get ready.
No!
Ohh.
Aah!
I have fulfilled my vow, Sadiq.
You came for me.
You're alive.
I would die for you.
By the power vested in me
by God's holy church...
I say any man
who has reason...
why these two
should not be joined...
let him speak now
or forever hold his peace.
Then I now pronounce you...
Hold it. I speak.
Richard.
It's King Richard.
I will not allow
this wedding to proceed...
My lord...
Unless...
I'm allowed
to give the bride away.
You look radiant, cousin.
Oh...
Richard.
We are deeply honored,
your majesty.
It is I who am honored,
Lord Locksley.
Thanks to you,
I still have a throne.
Friar, proceed.
My liege.
Husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
I know that.
- Hurrah!
Come on, get out of it.
We waste
good celebration time.
synchronized by kevink est