All of life is a coming home.
Salesmen, secretaries, coal miners,
beekeepers, sword swallowers,
all of us.
All the restless hearts
of the world...
all trying
to find a way home.
It's hard to describe
what I felt like then.
Picture yourself walking
for days in a driving snow.
You don't even know
you're walking in circles,
the heaviness of your legs
in the drifts;
your shouts
disappearing into the wind.
How small you can feel.
How far away home can be.
Home.
The dictionary defines it
as both a place of origin...
and a goal or destination.
And the storm?
The storm was all in my mind.
Or, as the poet Dante put it...
"In the middle of the journey of my life
I found myself in a dark wood...
for I had lost
the right path. "
Eventually I would find
the right path...
but in the most unlikely place.
How many fingers
do you see?
You crazy-
Stop sneakin' up on me like that.
How many?
-Four.
-Four?
Four?
Another idiot.
You gon' love it here.
Got a new one, Jane.
Hunter Adams.
Self-committed. Suicidal.
Slate him with Dr. Prack.
All right.
Hey, Rudy!
What's the word, my man?
He ain't left that bed in three weeks.
He won't give you any trouble.
He needs another bedpan. They're in
the closet. Wake-up is 7:00 a. m.
Excuse me.
Is there any way
I could have my own room?
Oh, absolutely.
Just call the concierge and ask
for a suite overlooking the fountain.
No, I-I prefer
the cabana room.
Get some sleep.
Hi.
You're, um...
you're a lot... fuzzier
than my last roommate.
Oh. Yeah.
Keeps me warm.
Aaaah!
-What's wrong?
-Get 'em away!
-Get what away?
-Get 'em-Get 'em away!
-Okay, I'm gonna have to-
-You traitor!
You brought 'em with you
when you opened the door!
Who?
We need help in here!
Somebody!
-All right.
-No! No! No!
They'll get me! Don't take me down!
They'll get me! No!
Don't let the squirrels get me!
Please!
That was a squirrel bite!
Squirrels.
My father died when I was nine.
He was in the army.
He wasn't home very much.
Two weeks before he died...
he told me that
in the Korean War...
it felt like
he'd lost his soul.
All this time
I thought it was me.
I moved seven times
in the last year.
I've, uh, had several jobs.
Nothing seemed to fit.
I don't seem to fit.
And when your father died,
how did that make you feel?
I don't know.
I was nine.
It was like there was
this distinction, suddenly...
between you
and the rest of the world.
I looked around me.
Life went on
just like it did before.
But it wasn't
like it was before.
My uncle helped.
He would visit.
He at least listened.
And I thought...
if I could light my own farts I could
fly to the moon, or at least Uranus.
But if I couldn't do that at least
I could use my penis as a pogo stick...
and that might be a way
of getting around.
I'm sorry?
-Yes, that's good.
-Mm-hmm.
Well, I think you're making fine progress,
Hunter. We'll talk later in group.
Thank you.
Four. Four? Four!
Ohh! Four! Ohh!
You are all insane!
Insane! Four!
Arthur Mendelson.
The Arthur Mendelson?
Brand Beaton Industries.
Guy was one of the most
innovative minds of our time.
Look at him now.
He can't even count the windows.
God. What happened to him?
Why is he here?
Self-committed. Genius syndrome.
Howard Hughes-type shit.
Constantly digging into the
creative potential of the human mind.
I guess he dug too deep.
This is real wood.
Rowff!
W-Why are we meeting in here?
It's cramped.
Well, Everton, we're meeting in here
so that Rudy can participate.
-It's cramped.
-Does anyone else have a thought on that?
-Cramped!
-I think he has a question.
Do you find that funny, Hunter,
making fun of a man's infirmity?
Maybe he does have a question.
He's alive.
-He's catatonic.
-Well, he still has a brain.
-Maybe he wants to participate too.
-Yeah.
Maybe he has a question.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe he knows why we're cramped!
Maybe Beany knows a lot more
than we give him credit for.
Excuse me. Beany?
Which way is heaven?
That's correct!
That'll be enough, Hunter.
Beany, how much taller
is Wilt Chamberlain than you?
Right.
Hey, Beany! Beany!
Where's the ceiling?
That's enough. Stop it.
Where do the birds fly, Beany?
How do you say hello to Hitler?
Beany, how does Hitler say hello?
How do you check
an elephant for a hernia?
Who would win a staring contest?
Beany!
Who-Who farted?
-Who likes to masturbate?
-Yea!
I do! I do!
Hey, Beany, how does an
one-armed referee say "field goal"?
Ha ha! Hey, Beany!
Ciao, Beany!
Arigato, Beany!
Bye, Beany.
It was a really good session,
I thought.
May I come in?
If you bend your medial
collateral ligaments...
and place one talus
in front of another...
I don't see where
you'd have a problem.
Of course, if there were a news story
covering this event...
the headline might read:
"Small Brain Enters Room. "
The fingers.
What's the answer?
Oh, you're another one of
those bright young fellows...
who always know the right answer,
is that it?
Welcome to real life.
How many do you see?
-There are four fingers, Arthur.
-No, no, no. Look at me.
What?
Y-You're focusing
on the problem.
If you focus on the problem,
you can't see the solution.
Never focus on the problem.
Look at me!
How many do you see?
No, look beyond the fingers.
Eight.
Eight. Eight.
Yes! Yes!
Eight's a good answer.
Yes.
See what no one else sees.
See what everyone else
chooses not to see...
out of fear
and conformity and laziness.
See the whole world anew
each day.
Ah, the truth is,
you're well on the way.
If you didn't
see something here...
besides a crazy,
bitter old man...
you wouldn't have come
in the first place.
What do you see
when you look at me, Arthur?
You fixed my cup.
I'll see you around...
Patch.
Rudy, stop.
You're throwing off
my rhythm.
You'll go blind.
-Please.
-I have to go to the bathroom.
Then go. It's right over there,
15 feet away.
-I would, but-
-But what? The squirrels?
-How many?
-There's only one just now.
You can't go to the bathroom
because of one squirrel?
If I get off the bed,
he'll get the others.
That's not the point.
They're squirrels.
Squirrels, Rudy.
They're one of the most
amiable creatures on the planet.
Oh, no, they're not.
On the list of hostile predators,
they're right above the bottom...
just above baby chicks
and slugs.
What could they possibly want?
Your nuts?
-Do you think?
-Oh, Rudy.
-Come on, I'll take you.
-Don't move.
-Another one?
It's on the end of your bed,
on the rail.
Be careful.
It's gonna jump.
-There's one, at the end of the bed!
-Bang!
There's one runnin'
across the sprinkler!
-Boom!
-In back of the door! Back of the door!
Coming out of the bathroom!
Bathroom! Bathroom!
Yea!
Eat lead, fur bag!
Blam! Ha-ha!
-You're cured-Aaah!
-You've got one on your shoulder!
Get it off me! Get it off me!
Get it off me! Aaaah!
We need more cover!
They're comin' in the back door!
Get under cover, Rudy!
Build a fort! Build a fort!
We can build a fort!
-We need a fort!
-Aaah! Down! Get down!
They're gone.
I think it's safe to go
to the bathroom, Rudy. Come on.
-No, it's too risky.
-No.
Not when you have...
this.
-A bazooka.
-Yeah.
Load.
-Let's do it!
-Aaaah!
Yes.
I'd like to leave.
Hunter, we'll have to discuss this
at your scheduled time.
I'm leaving.
Have you thought
about what you'll do?
I want to help people.
Last night with Rudy,
I connected to another human being.
I want more of that. I want to learn about
people, help them with their troubles.
-That's what I do.
-But you suck at it.
You don't even look at people
when they're talking.
I want to listen,
really listen to people.
I can't allow you to leave. I believe
you still have some issues to work out.
Ah. Well, I don't need your permission
because I admitted myself.
-Hunter.
-Mm-hmm?
I must warn you
my report will read "A.M.A."-
that you were signed out of this
hospital "against medical advice. "
And my report will read
"I.D.G.A.R.A."
"I don't give a rat's ass. "
And my name is Patch.
Hello.
How you doin'?
How do you do?
Hey, this is a nice room.
May I help you?
Yeah, I could really use a
foot massage right now.
Rephrasing:
What are you doing here?
I'm your new roommate.
I-I'm moving in.
I don't mean to be rude, but aren't you
a little old to be starting medical school?
You know, Babe Ruth was 39
when he joined the Yankees.
-No, he wasn't.
-You're right.
But I could really use an example like that,
and if you ever find one, let me know.
Hi. Patch Adams.
Mitch Vroman.
Georgetown University.
I was awarded the William F. Thompson
Scientific Achievement Award.
Mmm. Emerson Elementary.
I once drew a picture of a rabbit
that got me two gold stars.
I'm gonna go
back over there now.
First do no harm.
What is implicit in this
simple precept of medicine?
An awesome power.
The power to do harm.
Who gives you this power?
The patient.
A patient will come to you
at his moment of greatest dread..
hand you a knife and say,
"Doctor, cut me open. "
Why?
Because he trusts you.
He trusts you
the way a child trusts.
to do no harm.
The sad fact is...
human beings
are not worthy of trust.
It is human nature to lie...
take shortcuts,
to lose your nerve, get tired...
make mistakes.
No rational patient would
put his trust in a human being...
and were not gonna let him!
It is our mission here...
to rigorously and ruthlessly
train the humanity out of you...
and make you
into something better.
We're gonna make doctors
out of you.
Two years of studying.
I thought we'd have more contact
with patients. Didn't you?
Hi. I'm Patch.
You've just experienced
a North American greeting...
whereby one person offers
a verbal label to another...
as an expression
of welcome and friendship.
Lesbian. Ball-buster.
Airhead. Leech.
Whichever one of these disgusts
you the most, take your pick.
-Well-
-Please pass the word.
I am not here to date. I am not
here to flirt. I'm here to study.
Thank you.
I thought only I could repel women
with that kind of raw efficiency.
Well, you just met your match.
-Patch Adams.
-Truman Schiff.
Nice to meet you, Truman.
Will you go out with me?
May I ask you one question?
Do you buy everything
the dean was saying today?
What do you mean?
I mean, that whole
drill sergeant thing.
"We're gon' make doctors
out of you medical scum.
-Now drop down and give me 20."
-Mm-hmm.
That whole marine thing.
We're not even gonna see
a patient until the third year.
Up until then,
it's just memorizing facts.
-Why don't they just shove the book up-
-Hamburger?
Right here on the colon. That's where
it's going anyway. Thanks very much.
-So, why do you wanna be a doctor?
-I want to help.
I want to connect with people.
A doctor interacts with
people at their most vulnerable.
He offers treatment,
but he also offers counsel and hope.
That's why I love the idea
of being a doctor.
I've always been fascinated by
the development of the human mind.
Ah. Pumping neurons.
We start out so open
and spontaneous.
We're real individuals. Then somewhere
along the way we're drawn to conform.
It's as if we're conditioned
by programmed responses.
Well, that's true.
But sometimes you can alter
the programmed response...
just by changing some of the conditions,
altering the parameters.
Let me show you.
We'll call it
the "hello" experiment.
The goal will be to break through
programmed response...
by changing normal parameters...
and getting a new emotional response
from the person.
Ready to enter data.
Hello.
Hi.
Wait.
I don't get it.
"Hi" is a programmed response.
-I reached her.
-You scared her.
No. Wait.
Wait for it.
Oh, you're nuts.
A smile.
Ten seconds.
Victory.
There's more.
Come, my friend.
-Howdy!
-Hi.
See?
Response time is diminishing.
Yesterday I made
12 random phone calls.
I talked to one man named Dale for
three hours. He told me amazing things.
But what does this all prove,
other than you're out of your mind?
What's the difference between
a doctor and a scientist?
And don't say salary.
People. Hmm? We want to become doctors
because we want to help people.
I want to be
a pediatrician.
Okay, little people.
The point is, we have to treat
the patient as well as the disease.
That's why we have to dive into people,
wade into the sea of humanity, Truman.
Ballroom seven,
right upstairs on your left.
-You guys with the meat packers convention?
-Yes, sir!
Right up the stairs.
Ballroom seven.
-Hey! Does a chicken have lips?
-You'll find out upstairs!
Like a bulldog
on a pork chop!
You know, in New Zealand
they found a whole new use for sheep.
-What's that?
-Wool!
You're funny!
You kill me! You kill me!
-I love you!
-Oh, daddy!
And you-I bet you've heard that too!
Come here! Ha ha!
-"Herd" it? That's a goat joke!
-Ohh!
-Thank you.
On your meat!
Get set! Go!
Ohh! Yeah!
I won!
Pork packers,
rump wrappers, bull shippers,
lend me your steers!
You know, we packers have been
taking a bad rap for years.
Yeah!
Because we all want to be
the best damn packers there are!
-Yeah! Yeah!
-I'm proud of my meat!
-And I know you're proud of your meat!
-Yeah!
-Whip it, zip it and send it out!
You know,
some people say chicken.
-No!
-Some people say fish.
I say,
now is the time for cow!
Eat cow! Eat cow! Eat cow! Eat cow!
Eat cow! Eat cow!
Eat cow! Eat cow! Eat cow!
Hey, bud.
-Hey!
-Oh!
Yes, thanks.
Oh, yeah.
Hey-Whoa!
What is it?
What's the difference between a first-year
and a third-year medical student?
Doctor Vukov, please dial line 1242.
Dr. Vukov,
please dial line 1242.
Here we have
a juvenile onset diabetic...
with poor circulation
and diabetic neuropathy.
As you can see,
these are diabetic ulcers...
with lymphedema
and evidence of gangrene.
Questions?
-Any osteomyelitis?
-None apparent.
Although not definitive.
-Treatment?
-To stabilize the blood sugar.
Consider antibiotics,
possibly amputation.
What's her name?
I was just wondering
the patient's name.
Marjorie.
Hi, Marjorie.
Hi.
Yes, um, thank you.
Let's move on.
-What are you doing?
-Continuing the experiment. Come on.
We can start a lemonade stand together
after we get kicked out of medical school.
Bye, Marjorie.
I cannot stand it in there, Joletta.
He doesn't have
to talk to me like that.
I know, hon, but really,
how good a mood would you be in?
-May I help you?
-Oh, um-
So I'll meet you
at the club.
Oh, great.
Maybe we'll play the back nine, hmm?
Hello. I'm Patch.
I'm studying medicine here.
Well, not here, but-
Y-You know.
Lookit here, Judy.
Another future boss.
Oh, I wouldn't
look at it like that.
You may think
I'm exaggeratin'...
but in another five years
you'll be so full of yourself...
you'll have to hang a cup out your ass
just to catch the excess.
-Joletta!
-Ouch.
Well, hell, why not?
It's the only time in my life
I'm gonna outrank him.
Might as well enjoy it.
Who's in that room?
Don't even think about it.
He'll bite your head off.
Mr. Davis.
Pancreatic cancer.
How long does he have?
Longer than you,
if you go in that room.
So be sure
you steer clear.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Hey!
What year are you?
-Hi.
-Hey.
Dr. Landaker to Administration.
Dr. Landaker
to Administration, please.
Hi.
-What's your name?
-Cameron.
Hi, Cameron.
I'm Patch.
I have a cold. Just a bit of a cold.
Is my nose red?
Oh, it is. It's red.
Ohh! Oh.
What's that?
You don't know?
I don't either.
Let's find out.
Taxi!
Try on you.
Give it to me.
It's working very well.
Let's see what else we have.
Look at some of this stuff.
Bee kisses.
Hi.
-Hi.
-You mind if I sit down?
Hah? Well, then,
hello, hello.
Oh, look at-
Yee-haah!
Whoa! Whoa!
Come on, buddy!
Whee-haah!
What is going on here?
Sit down.
Get in your beds right now.
Sit down! Sit down!
Lie down in your beds
right now!
-I've checked up on you, Hunter.
-Patch.
Hunter, Dr. Prack was
a colleague of mine at Bringham.
He tells me
you have a brilliant mind...
and, like many brilliant people, you don't
necessarily think the rules apply to you.
Not all the rules, sir, but the Golden
Rule, I think that applies to everyone.
Don't you, sir?
I've also heard you have
a real passion to be a doctor, Hunter.
Patch.
Truth of it is, Hunter,
passion doesn't make doctors.
I make doctors.
Understood?
-Understood.
-Good.
Medical students, as a rule, have no
contact with patients until the third year.
-Is that clear?
-It is, sir, but don't you think-
Our way of doing things
is a product of centuries of experience.
It's all there for a reason.
It's my hospital.
I know everything
that goes on inside of it.
Everything.
Deviation of the tongue.
-A problem with the cranial nerve.
-Which side?
-Right side, tenth nerve.
-Twelfth nerve.
Do you know how many billions of dollars
are wasted on malpractice insurance?
That's money that goes to lawyers
that could go to patients.
Hi, guys. Sorry I'm late.
Does everybody know Carin Fisher,
Adelane's roommate?
I invited her to join
our study group.
So, Carin, why do you
want to be a doctor?
Is it just me, or do we
have a lot of work to do?
It's just a question.
I think it's the question.
Actually, I don't find the question
here in the outline.
-What page are you on?
-Uh, 1432.
Deviation of a tongue.
We'd learn more if we were
working closely with patients.
That's why we're studying-
to learn enough to help the patients.
Adelane, don't waste your breath.
Don't you th-
Don't you think
I see through you?
You act like you're above the system
when you're really just a nonconformist.
You have to get
under the fingernails...
of any authority figure
that crosses your path...
as a way of dealing
with some insecurity.
Antisocial personality, I believe.
Intriguing diagnosis.
Truman, this isn't funny. Smart people
flunk out of here all the time.
Yeah, uh, odds are one of
the five of us sitting here, actually.
I have another question.
In a perfect system...
why are patients referred to
by their disease...
as in "that interesting cancer
patient," and not by their name?
It certainly isn't to be mean.
It's to prevent transference.
And why is that bad?
-And the one flunking out is?
-Can we get back to the tongue?
What if a doctor becomes
emotionally involved with a patient?
Does a doctor explode?
No.
Who came up
with these rules?
It's against the Hippocratic oath,
I think.
I don't really have time for this.
Sorry.
Bye.
-Bye.
-Sorry.
-Charming.
-Bye.
-Truman?
-Yeah.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
stop you from studying.
Go away!
I believe there's more
to being a doctor...
than memorizing facts
about the ventricular artery.
I don't care what you think.
I care about my biology test.
Maybe I could help you.
I read the bio book.
The whole book?
Oh, yeah.
Now I'm on to Whitman.
You can get Leaves of Grass at the bookstore
if you have a 20% student I.D. card.
I don't want Walt Whitman.
He wouldn't want you either.
He was a homosexual.
But that's not relevant. What's relevant
is that he was a medical man.
He was a nurse in the Civil War
and wrote great poetry.
"Afoot and lighthearted,
I take to the open road-"
Look, I'm not sure
if you've noticed this...
but in a class of 163 students
there are eight women-eight.
I've had to work
really hard to get here,
and I'm gonna have to
work even harder to stay...
and I'm not about to blow it by wasting my
time on your flighty theories of goodness.
I'm here to learn about medicine.
Period.
Excuse me.
I think somebody is
running away from something.
Why can't it just be that
I'm running away from you?
Hi.
Very nice. Very nice.
Do I look thin to you?
'Cause I'm tryin' to lose
a little weight.
Is this too much?
Have I gone too far?
I got a boner.
I am a boner.
Donner, party of 50!
Donner! Donner party! Over here!
I don't know what's wrong here.
I'm tryin' to light
the dials here, but, uh...
bottom line is,
your TV's broken here.
My name is
Officer Patty O'Furniture.
I'm here today to talk to you
briefly about narcolepsy.
Narcolepsy-
Clown salute!
Very good!
Wide face!
Fart face!
The hospital will cover
all of your bills.
Any other questions?
My name is Doctor... Phil.
I'll be your surgeon-
Oh, there you are.
Ha ha ha! Hey!
Let's get ready to party!
Grazie! Hey! Grazie!
Grazie! Now take a bow!
Don't believe
everything you read.
Looks like you didn't need
that study group after all.
Well, it's no 98,
but I'm still here.
Yeah.
-Excuse me.
-Oh, excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
You know, this completely
disrupts my point of view.
Mm-hmm.
It was so much more convenient
thinking of you as an idiot.
-Don't count me out yet.
-It's frustrating.
I study all night, and I'm barely
hanging on by my fingernails.
Oh, forget about that. I want to
show you something that's extraordinary.
-An enema bulb?
-It used to be.
This amazing piece of rubber...
when applied to your face...
can brighten
another person's day.
Even a suffering patient.
-I'm sure it's really great for kids, but-
-No, not just kids. Anybody.
Patients are opening up
to me, Carin.
They're sharing their dreams,
their fantasies...
and if you hit on
the right topic...
they brighten up
for one brief moment.
They don't concentrate
on the pain.
They don't even feel the pain.
-Try it on.
-No, thank you.
I want you to try it on and help me.
Just try it on.
If you don't laugh,
you'll never see it again.
But if you do,
you have to help me.
Just try it on.
Hmm.
You didn't say anything about a mirror.
Who do you think
you look like?
Karl Malden?
You cheated.
You can take the nose off now.
So, what's the favor?
Psst.
Ready?
Dumbo incoming!
Bag 'im, Bwana!
Killer poodle! You got lucky!
Piranha fish!
Yea! Very good!
Man down!
-What was that?
-It's nothing.
Should I go check?
I said, it's nothin'.
One last one!
Oww!
Well, congratulations, Jackie.
You've done it all. You've nailed
every balloon from here to Timbuktu.
That was incredible, Patch.
Almost as good
as the real thing.
One last safari.
That's all I wanted.
Thank you, Truman.
Both of you.
That was wonderful.
Yes, it's been
a long time for me.
What about you, dear?
What's your fantasy?
Oh.
When I was a little girl...
whenever my mother
would cook spaghetti...
she would let me reach into the pot
and squeeze the noodles.
Oh!
I've always wanted...
to be in a swimming pool
full of noodles...
wall-to-wall
and top-to-bottom.
An entire pool
full of noodles.
Oh.
How about a poodle?
And the award for valor goes to
Truman Schiff and his red welt.
Thank you, Truman.
Located just above my
nasal bone, adjacent to my-
-Glabella!
Good night, Truman.
Right.
Fun's fun, kids, but my welt
and I have a study date...
with the autonomic nerves
of the thorax.
Good luck. Watch out
for the circle of Willis.
Good luck to you.
And our next award, in the tradition
of the great poodle handlers...
where no actual transference
took place-
All right. What you did in there,
it was very nice, I admit.
Whoa. Is that a little ice
that just chipped off?
-You're never serious, are you?
-No. I tried that for years.
Never really worked for me.
-Yeah.
Oh.
Well, I'd better go hit
the thorax as well, so-
I have a crush on you.
Ha! I can't believe I just
blurted that out.
Look, thank you for
taking me along tonight.
I actually had fun.
Good night.
Wait a minute.
When I said I had a crush on you,
you didn't say...
"No way, loser.
I'd rather have a lobotomy by a leper. "
That means something.
Maybe I was just being polite
and I didn't want to hurt your feelings.
But you're not polite.
You're rude.
Sometimes you're downright bitchy.
-Good night.
Dr. Hyer, please dial the pharmacy.
Blue skies
Shining on me
Nothin' but blue skies
Do I see
Bluebirds
Singin' a song
-Are you a doctor?
-No. I'm a medical student.
But if there's anything
I can do to help you-
-You wanna help me?
-Oh, yeah. What can I do?
Listen, you little
do-gooder prick.
If you wanna make yourself feel good,
don't make me pay for it.
Now get out of here,
'cause you don't help shit!
Dr. Maslow, line 214, please.
Dr. Maslow, line 214.
Yo! Ride 'em, cowboy!
Whoo-hoo!
Yea!
Oh! Oh! I surrender!
I'll tell you what you want to know!
Do you wanna tell me what it is
you think you're doing?
Oh.
Uh...
just getting
a few laughs, sir.
The American Journal of Medicine
has found that laughter...
increases secretion
of catecholamines and endorphins...
which in turn increases oxygenation
of the blood, relaxes the arteries...
speeds up the heart,
decreases blood pressure...
which has a positive effect on all
cardiovascular and respiratory ailments...
as well as overall increasing
the immune system response.
Smart clown, eh?
Mr. Adams.
When I told you
I knew Dr. Prack...
did I mislead you in some way
to think I'm a pushover, like he is?
Kindly remove that coat.
I told you you are not to see
the patients till the third year.
I'm just visiting friends, sir.
Why are you here?
If you want to be a clown,
go join the circus.
Patients don't need to be entertained.
They don't need a friend.
They need a doctor.
I don't want to see you
in this hospital again.
What if I visit the patients
on my own time?
Yes, about your own time.
It's been brought to our attention
that perhaps we should be suspicious...
of the level
of your grades.
What are you saying?
I'm cheating?
Your scores are among the top in
your class, yet you never seem to study.
That's ridiculous.
Your classmates
don't seem to think so.
Really. Who?
I'm warning you.
Stay out of this hospital.
You told Walcott I cheated.
I know you did it.
Just tell me why.
Look, cut the crap, Hunter.
I live with you. I know how much
you study, or don't study.
And you do better than me?
Give me a break.
You arrogant, pompous prick! Who appointed
you custodian of the medical profession?
Is it because your father and his father
was a doctor, some sort of genetic thing?
-You're damn right.
-Really?
I grew up with it.
I know what it takes to look in the eyes
of dying people day after day...
and come home
for dinner at night.
-I know what it takes. You don't have it.
-Oh, really. And you do?
If you don't like me,
just say it.
I don't like you!
Why don't you like me?
You're a prick, and I like you.
Because you make
my effort a joke!
I want to be a doctor!
This isn't a game to me!
This isn't playtime!
This is serious business!
I have it in me
to be a great doctor...
but in order to do that I have to
sacrifice if I want to be better.
"Better. "
Better than me, hmm?
I will save lives that
could have otherwise not been saved.
Now, I could be like you and go around
laughing and have a good time, ha ha...
but I prefer to learn,
because the more I learn...
the more likely I will have the right answer
at the crucial moment and save a life.
And you say I'm a prick?
You say I'm a prick?
You know, maybe I am...
but you ask the average person, when
death comes knocking at their door...
whether they want a prick on their side
or some kindergarten teacher...
who's gonna kiss their ass!
Because when that day comes
I want the prick...
and so will you.
You know, I forget
how young you are, Mitch...
that you think you have to be a prick
to get things done...
and that you actually think
that that's a new idea.
You know what I oughta do?
Take it to the state medical board.
There's gotta be some constitutional
right for visiting the sick.
Why don't you
say anything?
Sorry, Patch.
I think Walcott
has a point.
It's a hospital.
People are suffering
and dying.
We're all dying, Truman.
Our job is to increase health.
You know what that means?
That means improving the quality
of life, not just delaying death.
Either way, I-
For your own sake, I th-I think you
should just lay low for a while.
Maybe you're right.
Preview of coming attractions.
Nurse.
"Death. To die. To expire.
To pass on. To perish. "
To peg out. To push up daisies.
To push up posies.
To become extinct.
Curtains, deceased, demised,
departed and defunct.
Dead as a doornail.
Dead as a herring.
Dead as a mutton.
Dead as nits.
The last breath. Paying a debt
to nature. The big sleep.
God's way of saying,
"Slow down. "
To check out.
To shuffle off
this mortal coil.
To head for
the happy hunting ground.
To blink for an exceptionally long
period of time.
To find oneself
without breath.
-To be the incredible decaying man.
-Worm buffet.
-Kick the bucket.
-Buy the farm.
-Take the cab.
-Cash in your chips.
And if we bury you ass up,
we have a place to park my bike.
Whoo! Comin' out of chute number nine,
ridin' that morphine pony!
Whoo-aaah!
Come on now.
Hey, yeah
Let's check out the maternity ward.
You know those chicks put out.
Here we see that the vitreous body
is composed of a transparent jelly...
with a mesh
of collagen fibers.
Lights, please.
Uh, before we adjourn
Dean Walcott has a brief announcement.
He's gonna have the sex change!
Next Monday
the hospital is hosting...
a medical
seminar-slash-retreat...
for the Fellowship of the
American College of Gynecologists.
I'll get the strippers.
It is important that they be
received in a manner suitable...
to their status and position.
I have traditionally selected
an outstanding student...
to head
the welcoming committee.
The time demands are great,
and I wouldn't want to jeopardize...
the academic performance
of a weaker student.
This year I have chosen...
Hunter Adams.
Oh. Well, thank you.
Hunter...
there's a detailed list
of instructions in my office.
Oh, and, uh, the auditorium
could use a good cleaning.
Did you hear him? "In a style according
to their stature and position. "
"I am a great doctor!
Worship me! Spread before me!
Who dares stand?"
You know what I'm thinking? Maybe we
should decorate with a western motif.
How about that?
Ah.
Something with stirrups
and a big banner that says...
"Howdy, gyneroos!
Dilated to meet ya!"
-How about that?
-How about just doing it straight?
-What do you mean?
-As in, straight to graduation.
Oh. If anybody has a problem with this,
please, just walk away right now.
Oh.
All right.
Wow! Yes!
Okay.
They're right on time.
Good morning, Doctor.
Welcome to campus. Good to see you.
How you doing, Doctor?
Uh, gentlemen, I believe that
you'll find the facilities here...
are just perfect
for your purposes today.
We have everything set up
in the auditorium.
If you'd just follow me-
Welcome, cold-handed ones.
It's an honor
to greet-slash-welcome...
so many who have touched so many women
is such a powerful way.
Come on in.
Watch out.
It's a little slippery.
And if you think
it's hot out there-Whoa!
Come on!
Get him
in my office now.
All right, gentlemen,
if, uh-Ahem-
if you'd
just follow me.
You wanted
to see me, sir?
You are dismissed.
Sir.
From this school.
Kindly remove your things...
and vacate the school premises
as soon as possible.
What for?
For asking a group of doctors to have
a sense of humor about themselves?
Oh, I have a sense of humor, Hunter.
I find it hilarious that,
as smart as you are...
you could give me an airtight reason
to throw you the hell out of here!
Why am I such a threat
to you, sir?
Because what you want is for us to get down
there on the same level as our patients...
to destroy objectivity...
all to uphold some
idealistic buddy system...
that will allow you to work through
your own feelings of inadequacy.
What you have done here today...
is inexcusable.
You have made a complete mockery
out of our distinguished guests.
And if you think for one minute...
that I will further tolerate your
blatant disregard of the bylaws of this-
What are you smiling at?
Is this all
a big joke to you?
Get out of here!
Blatant disregard for
school code and procedure.
Defying direct orders
from a dean.
And I am aware
of your creative efforts...
to make sure our visiting gynecologists
feel right at home.
Now, what is it you'd
like me to do for you?
I want to graduate, sir.
Dean Walcott
thinks otherwise...
but my grades
are way above par.
I want to finish school
so I can become a doctor.
Well, I'm gonna give this
to you real straight.
I have a hospital and a medical school
to run here.
I have to trust the people
in my employ...
otherwise their quality of life
will turn to shit.
Their life turns to shit,
my life turns to shit. Do you follow?
-Yes.
-Good.
Now, uh, Dean Walcott is a-
a pain in the ass...
but I depend on him to keep me up to
speed on what's going on around here...
and I would never take the word
of any student over his.
However...
I also have a source
that informs me that your antics...
have improved the quality of life
for the patients.
They don't complain as much,
they take less medication...
and, uh, what's-his-name over in 305
has not thrown his bedpan at a nurse...
in over a week.
-It's Bill.
-Yeah, whatever.
So, from now on you will not
enter that hospital...
unless under the supervision of the
attendant, as part of the curriculum...
and you will steer clear
of Dean Walcott.
Yes, sir.
So I'm still in school?
I wouldn't
send my laundry out...
but, uh, you just
don't screw up, huh?
Come in. Please come in.
Hello?
-Hello.
-Patch?
-Welcome.
-What are you doing?
-I thought we were studying.
-We're studying cellular biology.
Where are you?
Somewhere.
Surprise!
-Happy birthday!
I don't believe this.
Where is he?
-I just saw him around here somewhere.
-Where is he, Truman?
He's here. You gotta find him.
-Patch?
-Ha-ha!
"I do not love you as if
you were a salt rose or topaz...
or the air o'er carnations
that fire shoots off.
I love you as certain dark
things are to be loved...
in secret 'tween
the shadow and the soul. "
We'll finish it later.
What the hell is this?
Hunter.
Hunter, please answer me!
Stop laughing! Truman, I see you!
Who the hell are you? You aren't-
Oh! Oh, damn it!
I hurt my ankle!
Somebody get somebody please!
Someone-Hello? My ankle!
You could have saved yourself
a lot of trouble and just asked me out.
Who said anything
about asking you out?
I heard something
about you.
-That I was in a mental hospital?
-Is it true?
Tried to kill myself.
The mental ward was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
-What did the doctors do to help you?
-The doctors didn't help me.
The patients helped me.
They helped me realize that by helping them
I could forget about my own problems.
And I did.
I really helped some of them.
It was an incredible
feeling, Carin.
There was one patient
named Rudy.
I helped him
be able to pee.
But for the first time in my life,
I forgot about my own problems.
It was an incredible high.
What?
It's just that, um, somebody,
you know, could do for me...
what you did for me tonight
after the way I've treated you.
No one's ever done anything
like that for me before.
Thank you.
Good night.
No, this is not a good night.
This is a great night!
You know?
Hi, I'm John the Baptist.
Any calls?
I've been trying
to reach you.
I love you.
Let's go outside. Okay?
Hey, Bill.
Turquoise is a nice color
on you.
You don't have to say anything.
I know I look good.
My boys.
My boys are beautiful, hmm?
-Yeah.
-Did you see my boys?
Yeah.
She's not bad either.
You think after you're gone,
maybe I could-
Oh, you're killin' me here,
Patch.
S-Sing me that stupid song.
Blue skies smilin' at me
Nothin' but blue skies
Do I see
Bluebirds singin' a song
Nothin' but bluebirds
All day long
Blue days
All of them gone
Nothin' but blue skies
From now on
See you, Bill.
Por favor. Dejeme ver a mi nina!
-I'm sorry, ma'am.
-Somebody speak-Alguien, ayudeme!
-Dejeme ver a mi nina!
-I need the forms filled out.
My baby! My baby!
Ma'am, if you fill out the forms,
you can see her in a moment.
-Alguien-
-Excuse me.
What's going on here?
Oh, drunk driver.
She lost her husband and son.
Her daughter's in Trauma One,
but it doesn't look good.
I need the forms filled out.
-Please! Quiero ver a mi nina!
-You can see her in one moment.
Quiero ver a mi nina!
My baby! Please!
Maybe you could explain
it to me so I might understand it.
It's hospital procedure.
It isn't right that a woman has to spend
the last moments of her dying child...
filling out forms.
Last year I had to have my appendix out.
I forgot my insurance card,
so they sent me home.
My appendix could have burst.
They didn't care.
You know, my antibiotics
cost 100 bucks a month.
I paid $250 just to find out
I had a sprained ankle.
I mean, do they really
need to do all those tests?
You know what they need to do.
The government needs
to pay for health insurance.
Health insurance companies are why
prices got so high in the first place.
-What do we do?
-Yeah, what the hell is the answer?
-Don't hurt your ankle.
-Yeah, right.
-Patch?
-Mm-hmm. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's it.
-I gotta tell Carin.
-What?
Oh.
-Can I borrow this stuff?
-Sure.
-What do you see?
-Patch, it's late.
What do you see?
Parsley.
-And a horn.
-No, no, no.
Look beyond the objects.
Look through them.
Over here. Look.
Kind of let them blur.
Tell me the first thing you see.
-Something with a nose.
-Okay.
Now imagine that's a building
with a nose.
-A free hospital.
-Can I go back to bed now?
-No, no.
Because I'm bursting with ideas,
and I need you to help me.
It'll be the first fun hospital
in the world.
It'll be a totally
free-form building.
It'll have, like, slides
and secret passageways and game rooms.
-Slow down. I can't write that fast.
-I can't slow down.
We'll use humor
to heal pain and suffering.
Doctors and patients
will work side-by-side as peers.
There'll be no titles,
no bosses.
People will come from all over the world to
fulfill their dream of helping other people.
They'll be a community
where joy is a way of life...
where learning is the highest aim,
where love is the ultimate goal.
You have all that?
Yeah, not verbatim,
but the overall insanity's intact.
-That's why you have to help me.
-Patch, no.
-Yes.
-No.
I know it's not gonna be easy, but you
said anything worth doing is difficult.
Look, um-
I'm not like you, Patch.
I want the white coat. I want people
to call me doctor more than anything.
I want the recognition.
You'll get it every day in the
eyes of patients you're helping.
There is more to life than
what Dean Walcott puts out there.
That is all about power
and control, all right?
-I know you're scared.
-You're right. I am scared.
I'm scared to death.
You know, you sit here and you talk
about life without limits...
you know,
and breaking the rules.
It all sounds
very, very romantic.
You wanna know what the truth
is about all that crap, Patch, hmm?
People get hurt.
And who did it to you?
I have to go.
No, don't. Please. No, no.
Listen to me. Come on.
Whatever it is-Come on.
You can tell me.
-I can help you. I swear I can.
-Good night. I'll see you tomorrow.
Please, let me help you.
I'm really starting to love
the back of your head.
Get this cleaned out,
and get him down to the suture room.
You're gonna be fine, Larry.
Larry's been in and out of
the E.R. for a couple of years.
-Not because he's accident-prone.
-No. His father died two years ago.
Since then he's been subject to fits
of depression and self-mutilation.
Head trauma, D-5.
-Thank you for doing this.
-You can thank me by not getting me fired.
Just observe rounds
and stay within hospital protocol.
Look, Patch.
You're a good thing
for this hospital.
You remind me of myself
when I first started out-
on fire,
wanting to save the world.
But you lose a little of that
after a while.
The system is what it is. It's not
perfect, but it's all we have.
Why does it have to be all we have?
Why can't it be changed?
You figure out how, Patch...
and I'll be there for you.
Bed six
needs blood work.
Mrs. O'Bannon
Hello, Ed.
You feeling a little dizzy?
-Yeah.
-Hello, Mrs. O'Bannon.
-May I call you Catherine?
-Mm-hmm.
We're gonna draw a little blood.
Can you tell how many fingers
I'm holding up?
How many do you see?
How many fingers?
How many fingers do you see, Ed?
How much longer do I have
to keep my eyes closed?
Just till I open mine.
Keep 'em closed.
You're almost there.
Not like that. This way.
Come on. Come on.
There you go.
All right.
Here, here.
Hold on to me.
It's just a little further.
Just a little further.
-All right, all right.
-There you go.
There you are.
That's all right.
-You're almost there.
-I'm afraid.
Don't be afraid.
It's gonna be worth it.
All right. Ready?
Watch your step.
There you go.
And... open your eyes.
It's beautiful.
It's 105 acres
of all-natural forest.
Seven streams, two waterfalls.
This is it-the future site
of the Gesundheit Institute.
This is yours?
Not yet,
but it will be soon.
-Come on. There's something else.
-Hmm?
What is it?
Our new home.
Carin, what do you think?
-How did you... find this?
-Him.
Arthur Mendelson. All this is his-
the land, the cottage.
He's letting us borrow it
till we can purchase it.
Mr. Mendelson, I realize that under
the terms of your commitment...
you retained control
of your assets.
Nevertheless-
You learn anything about
proctology yet, Patch?
-A little bit.
-Good.
Take care of this asshole
for me, will ya?
-Nice meeting you.
-Yeah. Mr. Mendelson, uh-
There's room for you.
-Hi, Bile.
-Hey, Patch.
-Who's Bile?
-An old friend.
-Oh.
-Without medical insurance.
He's just staying here
a couple of days.
What do you say?
Think potential.
Hey.
You're certainly a lovely couple.
We can't go on meeting like this.
Ma'am, this card is expired.
Have you a valid card?
Huh? Medicine.
Chinese medicine.
Yeah, yeah. That's painful there.
Uh, hang on a second.
I only have one arm.
Gesundheit.
-Let's go!
-Yeah. Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Hi. How can we help you?
I don't know.
Uh, I h-heard about this place...
and I, I thought maybe
I would get some, uh-
You know, maybe I'd talk to somebody,
because my thoughts-
This is crazy.
Word's getting out we're handling the
overflow from three different clinics now.
I start my pediatric clerkship next week.
I don't know how I'm gonna... keep up.
Anybody call for a doctor in here?
Let's try this right now.
There. Look at that there.
Hey, thank you, Judy and Cissy,
for that lovely medicine.
-How you feeling, Frank? You feel better?
-Yeah, feel better.
Well, keep on your medication. You can
never go wrong if you're a Marxist.
Hey, Patch?
-Yes?
-This is, um-I didn't get your name.
-Uh, Larry.
-Hi, Larry. How are you?
-Good.
-Nice to meet you.
What are you passionate about, Larry?
What excites you?
-What turns you on?
-I like to read.
I love to read. What do you like
to read? Who's your favorite author?
-Mmm, Kazantzakis.
-Kazantzakis.
Oh. "World is trouble.
Man needs a little madness, or else-"
"Or else he dare not
cut the rope and be free. "
That's great, Larry.
That's wonderful.
We're gonna get along just fine.
Truman.
Yeah, Patch. What?
Can you come over here
and show Larry around?
-Nice having you here, Larry. Welcome.
-Thanks. Okay.
-I've seen Larry in the E.R. before.
-He's weird.
I'm weird. If we don't
show him compassion, who will?
What's that name again? Right.
-Hi.
-Everyone asleep?
-Yeah.
But it ain't me.
You okay?
-Yeah.
-Hmm.
God, Patch, it's amazing.
What?
Just what you've done
with this place, you know.
-You too.
-Well.
These people
that we're helping-
they would have had
nowhere to go.
You're a good man.
What are we?
Is it me?
I mean, are we just-are we
good friends that occasionally kiss?
Patch...
my entire life...
men have been...
attracted to me.
My entire life.
When I was a little girl...
I would look out my bedroom window
at the caterpillars.
I envied them so much.
No matter
what they were before...
no matter...
what happened to them...
they could just hide away,
you know...
and turn into these beautiful
creatures that could fly away...
completely untouched.
I hated men so much.
I wanted nothing
to do with them.
Then I met you.
The way that
you help people, Patch-
The changes I see
in everybody that's around you-
I love you.
I've loved you for so long.
You scared me.
I was watching you sleep.
I have a real knack.
Impressive, hmm?
"I love you
without knowing how...
"or when or from where.
-I love you straight-"
-Patch.
Um, sorry.
It's okay.
Uh, we have a situation
out here...
that needs attention.
I've been trying
to warn you guys about this...
and now we have
absolutely zero supplies.
There's an older gentlemen over there.
He has a sprained shoulder.
I don't have any slings.
I had to wrap his arm in his own belt.
We have no iodine. We don't even
have any gauze, for God's sake.
There's an entire supply room
at the hospital.
That couldn't possibly be because
those supplies belong to the hospital.
No.
That's too obvious.
Come on.
I need your feet, and I want your body.
-Come on.
-Bye.
Behave.
Would you hurry, please?
This stuff is crushing me.
Quiet. You're a corpse.
-Ow!
-Shh!
-Damn it!
-Watch it!
-Quiet. Shut up!
Yeah, uh, this is Larry.
Uh, I was wondering i-if
somebody could come over.
Uh-
I'm not doin' too well.
Um-
I was, I was-I-It would help
if I could talk to somebody.
Uh... okay.
Hello?
Larry?
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I didn't know you could play.
You sound wonderful.
Thank you.
And this house-it's amazing.
Is it yours?
It's my father's.
He left it to me.
Here.
Let me take your jacket.
Sure.
-You okay?
-Yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Uh, come in.
Come in.
Thanks.
I really can't stay very long.
I just wanted to see how you were doing.
Yeah, you're right.
No, we don't wanna be late.
Patch.
-Oh.
-You just got a telephone call.
Dean Anderson wants to see you
in his office immediately.
Oh, no. Walcott found out
about our borrowed supplies.
We're dead.
Ye of little faith.
Dean Anderson, I know what this is
all about, and I assure you, sir-
Sit down.
Something happened last night.
Carin Fisher was murdered.
She was with Lawrence Silver.
There was a shotgun involved,
and then he turned the gun on himself.
Jesus Christ, Patch, I'm sorry.
I know she was a friend.
If there's, um,
anything I can do-
Hell of a deal.
"Into Your hands, O Merciful Savior...
we commend
Your servant Carin.
Receive her into the arms
of Your mercy,
into the blessed rest
of everlasting peace,
and into the glorious company
of the saints... on high. "
Amen.
Told you I'd finish it
some other time.
Guess now's okay.
"I love you without knowing
how... or when...
or from where.
I love you straightforwardly,
without complexities or pride.
I love you because I know
no other way than this.
So close...
that your hand on my chest
is my hand.
So close
that when you close your eyes...
I fall asleep. "
I'm sorry, honey! I'm sorry!
We can't disband.
You know that, right?
What about our patients?
What do we tell them?
They'll manage.
They managed before.
-I refuse to quit.
-Good.
God, you're being
so self-indulgent.
This has been your vision, but we all built
this place and it belongs to all of us.
Carin will always remain
within these walls.
If you walk away from that,
if you let that all die-
I've dedicated
every spare moment I have...
to assisting you in what I believe
is a pure and a good purpose.
Quitting is not going
to help you get through this.
-You've always told us-
-Stop it!
I've always told you what?
People are good.
Trust people? Ha!
You know, Truman...
in all of God's creations, only
human beings kill their own species.
There's a fun fact
for your final exam.
Carin's death cannot make
helping people wrong.
She saw it coming.
She knew there was something dangerous
about Larry. I didn't see it.
Patch,
why are you being like this?
Because I killed her,
Truman.
I taught her the medicine
that killed her.
She'd still be here
if I hadn't met her.
You can't leave.
If what you say is true, looks like
I'm defying the laws of possibility.
What are you doing?
Oh, I can't leave
until you beat me, is that it?
Okay. I surrender.
You're number one.
You're the top student in the class.
You're smarter than me.
Is that what you want to hear?
Now can I leave?
You know Mrs. Kennedy
in 212?
She doesn't eat.
I visited her room every day
for the last three weeks.
I can't get her to eat.
Now, I know everything
there is to know about medicine.
I've studied relentlessly.
I guarantee you I can outdo, outdiagnose any
attending and surgeon in this hospital.
But I can't make her eat.
You have a gift.
You have a way with people.
You know, they like you.
And if you leave,
I can't learn this way.
So what now, huh?
What do You want from me?
Yeah, I could do it.
We both know
You wouldn't stop me.
So answer me, please.
Tell me what You're doing.
Okay,
let's look at the logic.
You create man.
Man suffers enormous amounts
of pain.
Man dies.
Maybe You should have had just
a few more brainstorming sessions...
prior to Creation.
You rested
on the seventh day.
Maybe You should have spent
that day on compassion.
You know what?
You're not worth it.
Do you still want help
with Mrs. Kennedy?
Hey, Aggie.
We have a special
surprise for you.
Surprise!
Benvenuto, Aggie!
Aggie! Aggie!
Grab ahold, Aggie!
There you go.
Oh!
-Oh.
-Come on in, Aggie.!
Y-Yes.
Pasta angels, Aggie! Pasta angels!
Patch?
Hey. I'm supposed
to give you this.
You turn around and
walk right out of here.
Why?
Everything will be delineated
in your letter of dismissal.
-Why?
-You don't fit in.
There are standards
and codes.
You make the patients and everyone
else around you uncomfortable.
I make you uncomfortable.
Well, you can make this into
a personal issue if you'd like.
But the reality is,
you are not cut out to be a physician.
-And it is my responsibility-
-Responsibility?
You have one responsibility-to be
a dick-head. How hard can that be?
All you have to do is make sure your head
is a dick and it's attached to your neck.
-You leave immediately.
-I wanna see my records.
They're confidential.
Only the staff-
Please,
you have to have permission.
You can't just go in there
and take your own file!
Your marks are basically perfect.
You've gotta be near
the top of the class.
Look at this.
"Excessive happiness. "
-Actually says you're excessively happy?
-Mm-hmm.
And what does that mean?
Isn't that good?
-I gotta fight this.
-What can we do?
Dean Walcott seems thoroughly committed
to your not ever becoming a doctor.
Even Dean Anderson
signed this.
Nah, I'm screwed.
I like this.
You need my help.
I prefer to think
I'm using you.
-You have one shot.
-Mm-hmm.
You'd have to appeal to
the state medical board.
How does that work?
You claim that a prejudice
and injustice has occurred.
They'll be worried about a suit.
They'll have to investigate.
Then what?
-They'll review your grades, which is good-
-Mm-hmm.
you're almost
top of the class-
but mostly your behavior.
Do you have any idea
what Walcott has on you?
How'd you get these?
Don't ask.
They can't prevent me from graduating
because of a personality clash, can they?
Hunter, this is a medical institution
you're dealing with.
They draw their own law.
You'll have to get their focus
on your high marks and off of this.
I'm screwed, aren't I?
You're almost a doctor.
They're a panel of doctors.
Just think of them as your peers...
and return these.
Yeah.
And get a suit.
Hunter Adams.
You've been accused of
practicing medicine without a license.
That's a very
grave charge, son.
Are you aware that it's unlawful to practice
medicine without a medical license?
Yes, sir, I am.
Are you aware that running a medical
clinic without the proper licensing...
can place both you
and the public...
in a great deal of danger?
Is a home a clinic, sir?
If you are admitting patients
and treating them...
physical location
is irrelevant.
Sir, will you define
treatment for me?
Yes. Treatment would be defined as the care
of a patient seeking medical attention.
Have you been treating patients,
Mr. Adams?
I live with several people.
They come and go as they please.
I offer them
whatever help I can.
Mr. Adams...
have you or have you not
been treating patients at your ranch?
Everyone who comes to the ranch
is a patient, yes.
And every person who comes
to the ranch is also a doctor.
I'm sorry?
Every person who comes
to the ranch is in need...
of some form of physical
or mental help.
They're patients.
But also every person who comes to the ranch
is in charge of taking care of someone else-
whether it's cooking for them,
cleaning them...
or even as simple a task
as listening.
That makes them doctors.
I use that term broadly, but is not a
doctor someone who helps someone else?
When did the term "doctor" get
treated with such reverence, as,
"Right this way, Doctor Smith"...
or, "Excuse me, Dr. Scholl,
what wonderful footpads"...
or, "Pardon me, Dr. Patterson,
but your flatulence has no odor"?
At what point in history
did a doctor become more...
than a trusted and learned friend
who visited and treated the ill?
Now, you ask me if
I've been practicing medicine.
Well, if this means opening
your door to those in need-
those in pain-
caring for them, listening to them, applying
a cold cloth until a fever breaks-
if this is practicing medicine,
if this is treating a patient...
then I am guilty
as charged, sir.
Did you consider the ramifications
of your actions?
What if one of your patients
had died?
What's wrong
with death, sir?
What are we so mortally afraid of?
Why can't we treat death
with a certain amount...
of humanity and dignity and decency...
and, God forbid, maybe even humor?
Death is not the enemy,
gentlemen.
If we're gonna fight a disease, let's fight
one of the most terrible diseases of all-
indifference.
Now, I've sat in your schools and heard
people lecture on transference...
and professional distance.
Transference
is inevitable, sir.
Every human being
has an impact on another.
Why don't we want that in
a patient/doctor relationship?
That's why I've listened to your
teachings, and I believe they're wrong.
A doctor's mission should be
not just to prevent death...
but also to improve
the quality of life.
That's why you treat a disease,
you win, you lose.
You treat a person, I guarantee you,
you win, no matter what the outcome.
Now here today, this room
is full of medical students.
Don't let them anesthetize you. Don't let
them numb you out to the miracle of life.
Always live in awe of the
glorious mechanism of the human body.
Let that be the focus of your studies
and not a quest for grades...
which'll give you no idea what kind
of doctor you will become.
Please try and address the board.
Don't wait till you're on the ward
to get your humanity back.
Start your interviewing skills.
Start talking to strangers.
Talk to your friends,
Talk to wrong numbers, everyone.
-Mr. Adams!
-And cultivate friendships...
with those amazing people in the back of
the room-nurses that could teach you.
They've been with people every day.
They wade through blood and shit.
They have a wealth of knowledge,
and so do the professors you respect-
the ones who are not dead
from the heart up.
Share their compassion.
Let that be contagious.
Mr. Adams, I demand that you turn
and address the board.
Sir, I want to be a doctor
with all my heart.
I wanted to become a doctor
so I could serve others...
and because of that
I've lost everything...
but I've also
gained everything.
I've shared the lives of patients
and staff members at the hospital.
I've laughed with them.
I've cried with them.
This is what I want to do
with my life.
And as God is my witness...
no matter what your decision
today, sir...
I will still become the best damn doctor
the world has ever seen.
Now you have the ability
to prevent me from graduating.
You can keep me from getting
the title and the white coat.
But you can't control
my spirit, gentlemen.
You can't keep me from learning.
You can't keep me from studying.
So you have a choice-you could
have me as a professional colleague...
passionate...
or you can have me as an
outspoken outsider, still adamant.
Either way, I'll probably
still be viewed as a thorn.
But I promise you one thing.
I am a thorn
that will not go away.
Is that all?
I hope not, sir.
We will adjourn briefly.
Thank you.
Hunter Adams.
We find your methods
less than appealing.
Your appearance and your demeanor
do not reflect...
what we believe
is necessary...
to earn a patient's trust
and respect.
You openly accuse us of adhering
to time-honored practices...
that for years have been the backbone
of the entire medical institution.
However...
we find no fault
in your attempts...
to improve the quality of life
around you.
We find no fault
in your desire...
to expand upon existing
medical practices...
and theories.
We applaud your love
of the patient.
Your grades are among
the highest in your class...
and, therefore, we find
no merit in the decision...
to block your graduation
from medical school.
Now, along with your crass
and disdainful behavior...
you carry with you a flame...
which one could only hope...
would spread through
the medical profession like a brushfire.
And, uh, Dean Walcott...
in the future,
I think matters like this...
could best be solved if you yourself
would practice a little...
"excessive happiness. "
Well, today you go...
from being students in a class
to being members of a class-
a very select class.
You face the future
with your heads held high...
because you are now...
doctors.
Dr. Michael Ames.
Dr. Doris Ackerman
Dr. Hunter "Patch" Adams.
Yea, Patch!
Well, I'm happy to see
you've finally decided to conform.
More than you know, sir.