We are here.
At 8,000 feet. This is it, boys.
You got it, Zamp?
Roger.
You hit this one, drinks are on me.
I ain't going to a bar
with you, handsome.
You confuse all the broads.
Get your cameras, boys.
I'm gonna light it up like Christmas.
Pilot to bombardier, your ship.
Bombardier to pilot. Roger.
Bombardier to crew, bomb bay doors open.
Bay doors open!
Damn flak.
Oh, boy!
Come on.
Come on, Zamp.
There you are.
Bombs away.
- Bombardier to pilot, your ship.
- Roger.
Okay.
Here we go.
Yeah, just like Christmas.
Bomb bay doors are stuck.
- Zero, inbound, 10 o'clock, level.
- All right.
Here they come, boys. Call them out.
Gotta get those doors closed, Zamp.
Roger.
Get them, get them, get them, Mitchell.
Coming in high at nine o'clock.
Coming level to three.
Take 'em out, Mitchell.
Low, he's going low.
Brooks, he's going down.
He's coming to your side.
Glassman! Glassman!
Okay, okay.
I know, I know. I know.
Let me take a look at you.
I know, buddy, I know.
Just be brave now, all right?
You're still good looking.
You're still very handsome.
You make me sick!
Help me!
Yeah!
I know.
You got it, buddy. You got it.
I'm right here.
- I want to go home.
- You will, Harry.
You will. All right?
You think about home. Okay?
Oh, boy.
Louie?
Lambert.
Here, take this. All right? Take this.
Okay. It's okay. Take this.
Pillsbury?
Nice work, boys.
Everything's shot up back there, Phil.
We got no hydraulics
but we're still flying.
We got no flaps, Phil.
So basically we got no brakes.
How far to base?
I don't know. Five hours.
If we make it that far.
The runway is over 6,000 feet, but we're
gonna need at least 10 if we got no brakes.
God created two great lights.
The greater light to rule over the day,
and the lesser light
to rule over the night.
Now these things,
light and dark, day and night,
are separated from each other.
God created each in its place.
He did not create a battle between them.
He said, "I have created
both of these things."
You must live through the night.
Don't battle with it.
For God said, "the night also is mine."
He sent his son, Jesus,
not to do battle.
Not to wage war on the sins of man,
but to forgive them.
Forgive the sin.
Smile on the sinner.
Accept the darkness.
Live through the night.
Love thine enemy.
Zamperini!
facebook.com/groups/getdirectlink/
In this group you will be able to get Direct Download link of Movies and TV Shows.
Is that garlic I smell?
What are you doing, wop?
Hey, why don't you go back to Italy?
You and your greasy wop family.
- Get him up.
- Get up.
- Hey! Hey!
- Get off him!
Stay down. Dumb dago.
- Hey! Hey!
- Get him off me!
Jesus.
Hey!
- Oh, shit!
- Go, go, go.
Only reason
you're not in reform school now
is because of the respect
we have for your parents.
Everybody in town wants you put away.
Sorry, Louise. He was fighting again.
And... we found this.
He painted the bottle. It's liquor.
What do you think?
He's kinda cute, right?
Come on, Jimmy, pick it up! Go, go, go!
Come on, Pete! Go!
Come on, pass him!
Is someone down there?
Who's down there?
- This is so dumb.
- Since when were you so smart?
- Come on. Faster.
- Why? No one's chasing me.
I'm chasing you.
I can't do this, Pete. I'm not like you.
I'm nothing. Just let me be nothing.
- What are you talking about?
- I can't make a track team.
- I don't even know why you want me to.
- Yes, you can.
If you can take it, you can make it.
What?
All right. You train and you fight
way harder than those other guys.
And you win.
You get out from under them.
Or you keep going the way you're going
and you end up as a bum in the streets.
You can do this, Lou.
Just gotta believe you can.
I don't believe.
I do.
Come on.
Come on!
You dumb dago!
Come on, Louie!
Boy, oh, boy, can that guy fly.
They're calling him
The Torrance Tornado.
This kid Zamperini runs like his feet
never touch the ground.
Come on! Come on! Keep going!
Come on, Louie!
Come on, Louie! Come on, Louie!
Come on, come on, come on!
The Torrance Tornado smoked the mile
in 4 minutes, 21.3 seconds.
Zamperini is now officially the fastest
high school runner in American history.
Folks, this kid is on his way
to the Olympics!
Why would I come?
You're not going to win.
Sure. I know that. It's all right.
Four years' time, next Olympics,
that's when I show them.
This is just the tryouts for me.
- Tokyo.
Smart kid.
Take care of yourself, all right?
Go have a little fun, too.
Say hi to those pretty
German broads for me.
You know it.
Come here.
Thanks, Pete.
For everything.
Go on.
Louie.
A moment of pain
is worth a lifetime of glory.
You remember that.
- Gear is down.
- All right, here we go.
Still coming in pretty hot. 110.
Almost.
Still too fast.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay.
Flat tire.
Thank you, God.
Now you're praying?
I was busy before.
My mother does that sometimes.
Yeah. A lot of people do this.
He say anything back?
- Yeah.
- What?
He says my bombardier is a dope.
Really?
All right, buddy.
Now!
Come on, Louie!
Keep on, buddy.
Keep pushing.
Whoa!
Yeah?
Oh, boy!
4:12. Getting close.
I hope you're not that fast in the sack.
Oh, boy.
Wrap it up, speedy.
We got a mission.
Not a combat mission. Rescue.
B-24 en route to Kanton never made it
so looks like those boys ditched.
A lot of ocean.
Yeah. And... they got us some new crew.
We get a new plane?
This is just like sitting in a living room
trying to fly the house.
They've been taking parts off this
for other planes.
We're lucky it's still got an engine.
Lieutenant says it's airworthy.
It's been certified, he says.
By Helen Keller.
Lot of ocean.
Yeah. Lot of ocean.
- Mitchell.
- Yeah.
You're up.
So a duck walks into a bar, right?
Or, waddles, if you will.
So, he walks into the bar,
he says to the bartender,
"can I have a crème de menthe?"
Hang on, there.
All right, number one is out.
- Other engines are burning more fuel.
- Gotta feather it.
Hey...
- What's his name?
- I don't know.
Engineer? Can you come up
to the cockpit and feather the engine?
- What's going on, guys?
- Co-pilot to radio. Send to base.
- Which one?
- The left.
- We need more on the right.
- That's all we got on the right.
- We need more on the right!
- Damn it!
- Left engines are both gone.
- That's everything on the right, Phil.
- Okay.
- Hey, Phil?
- Yeah?
Is this a...
Prepare to crash.
Waist gunner! Get the rations box.
Tie the guns down.
- Who's on the raft?
- Glassman!
- Send Mayday.
- Is everyone in position?
- Anyone on the rafts?
- Yeah.
I got it!
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday!
This is Green Hornet. We are going down.
Okay.
Everybody brace.
Brace!
In an astounding performance,
negro American Jesse Owens from Ohio State
has won four gold medals in the 100 meter,
the 200 meter, the long jump
and the 400 meter relay.
Next up, the 5,000 meter
with America's record-breaking
Don Lash leading the American team.
Along with newcomer Louie Zamperini.
Fertig!
And already,
three sections of runners have formed
with America's Don Lash and the Finnish
Salminen and Höckert ahead of the pack.
The Finns always the favorite
in this long-haul event.
In the second group
is America's Louie Zamperini.
The Finns, Höckert,
Lehtinen and Salminen have set the pace
and they are not letting up.
And Zamperini is fading, too,
dropping further back.
And into the 8th lap
it's the Finns still in the lead,
with Salminen in first place.
Come on, Louie.
And we start the last lap.
The Finns seem to be in control.
It doesn't look like Don Lash
is gonna bring home the medal for the USA.
There seems to be
some movement back in the pack.
Yes, that's Zamperini
overtaking Norway's Rolf Hansen.
He seems to have some gas in reserve.
He really is making up some time.
Höckert and Lehtinen will be one and two.
But look at that Zamperini!
He's got Don Lash in his sights.
Well, the great Don Lash is not
gonna be the first American, folks.
It's high school kid Zamperini pushing past
the record-breakers on this field!
I have not seen that!
That final lap, folks,
the record for that was 69.2 seconds.
Zamperini just did it in 56 seconds.
That record is going to hold
for a while, let me tell you.
All right, Phil. Okay, buddy. All right.
On three. Two. Three.
Okay.
All right, here we go.
Glassman didn't make it.
- Cup didn't make it.
- Don't think about it, Mac.
- We're gonna die.
- No, we're not, Mac.
- They don't know where we are.
- They'll find us.
They'll never see us.
Tell him to shut up.
- Shut up, Mac.
- We're gonna die out here.
Come on, Mac, shut up.
Hey, Mac, chocolate.
One square at night,
one square in the morning.
All right?
Mac?
Two or three sips a day, yeah?
We gotta make it last.
Zamp?
- Zamp?
- Yeah, yeah?
Yeah, Phil?
I'm glad it's you.
Yeah, I'm glad it's me, too.
What was that?
Mac! Mac! Mac, come on!
Get the dye, Mac. Get the dye.
- Hey!
Hey!
Down here!
- Hey!
- Turn around!
You son of a bitch!
Turn around!
What did you do, Mac?
- It doesn't matter.
- It doesn't matter?
It doesn't matter?
It doesn't matter.
Jesus!
Get it, Mac! Get it.
I don't think I can do it.
We gotta try.
We had to try.
You know what?
Maybe the fish won't be so picky.
- Oh, boy.
- Yeah?
I got one. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Attaboy, Phil!
Here, here, here.
Damn it.
Okay.
Come here, Mac.
Come on.
Okay.
Buon appetito.
Good?
This is how the Japanese eat fish. Raw.
If you ask me,
it's not food until you cook it.
Little lemon,
little garlic...
When we get home, come around my house.
Mama will cook for ya.
You remember that story in Life Magazine
about Eddie Rickenbacker?
Him and his crew ran out
of fuel over the pacific.
They were drifting in rafts for 24 days.
Twenty-four days.
- They made it, right?
- Yeah.
Most of them lost their minds.
But they made it.
We gotta keep talking.
Gotta keep our minds sharp.
Hey, I'll tell you what else
you're gonna love. Mama's gnocchi.
- Italians.
- Nobody...
Nobody a-make-a gnocchi like her.
So light.
Like clouds.
First, she makes the dough
out of very fine flour.
So fine, it's like talcum powder.
Then she uses lots of eggs,
like, maybe 12.
And then she beats them up, Mac.
Beats them up.
And she drizzles them over.
...thou me on
The night is dark
And I am far from home
Lead thou me on
Do you think God made the stars, Phil?
Yes, I do.
So you think there's some
kind of a grand plan?
Why did we live and the others didn't?
Why are we here now?
Here's the plan.
You go on living the best you can.
You try to have some fun along the way.
Then one day it's over.
You'll wake up
and there's an angel
sitting at the edge of your bed.
Angel says,
"Okay,
"you can ask me
all those dumb questions now
"because I got all the answers."
That's what you believe?
Yeah.
That's what I believe.
Our father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
If you get me through this,
if you answer my prayers
I swear I'll dedicate
my whole life to you.
I'll do whatever you want.
Please.
Mac.
Here we go.
- Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
- All right, all right.
You got it?
Jeez.
Just a scratch.
- How is it?
- Stinks.
That's the bandage,
not you.
We beat Rickenbacker's record
four days ago.
You're keeping count?
Yeah.
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
Hey!
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Hey!
- Get out, boys. Get out!
- I can't!
Come on!
- Mac?
- Still here.
- Phil?
If the Japs are this bad,
we might even win this damn war.
Shit.
Phil.
Here.
Mac.
Did you see that surprise Mac attack?
Came down on that thing
like a goddamn dive bomber.
Damn sharks were scared shit.
He saved your skinny ass.
1937. Baseball MVP.
Kid from Detroit.
Gehringer.
Hey, Mac, get in the game.
facebook.com/groups/getdirectlink/
In this group you will be able to get Direct Download link of Movies and TV Shows.
- Mac?
- Still here.
Still here.
What are you gonna make
for breakfast, Zamp?
It's your call.
Your mother's gnocchi.
Gnocchi for breakfast?
Why not?
Am I gonna die?
Maybe, Mac.
You think tonight?
Maybe.
Yes, sir.
I think tonight.
So you got your dough...
and you roll it out.
Just rolling it out.
Good, no lumps.
Phil?
I got good news...
and bad news.
Phil?
Zamp?
You okay?
Land feels funny.
Funny.
Yeah.
Stop!
Stop it.
Please, stop it.
Colonel would like to know
disposition of troops in Hawaii.
I don't know.
Speak up!
I wouldn't know.
I haven't been there in...
Is this you?
You are famous Olympic athlete.
Colonel would like to know
location of radar in E-class, B-24.
We used the old one. D-class.
- You bombardier?
- Yes.
What happened to the marines
from Makin Island?
How you work the Norden bombsight?
You just twist two knobs.
What happened to the marines?
Draw Norden bombsight.
They were beheaded.
Fuck!
Take off clothes.
Kneel down.
Kneel down?
Kneel down!
- No, no! No, no!
- Phil?
- Zamp!
Zamp!
This is Tokyo, right?
Must be.
I was supposed to race here
for the Olympics...
before they got canceled.
Yeah?
I always wanted to come to Tokyo.
Careful what you wish for, fella.
Soldier. Soldier.
Officer.
Soldier.
Good evening, old prisoners.
Welcome, new hands.
This is Omori detention camp.
I am Corporal Watanabe.
You are enemies of Japan.
You will be treated accordingly.
Look at me.
Look me in the eye.
Look at me!
Don't look at me.
New prisoners,
you are not dismissed.
You will stand a quarantine.
We cannot have disease in the barracks.
- Evening, chaps.
- Evening, sir.
Tom Miller, your barrack commander.
Let's get you settled
into your bunks, shall we?
You're up top.
facebook.com/groups/getdirectlink/
In this group you will be able to get Direct Download link of Movies and TV Shows.
you're here next to sleeping beauty.
Take a pew.
307, you're in here.
You are?
- Frank Tinker.
- Tinker, you're up top.
I see you met the bird.
- Why do you call him "the bird"?
- Because he listens.
And if he heard the names
we'd like to call him, he'd kill us.
Apparently he grew up wealthy.
Wanted to be an officer.
Expected to be, too.
And was denied, which obviously
hasn't gone down too well.
Of course, none of this explains
his erratic behavior.
Commander Fitzgerald.
Zamperini, sir.
They were looking for answers.
Didn't get any though, did they?
Not one bit.
You should get some shut-eye.
Yes, sir.
Infirmary, turning right!
Dismissed!
Officers, turning right!
There is much talent in Omori camp.
We have an opera singer.
Who is the opera singer?
We have a chef...
from Sydney, Australia.
And we have an Olympic athlete.
Who is the Olympic athlete?
Don't get up.
You fail.
You are nothing.
Sir?
He's tracing so we can return it
before the Japs find out.
He's got most of the war mapped out.
We've invaded the Marshall Islands.
The US have invaded
the Marshall Islands.
Allies are gaining ground.
- You know, I gotta say...
- Please don't.
For a bunch of guys who don't eat anything
we sure do shit a lot.
Oh, yeah.
I think that one is mine.
You like Saipan?
I'm gonna kill him.
- Then they shoot you.
- I don't give a damn. Let them shoot me.
That's not how we beat them.
We beat them by making it
to the end of the war alive.
That's how we do it.
That's our revenge.
If I can take it, I can make it.
Precisely.
My brother Pete used to say that.
He used to think that I could do anything.
He used to think
that I was better than I am.
Who says you're not?
We're getting closer.
Why do you make me hit you?
You are dead.
In America, they say Zamperini dead.
They tell your family you died in war.
NBC radio tell America
famous Olympic runner Zamperini is dead.
You want to tell family you're not dead?
These gentlemen,
they're from radio Tokyo.
We have program go all over world.
It is name Postman Calls.
"Hello, mother.
"Your son is calling you.
"Mother, I love you.
"I'm alive and well."
- I'm only saying my own words.
- Of course.
Hello, America.
This is The Postman Calls.
Today The Postman calls
for Mrs. Louise Zamperini
of Torrance, California.
Louie Zamperini is not missing,
and not dead as erroneously announced
by your government.
He is safe and sound with us.
So keep listening, Mrs. Zamperini...
and don't mention it.
The pleasure is all ours.
Hello, mother and father,
sisters and friends.
This is your Louie talking.
And the first time in two years
that you will have heard my voice.
I am uninjured and in good health.
I am now interned
in a Tokyo prisoner of war camp
being treated as well as can be expected
under wartime conditions.
I hope Pete is still able to pay you
his weekly visits from San Diego.
Dad...
Keep my guns in good condition
so we can go hunting when I get home.
Get some good rabbits
for Mom's gnocchi sauce.
I wish you all a merry Christmas
and a happy new year.
Your loving son, Louie.
You were good. Very good.
You can speak on radio again.
I can't say this.
- Why not?
- Because it's not true.
What it says about America,
I can't say that.
They say that.
American like you.
They live here. Very comfortable.
Good food.
They have lovely food.
You want to go back to camp?
You make broadcast.
You are like me.
We are both strong.
I saw it in your eyes...
the first day.
I thought...
this man will be my friend.
But...
enemy of Japan.
You do not listen.
You do not do what is asked of you.
It is necessary to have respect.
No respect...
no order.
This man must be taught respect.
All other prisoners
will teach him this lesson.
Each prisoner...
will punch this man in his face.
Sir...
We cannot do that.
Do it.
Do it, sir. Come on.
Just get it over with.
Punch him in the face.
Come on.
Punch him!
- Next!
- Go on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Next!
Okay. Come on, come on, sir.
Come on.
- Hit hard!
- Come on! Hit me!
Next!
Come on, Tink, hit me good. Go on.
Come on.
Next!
Hit hard!
Harder!
Next!
- Cinderella!
Cinderella!
Where is that naughty little maggot?
Have you seen her, fella?
There you are, you lazy little girl.
How am I supposed to get ready for the ball
with you sitting there doing nothing?
That's as useful to us
as our morning dance routines.
Fix my dress so I can catch the eye
of the dreamy prince Hillenbrand.
You couldn't catch the eye of a prince
if it fell in your lap.
Come, Cinders, fix my hair.
Fix my dress!
- Fix my hair!
- Dress!
- Hair, hair, hair!
- Are you speaking kraut now?
Enough! Enough!
You guys make me do all these stupid,
impossible things with no food and no rest!
You lock me up in a rabbit hutch.
I've had enough!
I have good news.
I have had a promotion.
That's the good news.
The bad news?
I say goodbye to my friends.
I leave Omori tomorrow.
Nothing in this life
is hopeless, Cinders.
If you keep your head and your heart
you can do anything!
Fear not, dear child...
I am your fairy godmother.
You may congratulate me.
And there he goes.
Just like that.
I have got...
four kings.
And there you go.
The baron's been beaten, Tinker.
- Oh, yeah?
- Sugar for us tonight.
- Got it, Miller?
- Send another bucket!
We're helping the Japs now?
- Might as well let it burn.
- Pass it down!
There you go.
B-29s, boys!
Won't be long now.
I wouldn't get too excited.
If the allies win,
the Japs issue kill-all orders.
I overheard them.
We win, we're dead.
Well, what are we supposed
to be praying for?
Down! Get down!
Grab your gear. They're moving us out.
- To where?
- I don't know. Some new camp.
Tokyo Ritz.
Some place the allies can't find us.
This is Naoetsu prison camp.
I am Sergeant Watanabe,
your commanding officer.
You are enemies of Japan.
You will be treated...
accordingly.
You will help the Japanese
by working on the coal barges.
Anyone who will not work...
will be executed.
Why don't you look me in the eye?
You boys can sleep here.
You two over there.
This is the end, mates.
No one knows you're here.
It's best if you just resign
to your fate.
Your president Roosevelt...
is dead.
Louie?
Are you all right?
Pick up!
Lift it.
Lift it!
Over your head.
If he drops it
shoot him.
Come on, Louie.
Come on, boy.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me! Don't look at me!
"Prisoners of Naoetsu...
"The war has come
to a point of cessation.
"Today...
"in the spirit of the new future
of our great nations,
"we invite all prisoners
to bathe in the Hokura river."
This is it.
We're dead.
That's our boys! That's our boys!
They've seen us!
It's over! The war is over!
Louie!
You made it.
Oh, God, look at you.
Oh, Mama.
From up above I heard
The angels sing to me these words
And sometimes in your eyes
I see the beauty in the world
Oh, now I'm floating so high
I blossom and die
Send your storm and your lightning
To strike
Me between the eyes
Eyes
Sometimes the stars decide
To reflect in puddles in the dirt
When I look in your eyes
I forget all about what hurts
Oh, now I'm floating so high
I blossom and die
Send your storm and your lightning
To strike
Me between the eyes
And cry
Believe in miracles
Oh, hey, I'm floating up above
The world now
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
facebook.com/groups/getdirectlink/
In this group you will be able to get Direct Download link of Movies and TV Shows.