The oldest stories ever told
are written in the stars.
Stories of time before man and
gods, when Titans ruled the earth.
The Titans were powerful...
but their reign was ended
by their own sons...
Zeus, Poseidon and Hades.
Zeus convinced his
brother Hades...
to create a beast so strong it
could defeat their parents.
And from his own flesh...
Hades gave birth to an
unspeakable horror...
the Kraken.
Zeus became king of the heavens.
Poseidon, king of the seas.
And Hades, tricked by Zeus...
was left to rule the underworld
in darkness and in misery.
It was Zeus who created man...
and man's prayers fed
the gods' immortality.
But in time, mankind
grew restless.
They began to question the gods...
and, finally, rise
up against them.
Into this world, a child was born.
A boy who would change everything.
Perseus.
What is it, son?
I'll have a brother
or a sister soon.
Think we're gonna love
this child differently
to the way we love you? We won't.
This child will be yours.
Me...
I'm no one's son.
I am your father, Perseus.
Marmara is your mother.
And you'll always be our son.
The bond between us is much
more than flesh and bone.
The love we have for you...
it's that love that gods
and kings fight over.
I've never understood the gods.
But even I don't question that
you were saved for a reason.
And some day...
that reason is gonna take
you far away from here.
But not tonight?
Perseus. Perseus.
Getting frail, old man.
Marmara. Marmara.
Another day, nothing.
Caught on the reef.
To whom do I direct our gratitude
for this glorious bounty?
Spyros, please.
Poseidon, Zeus? Who
do I thank, Marmara?
- Thank the men who provoke them.
- They crush my island.
They put a plague on yours.
They take from us what they
want. We're their slaves.
The gods gave us life.
For that, we should be thankful.
I'm tired of being
thankful for scraps.
I'm a fisherman. Perseus
is a fisherman.
They've even taken that
away from us. What we are.
Still they want us
to love them anyway.
One day...
somebody's gonna have
to make a stand.
One day, somebody's
gonna have to say:
"Enough."
Just like the day you came to me.
The storm brought me right to you.
I know you have questions, son.
I wish I had the answers.
I have everything I need...
right here.
Good night, son.
Hold her steady.
Tekla, the wreath.
Fetch the wreath.
The statue of Zeus. Magnificent.
Something isn't right.
The soldiers, what are they doing?
Come on.
Lift it.
Hang on.
In the name of the king and queen.
Who are they?
Soldiers from Argos.
What have they done?
They've declared war.
War against the gods.
- Let's turn the boat around.
- No.
Do nothing.
Behind you.
Hold on.
Tekla.
Where's the boy?
No.
- Go.
- No.
No.
Zeus, you must bring an end to
this. They attack our temples.
Now they dare to
desecrate Zeus' image.
We could reach out to them.
An accommodation could
be made. A truce.
No.
I created them...
and they reward my
love with defiance?
There will be no truce.
Finally.
Some rage from you.
How long has it been?
How long, brother...
since you've seen my face?
Hades.
Endless years, I've watched
from the underworld...
and saw your wrath
tempered with love.
You created them for one reason...
so their prayers would
fuel our immortality.
But you love them too well.
They've grown strong.
And now I am forced to rise
because we are all threatened.
What do you want, brother?
Let me loose upon them.
They will pray again...
and you will bathe in
their awe and fear.
And we will grow strong again.
He belongs in the
underworld, not here.
You do not tell me where I belong.
You say it is love that feeds us.
But you depend on their love.
I've only learned to
live on their fear...
their pain.
Zeus, our brother speaks
the truth. Hear him.
Go. Do what you will.
Father, we need the mortals.
No, Apollo.
Hades is right.
Their insolence has a price.
Like children, they need to be
reminded of the order of things.
Set an example, brother.
Turn them on each other...
and back into our arms.
- Are we the last boat to come in?
- No, captain.
You're the only one.
Is he one of ours?
No. We found him off
Paxos amongst our dead.
He was the only survivor.
Let the palace figure out
what to do with him.
Squad by four.
Go on.
Because if we show
the gods our love...
they shall show us love
in return. They shall.
They gave us the corn in the
fields, the sun in the sky.
These are all gifts given to us.
Gifts can be taken away.
This will be taken away...
if we do not pay love to our gods.
If we do not, we stay
in filth and misery,
which we have brought
upon ourselves.
- Move. Out of the way.
- Our gods, we beg for the whip...
The beauty and clarity
of servitude.
Man cannot rule man. You defy the
gods and you will be punished.
Is this all there is?
We lost many men, Your Majesty...
but we have victory.
To King Kepheus. To
Queen Cassiopeia.
No.
To you...
our mighty legion.
Our heroes who have
dared to strike
a blow at the heart of Zeus.
The temples are burning.
The statues have fallen.
We have starved them
of our prayers.
Tonight...
after a generation of struggle...
the sun does not set
over the ocean.
It sets on Olympus itself.
A new era has begun.
The era of man.
That frown doesn't
suit you, Andromeda.
Have something to drink.
You'll feel more lively.
Andromeda.
What's your name?
Perseus.
Take this.
Please drink.
- Hands off.
- Enough.
Our daughter, the missionary.
Have you seen what's
happening out there?
Have you even bothered to look?
We serve as an inspiration.
Hundreds of our men have
lost their lives...
yet we celebrate.
You provoke the
gods and you act as
if there will be no consequence.
Well, what do you want?
Should we be afraid?
Should we be trembling and
soiling ourselves in fear?
The gods need us.
They need our worship.
What do we need of them?
- Look at my daughter.
- Don't.
What could be more
divine than her face?
More beautiful than all
the women of Greece.
More beautiful than
Aphrodite herself.
The Olympians should envy her.
We are the gods now.
My queen. You're
making a spectacle.
Interesting.
You.
You are specks of dust
beneath our fingernails.
Your very breath is a
gift from Olympus.
You have insulted powers
beyond your comprehension.
Who are you?
I am Hades.
Kneel.
Not now, Perseus.
You will have your chance.
What do you know of beauty?
What is more beautiful than death?
Gaze upon me, mortal queen.
- Mother.
- Princess.
In 10 days...
when the sun is eclipsed...
I will unleash the Kraken.
Argos will be swept
from the earth...
and all of you with it.
Unless...
you sacrifice the princess...
you so foolishly
compare to the gods.
Only her blood will
sate the Kraken...
and Zeus...
who you have so offended.
Choose your penance, Argos.
Destruction or sacrifice.
This is the will of Zeus.
The will of your father.
There is a demigod in Argos.
That is impossible.
He's yours.
His name is Perseus.
We could offer him sanctuary.
Have I heard his prayers?
This son knows no love for me.
He's no different from
any of the others
who have turned their backs on us.
For the last time, demigod, speak.
- I'm not a demigod.
- Who are you? Why were you sent?
I don't know.
I advise against this, sire.
He's not to be trusted.
What would you have me do? Draco.
Leave him.
Is it possible?
If it's true you are
the son of Zeus...
you can save us.
You must save us.
I can't save you. I'm just a man.
My lord, as terrible as it
is to utter the words...
a sacrifice is the only way.
Don't even say the word.
He's right.
No one should have to die for me.
Let Perseus go.
Sire, we need to get the
princess out of the city now.
- I'll find a place to hide her.
- You can't hide from Hades.
So says the bastard son of a god.
My father...
was killed by a god.
My mother, sister...
everyone I loved was
killed by a god.
I mend nets...
not wield a sword.
So, demigod, you have a visitor.
She says she knows you.
My name is Io, Perseus.
And how do you know me?
I've watched you all your life.
I guided you to your family.
Are you a god?
There are gods and
there are men...
and there are those of
us who are in between.
Many years ago...
I refused a god's advance.
I was cursed with agelessness.
That's not much of a curse.
I've lived for years
watching my loved ones die.
I imagine you're sympathetic
to that plight.
Is it true?
Am I the son of Zeus?
Yes.
The story of your birth began with
the rebellion of King Acrisius.
Mankind had grown tired of the
gods' mistreatment and cruelty.
Acrisius led a siege on Olympus.
It is said the other gods...
wanted to simply lay waste
to Acrisius and his army...
but Zeus loved man too much.
Instead, he chose to make
an example of Acrisius.
He disguised himself
as the king...
and visited the chamber where
the king's wife was sleeping.
My king.
Zeus?
Acrisius grew mad with rage.
He ordered the execution
of his wife...
and Zeus' newborn son.
I curse you, Zeus.
I deny you the body you soiled...
and the bastard child with it.
No.
The queen and her child
were cast into the sea.
Your mother was killed, but you...
part man, part god, you lived.
I've watched over
you ever since...
waiting for the day
when you will help
bring an end to the
tyranny of the gods.
You were born to kill the Kraken.
I don't know why I was born...
or what I am.
But I know it's not the
Kraken I wanna kill.
How do I get to Hades?
If the Kraken falls...
Hades will be weak enough for
you to strike a deathly blow.
Only then will you have
the revenge you seek.
Then they better release me.
If the Kraken can be killed...
the Stygian witches will know how.
The witches are further away
than the legion has ever been.
No man can go there.
No man.
Keep your distance, Io.
Zeus, forgive us for these
affronts and protect us.
And you still believe
they're going to help?
This is suicide.
And the shields. Come on, boys.
It's a lost cause.
We've no chance, and you know it.
Here's who you drew into this,
Perseus. An honour guard.
Young men who look good
on a reviewing stand...
and old soldiers, heading
towards retirement.
Do you know what the Kraken is?
The Kraken is the end of us.
A colossal, elemental beast.
It doesn't think. It doesn't
feel. Even the gods fear it.
And you, you're going to kill it?
Don't come.
- I don't need your help.
- Of course not.
You're the son of Zeus.
- But we have orders.
- Come, we need to leave.
Gentlemen, may our
journey be long,
filled with agony and torment...
and may we all complain about
it bitterly as old men.
- So what should we bring?
- Bring everything.
What makes you think the
witches will tell us anything?
Oh, they'll tell us,
or I'll kill them too.
Come on. Let's go, boys.
- What is this?
- Just leave it.
Don't leave us to the mercy
of the gods. Please.
Don't go. Please stay.
Stay here. Please?
Please? Help us.
You're just going to make
the gods angrier. Please.
Just sacrifice the princess.
Watch your mouth.
Stay back. Stay back.
You'd think they
might be thankful.
You cannot desert us.
Maybe they're tired
of being thankful.
Good news.
My brother and I have decided...
to accompany you on your journey.
We have enough strangers here.
We can be of great help to
you, trust me. You'll need us.
I need soldiers, not hunters.
Which one of your
soldiers knows how
to cut the impenetrable skin...
of the Nemean lion?
Which one of them knows the soft
points on a centaur's armour?
Which one of them
knows which jugular
to slice on a five-headed Hydra?
- The middle one.
- The middle one. Good guess.
My brother and I, we
know how to kill.
- We enjoy it.
- If you can keep up...
and you don't mind
dying, come along.
It is death who should
be afraid of us.
King Acrisius.
There is no Acrisius.
Just Calibos.
We have an enemy in common.
- Zeus.
My brother.
What do you want from me?
Zeus' seed in your wife survived.
The child of your shame.
Perseus.
He lives?
You murdered your
wife for nothing.
Now Perseus hurls himself
from Argos to destroy me.
He must die.
- What would you have me do?
- Zeus must think I serve him...
but I am growing stronger.
Until I possess my full power...
you will be my weapon.
Come.
Use this.
Kill Perseus for me.
And I'll destroy Zeus for you.
I serve you.
The boy will die.
How far is it?
Four days to the witches.
Four days? I'm tired already.
Here, use this.
Would you like us to wait?
Oops.
You really are a fisherman.
You should've seen my father.
You.
Bring your weapon.
Have you handled a sword before?
- There's been no need.
- I see.
Left foot forward.
Your motions should be fluid.
The weapon is a part of you.
Like the sting on a wasp.
Stay focused.
Know what's around you.
Keep your balance at all times.
You fall...
you die.
Get up.
Don't...
There is a god in you.
Be sure to bring it.
End of lesson.
Perseus.
A gift from the gods.
- Forged on Olympus.
- Why?
Just accept it.
I can do this as a man.
So it's yours.
Gentlemen, retrieve our saviour.
The Pegasus.
No man has ever ridden one.
It's a message.
They're watching us.
Perseus.
Why does it always have to be...?
Listen.
Help me.
You reek of your father.
- Who was that?
- I don't know. Let's ask him.
Let it go.
No. We split up.
Just follow the blood.
Come on.
Look. His blood.
Are you happy now?
Attack.
Wait. Wait.
What is that?
Come on.
Ixas.
Spear.
Draco.
Faster.
Let's go, let's go.
Go, jump.
Run.
- Back up. Back up. Back up.
- There's more.
- Run.
- Everyone. Back to back.
Stand your ground.
Three more. In the name of
the gods, they're bigger.
What are they?
Djinn.
I fought them in the legion.
This is their desert.
- Enemies?
- I thought so.
They aren't human. Not any more.
Desert conjurers, cutthroats.
Well, somebody should thank them.
What?
- What is it?
- Venom. From Hades.
- Pray. Pray to Zeus for strength.
- No. No.
Pray to your damn father.
Hear my prayer. Protect
and heal your son.
- No.
- Please, Zeus, hear me.
Would you like some bread?
- Thank you.
- Please.
- Have some bread.
Over here. Over here.
- For you.
- Please.
No.
We must turn our hearts to Hades.
It is the only way.
Brothers and sisters.
Come to me. Come.
I have the way out of our misery.
Hades has asked for the princess.
Sacrifice one for the
life of the city.
Why do they remain
silent while we suffer?
Why do they guard the woman
whose death will save us?
Is she better than any one of you?
We have long worshipped
Zeus in Argos.
But it is Hades who now
offers us salvation.
We must pray to the one
who showed us our sin...
and who offers us redemption...
through blood.
A bribe for the ferryman.
When they get injured in battle...
they replace their limbs with
charwood and black magic.
They feel no pain.
Live hundreds of years.
So how old is that one?
I don't care. I don't trust them.
You're burning.
Drink this.
I'll get more water.
Come on.
Look out.
What?
What's he saying?
The Djinn have waited
many years for the
one who will free
them from the gods.
He says he is no
friend of the humans.
You don't say.
But the only way we can
help Perseus is together.
Draco.
Look.
Together.
- He's not ready to travel.
- Time is slipping away, Io.
He may be a demigod,
but he's still mortal.
Feeling better?
- Yeah, a bit.
- Good.
Your pride is killing my men.
- You were given gifts. Use them.
- Those gifts are a trap.
I don't care what
they are. Use them.
No.
I will not use that sword or
anything that they give me.
So we'll just continue to die.
I can't become like them.
If I do this, I do it as a man.
But you are not just a man.
I choose to be.
A man cannot do this, Perseus.
According to who?
The gods?
If I had your gifts...
When you need your
sword, it's in my bag.
They're riding them.
They tried to kill us.
I'm not getting on it.
Magnificent.
What are you waiting for?
Well, we need to make
up for lost time.
We're making good time.
Not good enough. The
eclipse is drawing near.
How close are we to
the Norn Mountains?
It'll be two days before
we reach the witches.
This thing is making me feel sick.
Trust me, it's better to
be on one than in one.
What, don't you ever smile?
When I spit in the
eyes of the gods...
then I'll smile.
- What is this place?
- The Garden of Stygia.
This is where the Kraken
defeated the Titans.
It's what Argos will
look like when we fail.
Every step we take is
an insult to the gods.
- Good.
- Perseus.
Only ask what you need
to know. Nothing more.
Of course.
Visitors.
- Who is it?
- Visitors.
Got the eye.
- Give it to me.
- Who is it?
Who is it? Who is it?
The eye. Give it to me.
Perseus, no.
We didn't come here to fight.
- We just have one question.
- Young Perseus.
- Son of Zeus.
- So fresh.
- Perseus.
- Closer.
A little nibble.
- Flesh of a god.
- Witch.
- Don't. Easy.
Stale meat, ladies.
So which one's gonna
answer my question?
You want to know about the Kraken.
Kraken?
- Do it.
- Kill it.
- That's right.
- A wasted journey.
The Kraken fears no weapon.
It must have a weakness.
Maybe.
But knowledge demands payment.
- Sacrifice.
- Eusebios.
- Watch out.
- Look out.
- Ixas, shoot.
- Help.
- The eye.
- Let him go. Do it.
- You wouldn't dare.
We cannot see the answers
without the eye.
Let him go.
Now answer the question.
How do we kill the Kraken?
- There is a solution.
- Solution.
But it is an impossible one.
- Yeah?
- The Gorgon, Medusa.
Medusa.
Anything of flesh is
killed by her gaze.
Killed by her.
Her prison lies across
the River Styx...
- at the edge of the underworld.
- A Titan against a Titan.
She's no use against the
Kraken. We can't control her.
Then we take her head.
- Clever boy.
- Now the eye. Give us the eye.
- The eye.
Where is it?
But wait. There's more. Don't
you want to know more?
Perseus, no.
- Tell him.
What?
Your journey does not end well.
Fate has spoken.
You will die, son of Zeus.
It's a lie. Come.
Written as history.
Perseus.
You will die.
Why are the Djinn leaving us?
They believe we will all
die. It's the prophecy.
Who are you?
Well, you can call me Father...
- if you wish.
- My father's dead.
He was killed by a god.
An unfortunate casualty in a
war men brought on themselves.
Men didn't murder my
family. Your brother did.
You heard the witches' prophesy.
You will not defeat the
Kraken, much less Hades.
If you continue this journey, you
will die, and Argos
will still fall.
If you're so sure,
why are you here?
To offer you sanctuary.
Your blood is mine, Perseus,
and that makes you a god.
It's time you came to Olympus
and started living like one.
Rather die in the mud with those
men than live forever as a god.
You foolish boy.
Man's entire existence
is a gift of my grace.
For someone who created man...
you don't know much about us.
We live...
we fight and we die...
for each other, not for you.
Tell Hades I'll see him soon.
I will not make this offer again.
Good.
Because I'd hate to
refuse you twice.
Perseus.
Wait.
It's expensive where you're going.
Kucuk fashioned this
shield from the Scorpioch.
Stronger and lighter
than any metal.
Very rare and high-quality item.
We can fight anywhere...
but not in the underworld.
Yeah.
Good luck, fisherman.
We all heard what
the witches said.
But we can prove them wrong.
I need your help.
It wasn't the gods that
saved me up there.
If you believe that
we have a chance.
I never liked Argos much anyway.
I know the way.
Then we go to the
underworld. We kill Medusa.
- Now what?
- We wait for Charon.
Charon only ferries the dead.
Any volunteers?
Heads we swim.
A bribe for the ferryman.
So, what happens
when we get there?
Just another beast to kill.
A beast?
Medusa was beautiful once.
So beautiful as to tempt Poseidon.
When he came for her...
she ran to Athena's
temple thinking
that the goddess
would protect her.
She didn't.
Poseidon took her
on the cold floor.
She prayed to Athena
for comfort...
but the goddess felt
nothing but disgust.
She made sure no one would
ever want Medusa again.
One look at the
creature she has become
will turn any living
thing to stone.
I cannot assist you there.
A curse prevents me.
It was Athena's one bit
of solace to Medusa
so that Medusa would
never harm a woman.
Only men are allowed
in the temple.
Though no man has
ever made it out.
Medusa's got a tail and
that's how she'll use it.
Listen.
Hear her muscles coil.
Smell her skin.
Feel her hunger in your gut.
Medusa's killed you twice now.
Do you think she'll
hand you her head?
She won't be gracious about it.
One look in her eyes and
you'll turn to stone.
Good.
- Try not to enjoy this so much.
- I'm trying to help you live.
Don't look at me.
Ease your storm.
We're nearing Medusa's lair.
I never thought I could
reach this place.
Who'd you lose?
My daughter.
Taken away on her 16th birthday.
Dragged down here.
I have a feeling
I'll see her soon.
You brought us this far. Let's
go the rest of the way.
How many coins did
you get, Perseus?
Just the one.
I only knew one great
man in my life.
My father.
Now I know four more.
And a woman.
And whatever the hell you are.
I know we're all afraid.
But my father told me:
Someday someone was gonna
have to take a stand.
have to say enough.
This could be that day.
Trust your senses.
And don't look this
bitch in the eye.
Doesn't really inspire confidence.
Quiet.
- Listen.
- Eusebios.
Keep your eyes down.
Here we go.
Solon.
Keep going.
Flank her.
- Draco.
- Go.
Eusebios, follow me.
Hang on.
Eusebios.
Remember what Perseus said.
Eyes down.
Ixas, no.
Where are you?
Eusebios.
Go.
Wait here.
I'll lure her out.
Get ready.
Now.
Together.
Let them know men did this.
Just you and me, son of Zeus.
Perseus.
Don't become one of them.
Io, I'm here.
There's no time.
The eclipse.
Perseus, you must go
before it's too late.
I'm not going anywhere.
My fate is certain.
But the fate of Argos
is still in your hands.
All my life you've been there.
You never left me.
I can't leave you.
This part of the journey
you must do alone.
Perseus...
you're not just part
man, part god...
you're the best of both.
Everything will be all right.
Brother.
It is time for the mortals to pay.
My child waits to do your will.
Leave us.
Release the Kraken.
The Kraken comes now.
Our suffering ends when
the beast is sated.
Will it take us...
or will it take Andromeda?
Andromeda.
It's my name they're calling.
This cannot continue.
- Stay back.
Look. The Kraken. Help us.
Andromeda.
Hades, we sacrifice our
princess in your name.
It comes, brothers and sisters.
Argos has fallen.
Do you feel stronger, brother?
You thought the Kraken would
bring you their prayers.
But the Kraken is my
child. It feeds only me.
I command Olympus.
Remember who you serve.
I serve myself.
I have since you cheated me.
You sent me to the
underworld to be hated...
while you basked in their love.
We need the love of humans.
No, you need it.
I survive on their fear.
Your reign is over, brother Zeus.
You'll watch while my blessed
avenger devours their hopes.
And then finally
you'll know my pain.
There is still a
demigod in Argos...
brother.
Perseus.
The bag. Come on.
Hyah.
Hey, fisherman.
Come on.
No.
I'm a god.
I will live forever.
But not here.
The boats are coming for us.
For you. Not for me.
You won't stay, will you?
Perseus, Argos needs a ruler.
I cannot be a king.
I serve you better as a man.
You'll make a fine queen for them.
Olympus owes you a
debt of gratitude.
As do I.
Hades lives.
He's just sent back
to the underworld.
Biding his time, no doubt.
Waiting for men to
grow weak, and in
their weakness, he grows stronger.
It's mankind who holds
the key to Hades' rise.
It always was.
So we'll see him again.
Yes.
But now the world knows
a man can stop him.
Of course, you had some help.
A sword, the Pegasus...
I wanted men to
worship us again, but
I didn't want it to cost me a son.
That's almost human of you.
I don't suppose
you'll reconsider my
offer to take your
place as one of us.
I've got everything
I need right here.
You may not want to
be a god, Perseus...
but after feats like yours,
men will worship you.
Be good to them.
Be better than we were.
And if you insist on continuing
this mundane human existence...
I won't have you do it alone.
You're the son of Zeus, after all.