Provided by explosiveskull
Improved by Synchronized
Open your eyes.
This is where our magic comes from?
Mm-hmm.
This candle holds the miracle
given to our family.
How did we get a miracle?
Long ago...
when my three babies
had just been born...
your abuelo Pedro and
I were forced to flee our home.
And though many joined us...
hoping to find a new home...
we could not escape the dangers...
and your abuelo was lost.
But in our darkest moment...
we were given a miracle.
The candle became a magical flame
that could never go out.
And it blessed us with a refuge
in which to live.
A place of wonder.
An encanto.
The miracle grew.
And our house...
our casita itself...
came alive to shelter us.
When my children came of age...
the miracle blessed each
with a magic Gift to help us.
And when their children came of age...
They got magic, too.
That's right!
And together, our family's Gifts...
have made our new home a paradise.
Tonight, this candle will
give you your Gift, mi vida.
Strengthen our community,
strengthen our home.
Make your family proud.
Make my family proud.
Yes, yes, casita, we're going!
What do you think my Gift will be?
You are a wonder, Mirabel Madrigal.
Whatever Gift awaits...
will be just as special as you.
Make your family proud.
Morning, Abuelo!
Hey! When's the magic Gift happen?
My cousin's ceremony is tonight.
What's his Gift?
We're gonna find out!
What's your Gift?
Who's asking?
Us!
Well, "us," I can't just talk about myself.
I'm only part of the amazing Madrigals.
Who's all the amazing Madrigals?
Ah, you're not gonna
leave me alone, are you?
Casita, help me out.
Drawers!
Floors!
Doors!
Let's go!
♪ This is our home
We've got every generation ♪
♪ So full of music
A rhythm of its own design ♪
♪ This is my family
A perfect constellation ♪
♪ So many stars
And everybody gets to shine ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ But let's be clear
Abuela runs this show ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ She led us here
So many years ago ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ And every year
Our family blessings grow ♪
♪ There's just a lot
You simply got to know so ♪
♪ Welcome to the family Madrigal ♪
♪ The home
Of the family Madrigal ♪
♪ We're on our way ♪
♪ Where all the people are fantastical ♪
♪ And magical ♪
♪ I'm part
Of the family Madrigal ♪
- Oh, my gosh! It's them!
- What are the Gifts?
- I can't remember all the Gifts!
- But I don't know who is who.
All right, all right, relax!
- It is physically impossible to relax!
- Tell us everything!
- What are your powers?
- Just tell us what everyone can do!
And that's why coffee's for grown-ups.
♪ My tía Pepa
Her mood affects the weather ♪
♪ When she's unhappy ♪
♪ Well, the temperature
Gets weird ♪
♪ My tío Bruno ♪
♪ We don't talk about Bruno! ♪
♪ They say he saw the future
One day he disappeared ♪
♪ Oh
And that's my mom Julieta ♪
♪ Here's her deal ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ The truth is she can heal you
With a meal ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Her recipes
Are remedies for real ♪
♪ If you're impressed
Imagine how I feel ♪
Mom!
♪ Welcome to the family Madrigal ♪
♪ The home
Of the family Madrigal ♪
Hey, coming through!
♪ I know it sounds a bit fantastical ♪
♪ And magical ♪
♪ But I'm part of
The family Madrigal ♪
♪ Two guys fell in love ♪
- ♪ With family Madrigal ♪
♪ And now they're part of ♪
- ♪ The family Madrigal ♪
♪ See, yeah, Tío Félix married Pepa ♪
♪ And my dad married Julieta ♪
♪ That's how Abuela became ♪
- ♪ An abuela Madrigal ♪
- ♪ Abuela Madrigal ♪
♪ Let's go
Let's go ♪
♪ We swear to always
Help those around us ♪
♪ And earn the miracle
That somehow found us ♪
♪ The town keeps growing
The world keeps turning ♪
♪ But work and dedication
Will keep the miracle burning ♪
♪ And each new generation
Must keep the miracle burning ♪
Wait, who's the sister and who's the cousin?
There are so many people!
How do you keep them all straight?
Okay, okay, okay.
♪ So many kids in our house
So, let's turn the sound up ♪
♪ You know why? I think it's
time for a Grandkid Round-up! ♪
♪ Grandkid Round-up ♪
♪ Cousin Dolores
Can hear a pin drop ♪
♪ Camilo shapeshifts
Antonio gets his Gift today ♪
♪ My older sisters ♪
- ♪ Isabela and Luisa ♪
♪ One strong, one graceful
Perfect in every way ♪
♪ Isabela ♪
♪ Grows a flower
And the town goes wild ♪
♪ Isabela ♪
♪ She's the perfect golden child ♪
♪ Luisa, Luisa ♪
♪ And Luisa's super strong ♪
♪ The beauty and the brawn
Do no wrong ♪
- Let's get ready!
- Coming, Abuela!
♪ That's life
In the family Madrigal ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Now you know
The family Madrigal ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Where all the people
Are fantastical ♪
- ♪ And magical ♪
- ♪ Whoa ♪
♪ That's who we are
In the family Madrigal ♪
♪ Adiós ♪
But what's your Gift?
♪ Well, I gotta go
The life of a Madrigal ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ But now you all know
The family Madrigal ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ I never meant this
To get autobiographical ♪
♪ It was just to review
The family Madrigal ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
- ♪ But what about Mirabel? ♪
- ♪ It starts with Abuela ♪
♪ And then Tía Pepa
She handles the weather ♪
♪ But what about Mirabel? ♪
♪ My mom Julieta
Can make you feel better ♪
♪ With just one arepa ♪
- ♪ But what about Mirabel? ♪
- ♪ My dad Agustín ♪
♪ Well he's accident-prone
But he means well ♪
♪ But what about Mirabel? ♪
♪ Hey you said you wanna know
What everyone does ♪
♪ I got sisters and cousins and ♪
♪ Mirabel ♪
♪ My primo Camilo won't stop
Until he makes you smile today ♪
♪ My cousin Dolores can hear
This whole chorus a mile away ♪
♪ Look
It's Mr. Mariano ♪
♪ Hey you can marry my sister
If you wanna ♪
♪ Between you and me
She's kind of a prima donna ♪
♪ Oh, I've said too much
And thank you ♪
♪ But I really gotta go ♪
- ♪ My family's amazing ♪
- ♪ Mirabel ♪
- ♪ And I'm in my family so ♪
♪ Well ♪
Mirabel!
What are you doing?
They were just asking
about the family and...
She was about to tell us
about her super awesome Gift!
Oh, Mirabel didn't get one.
You didn't get a Gift?
Mirabel! Delivery!
I gave you the special since
you're the only Madrigal kid with no Gift.
I call it the "Not Special Special"
since you have no Gift.
Thanks.
Oh, and tell Antonio good luck.
The last Gift ceremony was a bummer.
Last one being yours that did not work.
If I was you, I'd be really sad.
Well, my little friend, I am not.
Because the truth is, Gift or no Gift...
I am just as special
as the rest of my family.
Who wants more pink?
All right, guys,
where do I drop the wagon?
Maybe your Gift is being in denial.
I made a rainbow!
Get the chairs out of the way.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Dolores, can you hear
if anyone is gonna be late?
Lift it higher. Higher.
- Hey, nice job over there.
- Yeah, yeah.
Camilo, we need another José!
José!
Luisa, the piano goes upstairs!
I'm on it!
Careful, sis!
My baby's night has to be perfect,
and it's not perfect.
And people are going to be coming.
And nothing's ready.
The flowers!
Did someone say flowers?
Isabela!
Our angel, our angel!
Please don't clap.
- Thank you.
- Oh, it's nothing.
A little sisterly advice...
if you weren't always trying too hard,
you wouldn't be in the way.
Actually, Isa, this is called helping.
And I'm not in the way.
You are.
Excuse me.
Mi vida, you okay?
You don't have to overdo it.
I know, Mamá.
I just wanna do my part
like the rest of the family.
She's right, amor.
First Gift ceremony since yours.
A lot of emotions.
- Bee stings!
- And I've been there.
When me and your tío Félix
married into the family...
outsiders who had no Gift,
never, ever would...
surrounded by the exceptional,
it was easy to feel...
un-ceptional.
Okay, Papi.
- I'm just saying, I get it.
- Eat.
Mi amor, if you ever wanna talk...
I gotta put out the stuff.
The house isn't gonna decorate itself.
Sorry, you could. You look great.
- Corazón, remember!
- Yeah, remember!
- You have nothing to prove!
- You guys can set up over here.
- Clean your rooms!
I don't care how big they are.
Has anybody seen my tiple?
One hour!
No, no, no!
Maybe you should leave the decorations
to someone else?
No, I actually made these
as a surprise for you.
Mirabel, I know you want to help.
But tonight must go perfectly.
The whole town relies on our family,
on our Gifts.
So, the best way for some of us to help
is to step aside.
Let the rest of the family
do what they do best.
Okay?
Mm-hmm.
- Pepa! You have a cloud!
- I know, Mamá.
But now I can't find Antonio.
What do you want from me?
Mamá, be nice to Mirabel, okay?
You know tonight will be hard for her.
If the Gift ceremony doesn't go well
this time...
tonight will be hard for us all.
Antonio!
Everyone's looking for you.
This present will self-destruct
if you don't take it...
in three...
two...
one...
Nervous?
You have nothing to worry about.
You're gonna get your Gift
and open that door...
and it's gonna be the coolest ever.
I know it.
What if it doesn't work?
Well, in that impossible scenario...
you'd stay here in the nursery with me.
Forever.
And I'd get you all to myself.
I wish you could have a door.
You know what?
You don't have to worry about me...
'cause I have an amazing family...
and an amazing house.
And an amazing you.
And seeing you get your special Gift
and your door...
that's gonna make me
way more happy than anything.
But, alas, I am gonna miss
having the world's best roomie.
I know you're an animal guy...
and I made this so, when you
move into your cool, new room...
you always have something
to snuggle with.
All right, hombrecito, you ready?
Sorry, I got to get one more squeeze.
Okay, okay, we're going!
Gracias!
♪ Party night ♪
♪ Everyone's coming to celebrate ♪
♪ Everyone's coming to have fun ♪
♪ Keep dancing ♪
♪ Happy in my paradise ♪
- Here you go!
- ♪ And revealing ♪
♪ Miracles on every floor ♪
♪ Enchantment ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
Cecilia, up top!
♪ I always fall in love
with your enchantment ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ May you keep blessing
your enchantment ♪
♪ Enchantment ♪
♪ Opening doors
The morning is arriving ♪
♪ They stay open ♪
♪ And the coffee is made at home ♪
♪ Happy song
So that good wins over bad ♪
♪ Don't wake me up ♪
♪ This looks like a real dream ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I always fall in love
with your enchantment ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
- Whoa!
- ♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Your charm continues to bless you ♪
- Whoa!
- Whee!
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh... ♪
There you are.
Look at you! All grown up.
Pepi, amor,
you're gonna get him all wet.
You are making your papa proud.
I don't sound like that.
Abuela says it's time.
We'll be waiting at your door.
Okay, okay.
All right, I'm done!
Fifty years ago...
in our darkest moment...
this candle blessed us with a miracle.
And the greatest honor of our family...
has been to use our blessings
to serve this beloved community.
Tonight, we come together once more...
as another steps into the light...
to make us proud.
I can't.
I need you.
Come on, let's get you to your door.
Will you use your Gift
to honor our miracle?
Will you serve this community...
and strengthen our home?
I understand you.
Of course they can come!
We have a new Gift!
It's bigger on the inside?
Antonio!
You wanna go where?
- That was great!
- Okay! All right!
That was amazing.
I knew you could do it!
A Gift just as special as you.
We need a picture!
Everyone! Come, come, come!
It's a great night!
It's a perfect night!
Everyone, together!
La Familia Madrigal!
♪ Don't be upset or mad at all ♪
♪ Don't feel regret
Or sad a t all ♪
♪ Hey, I'm still a part
Of the family Madrigal ♪
♪ And I'm fine
I am totally fine ♪
♪ I will stand on the side
As you shine ♪
♪ I'm not fine
I'm not fine ♪
♪ I can't move the mountains ♪
♪ I can't make flowers bloom ♪
♪ I can't take another night
Up in my room ♪
♪ Waiting on a miracle ♪
♪ I can't heal what's broken ♪
♪ Can't control the morning rain
Or a hurricane ♪
♪ Can't keep down
The unspoken invisible pain ♪
♪ Always waiting on a miracle
A miracle ♪
♪ Always walking alone ♪
♪ Always wanting for more ♪
♪ Like I'm still at that door
Longing to shine ♪
♪ Like all of you shine ♪
♪ All I need is a change ♪
♪ All I need is a chance ♪
♪ All I know
Is I can't stay on the side ♪
♪ Open your eyes ♪
♪ Open your eyes
Open your eyes ♪
♪ I would move the mountains ♪
♪ Make new trees and flowers grow ♪
♪ Someone please
Just let me know where do I go ♪
♪ I am waiting on a miracle
A miracle ♪
♪ I would heal what's broken ♪
♪ Show this family something new ♪
♪ Who I am inside
So what can I do? ♪
♪ I'm sick of waiting
On a miracle ♪
♪ So here I go ♪
♪ I am ready
Come on, I'm ready ♪
♪ I've been patient
And steadfast and steady ♪
♪ Bless me now ♪
♪ As you blessed us
All those years ago ♪
♪ When you gave us a miracle ♪
♪ Am I too late for a miracle? ♪
Casita?
Come on, Abuela!
The house is in danger!
The tiles were falling,
and there were cracks everywhere.
And the candle almost went out.
Show me.
What?
No, that's...
The cracks were there.
They were everywhere.
The house was in trouble,
the candle was...
Abuela, I promise...
That's enough.
There is nothing wrong
with La Casa Madrigal.
The magic is strong.
And so are the drinks.
Please! Music!
If it was all in my head,
how did I cut my hand?
I would never ruin Antonio's night.
Is that really what you think?
What I think
is that today was very hard for you.
That's...
I was looking out for the family.
And I might not be
super strong like Luisa...
or effortlessly perfect
like señorita perfecta Isabela...
who's never even had
a bad hair day, but...
whatever.
I wish you could
see yourself the way I do.
You are perfect just like this.
You're just as special
as anyone else in this family.
You just healed my hand
with an arepa con queso.
I healed your hand
with my love for my daughter...
with her wonderful brain...
- and big heart, cool glasses...
- Stop!
Mamá!
I know what I saw.
Mira, my brother Bruno
lost his way in this family.
I don't want the same for you.
Get some sleep.
You'll feel better tomorrow.
Pedro.
I need you.
Cracks in our casita.
If our family knew
how vulnerable we truly are...
If our miracle is dying...
We cannot lose our home again.
Why is this happening?
Open my eyes.
If the answer is here, help me find it.
Help me protect our family.
Help me save our miracle.
I will save the miracle.
Wait. How do I save a miracle?
I figure out what's happening
to the miracle.
Oh, I have no idea.
But there is one person in this family
who hears everything about everything.
So, if anyone would know what's wrong
with the magic...
Hey!
...it's her.
Dolores, hey.
You know, out of all my older cousins,
you're, like, my favorite cousin...
so I feel like I can talk to you
about anything...
ergo you can talk to me about anything.
Like the problem with the magic last night
that no one seemed to worry about...
but maybe you heard about
that maybe I should know about.
Camilo! Stop pretending you're Dolores
so you can have seconds.
Worth a shot.
The only one worried about the magic
is you...
and the rats talking in the walls.
And Luisa, I heard her eye twitching
all night.
There we go.
Everyone, to the table!
Let's go, let's go.
- Luisa.
- Family.
We are all thankful
for Antonio's wonderful new Gift.
I told them to warm up your seat.
Thank you, Toñito.
I'm sure today we'll find a way
to put your blessings to good use.
Luisa, Dolores says
you're totally freaking out.
Any chance you maybe know something
about last night with the magic...
- You do!
- Mirabel!
- If you can't pay attention, I will help you.
- Actually...
Casita!
As I was saying...
we must never take
our miracle for granted...
so today we will work twice as hard.
- Mm-hmm. I will help Luisa.
- Stop.
First, an announcement.
I've spoken to the Guzmáns
about Mariano's proposal to Isabela.
Dolores, do we have a date?
Tonight. He wants five babies.
Wonderful!
Such a fine young man
with our perfect Isabela...
will bring a new generation
of magical blessings...
and make both of our families stronger.
Okay. Our community is counting on us.
La Familia Madrigal!
Luisa, hey. What?
- Sorry.
- What is your problem?
Hey! Luisa, hold up!
- Luisa, can you re-route the river?
- Will do.
- Luisa, the donkeys got out again.
- On it.
Luisa!
Wait a second!
You gotta tell me about the magic.
What's going on?
What are you hiding?
Nothing. Just got a lot of chores,
so maybe you should just go home.
Luisa, my house is leaning to the...
Dolores said your eye was twitching,
and it never twitches.
Something's making you nervous.
Hey, move.
You're gonna make me drop a donkey.
Luisa, will you just...
- Just tell me what it is.
- There's nothing to tell.
You're obviously worried
about something.
Luisa, if you know
what's hurting the magic...
and it gets worse,
'cause you won't tell me what's wrong...
Nothing's wrong!
Wow, sorry.
That snuck out there.
What I meant was...
Why would anything be wrong?
I'm totally fine.
The magic's fine.
Luisa's fine.
I'm totally not nervous.
Your eye is doing the thing...
♪ I'm the strong one
I'm not nervous ♪
♪ I'm as tough as the crust
Of the Earth is ♪
Okay.
♪ I move mountains ♪
♪ I move churches ♪
♪ And I glow 'cause I know
What my worth is ♪
Of course, I mean...
Hey, where are you going?
♪ I don't ask
How hard the work is ♪
♪ Got a rough
Indestructible surface ♪
♪ Diamonds and platinum ♪
♪ I find 'em
I flatten 'em ♪
♪ I take what I'm handed
I break what's demanded ♪
♪ But under the surface
I feel berserk ♪
♪ As a tightrope walker
In a three-ring circus ♪
♪ Under the surface
Was Hercules ever like ♪
♪ "Yo, I don't wanna fight Cerberus" ♪
♪ Under the surface ♪
♪ I'm pretty sure I'm worthless
If I can't be of service ♪
♪ A flaw or a crack ♪
♪ The straw in the stack
That breaks the camel's back ♪
♪ What breaks the camel's back? ♪
♪ It's pressure
Like a drip, drip, drip ♪
♪ That'll never stop ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Pressure that'll tip, tip, tip
Till you just go pop ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Give it to your sister
Your sister's older ♪
♪ Give her all the heavy things
We can't shoulder ♪
♪ Who am I
If I can't run with the ball? ♪
♪ If I fall to pressure
Like a grip, grip, grip ♪
♪ And it won't let go ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Pressure like
A tick, tick, tick ♪
♪ Till it's ready to blow ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Give it to your sister
Your sister's stronger ♪
♪ See if she can hang on
A little longer ♪
♪ Who am I
If I can't carry it all? ♪
♪ If I falter ♪
♪ Under the surface ♪
♪ I hide my nerves
And it worsens ♪
♪ I worry
Something is gonna hurt us ♪
♪ Under the surface ♪
♪ The ship doesn't swerve ♪
♪ As it heard
How big the iceberg is ♪
♪ Under the surface
I think about my purpose ♪
♪ Can I somehow preserve this?
Line up the dominos ♪
♪ A light wind blows
You try to stop it topplin' ♪
♪ But on and on it goes
But wait ♪
♪ If I could shake ♪
♪ The crushing weight
Of expectations ♪
♪ Would that free
Some room up for joy ♪
♪ Or relaxation? ♪
♪ Or a simple pleasure
Instead we measure ♪
♪ This growing pressure
Keeps growing ♪
♪ Keep going
'Cause all we know is ♪
♪ Pressure like
A drip, drip, drip ♪
♪ That'll never stop ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Pressure that'll tip, tip, tip
Till you just go pop ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Give it to your sister
It doesn't hurt ♪
♪ And see if she can handle
Every family burden ♪
♪ Watch as she buckles
And bends but never breaks ♪
♪ No mistakes ♪
♪ Just pressure
Like a grip, grip, grip ♪
♪ And it won't let go ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Pressure like
A tick, tick, tick ♪
♪ Till it's ready to blow ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Give it to your sister
And never wonder ♪
♪ If the same pressure
Would have pulled you under ♪
♪ Who am I
If I don't have what it takes? ♪
♪ No cracks
No breaks ♪
♪ No mistakes
No pressure ♪
I think you're carrying way too much...
Maybe I overdo it.
Yep.
There is something you should know.
Last night, when you saw the cracks...
I felt... weak.
What?
- Luisa! The donkeys!
- On it!
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you mean?
What do you think's hurting the magic?
Don't know,
but I heard the grown-ups once.
Before Tío Bruno left...
he had, like,
some terrible vision about it.
Tío Bruno?
What was in his vision?
No one knows.
They never found it.
But if something's wrong with the magic,
start with Bruno's tower.
Find that vision.
Wait! How do you find a vision?
What am I even looking for?
If you find it, you'll know.
But be careful.
That place is off limits for a reason.
Such a perfect match.
So perfect.
And so good for the encanto.
Casita.
Can you turn off the sand?
You can't help in here?
I'll be fine.
I need to do this.
For you, for Abuela...
maybe a little for me.
"Find the vision, save the..."
Oh, hello.
Lot of stairs...
but at least I'll have a friend.
No. He flew away immediately.
All right.
♪ Welcome to the family Madrigal ♪
♪ There's so many stairs
In the casa Madrigal ♪
♪ You think there would be
Another way to ♪
♪ Get so high
'Cause we're magic, but no ♪
Magical how many stairs fit in here!
Bruno, your room is the worst!
Come on...
Okay, I can do this.
Quitter!
Empty.
What's hurting the magic?
Me.
Where are you coming
from in such a hurry?
I'm sorry I was...
What is in your hair?
My Gift!
- I'm losing my Gift!
- What?
Mirabel and I were having
this little talk about me carrying too much.
So, I tried not to carry so much,
but I realized it was putting me behind.
And I knew I was gonna let everyone down.
And I felt really bad,
so I was grabbing all the donkeys...
but then when I went to throw
the donkeys in the barn, they were...
heavy!
What did you do?
What did you say to her?
Nothing. I don't...
Mirabel, I have to go get the Guzmáns
for Isabela's engagement.
Stay away from Luisa
until I can talk to her.
Tonight, we can't have
any more problems.
And whatever you're doing,
stop doing it.
Why am I in your vision, Bruno?
Tía! Jeez.
Sorry, I didn't mean to...
Shoo, shoo, shoo!
I just wanted to get
the last of Toñito's things...
and then I heard
the name we do not speak.
Great. Now I'm thundering,
and that thunder will lead to a drizzle...
and a drizzle will lead to a sprinkle...
Clear skies, clear skies.
Clear skies.
Tía Pepa? If...
If he had a vision about someone,
what would it mean for them?
We don't talk about Bruno.
I know. It's just hypothetically,
if he saw you...
Mirabel, please,
we need to get ready for the Guzmáns.
I just wanna know if it was generally
positive or, like, less positive...
- It was a nightmare!
- Félix!
Hey, she needs to know, Pepi,
she needs to know.
We don't talk about Bruno.
He would see something terrible.
And then...
Boom! It would happen.
We don't talk about Bruno.
What if you didn't
understand what he saw?
Then you better figure it out,
because it was coming for you.
♪ We don't talk
About Bruno-no-no-no ♪
♪ We don't talk about Bruno ♪
- ♪ But it was my wedding day ♪
- ♪ It was our wedding day ♪
♪ We were getting ready ♪
♪ And there wasn't a cloud
In the sky ♪
♪ No clouds allowed in the sky ♪
♪ Bruno walks in
With a mischievous grin ♪
♪ Thunder ♪
♪ You're telling the story
Or am I? ♪
♪ I'm sorry, mi vida
Go on ♪
♪ Bruno says it looks like rain ♪
♪ Why did he tell her? ♪
♪ In doing so
He floods my brain ♪
♪ Abuela gets the umbrella ♪
♪ Married in a hurricane ♪
♪ What a joyous day
But anyway ♪
♪ We don't talk about
Bruno-no-no-no ♪
♪ We don't talk about Bruno ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Grew to live in fear of
Bruno stuttering or stumbling ♪
♪ I can always hear him
Sort of muttering ♪
♪ And mumbling ♪
♪ I associate him with
The sound of falling sand ♪
♪ It's a heavy lift
With a Gift so humbling ♪
♪ Always left Abuela
and the family fumbling ♪
♪ Grappling with prophecies
They couldn't understand ♪
♪ Do you understand? ♪
♪ Seven-foot frame
Rats along his back ♪
♪ When he calls your name
It all fades to black ♪
♪ Yeah, he sees your dreams
And feasts on your screams ♪
♪ We don't talk about
Bruno-no-no-no ♪
♪ We don't talk about Bruno ♪
♪ He told me my fish would die
The next day dead ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ He told me I'd grow a gut
And just like he said ♪
- ♪ No, no ♪
- ♪ He said that all my hair ♪
♪ Would disappear ♪
♪ Now look at my head ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ Your fate is sealed
When your prophecy is read ♪
♪ He told me
That the life of my dreams ♪
♪ Would be promised
And someday be mine ♪
♪ He told me
That my power would grow ♪
♪ Like the grapes
That thrive on the vine ♪
♪ Oye Mariano's on his way ♪
♪ He told me
That the man of my dreams ♪
♪ Would be just out of reach ♪
♪ Betrothed to another ♪
- ♪ It's like I hear him now ♪
- ♪ Hey, sis ♪
♪ I want not a sound out of you ♪
♪ I can hear him now ♪
♪ Um, Bruno
Yeah, about that Bruno ♪
♪ I really need to know
About Bruno ♪
♪ Give me the truth
And the whole truth, Bruno ♪
♪ Isabela
Your boyfriend's here! ♪
♪ Time for dinner ♪
- ♪ It was my wedding day ♪
- ♪ It was our wedding day ♪
♪ And there wasn't a cloud
In the sky ♪
♪ No clouds allowed in the sky ♪
♪ He told me that
my power would grow ♪
♪ Thunder ♪
♪ You're telling the story or am I? ♪
♪ Oye Mariano's on his way ♪
♪ Bruno says it looks like rain ♪
♪ Why did he tell her? ♪
♪ In doing so,
he floods my brain ♪
♪ Abuela gets the umbrella ♪
♪ Married in a hurricane ♪
♪ He's here, don't talk about Bruno-no
♪
♪ Why did I talk about Bruno? ♪
♪ Not a word about Bruno ♪
♪ I never should have
Brought up Bruno ♪
Miraboo!
Got your party pants on? 'Cause I...
I broke into Bruno's tower.
I found his last vision.
The family's in trouble.
The magic is dying. The house is breaking,
Luisa's gift is fading.
And I think it's all because of me?
Pá?
We say nothing.
Abuela wants tonight to be perfect.
Until the Guzmáns leave,
you did not break into Bruno's tower.
The magic is not dying.
The house is not breaking.
Luisa's gift is not fading.
No one will know.
Just act normal.
No one has to know.
I know.
She's gonna tell everyone.
Time to eat!
The Guzmáns and the Madrigals together
will be so good for the encanto.
Yes. Then, let's hope
tonight is not a horrible disaster.
To a perfect night!
Avocado?
Camilo. Fix your face.
Water?
Mirabel.
The cream, please?
Pá, the cream?
...Bruno's vision.
Pepa, the cloud.
Clear skies, clear skies, clear skies.
Bruno's vision.
Mirabel?
Everything okay?
Everything is great.
She's just excited.
For you to propose.
Which you should do!
- Yes.
- As fast as you can.
I was actually gonna...
You were actually gonna.
Great!
Well, since everyone here has a talent...
my Mariano wanted to
begin with a song!
Luisa, could you bring over the piano?
Okay.
It's actually family tradition
to sing after.
Isabela, most graceful of all the Madrigals.
You're doing great.
The most perfect flower
in this entire encanto...
No!
Will you marry...
What is happening?
Mirabel found Bruno's vision. She's in it.
She's gonna destroy the magic and now,
we're all doomed!
Abuela, please!
There's gotta be an explanation.
I hate you!
- I'm a loser!
- Luisa!
What did you do?
I'm not doing anything!
It's Bruno's vision!
The magic is strong! Everything is fine!
We are the Madrigals!
Mirabel!
Hey!
It's okay, mami.
Deep breath in, deep breath out.
Stop!
No! No!
Help! Help...
Casita! Casita!
Help me!
You're very sweaty.
Oh, no!
- Bye.
- What?
No. Hold on!
Wait! Wait!
Why did you take the vision?
Knock, knock, knock, knock, knock.
Knock on wood.
What does it mean?
Is it why you came back or...?
Tío Bruno?
Knock, knock, knock, knock, knock.
Knock on wood.
You were never supposed to see that vision.
No one was.
- But...
- A little salt.
Sugar.
Wait.
Have you been in here
patching the cracks?
Oh, that? No, no, no.
I'm too scared to go near those things.
All the patching's done by Hernando.
- Who is Hernando?
- I'm Hernando and I'm scared of nothing!
It's actually me.
I used to say my real Gift was "acting."
I'm Jorge. I make the spackle.
How long have you been back here?
You never left.
Well, I left my tower, which was,
you know, a lot of stairs...
and here, kitchen adjacent.
Plus, free entertainment.
So, what do you like?
You like sports?
Game shows?
Telenovelas?
Their love could never be.
I don't understand.
Well, because she's his aunt
and she has amnesia...
so she can't remember
that she's his aunt.
It's like a very forbidden kind of...
I don't understand why you left,
but didn't leave.
Oh, well, because, the mountains
around the encanto are pretty tall.
And like I said,
free food and everything.
You guys love the free food, don't ya?
Always hungry.
Never satisfied.
My Gift wasn't helping the family...
but, I love my family, you know?
I just don't know how to...
Well, anyway,
I think you should go, because...
I don't really have a good reason,
but, if I did, you'd be like...
"I should go, because that's a good reason."
Why was I in your vision?
Tío Bruno?
I just wanted to make
the family proud of me.
Just once.
But if I should stop...
if I'm hurting my family...
just tell me.
I can't tell you...
because I don't know.
I had this vision the night
that you didn't get your Gift.
Abuela worried about the magic.
So, she begged me to look into the future.
See what it meant.
And I saw the magic in danger.
Our house breaking.
And then, and then, and then, I saw you.
But the vision was different.
It would change.
And there was no one answer.
No clear fate.
Like your future was undecided.
But I knew how it was gonna look.
I knew what everyone would think...
because I'm Bruno and
everyone always assumes the worst, so...
so...
You left to protect me?
I don't know which way it'll go...
but my guess...
the family, the encanto...
and the fate of the miracle itself...
Well, it's all gonna come down to you.
Or maybe I'm wrong.
You know, it's a mystery.
That's why this vision is...
Look, if I could help anymore,
I would...
but that's all I know.
Good luck.
I wish I could've seen more.
Yeah.
You wish you could have seen more,
so see more!
Have another vision.
No, no.
See, I don't do visions anymore.
- But you could.
- But I won't.
You can't say the weight of the world
is on your shoulders. The end.
If our fate's up to me,
me says have another vision.
Maybe it'll show me what to do.
Look, even if I wanted to, which I don't,
you wrecked my vision cave.
Which is a problem,
'cause I need a big open space.
- We'll find one.
- Where?
Use my room.
The rats told me everything.
Don't eat those.
Our family needs help,
and you need to get outta here.
You should have told me
the second you saw the vision.
Think of the family.
I was thinking of my daughter.
Pepa, calm down.
- I'm doing my best.
- Yes.
You're lucky it's not a hurricane.
Mamá, you've always been
too hard on Mirabel.
Look around.
We must protect our family, our encanto.
We cannot lose our home.
People in town are becoming anxious
about the magic.
They want to see you.
Mirabel was in that vision for a reason.
Find her.
We might wanna hurry.
You can't hurry the future.
What if I show you something worse?
If I see something that you don't like,
you're gonna be all...
"Bruno makes bad things happen. Oh, he's
creepy and his vision killed my goldfish."
I don't think you
make bad things happen.
Sometimes family weirdos
just get a bad rap.
You can do this.
For the nerves.
I can do this. I can do this,
I can do this, I can do this.
You might wanna hang on.
It's just the same thing.
I gotta stop!
No. I need to know which way it goes.
There's gotta be an answer.
Something we're not seeing!
You're looking at the same thing that I am.
- If there was something else...
- There!
Over there!
Butterfly!
Follow the butterfly!
Where is that?
It's all out of order.
It's the candle.
The candle's getting brighter!
- I think you're gonna help the candle!
- How?
There's someone with you.
- And you fight her!
- What?
Wait, no, no.
Is that a hug?
Am I fighting or hugging?
An embrace.
An embrace!
To make the candle bright
you have to embrace her.
Embrace who?
Almost there.
- Who is it?
- Almost there.
I got it!
Isabela?
Your sister? That's great!
Every time.
Why would embracing Isabela
do anything?
I don't know. Our family got a miracle.
How do you help a family miracle?
You hug a sister.
Mirabel?
Well, I think
we're running out of time here.
It's not gonna work.
She won't hug me ever, okay?
She hates me!
Also, I don't know if you heard,
I ruined her proposal!
- Plus, P.S., she is just annoying.
- Mirabel?
- Of course it's Isabela!
What's her problem with me anyway?
She's the one with roses
coming out of her...
Mirabel!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You see, you're missing the point.
The fate of the family,
it's not up to her.
It's up to you.
You're exactly what this family needs.
You just have to see it.
By yourself, after I leave.
What, you're not coming?
It was your vision, Mirabel. Not mine.
You're afraid Abuela will see you.
Yep. I mean, yes, that too.
Hey, after you save
the miracle, come visit.
After I save the miracle,
I'm bringing you home.
Knock, knock, knock, knock, knock.
Knock on wood.
You got this.
Just gonna save the miracle.
With a hug.
Isa? Hey.
I know we've had our issues...
but I'm ready to be a better sister...
to you.
So, we should just hug.
Let's hug it out, huh?
"Hug it out"?
Luisa can't lift an empanada...
Mariano's nose
looks like a smashed papaya!
Have you lost your mind?
Isa, I feel like you're upset.
And you know what cures being upset?
A warm embrace.
Get out.
Everything was perfect.
Abuela was happy.
The family was happy.
You wanna be a better sister?
Apologize for ruining my life.
Go on. Apologize.
I...
am...
sorry...
- that your life is so great!
- Out.
Wait!
Fine! I apologize!
I wasn't trying to ruin your life!
Some of us have bigger problems...
you selfish, entitled princess!
"Selfish"?
I've been stuck being perfect
my whole entire life!
And literally, the only thing you have ever
done for me is mess things up!
Nothing is messed up!
You can still marry that big dumb hunk!
I never wanted to marry him!
I was doing it for the family!
Oh, my gosh.
Isa...
that is a very serious confession.
Okay, get over here.
Bring it in.
Isa?
♪ I just made something unexpected ♪
♪ Something sharp
Something new ♪
Isa? Uh, this is
the part where we...
♪ It's not symmetrical
Or perfect ♪
♪ But it's beautiful ♪
♪ And it's mine
What else can I do? ♪
♪ Wait!
Bring it in, bring it in ♪
♪ Good talk
♪ What else can I do? ♪
♪ Let's hug
Bring it in, bring it in ♪
♪ Free hugs
♪ I grow rows and rows of roses ♪
♪ Flor de mayo by the mile ♪
♪ I make perfect
Practiced poses ♪
♪ So much hides behind my smile ♪
♪ What could I do if I just grew ♪
♪ What I was feeling
In the moment? ♪
♪ Do you know
Where you're going? ♪
♪ What could I do if I just knew
It didn't need to be perfect? ♪
♪ It just needed to be
And they let me be ♪
♪ A hurricane of jacarandás ♪
- ♪ Strangling figs ♪
- ♪ Fig! ♪
♪ Hanging vines ♪
♪ This is fine ♪
♪ Palma de cera fills the air
As I climb and I push through ♪
♪ What else can I do? ♪
♪ Can I deliver us
A river of sundew? ♪
♪ Careful, it's carnivorous
A little just won't do ♪
♪ I wanna feel the shiver
Of something new ♪
♪ I'm so sick of pretty ♪
♪ I want something true
Don't you? ♪
♪ You just seemed
Like your life's been a dream ♪
♪ Since the moment
You opened your eyes ♪
♪ How far do these roots
Go down? ♪
♪ All I know
Are the blossoms you grow ♪
♪ But it's awesome to see how
You rise ♪
- ♪ How far can I rise? ♪
- ♪ How far can you rise? ♪
♪ Through the roof to the skies
Let's go ♪
♪ A hurricane of jacarandás ♪
- ♪ Strangling figs ♪
- ♪ Go ♪
- ♪ Hanging vines ♪
- ♪ Grow ♪
♪ Palma de cera fills the air
As I climb and I push through ♪
♪ What else?
What else? ♪
♪ What can you do when you are ♪
♪ Deeply madly truly
In the moment? ♪
♪ Seize the moment
Keep going ♪
♪ What can you do when you know ♪
♪ Who you want to be
Isn't perfect? ♪
- ♪ But I'll still be okay ♪
- ♪ Hey, everybody clear the way ♪
♪ I'm coming through
With tabebuia ♪
♪ Tabebuia ♪
- ♪ Making waves ♪
- ♪ Changing minds ♪
- ♪ You've changed mine ♪
♪ The way is clearer
'Cause you're here ♪
♪ And well
I owe this all to you ♪
♪ What else can I do? ♪
♪ Show them what you can do ♪
- ♪ What else can I do? ♪
- ♪ There's nothing you can't do ♪
♪ What else can I do? ♪
You're a bad influence.
What is going on?
Abuela? It's okay! Everything's...
We're gonna save the miracle.
The magic...
What are you talking about?
Look at our home! Look at your sister!
Please just...
Isabela wasn't happy.
Of course she isn't happy.
You ruined her proposal.
No, no, no.
She needed me to ruin her proposal.
And then we did all this!
And the candle burned brighter
and the cracks...
- Mirabel.
- That's why I'm in the vision!
I'm saving the miracle!
You have to stop, Mirabel!
The cracks started with you.
Bruno left because of you.
Luisa's losing her powers.
Isabela's out of control.
Because of you!
I don't know why you
weren't given a Gift...
but it is not an excuse
for you to hurt this family.
I will never be good enough for you.
Will I?
No matter how hard I try.
No matter how hard any of us tries.
Luisa will never be strong enough.
Isabela won't be perfect enough.
Bruno left our family because
you only saw the worst in him.
Bruno didn't care about this family.
He loves this family.
I love this family.
We all love this family.
You're the one that doesn't care.
- You're the one breaking our home.
- Don't you ever...
The miracle is dying, because of you.
No, no, no!
The candle!
Casita! Get me up there!
No!
Careful, Antonio!
We gotta get out of here!
Mirabel! Mirabel!
Mirabel, we have to get out!
- Mirabel!
Mirabel, leave it!
Mirabel! The house is going to fall!
- Mirabel, get out!
- Mirabel!
No.
Mirabel!
Mirabel, are you hurt?
Julieta, come quick!
Julieta!
Don't move.
I'll be right back.
How did this happen?
Here, let me help you.
Let me help you.
- Everyone okay?
- Antonio, don't cry, papito.
How is this possible?
The encanto's broken.
What do we do now?
My powers. They're gone.
What about Antonio?
What is he gonna do?
Mirabel?
Mirabel!
Where's Mirabel?
Where is she?
Mirabel!
Mirabel?
They haven't found her yet?
- Mirabel!
Mirabel!
Mirabel.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to hurt us.
I just wanted...
to be something I'm not.
I've never been able to come back here.
This river is where we were given
our miracle.
Where Abuelo Pedro...
I thought we would have
a different life.
I thought I would be a different woman.
♪ Two caterpillars ♪
♪ In love ♪
♪ Spend their nights and dawns ♪
♪ Full of hunger ♪
♪ They keep walking ♪
♪ And navigating the world ♪
♪ That changes and keeps changing ♪
♪ Navigating a world ♪
♪ Two caterpillars stop the wind ♪
♪ As they hold each other
with warmth and consent ♪
♪ Keep growing
They don't know when ♪
♪ To find some corner shelter ♪
♪ The time keeps changing ♪
♪ They are inseparable ♪
♪ And the weather keeps changing ♪
♪ Oh, caterpillars ♪
♪ Don't hold each other any longer ♪
♪ You must grow apart and return ♪
♪ That's the way forward ♪
♪ Miracles are coming ♪
♪ Chrysalises are coming ♪
♪ You must part ♪
♪ And construct your own future ♪
♪ Oh, caterpillars ♪
♪ Don't hold each other any longer ♪
♪ You must grow apart and return ♪
♪ That's the way forward ♪
♪ Miracles are coming ♪
♪ Chrysalises are coming ♪
♪ You must part ♪
♪ And construct your own future ♪
♪ Two caterpillars ♪
♪ Disoriented ♪
♪ In two cocoons ♪
♪ All bundled up ♪
I was given a miracle.
A second chance.
And I was so afraid to lose it...
that I lost sight of who
our miracle was for.
And I am so sorry.
You never hurt our family, Mirabel.
We are broken...
because of me.
Abuela.
I can finally see.
You lost your home.
Lost everything.
You suffered so much...
all alone...
so it would never happen again.
We were saved because of you.
We were given a miracle,
because of you.
We are a family,
And nothing could ever be broken
that we can't fix... together.
I asked my Pedro for help.
Mirabel.
He sent me you.
♪ Oh, butterflies ♪
♪ Don't hold each other any longer ♪
♪ You must grow apart and return ♪
♪ That's the way forward ♪
♪ You are already miracles ♪
♪ Breaking chrysalises ♪
♪ You must fly ♪
♪ And find your own future ♪
She didn't do this!
I gave her a vision!
It was me!
I was, like, "Go!"
And she was, like...
She only wanted to help.
I don't care what you think of me,
but if you're too stubborn to...
Brunito.
I feel like I missed
something important.
Come on.
What's happening? Where are we going?
Home.
It's her! I found her!
I found her!
She's back! She's back, she's back!
Mirabel!
Mamá.
Mi amor, I was so worried.
We couldn't find you.
There were bees everywhere.
I'll be okay.
Not if we don't have a house.
What? We don't have a house.
I can't say we don't have a house?
What is that? Not a house.
♪ Look at this home
We need a new foundation ♪
♪ It may seem hopeless
But we'll get by just fine ♪
♪ Look at this family
A glowing constellation ♪
♪ So full of stars
And everybody wants to shine ♪
♪ But the stars don't shine
They burn ♪
♪ And the constellations shift ♪
♪ I think it's time you learn ♪
♪ You're more
Than just your Gift ♪
♪ And I'm sorry
I held on too tight ♪
♪ Just so afraid
I'd lose you too ♪
♪ The miracle is not
Some magic that you've got ♪
♪ The miracle is you ♪
♪ Not some Gift
Just you ♪
♪ The miracle is you ♪
♪ All of you
All of you ♪
♪ Okay so
We gonna talk about Bruno? ♪
♪ That's Bruno? ♪
♪ Yeah
There's a lot to say ♪
♪ About Bruno ♪
♪ I'll start, okay ♪
♪ Pepa, I'm sorry
About your wedding ♪
♪ Didn't mean to be upsetting ♪
♪ That wasn't a prophecy ♪
♪ I could just see
You were sweating ♪
♪ And I wanted you to know
That your bro loves you so ♪
♪ Let it in, let it out
Let it rain, let it snow ♪
♪ Let it go ♪
♪ That's what I'm always saying, bro ♪
♪ I got a lot of apologies I got to say ♪
♪ Hey, we're just happy
that you're here, okay? ♪
- ♪ Come into the light ♪
- ♪ That trip was only a night ♪
♪ And no matter what happens
We're gonna find our way ♪
♪ Yo, I knew he never left
I heard him every day ♪
What's that sound?
I think it's everyone in town.
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Lay down your load
Lay down your load ♪
♪ Roll me down the road
Roll me down the road ♪
♪ We have no Gifts
But we are many ♪
♪ And we'll do anything for you ♪
♪ It's a dream
When we work as a team ♪
♪ You're so strong ♪
- ♪ Yeah, but sometimes I cry ♪
- ♪ So do I ♪
♪ I may not be as strong
But I'm getting wiser ♪
♪ Yeah, I need sunlight
And fertilizer ♪
♪ Come on
Let's plant something new ♪
♪ And watch it fly ♪
♪ Straight up to the sky ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ The stars don't shine
They burn ♪
♪ The constellations glow ♪
♪ The seasons change in turn ♪
♪ Would you watch
Our little girl go ♪
♪ She takes after you ♪
♪ Hey, Mariano
Why so blue? ♪
♪ I just have
So much love inside ♪
♪ You know
I've got this cousin too ♪
♪ Have you met Dolores? ♪
Okay, I'll take it from here. Goodbye!
♪ You talk so loud ♪
♪ You take care of your mother
And you make her proud ♪
♪ You write your own poetry ♪
♪ Every night
When you go to sleep ♪
♪ And I'm seizing the moment ♪
♪ So would you wake up
And notice me ♪
Dolores, I see you.
- And I hear you.
- Yes!
♪ All of you
All of you ♪
- Let's get married.
- Slow down.
♪ All of you
All of you ♪
♪ Home sweet home
I like the new foundation ♪
♪ It isn't perfect ♪
- ♪ Neither are we ♪
- ♪ That's true ♪
♪ Just one more thing
Before the celebration ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
- ♪ We need a doorknob ♪
We made this one for you.
♪ We see
How bright you burn ♪
♪ We see how brave you've been ♪
♪ Now see yourself in turn ♪
♪ You're the real Gift, kid
Let us in ♪
♪ Open your eyes ♪
What do you see?
I see... me.
♪ All of me ♪
Come on! Get in here!
♪ Party night ♪
♪ Everyone's coming to celebrate ♪
♪ Everyone's coming to have fun ♪
♪ Keep dancing ♪
- ♪ Happy in my paradise ♪
- Yeah!
♪ And revealing ♪
♪ Miracles on every floor ♪
♪ Enchantment ♪
♪ A-ha. Yeah, amor! ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Everyone, together...
La Familia Madrigal!
♪ Enchantment ♪
♪ Opening doors
The morning is arriving ♪
♪ They stay open
And the coffee is made at home ♪
♪ Happy song
So that good wins over bad ♪
♪ Don't wake me up
This looks like a real dream ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I always fall in love
with your enchantment ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Your charm continues to bless you ♪
♪ Colombia ♪
♪ Enchantment ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Your name has an enchantment ♪
♪ From Bogotá to Palenque
I went with everybody ♪
♪ Colombia, beautiful earth ♪
♪ Mother Nature gave you your form ♪
♪ Colombia stays my favorite place ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I always fall in love
with your enchantment ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Your charm continues to bless you ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Party night
Everyone's coming to celebrate ♪
Everyone's coming to have fun ♪
♪ Keep dancing ♪
♪ Happy in my paradise ♪
♪ And revealing ♪
♪ Miracles on every floor ♪
♪ Enchantment ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I always fall in love
with your enchantment ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Colombia, I love you so much ♪
♪ May you keep blessing
your enchantment ♪
♪ Enchantment ♪
♪ Two oruguitas ♪
♪ In love and yearning ♪
♪ Spend every evening
And morning learning ♪
♪ To hold each other
Their hunger burning ♪
♪ To navigate a world ♪
♪ That's changing
Never stops turning ♪
♪ Together in this world ♪
♪ That's changing
Never stops turning ♪
♪ Two oruguitas ♪
♪ Against the weather ♪
♪ The wind grows colder
As they're together ♪
♪ They hold each other
No way of knowing ♪
♪ They're all they have for shelter ♪
♪ And something inside them is growing ♪
♪ They'll all just stay together ♪
♪ But something inside them is growing ♪
♪ Aye, oruguitas ♪
♪ Don't you hold on too tight ♪
♪ Both of you know
It's your time to grow ♪
♪ To fall apart
To reunite ♪
♪ Wonders await you ♪
♪ Just on the other side ♪
♪ Trust they'll be there
Start to prepare ♪
♪ Don't wait for tomorrow ♪
♪ Aye, oruguitas ♪
♪ Don't you hold on too tight ♪
♪ Both of you know
It's your time to grow ♪
♪ To fall apart
To reunite ♪
♪ Wonders await you ♪
♪ Just on the other side ♪
♪ Trust they'll be there
Start to prepare ♪
♪ Don't wait for tomorrow ♪
♪ Two oruguitas ♪
♪ Cocooned and waiting ♪
♪ Each in their own world ♪
♪ Anticipating ♪
♪ What happens after ♪
♪ The rearranging ♪
♪ And so afraid of change ♪
♪ In a world that never
stops changing ♪
♪ So let the walls come down ♪
♪ The world will never
stop changing ♪
- ♪ Never stop changing ♪
♪ Never stop changing ♪
♪ Aye, mariposa ♪
♪ Don't you hold on too tight ♪
♪ Both of you know
It's your time to go ♪
♪ To fly apart
To reunite ♪
♪ Wonders surround you ♪
♪ Just let the walls come down ♪
♪ Don't look behind you ♪
♪ Fly till you find
Your way till tomorrow ♪
♪ Aye, mariposa ♪
♪ Don't you hold on too tight ♪
♪ Both of you know
It's your time to grow ♪
♪ To fly apart
To reunite ♪
♪ Wonders surround you ♪
♪ Just let the walls come down ♪
♪ Don't look behind you ♪
♪ Fly till you find
Your way till tomorrow ♪
♪ Aye, mariposa ♪
♪ Don't you hold on too tight ♪
♪ Both of you know
It's your time to grow ♪
♪ To fly apart
To reunite ♪
♪ Wonders surround you ♪
♪ Just let the walls come down ♪
♪ Don't look behind you ♪
♪ Fly till you find
Your way till tomorrow ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
Improved by Synchronized