It had to be a cow.
Couldn't be like a dog or something
that isn't 10,000 pounds.
- Come on! Can you just help me, dude?
- I'm doing all the work here, man.
- Push! Push! Come on!
- Jason, it stepped on my foot.
Pull yourself together.
Just tie it to the bench
- and let's get out of here, please.
- Cow seems unhappy, huh?
Well, it shouldn't be unhappy,
because I just milked her.
Him.
- You just milked him.
- This is a him?
- Was it one udder?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's not an udder, dude.
I was gonna say,
it was actually kinda weird.
It was really big,
and I had to use two hands.
- It didn't...
- Stop. We will never discuss this again.
That'd be great.
Cops!
The cops are coming.
Beefcake, hide!
What? I'm sorry, Beefcake!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Damn!
Whoa!
Okay.
Come on.
Whoo! Yeah!
Whoa!
You know, I don't think we're ever gonna
understand each other.
Just when I think you've done
the dumbest thing you could possibly do,
you find something
even dumber and you do it.
Thank you.
I promise you, this is not the moment
to be a wiseass.
And I know you think it's noble
that you didn't rat out your friends.
I acted alone.
Beefcake and I had a connection.
Yeah, that's funny.
You know what's not funny?
This was supposed to be your season.
I had scouts coming to every game.
You could have written your own ticket.
Now it's all gone.
Now you gotta come here every Saturday
for the rest of the year
just so you can graduate!
With all these other weirdos
and criminals.
Yeah.
Like you said,
we'll never understand each other.
One play left in the entire game.
Can Angel Grove do it?
They're down by five.
Jason Scott takes his position
at quarterback. Here comes the snap.
Wide receiver Marty Borne
looks like he's open.
He's getting ready for a pass.
Jason Scott makes...
no, no, wait, he doesn't make a pass!
What a pump fake!
He's running with the ball.
He's at the 20, the 15, the ten.
Jason Scott scores!
Touchdown!
Jason Scott singlehandedly
brings the team home for the championship!
Moo!
That's so funny.
Hey, you sure you're in the right room?
Oh, big tough guy.
This one goes here. That one goes there.
Primary colors go on this side,
this one goes...
I'm sorry.
Here, let me help you.
You're a freak. You know that?
I've had to watch you play
with these for weeks.
Are you crazy?
No? What if you had an extra one?
Freak.
Why don't you cut this little act
and do something?
Why don't you stop me? Huh?
- Are you gonna stop...
- Hey!
How old are you? Five?
Hi, I'm Jason. It's my first time here.
It's exciting.
And you must be the bully of detention.
How dumb can you be?
Oh!
Did you just slap me?
I did. Weird, right?
Now I'm gonna be here every day
for what seems like the rest of my life,
and I'm sure that you are, too.
So let's make a deal.
Don't sit near me,
or him,
and we'll be okay.
Okay!
Uh, approved homework,
or working on the Better Choices workbook.
- These should be out and in progress.
- I need to go to the ladies' room.
Uh... Okay. And good morning.
Oh, my God.
I got your text and I was like,
"Where are they?"
So, this is where you come every Saturday
instead of practice.
- God, this must suck.
- It does.
Well, then you shouldn't have
sent Ty that picture of me.
That's not exactly how it happened.
I mean, he's a liar.
- You punched his tooth out.
- They put it back.
Water under the bridge now. Let's move on.
Oh, thank God.
We're moving on. Without you.
Cutting you out. Literally.
You can show up for cheer practice
if you want,
but I wouldn't.
Damn, girl!
Oh, my God, what have you done?
Kimberly, what have you done to your hair?
You cut off your hair?
- Hey... door!
- Kimberly what...
Hey, thanks for that in there.
Ah, no worries. I hate guys like that.
Yeah. Oh... so, hey, we should,
uh, hang out sometime, huh?
Not that we have to.
But I think tonight we should.
- What's your name again?
- Billy.
Billy Cranston.
Or William Cranston.
You remember kids used to call me
Billy Crams-tons as a third-grade joke?
Like Billy crams tons of crayons
in his butt.
Which I didn't! But it's really impossible
to cram a ton of crayons in a butt.
- No, no, I'm sorry, I shouldn't say that.
- Okay, Billy,
I would honestly hang out with you,
but I have a date every night
with the Angel Grove Sheriff's Department.
So... I'm sorry.
Wait... no, no, no.
Don't leave, don't leave, hey.
All right, so I don't really expect
for us to hang out.
Truth is I need to get somewhere tonight,
and I could really use your help.
Billy, I hear you, but as I told you,
I have house arrest.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I'm sorry.
Well, like, I mean, I can fix that.
I know how to trick the SIM.
I have, uh... I have tools.
I have to be in my house before 7:00.
Well, if you come to my house before
7:00, then I can fix it for you.
Oh! I also have a car. Or access to a car.
And if you decide to help me,
you can have the car for a few hours.
Come on, honey. Let's go.
Don't be so hard on him.
How do you think he feels
walking around town now?
How do you think I feel
Let's not do this tonight.
What's the plan, huh?
What's he gonna do with his life?
He could've been so much more.
Get out of the way!
Oh, my God, is that Jason Scott?
Oh, my God! Jason Scott!
- Billy?
- Yeah.
- Billy!
- Yes?
- It's 6:56...
- 6:56, I know.
You got four minutes. Grab that chair.
- What's all this stuff?
- It's objects that I found with my dad.
Most of it is his.
- Hey.
- Where's the cage? Where's the cage?
Here. Here it is.
- Put your foot in this.
- What is it?
It's a Faraday cage. It should stop
the cell signal if we're lucky.
That's the three-minute warning.
- Come on, bud. If the signal goes off...
- My dad's been dead
now seven years,
four months, and two days?
- Yeah, two days.
- Um, okay, um...
That's a long time.
He used to work at the mine.
Billy, I really don't think
that we have time...
You still live at 4455 Old Wharf?
- Yes... yes, I do.
- Great house.
- Okay.
- So, yeah, about my dad.
We used to go and find objects together.
Some really, really old.
I'm gonna get in trouble, Billy.
Oh! Almost like that show
American Pickers.
Billy, the signal's gonna go off.
We should've definitely
had our own TV show.
That would've been so crazy.
What are you doing?
Dude, come on, seriously!
It's gonna go... Billy, come on!
What?
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm. Can you stop touching me now?
It's so cool you actually showed up.
Well, you are giving me the van.
Lending you the van. But, yeah.
How much further is it?
Just 44 minutes and 52 seconds.
Uh... Okay.
Thank you for helping me today.
That's okay, Billy.
Uh... Okay, this is the entrance
to the gold mine, and clearly,
Billy, the sign says...
Keep driving.
Okay.
If we find something cool,
then you can keep half.
- It's a rule that me and my dad made.
- Thanks, Billy.
They're gonna blow this whole thing.
It'll all be gone in a week.
Billy, can I be honest? The deal was
I drop you somewhere,
and I get the van for a few hours, okay?
This is weird.
Like, we don't know each other at all.
I don't know what we're doing here.
- And you seem kinda...
- Wait, I gotta tell you something, okay?
I'm on the spectrum.
Well, is that like a workout program?
Like Tae Bo?
No. It's a diagnosis. Excuse me.
I know. It was a joke. I was kidding.
See, that's the thing.
I didn't get the joke.
Like my brain doesn't work the same
as yours does, you know?
Yeah, well, consider that a good thing.
It's just that I can't read
humor or... or sarcasm.
- Oh! But I do remember things.
- Okay.
- I remember everything.
Billy, let me stop you.
Okay.
You don't need to tell me all this.
We're cool.
Okay. Well, we're almost there.
Which is good news, so...
take my spare flashlight now,
'cause it's gonna be dark
- when we get back.
- Bye, Billy!
Okay!
Ah, she's back again.
Oh, crazy girl.
Just like clockwork.
Who are you?
No way!
Uh... hello?
Hey!
No, no, no, no. Kimberly!
Kimberly!
Okay. Okay.
- It's strange to hear you say my name.
- What?
What did you say?
I said, it's strange
to hear you say my name.
Like we know each other.
We... we do know each other.
Oh, we know who each other are,
but we don't really know each other.
I know you used to date Ty Fleming.
Oh. Then you know I punched his tooth out.
I know they put it back.
Dad, I hope you're watching.
Gonna make you proud.
Dad, I forgot to tell you, uh,
I took the van without
asking Mom's permission.
Well, I'm telling you,
so I think that's okay.
Anyways, I gotta focus. Okay.
So what are you doing up here?
Did you follow me?
I, uh, came with... Billy.
Billy Cranston? Weird.
But I've seen him up here before.
My house is on the other side
of the mountain.
I hike these trails sometimes,
clear my head,
and I stare down at Angel Grove and wonder
how such a small, crap town
could cause me such misery.
That funny to you?
No, I just... I feel the same way.
Yeah. Jason Scott, star quarterback,
crashes and burns.
Destroys his career
and destroys our season.
Go Tigers.
Yeah, now I walk around town
and everyone's looking at me
like I ran over their dog.
So why don't you leave? You know, just go.
- I could leave here, you know?
- Where?
God, anywhere.
So let's go.
What?
- You'd never do it.
- Try me.
Oh, what, you and me? You got a car?
- I have a van.
- Ooh, that's creepy.
It's not that kind of van.
Every van is that kind of van.
So, let's go.
Are you daring me? 'Cause I'll go.
Okay.
Dad, get ready.
That didn't work.
Whoa! Whoa!
- That really rung my bell.
- Hey, hey, hey!
Go, go, go, go, go!
- Oh! Wow!
- Hey!
What are you doing, dude?
I been digging up here for some years.
Hey! Easy, guy. Let's sort this out, huh?
- I seen him up here before.
- Hey, Jason.
Dude cannot be walking around
blowing stuff up!
I was just trying to dig a little deeper!
Maybe I dug too deep, huh?
Billy, you don't have to yell.
We can hear you, okay?
- Okay!
- Hey!
You guys looking
to get busted or something?
This place is a restricted area!
Oh, really, Einstein? Restricted?
As in, we shouldn't be standing
on crazy rocks
doing Karate Kid moves, right?
Uh... Guys...
Yeah. I see you.
Yeah, or camping out on old trains.
I see you, too, homeboy.
Uh, guys...
There's a lotta mine security out tonight.
- Who is she?
- I don't know.
I've never seen her before.
Oh, no.
Whoa!
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Whoa.
What is it?
I've never seen glass like this before.
Oh, my God.
What is it? What is that?
There's something in there.
Move.
- All right, watch out, watch out. Look!
- What are you doing?
- Wait, no, no, no! No, no!
- Seriously?
- What are you doing?
- Oh, yeah!
My dad always knew the right spots.
There's gotta be more. Let's get it!
- Get out of the way.
- That doesn't mean keep banging!
Oh!
What is it?
What is that?
- What? No, no! Don't break it.
- No. No, no, no!
Don't break it! Don't break it!
Don't break...
You broke it. Okay.
Wow. What?
- Oh, my God.
- What is that?
Yo, look, we all found these.
- If they're worth any money...
- No, he found them.
Now chill out.
- Chill out?
- Guys, guys, do you hear that?
Mine security. Peace.
Somebody should have pointed
that out. Wait, I did.
Billy!
- Wait, okay, okay.
- Run!
Billy! Just run to the... come on!
Billy, let's go!
- Haul ass, dude!
- I'm coming!
Are you kidding me?
Ja... Jason! Jason!
- What are you doing?
- You gotta open the doors!
Open the door!
- Yes, okay, just get in.
- What are you doing?
Did you see them? Are they down the road?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
Okay, what about the others?
- You gonna leave the others?
- Hold on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Jason!
Whoo!
- Oh, my mom's gonna kill me.
- Stop right there!
- Shit! Put your seat belt on.
- I got my seat belt on!
- Jason! Somebody's gonna die.
- Whoa!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
- There they are!
- Okay, so...
- Up the hill. Come on!
- Get 'em!
Okay!
- Okay, you drive.
- No, I... I really don't drive.
Okay, then really don't drive,
so I can pull them in.
I don't drive!
Get your foot!
- I got it.
- Wait, it says that the door's open.
That's because it's open, Billy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Go, go, go!
- Okay. Okay.
There they are! Get closer to them.
Get in!
Gotcha.
- I gotcha!
- I'm in!
What about the other guy?
- Just go!
- Go! Go!
Billy, look out!
Let's go downhill! Go to the lights below!
- You wanna drive now?
- Keep going, Billy,
- we're almost there.
- Guys! Guys, there's a train.
We got it.
Okay.
- Oh, my God!
Hey!
Hey, what do you want me to do?
- Hey!
- Keep going! I'll pull him in!
Okay.
Are you crazy?
Yeah, I am.
Yo, it's catching up.
Look, there's the railroad crossing.
That's the way out, Billy.
- You got it.
- You got it!
I hope he has it.
- He definitely doesn't have it.
- I got it! I got it!
Storm's turned. It's gotten bad.
We're getting out of here.
Let's go!
Pull it port!
Pull up the net!
Let's go, boys! Pull!
A little more starboard!
Let her go!
What the hell is that?
Get back!
- Wide to the port!...now!
- Yeah!
Okay.
Billy! What's happening down there?
What?
- Where's your bodyguard?
- What are you doing?
I'm just gonna quietly snap your wrist,
you little bitch.
Oh, no, no, no. Oh... Okay.
Billy Cranston
just knocked Colt Wallace
out cold! Damn, Billy!
What happened? What happened?
- I didn't see it!
- Hi, Billy.
Hey. Come on, come on.
- Am I crazy or this is crazy, right?
- It's crazy.
We got hit by a train
and we're standing here.
How is that possible?
I don't remember getting home
from the mine at all.
I slept all day yesterday.
We gotta find Billy.
You know I wasn't trying to start
any trouble or anything like that.
And I say, "Hey, man, look,
I'm not a violent person.
But if you must come at me,
come at me, bro."
- Sweet!
- Yeah!
Boom! Down goes douchebag.
- Down goes... I... I can't say that word.
- Billy.
Hey, Kimberly... Kimberly Hart.
We need to talk.
How... what?
- Since when does he know Kimberly Hart?
- Billy's awesome.
Nice hair.
- Billy, look at me.
- Huh?
Do you feel weird?
You mean like weirder than usual?
Yeah. Different.
Oh.
Listen, we know something
happened up there, okay?
I'm not the same.
Me either. Oh! I'm strong.
- How strong?
- Like, insanely strong.
I feel like we need to go back up there.
The counter's boiling.
We're going back today.
Yeah.
Come on up.
Oh, she's down here.
So you're sure it's a woman?
Not a great-looking woman.
Come see for yourself.
Oh, that smell is... it's intense.
You should make a note of that.
Smell inside an old fishing boat
that holds tons of dead fish
doesn't smell so good.
Freaky, right?
- Look, do you need us?
- No.
All right, 'cause I need to get to bed.
Lock up when you're done.
There's beers in the fridge.
Jesus.
Unit two, this is Meinen.
I have a body. A deceased female.
Let's just keep going.
Guys, look. Look, it's that guy again.
Find anything interesting?
If I do, I'm keeping it!
- We know why you're here.
- Oh, yeah?
You guys wake up surprised to be alive
and jump over a house?
Yeah. Kinda. Well... no.
Look, we're different, all right?
Everything's different.
Uh, you're Zack, right?
Yup.
You still go to Angel Grove?
Ha! Sometimes!
You know, the other girl was here too,
about an hour ago.
Hey, you mean that girl right there?
Hey! Come on down!
We should figure this out together!
- Whoa.
- Oh, screw this.
- Okay, let me handle this.
- She got up there pretty fast.
No, no, no!
Yo, keep up.
Stop!
Just... just talk to me.
You have a coin. We have a coin.
We should just talk about this.
I mean, we don't know what this...
- Whoa! Whoa!
- What is wrong with you?
Whoa.
Oh, you're crazy! But so am I.
- Whoa, Zack.
- No, I got this.
- Wait, wait.
- What are you doing?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey!
- I got her!
- Get off of me.
Just jump over.
Let's go. Jump with me. Yeah.
- No, no, no! Don't... don't jump.
- Okay.
- Don't jump. Don't jump.
- I'm gonna jump across with her,
and then you jump, okay?
- Piece o' cake.
- No, no, no!
Don't, don't! Jason! Hey!
That's not a piece o' cake!
- You all right?
- Yeah, no problem.
You got this, Billy!
No, I don't!
- It's fun.
- It's such a far jump.
- Come on, let's go, dude.
- Billy, come on.
- We all did it.
- Yeah, you'll be fine, I promise. Just jump.
Come on, do it, dude. Let's go.
The drop is probably more than
100 feet, which means death is imminent.
Okay, so if you die, Billy,
what's gonna happen?
Okay, your mom'll be alone.
But it's okay 'cause
she could find somebody else.
But she couldn't, 'cause you love your mom
- and you won't really...
- He's scared.
He'll come across, he's fine.
Okay. Okay.
Visualize jumping across!
- And then do it!
- Come on, you got this!
Okay!
Billy, you got this!
Whoa! Oh, shit!
Whoa!
- Are you okay?
- I got it.
- Come on, climb up. Climb up.
- I did it.
- Billy, you got it.
- I did it!
See, what'd we tell you, Billy?
You got it!
Told you. See?
- Whoo!
- Yes!
Billy, right! Yeah!
- Whoa!
- Billy!
- Oh, my God!
Billy!
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Billy!
- We just kill that dude?
- What do we do?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, guys, you gotta come down here!
It's water! You gotta see this!
Yo, all right!
I'll see you guys down there.
Uh... bring that crazy girl.
Come on, you guys, let's go! Whoo!
Whoa!
Uh, hey... could I get a sip
of your water?
I'm dying.
Okay. Just don't finish it.
Thanks. And I'm really sorry.
Sorry for what?
Whoa!
Yeah!
Welcome to the club!
'Sup, crazy girl?
We gotta do that again.
Oh, thank goodness.
- Hey, guys. Guys!
- What?
- Check out how we glow.
- Cool.
- Oh, yeah!
- I like this.
I'm blue!
That's not my favorite color,
but it's cool.
I'm black!
- What?
- I am.
No, you're not.
Hey, guys. There's something down there.
Follow me.
- Where are we?
- I don't know.
Jason, I'm sliding!
- Hi.
- Again?
Well, that is unusual.
This just gets better and better.
Do you feel that?
There's something out here.
The walls are shaking.
Come on.
That's impossible.
This must have been here
for millions of years.
I mean, look how the rock
has grown around it.
I don't like this place.
Hey, guys.
Check it out.
- Okay.
- Holy sh...
- Shh!
- What? Think there's aliens in here?
- Just be quiet, Zack.
It's so cold in here.
Jason, is this real?
Like, are we really in a spaceship
right now?
I think so. Just... just breathe, okay?
Okay.
Hey. We've all seen enough.
Right? We should go now?
What? We're gonna be famous!
- What is wrong with you?
- Quiet!
There's something here.
Whoa!
- Ah!
- What was that?
Whoa.
What's going on?
- The stairs!
- Oh, my God!
There's no way out.
- Guys, guys, guys!
- Let's go! That way! Let's go! Let's go!
- I'm going!
- Run!
Come on, come on.
Didi, I'm coming!
You're real!
Leave her alone!
We will kill you.
Kill me? How?
There's five of us.
Yes, I know! I've been waiting for you.
Wait, where's the other guy?
One, two, three, four... oh! There he is.
Oh, no, no, no!
All of you.
In a spaceship buried underground?
How long have you been waiting?
- What's today? Monday?
- Yeah.
Then 65 million years.
I've been very lonely.
You're all so young-looking.
This has to do with the coins?
Yes, yes, the coins!
Different colors. Different kids.
Different-colored kids!
I'm so excited you're here!
Turn around.
Go on.
No way.
Proceed.
Think this'll work.
One, two, three, four, five.
Different colors.
Guys, let's focus on getting out of here.
Stay together,
and then when we see a chance...
- We run like hell.
- Okay. And if we don't get a chance?
Then we kill it.
Shouldn't hurt, but let's see.
Please, step into the footprints.
No. We are not going to do that.
Hey, question. Um, what are you?
I'm Alpha 5,
an alphormic lorcaid persona android.
- What? Yeah, I know.
- He said he's a Alpha 5...
I'm a talking robot. You can trust me.
Billy!
What the hell?
Okay.
Why do you keep looking at each other?
Is that, like, a human thing?
Fascinating.
Oh, it's working!
This is great! It's working!
Zordon, are you there? Zordon!
Okay. Okay.
Come on! Let's go! Move!
Go, go, go!
Come forward, please!
Do we have a choice?
Don't think so.
Look! It's Zordon!
What?
Zordon, they don't know who you are.
Come in! Come in!
These are them? They're so small.
Funny, I said the same thing, actually.
You mean to tell me
that the fate of the universe
is placed in the hands
of these... these children?
The universe? That's a big place.
They're teenagers.
Somewhere between infancy
and full maturity.
- It's hard to explain, really. I don't...
- Show me the coins.
The morphing grid is never wrong.
If the power coins
have returned to the ship with these...
Teenagers!
With these teenagers,
then these teenagers
are the Power Rangers.
Power Rangers!
What?
Okay, quick question.
Hello. Hate to interrupt.
Did I just hear you say
we're Power Rangers?
Yes. Yes. You are the Power Rangers.
Any other questions?
- No, I think I'm good.
- Good.
I got a question. Um... Hi, how you doing?
Oh, okay... um, my name is Billy.
Billy Cranston.
- Kids used to call me Billy Crams-tons...
- Billy! Stop.
I'm sorry.
Uh... the images here in this sphere
tell a history of the Power Rangers.
Looks like the Power Rangers
were a team that protected life.
And life is a bright light.
Or... a piece of light?
Yes. Yes, very good, Billy.
It is called the Zeo Crystal.
Oh, I love this part. This is good.
And every planet
in the universe that has life
has a piece of the crystal
buried inside it.
Sixty-five million years ago,
Zordon's team died defending the crystal
here in what is now Angel Grove.
- The coins have chosen you five.
- Yes! I knew it!
Now you must protect the Zeo Crystal
and life on earth.
Because... we... are the Power Rangers?
He's smart!
I'm sorry, um, is this some kind of joke?
Like, I'm standing here with a wet wedgie.
My socks are soaked.
We're squishing around in here.
We're talking to a wall. I mean, guys...
Silence!
Dig! Dig, Goldar!
Sir, I'm detecting elevated heart rates.
They're... they're very scared.
I don't understand.
Why would you show us that nightmare?
It's not a nightmare. It's the future.
- Was that for real?
- Felt like it.
- And who was that woman?
- Her name is Rita Repulsa.
She will create Goldar,
a huge monster who will rip the crystal
from the earth,
and all life on your planet will die.
With the crystal, Rita will have the power
to create and destroy worlds.
So, let me guess.
You want us to kill this woman? R... Rita?
Ay, ay, ay! Rita!
She must be stopped.
When is she coming?
She's already here.
My best guess is we have 11 months.
Oh, I'm sorry, days. Days, 11 days.
If we're the Power Rangers
and this is our ship,
if I walk through that door right now,
will it open for me?
Yes, of course.
Let's go.
Whoa, what you doing?
No, no, no, come back!
No. No, please, don't leave.
Jason, my ranger team died
defending the crystal from Rita.
That's why I'm in this wall.
How'd you know my name?
Because it's you, Jason Scott.
You are the leader.
You are the Red Ranger.
Rita was a ranger, too. And my friend.
But she betrayed us.
Wanted more power.
She lost her way.
Now she is just pure evil.
You must bring them back.
All of the rangers.
You must train your team to stop Rita
before she has the strength
to find the crystal.
Okay. I'm leaving.
- And I only speak for myself when I...
- No! You speak for all of them.
You know that, deep down,
what I'm saying is true.
You were born for this.
You all waited.
Even you.
Who... exactly are you?
Really? Now you're gonna ask me who I am?
- Look, her name is Didi.
- Trini.
She's new at school.
Transferred in a month ago.
We have English together, right?
I've been at Angel Grove
for over a year now.
We have biology together. Good talk.
Wait, look...
none of us really know each other, okay?
But somehow...
we were all in the same place at the
same time when Billy found those coins.
- And...
- Wait, wait, wait! Can I ask a question?
Are we really superheroes?
Like are we more like
Iron Man or Spider-Man?
'Cause I feel like I been bit by a spider,
but I feel really good, you know, not as...
All right, look, bro,
trust me, you're not a superhero.
Why are you talking to us
like you're the boss now?
Hey, hold up.
Can any of this Rita stuff be real?
Can any of it be true?
I don't know.
But I know that the answer
to what's wrong with us
and to what's happening to us...
is here.
So what are you saying?
I think we gotta come back.
I can't make you come back here.
But 4:00 tomorrow... I'll be here.
Hey, Jason, we don't... we don't...
- That makes sense. That makes sense.
- Of course.
I don't know why I didn't think
about that one in the first place.
So where were you today?
Were you with friends?
Do you have any friends?
- Why are you so tired...
- Okay, this is the problem.
You ask her four questions before
she's even answered the first.
Because she's like a ghost around here.
She needs to start communicating.
- June...
- Say something.
- Speak! I just...
- Relax.
Okay. Relax.
Okay, Trini, let's start over.
Please tell us one thing you did today.
Me and four kids from Angel Grove
found a spaceship buried underground.
What?
I'm pretty sure I'm a superhero.
Cool.
Not cool.
Pee in that cup!
This to remind me of my screw-up?
No. Wrecking yard
only offered me 300 bucks for it and...
you know, the frame's straight
and the engine still runs.
Figure I'd leave it up to you to decide
if you wanted to fix it.
Oh, shit.
Mr. Scott,
there's been an incident on your boat.
It's a terrible situation.
You gotta come with me.
A series of grisly crime
scenes has the sleepy fishing hamlet
of Angel Grove reeling.
- Bodies were discovered...
- I'm building Goldar for you....
This rash of violence
has the town on edge.
Goldar's coming. Goldar's coming.
What the hell you doing?
I need gold.
I will build my beautiful Goldar.
Goldar takes the Zeo Crystal.
I take the universe.
Me, too!
- What's up, crazy girl?
- Hey.
Shall we do this?
You need to follow the three rules
to being a Power Ranger.
You must never use your powers
for personal gain.
You must never escalate a fight,
unless your enemy forces you to.
And you must never reveal
your identity. Ever.
To assume your ranger identities,
you need to morph.
Have any of you morphed before?
Yes. But only in the shower.
Okay, okay. Let's step
into the footprints, please.
Let's try this.
Standing in this circle as a team,
you can easily connect
to the morphing grid.
- Do you feel it?
- Yeah, they do.
No. Not feeling it.
You need to morph to get your armor.
I knew it! We do get armor.
Jason! We get armor! Oh, we get armor.
Cool. When do you give us the armor?
You already have it inside of you.
You bring it out by connecting to each
other and connecting to the morphing grid.
Clear your minds and focus.
Power Rangers were a legion of warriors
sworn to protect life.
Yes!
You must become those warriors.
Become the warriors!
What?
What? What, did it... did it work?
Alpha 5, why didn't they morph?
Yeah, I don't... I don't know, sir.
It's... it's disturbing.
Very disturbing.
This might take some time.
We don't have time.
If they can't morph,
what are we supposed to do?
They'll have to train without armor.
- They need to prepare.
- Without armor?
Sir, that'll be very painful.
Take them down to the pit.
All right, follow me.
We're going to the pit!
Jason, I don't wanna find out
what the pit is.
So this is the pit. It's nice, right?
Alpha 5, begin the exercise.
Uh... sorry, guys.
- What exercise?
- Chill out, dude.
These creatures before you
are a simulation of Rita's army.
They're called Putties.
You must get through them to get to her.
No, no, no, no, Jason.
Cool. Look, relax, guys. It's a hologram.
Like a video game. Look.
Whoa!
That's a strong-ass hologram.
Not a video game.
This is why you must morph
into your armor.
If Rita becomes strong enough
to build her army,
it'll be the beginning of the end.
Rangers, welcome to training.
I'm so excited you guys are back.
Aim for the center mass.
One more time.
Come on, duck the punches.
Find their weak side.
Oh...
Let's go a couple o' hits, okay?
Hit one...
No, let's try it again.
Now this is exciting.
Yeah, Trini!
Hai!
Ready, master Billy?
You need to learn the element of surprise.
Ready? Let's go again.
All right, Billy, lighter on your feet.
Hands up.
Play with some energy now! Let's go!
Focus! Focus! Everybody just focus!
Lucky shot.
You guys all know
you could be murdered, right?
No.
You must shed
your masks to wear this armor.
I don't feel anything.
Take them down to the pit.
Now watch me...
slip, grab, lift.
Yeah!
Slip, grab, lift!
Yes!
Think only of each other,
and the morphing grid will open to you.
Is it working?
No, it's not.
Come on! Try harder!
Let's just concentrate.
I've been concentrating though, Jason.
'Cause we haven't been concentrating...
all we need to do is just concentrate.
Don't tell me to concentrate.
Just follow my lead.
Let's not fight with each other.
Zack, now is not the time.
Come on. Let's go train.
The information we need to triangulate
the location of the crystal
was lost in the battle. So...
Billy, are you listening to me?
Billy, what are you doing?
Billy!
Where's the crystal?
Find it, Billy, find it.
There.
One, two... Okay, 17 degrees north...
Hey, idiot, watch where you're going!
- One, two, three...
- Wake up!
Two fishermen were laid
to rest today at Saint Andrew's Cemetery.
Residents of Angel Grove
are feeling the shock.
Fear has the town on edge.
This series of murders has police baffled
as police have linked the loss of gold
to each crime scene.
What is now being dubbed
"Angel Grove's Gold Killer"
is still on the loose.
...Rita manages to create Goldar...
Are you listening to me?
And he rips the crystal from the ground,
it'll be like 10,000 nuclear bombs
washing over Earth.
Supposed to freak us out?
You keep making this harder.
We're busting our asses.
Feel free to throw us a bone
at some point.
Yes, I see you busting your "asses."
So I've decided
to give you some inspiration.
What you will find beyond this wall
will forever change your lives.
Come on.
The Zords!
- Pretty cool, right?
- Yeah.
They take on the form
of the most powerful organism
on the planet.
When these Zords formed,
dinosaurs reigned supreme.
They will be an extension of you.
And their power... is all but limitless.
But you're not ready for this power.
When you morph,
your armor will make you one
with the Zords.
So come on, let's go train.
Today's the day you become rangers!
I can feel it!
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Yeah. Let's go.
This was a bad idea.
Okay, okay, uh, signals, brakes.
Brakes, I need brakes!
Manual. Man-u-al.
Where are the brakes... Alpha 5!
Ahh! Oh, crap!
Hey! Move! Move!
Out of the way!
@ Go tell it on the mountain @
You have to remember that in today's
training lesson the important thing is to...
- Wait. Where's Zack?
- Seriously?
Run, run, run! Run!
Run! Run!
It's bad!
You all right?
Ay, ay, ay!
All right, my bad, my bad.
That's on me, right there.
What's your problem?
You could've killed yourself. Or us.
- Back off, bossman.
- Hey!
Oh, come on, guys. Wow.
- Guys, guys, guys, come on!
- Watch it!
Wait. What are you doing?
Just stop fighting, please!
What?
That's dope.
What? I got something on my f...
- Yeah!
- Whoa!
Okay, now that's cool! Oh, yeah!
- Hold still.
- Don't touch it. Zack, don't touch it.
Zack, do not touch it.
Whoa!
Where'd it go? Bring it back.
Bring it back, dude.
Get out.
Training is over for today. Go home.
I'm sorry, he just morphed.
He did it. You saw it, right?
Do it again.
All of you. Any of you.
- Billy. How'd you do it, Billy?
- Come on, Billy, let's do it.
- Show us what you did.
- Come on. Do it again.
- Do it again!
- I'm trying, I'm trying! I can't focus!
Billy, how'd you do it? Show us.
Okay, we don't know how.
That's what I thought.
If you can't morph, you are not rangers.
Go home. All of you.
Now what?
Damn.
Seriously?
Hey, guys...
guys, look, uh...
I'ma stay up here tonight.
Make a fire. I got some food
if you guys wanna stay.
I'm down.
All right. Cool.
Jason's team is failing.
I shall destroy Rita myself.
There must be a way to free me
from this wall.
Yes, but the irony is,
is that you need these rangers to morph.
If they morph, you can harness that energy
to regenerate your body
and come back through.
There's got to be another way! I can't...
What, Zordon? You can't what?
Wait for us dumb kids to morph
so that you can come back to life?
That's what all this
has been about, right?
You coming back?
This has only ever been
about protecting the crystal.
Rita could be building Goldar as we speak.
- Don't underestimate me or my team.
- You can't stop him.
She will have him dig up the crystal
and life on earth will die.
And we need you.
Because you were so successful
at stopping her last time.
I died burying those coins
in hopes that they would find
the next real rangers.
Those who are worthy.
Well, sorry to disappoint you.
I don't need to stand here
and have you tell me what I did wrong.
- I can go home and get that.
- Jason, you need me out of this wall.
To help lead this team!
Your team's dead.
And you're just as scared as we are.
These... are all 24 karat gold bands.
Hello, I'll be right with you.
They're at the top of your budget...
I'll get you anything you want.
Aw. You're so sweet.
Get my cookie anything she wants.
I'll be right back.
Uh... can I help you?
Gold.
I'm interested...
in gold.
Yeah.
We have some very nice pieces here.
Come closer.
- Closer. Closer. Closer.
- Oh...
- This. Give it to me!
- Of course!
Okay. Here you go.
Ah...
Grow.
More!
Police! Don't move!
Drop your... weapon,
and put your hands on your head.
Do it now!
Do what I say, lady!
Lady... I like the sound of "lady."
Get on the ground and you won't get hurt.
Unit five, I need backup
at Fenix Jewelers.
Shots fired. I repeat, shots fired.
Get down!
It's been too long
since I raised my beautiful creatures.
Did you miss me?
Oh, my God.
Kill him!
All right.
If I weren't stuck in this wall,
I would eat that junk food!
What happened back there?
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
Billy, how'd you do it?
How'd you morph?
I don't know.
What are you guys thinking about
when we're trying to morph?
You must shed
your masks to wear this armor.
Think only of each other
and the morphing grid will open to you.
Yeah, that's better.
Well, maybe it's because
we don't know each other.
Maybe that's why we can't morph.
Okay.
No, I'm serious. Let's do this. For real.
- What?
- I'm Zack.
And I am a Power Ranger.
Hi, Zack.
Truth: I live
in the Melody Mobile Home Park.
It's just me and my mom.
And my mom?
My mom is the best!
But my mom, she's sick.
I do what I can, but...
but I'm scared.
Sometimes I get too scared
to stay there at night, 'cause...
'cause I'm afraid she can't make it.
And if she goes...
when she goes,
I got nobody else.
Look, I think
being with you guys is good for me.
Let's do that.
Let's tell our secrets.
It'll... it'll help us.
Okay, I got a secret.
- I like country music.
- What?
No, matter of fact, I love country music.
And I don't...
I don't miss my dad as much.
I mean, coming to the mine
with him was all I had.
But coming to the mine
with you guys is just as good.
Yeah.
Bigger secret is why
were you in detention?
- I blew up my lunchbox.
- What?
What, it was a accident, okay?
- Of course.
- My lunchbox was in my locker.
Boom goes the lunchbox,
in detention goes Billy.
But let's not forget that Kimberly Hart
was also in... in detention, too, so...
Not tonight.
Skip me.
What about you, dude?
Why don't you tell us who you really are?
Because everyone knows exactly who I am.
Okay.
What about you, crazy girl?
I could tell you anything
and you'd have to believe me.
Okay, um...
I'm the new girl. Always.
Three schools in three years.
What's crazy is I like it that way.
You know, it's just easier.
Nobody ever has to get to know me and uh,
my parents don't have to worry
about my relationships.
Boyfriend troubles?
Yeah. Boyfriend troubles.
Girlfriend troubles?
My family is so normal.
Too normal.
They believe in labels.
They'd like for me to, um...
dress differently.
Talk more.
Have the kind of friends
they want me to have.
It's just... I don't know how to tell them
what's really going on with me.
And I've never said any of this out loud.
Well, it's cool. You're with us now.
Am I?
What does that mean?
When all this is over.
Are we Power Rangers or...
are we friends?
Do you know who I am?
Yes.
I was once just like you.
So pretty.
Innocent.
Are all the rangers on Zordon's new team
as young as you?
Delightful!
Have you morphed yet?
Trick question.
If you could morph,
we'd be having
a very different conversation.
Mmm. The Yellow Ranger.
Should I kill you?
I killed the Yellow Ranger... before.
And I loved it!
Oh, you want your armor.
I'll show you mine, if you show me yours.
No, please, you're hurting me!
You're so strong!
I'm just kidding.
You've got spunk, little Yellow.
I see myself in you.
I was an outsider on Zordon's
team just like you.
All I need to know is,
where is the Zeo Crystal?
I don't know.
Sadly, I believe you.
Tomorrow, I am going to destroy
Angel Grove.
But, in exchange for your life,
you will find out where that crystal is,
and you will come to me.
We can have a little deal,
Didi, my friend.
- Shh! It's me.
- Kim.
How did you get in here?
I'm a superhero.
And you left your window open.
Is everything okay?
I think I'm the reason we can't morph.
I haven't really been honest.
Okay. I punched Ty Fleming in the face
because he told everyone
I was the meanest person he'd ever met.
And he was right.
Well, that can't be true.
Okay.
Whoa.
- You took that picture?
- No.
Amanda Clark took that picture.
Of herself.
But she shared it with me.
Privately. She trusted me.
And you sent that pic to... to Ty?
With a text that said,
"Is this the girl you wanna
bring home to your mom?"
Oh.
I didn't realize how mean
it was until I saw her face.
Kim, there's literally thousands of photos
going around school.
I don't care about them.
I care about this. I did this.
I had to sit in Mr. Detmer's
office with Amanda's father
and watch as they showed him
that photo of his daughter.
In his eyes, for the first time,
I could see who I'd become.
You know, so I lied.
I blamed everyone else.
I wanted to die, that's why...
that's why when you asked me to run away,
I was ready.
Okay, listen. Start over.
Erase that picture right now.
- Jason, it can't be erased.
- Then live with it.
You did an awful thing.
It doesn't make you an awful person.
Just be the person you wanna be.
So, we all got the same text.
So where is she?
I'm here.
Look, Rita came to my house tonight.
- What?
- Yeah. She's real...
insane.
She nearly killed me.
She was trying to get me to join her.
She said she'd spare my life,
if I could keep a secret.
What secret?
At dawn, the destruction
of Angel Grove begins.
This is real. This is the end.
No, it's not. Where is she?
She said to meet her
where the dead ships live.
Okay. That's the boatyard
by the docks, right?
- Let's go.
- What?
Are you serious? No one?
Jason, we're not even Power Rangers yet.
I say we go back to Zordon.
Okay, the only reason Zordon
wanted us to become Power Rangers
is so that he can come back to life.
What makes you say that?
Because he told me.
Wait, so this all is a lie?
Of course it was a lie, Billy.
We failed.
Let's stop being delusional
about being a team of superheroes.
We're all screw-ups.
And as much as I hate this scrubby,
bullshit town,
I don't wanna just sit around
and watch it die, okay?
Let's go and do the one thing
that's been asked of us
and kill Rita.
You know this is a really bad idea, right?
The worst.
Let's vote. Show of hands.
Let's do it.
Okay. Okay, let's go.
Take the left, I'll take the right.
Okay. Got it.
- We'll, untie him. Hold this.
- No, no, no.
Let's just think about this, okay?
Oh, shit!
Right on time.
I was beginning to think you were too dumb
to know where the dead ships live.
Let's play.
Five little rangers tied up like fish.
The leader? Oh, hello, Red.
Oh!
You're not entirely disappointing.
Oh, look at you.
Trying to figure out my plan.
I'll just tell you.
Yellow has led you to your deaths.
Because I'm going to kill you,
one by one, until you tell me,
where is my crystal?
We don't know.
No, Red. You don't know!
But guess what?
One of you does.
Who could it be?
Eenie, meenie, miney...
Blue.
Blue, so loyal.
Pure of heart.
Tell the class what you know!
Where's my crystal?
You can tell me now, Blue,
or you can tell me after I kill
all of your friends.
Let's start with Black.
No! Stop!
No.
He dies in three, two...
Okay! Okay!
Don't hurt my friends, all right?
It's at a dining establishment.
Where? What does that mean?
What's it called?
It's a Krispy Kreme.
- Krispy Kreme?
- Krispy Kreme.
This is a special place?
- Very special.
- It must be.
The source of life itself is buried there.
Thank you, Blue, for being so weak.
Zordon would lose all respect
for me if I don't kill you.
- At least one of you.
- What?
No! Billy!
- Billy!
- Jason, we gotta help him!
- Billy! Billy!
You're not ready to kill me.
Ha! You're not worthy.
Quick! Get the rope!
Billy!
Billy?
He's gonna be okay, right?
Come on.
Hey, hey. You got this, big guy. Come on.
He's dead.
No.
Pick him up.
Help me pick him up!
Come on!
Okay. Okay. Come on, Billy.
We got you, buddy.
Take him. Take him.
Yeah.
- Let's just put him down.
- Okay.
- Slow, slow, slow.
- Master Billy.
Do something, okay?
There must be something
you can do for him.
I told you that you were not ready.
Zordon, please help us, okay? Please.
There's nothing that I could do for him.
We were both reckless with our teams.
No.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, guys.
He's dead because of me.
No, Jason, it was all of us.
No, I pushed it.
And as usual I made the wrong decision.
Out of... out of fear, anger...
I don't know, I was just so angry.
He's... he's a great kid, you know?
And he loved us.
He loved... being a ranger.
I'm sorry, Billy.
I'd trade my life for yours if I could.
Maybe he traded his life for us.
Yeah. Probably did.
I would.
Me too.
Yeah. Me too.
It's just the four of us now.
The truth is,
whatever we've said to each other,
it doesn't matter.
This. This is the only thing that matters.
She's right.
Zordon! Zordon! Look at the grid!
This is your time! Do... do you see it?
The grid is open! Step through!
Yes, I see it. I see it.
Step through, Zordon!
- Hey!
- What's happening?
The morphing grid is open!
What's going on?
Zordon? Master?
Where is he?
He must have stepped through the grid.
Alpha, where'd he go?
I don't know where he is.
Zordon, what? Why didn't you step though?
That was your only chance.
I know.
But only one can come back.
Billy!
- Billy!
- Oh, my God! Hey!
Are you okay?
- Did I die?
- Yes.
- No.
- Little bit.
And you guys brought me back to life.
I told you we were superheroes.
There can only be one Red Ranger.
Jason, this is your time.
This is your team.
Thank you.
Dude. That was loopy.
Seein' my dad.
Welcome back, my friend.
- Oh, we gotta go to Krispy Kreme, Jason.
- What?
Not for donuts.
Okay. Let's try this.
Thank you, Zordon.
It's morphin' time.
Who is that?
Oh, my God!
Yes.
Come back to me, Goldar.
Come back.
Hold up. Look.
All right. Let's do this.
Yes!
Yee-haw!
Whoa, this is so much better with armor.
Come on! Bring it on!
Hey, heads up!
Guys, they just keep coming.
There's too many of them.
- You guys hold them off.
- Zack, where are you going?
Whoo-hoo!
Make my monster grow!
I've missed you, my friend.
They're gonna push us off the edge!
Incoming!
Let's kill everyone.
Did you guys see that?
All right, who wants me
to pimp their ride, too?
Uh, guys? We're too late.
Oh, man.
That's... that's a lotta gold.
We're gonna protect the crystal, right?
- We're going to Angel Grove.
- Let's get the Zords.
This is a lot different than the van.
Whoo!
Yippie-kay-yay, motherfu...
Mother's good. Mother's good.
Go, go, Power Rangers!
I'm not going the right way! What?
Jason, I'm going backwards.
Guys... our town. She's destroying it.
Krispy Kreme!
Not there.
Rita and her golden boy
haven't found Krispy Kreme yet.
Okay, Kim, you hold them there.
Zack, Billy, you circle the Krispy Kreme
and make sure it's safe.
I'm headed straight for Goldar.
Copy! I'll hold her off.
Kim, I'll go with you.
Let's go, boys.
Billy, just the two of us.
I'm right behind you.
Oops.
Surprise.
How cute.
The rangers found their costumes
and their dino-cars.
Well, let's give them something else
to play with.
Crush them!
How many does she need?
This is insane.
Take that!
Okay. Let's try this!
Sorry, Bumblebee! Whoo!
Yeah!
I can't get 'em off!
Turn your head. Trust me.
Okay. Thanks, Kim.
That's all right.
That's what you get.
Whoo!
The crystal.
She just found the crystal.
Okay, come on, let's move!
I'll take Goldar from the right.
J! I'm right behind you.
Come on!
Jason, it's your dad.
I'm looking for you. I'm downtown.
I'm at Mariner Bay and Reefside.
Call me back soon as you get this.
How's that feel?
We got this. Come on!
- No!
I'm coming!
Ahh!
Help!
Give me your hand.
- Sam! Look at me.
- Huh?
It's okay.
Give me your hand.
Dig. Dig, Goldar.
Me and Zack are gonna try
to push Goldar to the water.
We're okay. I'm okay. Go.
Guys, help!
Billy, I have an idea. Ready?
Uh... Yeah? For what exactly?
Oh-ho-ho!
I don't know what to press, okay?
Open wide, Rita.
Let me try...
Hey, Billy, you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
That was crazy brave, dude.
Did we do it?
Did we... did we win?
Yeah!
I feel the crystal.
She's back.
That's incredible.
Oh, my God.
Come on, let's go!
Okay, everyone.
Hold the line.
Okay.
We got this.
Come on!
Crush them!
Okay, fire!
Yeah!
Come on, guys!
Ohh!
If you must come at me... come at me, bro!
Watch out! Billy!
Okay.
Yes!
Jason, I'm coming in.
Kim! I got your back.
I got you.
I'm burning.
I can't... I can't breathe.
He's crushing me!
Push them into the pit!
Guys, we're sliding!
- Come on, everybody, hold the line!
- Fight back!
It's getting too hot, guys.
I don't know how much longer
I can hold it.
No one dies alone.
I'm okay with that.
Hold the line. Hold the line.
Hold the line.
Zack! Zack, stay with me, Zack. Come on.
Thank you for being my friends.
Hold on to each other.
Get my crystal!
We're alive.
Guys, we're alive!
We're like one big, uh... one big Zord.
Like a mama Zord.
- What?
- No, no, no. That sounds lame. Um...
a Megazord!
How?
Whoa.
What?
Oh, shit.
Bring it on.
Everyone, let's go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, no, no, no, no!
That might
have been my fault. I'm sorry, y'all.
I think Kimberly needs to move our feet.
- No, I've got the arm.
- Uh, no, I do. I've got the leg.
- You're a leg, too?
- I have the arm.
We all have to move together.
I'll lift us.
All together on three.
One, two, three!
We got this! Come on!
Zack, catch us.
Let's go again!
Kimberly, throw a hook! Now!
Whoo!
Oh, I wish I could punch.
Nice one, Billy!
Jason, we got anything for that?
Remember the pit?
Yeah.
Hey, I hate the pit!
- Ready?
- Ready.
Ready.
Now!
Slip!
Grab!
Lift!
Kim, Trini, pull back on the arms.
We've got swords.
Ha!
Wait!
Guys...
Look at me.
You think you've won?
I came for the crystal.
Others will come!
What you have... it can't last.
You know I'm right!
- No.
I don't know. But for now,
I need you to give your staff
and your coin to us.
And we'll take you to Zordon
and let him be the judge.
Zordon? Judge me?
Never!
No matter what Zordon says,
I know I am worthy!
Trini! Now!
Jason, did you just slap her?
I did. Weird, right?
That's cool.
I guess the bully...
you guys don't get...
It's the... I got it, buddy.
Oh, that was scary.
We did it.
I told you we'd be famous.
Is that Principal Feig?
Hey. No, I... I don't think he can see me.
Oh, let's wiggle, Jason.
I call this the algebra. Woo!
How do you even do that?
You should keep that.
You've earned it.
I'll come back for it.
That was terrifying. See you, buddy.
Jeremy Franklin told everyone at school.
The blue was the best one.
That's who I wanna be.
Hey, no, I wanna be the blue one!
I wanna be blue one.
Hey, how about one of you guys
try to be the yellow one?
Oh, yeah, the yellow one!
Oh, he's so cool!
How do you know it's a he?
Checkmate.
Billy! Jason Scott is here
and Kimberly Hart and Zack Taylor
and some girl named Didi.
Mom, it's Trini! I'm coming! I'm coming!
This ranger team
did what my team could not.
You will humbly walk amongst your peers,
but heroes you all will be.
- Attention! Attention in detention.
- Each of your names
will be etched alongside
the great ranger teams before you.
I will always owe a debt
of gratitude to you all.
Oh, we have a new detention student.
"Tommy Oliver."
Tommy Oliver?
Tommy Oliver!
Cranston.
That might have been my fault.
That might have been my fault,
I'm so sorry.