You shoud be practicing.
I am practicing
What you're doing, you won't be needing these.
What's your problem?
What do we learn here?
No weakness! No pain! No mercy!
Begin!
He's had enough.
Don't you remember what we learned?
No weakness. No pain.
No mercy!
Go home.
What are you doing?
Why did you stop?
Finish!
Okay, Mr. Han, let's get out of here.
We do not stop when our enemy is down!
No mercy.
No mercy in the studio.
No mercy in life.
What are you looking at?
He's the one that attacked me.
We are here to make peace.
Let your little thing mind himself.
One to one, no problem...
Six to one,
too much to ask of anyone.
I see.
Prepare for match!
We are not here to fight.
You attack my students
and disrespect my studio?!
You want to leave?
Not so easy.
Master Li...
You both came here.
One of you fights now.
The boy will fight there.
OPEN KUNG FU TOURNAMENT
We accept your challenge.
Please instruct your students
to leave my boy alone to train.
Attention!
From now on the little thing
is to be left alone...
until the tournament.
- Understood?!
- Yes!
If he does not show up
for the competition...
I will bring pain to him and you.
Sir...
My name is Dre Parker.
My actions have brought
dishonor to your family.
Your daughter has been
a great friend to me.
And from her I have learned...
...that a true friend...
...is a person
who makes your life better.
But, if you give me a second chance...
...I promise that I will be...
...the best friend your
daughter has ever had.
Let the tournament begin!
Dre Parker advances to the semi-finals!
And now the 1st semi-final
of the evening.
TOURNAMENT OF CHAMPIONS
SEMI-FINAL
First Round
Cheng vs, Wu Ping
Next semi-final:
Introducing Fighting Dragon Liang . . .
. . . and the surprise finalist, Dre Parker.
You're disqualified!
He's done.
I'm sorry, you should not continue.
You've brought honor to your family.
Dre Parker has 2 minutes
to return to the match.
If he is unable to return . . .
. . . the Fighting Dragons win by default.
Since Dre Parker has
not returned to the ring . . .
Dre Parker will fight!
No mercy.
The score is tied.
The next point wins!