(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING AND BUZZING)
(GRASS RUSTLES)
(GASPS)
No, no, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
I'm lost! Where's the line?
(MURMURING)
It just went away. What do I do?
- Help!
- We'll be stuck here forever!
SOIL: Do not panic. Do not panic!
We are trained professionals.
Now, stay calm.
We are going around the leaf.
Around the leaf?
I don't think we can do that.
Oh, nonsense. This is nothing
compared to the twig of '93.
That's it. That's it. Good!
You're doing great!
There you go. There you go!
Watch my eyes. Don't look away.
- And here's the line again.
- Thank you. Thank you, Mr. Soil.
Good job, everybody!
Oh, my. There's quite a gap, Mr. Soil.
Shouldn't we tell the queen?
I don't think we need
to involve the queen in this.
She's got enough on her plate already,
training her daughter.
Oh, yes. Princess Atta, the poor dear.
Oh, wind's died down.
They'll be here soon.
- Just be confident, dear. You'll be fine.
- Ah! There's a gap.
There's a gap in the line.
What are we gonna do?
It's okay, Your Highness.
Gaps happen.
We just lost a few inches, that's all.
Oh, right.
Your Highness, I can't count
when you hover like that.
Oh, of course. I'm sorry. Go ahead.
Guys, go shade someone else
for a while.
Okay, Atta. Now what do we do?
Oh! Don't tell me.
I know it. I know it. What is it?
- We relax.
- (CHUCKLES) Right.
Oh, it'll be fine.
It's the same, year after year.
They come, they eat, they leave.
That's our lot in life.
It's not a lot, but it's our life.
Isn't that right, Aphie?
Oh, you're such a cute little aphid.
(RUMBLING)
- Ditch Dot!
- Yeah, yeah!
Hey, come back here!
(BUZZING)
(GRUNTS)
- QUEEN: Dot!
- Yes, Mother.
What did I tell you about trying to fly?
Not until my wings grow in.
- QUEEN: Right.
- But, Mom...
Dot, you're a young queen ant,
and your wings are too little to be...
I was talking to Mother.
You're not the queen yet, Atta.
Now, Dot, be nice to your sister.
It's not my fault she's so stressed out.
(SIGHS)
I know, I know.
I'm always acting like the sky is falling.
- MALE ANT: Look out!
- Atta!
- ANT 1: Princess Atta!
- ANT 2: Princess Atta!
- ATTA: Oh!
- ANT 1: Hey!
- ANT 1: Stop that!
- ANT 2: What do you think you're doing?
ANT 1: You could have killed somebody
over here.
- (GASPS) I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- Oh, it's Flik.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me. I'm sorry!
(COUGHS)
- Princess Atta!
- Flik, what are you doing?
Oh... Oh, this! This is my new idea
for harvesting grain.
No more picking individual kernels.
You can just cut down the entire stalk!
- Flik, we don't have time for this.
- Exactly!
We never have time
to collect food for ourselves,
'cause we spend all summer harvesting
for the offering.
But my invention
will speed up production.
(GROANS)
Another invention?
Yeah, and I've got
something for you, too.
- Flik!
- Since you're gonna be queen soon,
you could use this
to oversee production.
Dr. Flora, if I may.
- ATTA: This is all very nice, but...
- What?
Just an ordinary blade of grass
and a bead of dew, right?
- Flik, please.
- Wrong! It is, in fact, a telescope.
- It's very clever, Flik, but...
- Hello, princess!
My, aren't you looking
lovely this morning!
Not, of course, that you would need
a telescope to see that.
All right, listen!
The princess doesn't have time for this!
You want to help us fill this thing?
Then get rid of that machine,
get back in line
and pick grain like everybody else!
- Like everybody else!
- Please, Flik. Just go.
I'm sorry. I was...
I was really just trying...
Trying to help.
Harvester. Why, we've harvested
the same way ever since I was a pupa.
ATTA: Where were we?
THORNY: The food pile,
Your Highness.
ATTA: Oh, yes. Yes.
DOT: Hey, Flik! Flik! Wait up!
- Oh. Hello, princess.
- You can call me Dot.
Here, you forgot this.
Thanks. You can keep it.
I can make another one.
- I like your inventions.
- Really? Well, you're the first.
I'm beginning to think
nothing I do works.
- This works.
- Great. One success.
(SIGHS)
- I'm never gonna make a difference.
- Me, neither.
I'm a royal ant, and I can't even fly yet.
I'm too little.
- Being little's not such a bad thing.
- Yes, it is.
- No, it's not.
- Is, too!
- Is not. Is not.
- Is, too. Is, too.
- Is not. Is not. Is not...
A seed. I need... I need a seed.
(GROANS)
Here, here.
Pretend... Pretend that that's a seed.
- It's a rock.
- I know it's a rock. I know.
But let's just pretend for
a minute that it's a seed, all right?
We'll just use our imaginations.
Now, do you see our tree?
Everything that made that giant tree
is already contained
inside this tiny little seed.
All it needs is some time, a little bit
of sunshine and rain, and voilà!
This rock will be a tree?
Seed to tree. You've got to work
with me, here, all right? Okay.
You might not feel
like you can do much now,
but that's just because,
well, you're not a tree yet.
You just have to give yourself
some time. You're still a seed.
- But it's a rock.
- I know it's a rock!
Don't you think I know a rock
when I see a rock?
- I've spent a lot of time around rocks!
- You're weird, but I like you.
(CONCH SOUNDING)
(GASPS)
They're here.
ALL: They're here!
DOT: Mom! Where are you?
- MALE ANT: They're coming!
- FEMALE ANT: Run!
- Dot! Dot!
- Mom!
- Thank heavens!
Food to the offering stone.
(WHISTLES)
Okay, everyone, single file.
Food to the offering stone
and into the anthill. Now let's go!
ANT: Go, go, go, go!
Come on.
Keep moving, keep moving! Good.
Okay. That's everyone.
FLIK: Hey! Hey, wait for me!
Get the food to the offering stone,
then into the anthill.
(RATTLING)
(SCREAMS)
No! No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no.
Princess Atta! Princess Atta!
(DRONING BUZZ APPROACHING)
Princess Atta!
(MUFFLED DRONING)
They come, they eat, they leave.
Excuse me, pardon me. Pardon me.
Coming through. Excuse me.
Sorry. Coming through. Princess Atta,
there's something I need to tell you.
Not now, Flik.
But, Your Highness,
it's about the offering!
GRASSHOPPER 1: Hey, what's going on?
GRASSHOPPER 2: Yeah, where's the food?
(ALL GASP)
- What did you do?
- It was an accident?
(CACKLING)
(GRASSHOPPERS WHOOPING)
Ooh.
Where's the food?
Hopper.
HOPPER: So where is it?
Where's my food?
(ECHOING)
- Isn't it up there?
- What?
- The food was in a leaf sitting on...
- Excuse me.
Are you sure it's not up there?
- Are you saying I'm stupid?
- ATTA: No.
Do I look stupid to you?
Let's think about the logic, shall we?
Let's just think about it for a second.
If it was up there,
would I be coming down here,
to your level, looking for it?
- I...
- Why am I even talking to you?
You're not the queen.
You don't smell like the queen.
She's learning
to take over from me, Hopper.
Oh, I see. Under new management.
So it's your fault.
No, it wasn't me. It was...
HOPPER: Uh-uh-uh.
First rule of leadership,
everything is your fault.
It's a bug-eat-bug world
out there, Princess,
one of those circle-of-life
kind of things.
Now, let me tell you
how things are supposed to work.
The sun grows the food.
The ants pick the food.
- The grasshoppers eat the food...
- And the birds eat the grasshoppers.
Hey, like the one that nearly ate you,
you remember? You remember?
- Oh, you should've seen it.
- Molt.
This blue jay, he has him halfway
down his throat, okay?
And Hopper's kicking
and screaming, okay?
And I'm scared, okay?
I'm not going anywhere near, okay?
Come on. It's a great story.
(MOLT EXCLAIMING IN PAIN)
I swear, if I hadn't promised Mother
on her deathbed
that I wouldn't kill you, I would kill you.
And believe me,
no one appreciates that more than I do.
I don't want to hear another word
out of you while we're on this island.
Do you understand me?
(WHIMPERS)
- I said, do you understand me?
- Well, how can I answer?
You said I couldn't say another word.
Remember Ma!
(PANTING)
Hey, I'm a compassionate insect.
There's still a few months
till the rains come,
so you can all just try again.
But, Hopper, since
it's almost the rainy season,
we need this time
to gather food for ourselves.
Listen, if you don't keep
your end of the bargain,
then I can't guarantee your safety.
And there are insects out there
that will take advantage of you.
Someone could get hurt.
(SNARLING)
(ROARS)
(GASPS)
What's the matter?
You scared of grasshoppers?
- Dot!
- You don't like Thumper?
Leave her alone!
You want her? Go ahead. Take her.
No? Then get back in line.
It seems to me
that you ants are forgetting your place.
So let's double the order of food.
(ANTS GASPING)
No! But... But...
We'll be back at the end of the season,
when the last leaf falls.
You ants have a nice summer.
Let's ride!
(WHOOPING)
(WINGS BUZZING)
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
Flik, what do you have
to say for yourself?
Sorry. I... I'm sorry for the way I am.
I didn't mean for things to go so wrong.
I especially didn't want
to make you look bad, princess.
- Well, Flik, you did.
- I was just trying to help.
Then help us. Don't help us.
Help? Help? Help?
Flik, you are sentenced
to one month digging in the tunnels.
Excuse me, Your Highness.
Need I remind you
of Flik's tunnel-within-a-tunnel project?
Helpers to help us.
That's it! That's... We could...
It took the whole Engineering
Department two days to dig him out.
- Send him to Health and Ant Services.
- Heavens, no!
We could leave the island.
The riverbed's dry right now.
We'd just walk right across.
We could go get helpers. We could!
We could go find helpers to help us.
- It's perfect!
- Perfect? What's so perfect?
Your Highness, don't you see?
We could send someone to get help!
(ALL GASP)
Leave the island?
Now, why didn't I think of that?
Oh! Because it's suicide!
- She's right. We never leave the island.
- Never leave!
There's snakes and birds
and bigger bugs out there!
Exactly! Bigger bugs!
We could find bigger bugs
to come here and fight
and forever rid us
of Hopper and his gang!
- Ludicrous!
- Who would do a crazy thing like that?
I'll volunteer.
I'd be very happy to volunteer.
You got a lot of spunk, kid, but
no one's gonna help a bunch of ants.
At least we could try. Oh, I could
travel to the city, search there!
If you went, you'd be
on that silly search for weeks.
Royal huddle.
Great idea, princess. It's perfect.
- Exactly.
- Wait a minute.
- What did we just decide here?
- To let Flik leave.
While we keep harvesting
to meet Hopper's demands.
- You see, with Flik gone, he can't...
- He can't mess anything up!
Flik, after much deliberation, we have
decided to grant you your request.
- Really?
- Really.
- Thank you, princess.
Thank you so much for this chance.
- I won't let you down, I promise.
- That's fine. No, forget it.
But I should probably help repair
some of the damage before I go...
- No!
- ALL: No, no! Just go.
- Just go.
- Just leave!
(BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(EXHALES)
Hey.
Don't worry!
The colony is in good hands!
Bye, now.
(ANTS CHEERING)
All right.
Hey, fellas. Beautiful morning, huh?
My dad says he gives you one hour
before you come back
to the island crying.
- Does he, now?
- My dad doesn't think that.
- He doesn't?
- No, he's betting you're gonna die.
Yeah, he says if the heat
doesn't get you, the birds will.
DOT: Well, I think he's gonna make it.
- Nobody asked you, Royal Shortness.
- Yeah, Dot. What do you know?
Hey, hey, hey.
Ease up, all right? Come on.
She's entitled to her opinion, too.
(FLIK GASPS)
(BIRDS CAWING IN DISTANCE)
(SAND CRACKLING)
FLIK: Ohh...
So go, already.
- Hey!
- The city's that way.
I know.
You're supposed to look for bugs,
not dandelions.
You leave him alone.
He knows what he's doing.
FLIK: That's right.
Here I go. For the colony,
and for oppressed ants everywhere!
DOT: Wow!
FLIK: Hey!
Bye, Flik!
Wow.
(WIND GUSTING)
Whoa!
DOT: Good luck, Flik!
Bye!
Flik!
FLIK: (MUFFLED) I'm okay!
- Your dad's right. He's gonna die.
- You just watch.
He's gonna get the bestest,
roughest bugs you've ever seen!
(DIM ROARING)
Get back! Get back!
Get back, you horrible beast!
I have no fear!
Oh, my goodness.
(CRYING)
(CROWD BOOING)
(BAND PLAYS FLOURISH)
Oh, I'm so sorry, Dim. An owie?
Okay, show Rosie the owie.
All right, Dim. It's okay.
(BUZZING)
I have been in outhouses
that didn't stink that bad.
This is ridiculous.
What a disappointment.
- (GASPS) No!
- You! Come here!
I want my money back!
No refunds after the first two minutes.
Popcorn! Stale popcorn!
We're losing the audience!
You clowns get out there now!
I hate performing
on an empty stomach!
Do your act, Heimlich.
- Then you can eat.
- SLIM: P.T., what's the point?
Not now, Slim.
What's the point of going out there?
They'll only laugh at me.
- That's because you're a clown!
- No, it's because I'm a prop!
You always cast me as the broom,
the pole, the stick, a splinter.
You're a walking stick. It's funny!
- Now go!
- You parasite.
(CROWD BOOING)
(PLAYING FLOURISH)
Tra la, la, la, la.
Spring is in the air.
And I'm a flower
with nothing interesting to say. A bee!
I am a cute little bumblebee!
Here I come!
(SLIM SHOUTING)
(PANTING)
Slow down, you flowers!
Candy corn! Here. Here.
Let me help you to finish it.
Hey, cutie!
Want to pollinate with a real bug?
(LAUGHING RAUCOUSLY)
Come to Papa, yeah!
So, being a ladybug
automatically makes me a girl,
is that it, fly boy?
(EXCLAIMS)
- She's a guy!
- Francis, leave them alone.
- They are poo-poo heads!
- Not again.
Judging by your breath,
you must have been
buzzing around a dung heap all day.
Come on, Francis.
You're making the maggots cry.
(OPERATIC VOCALIZING)
All right, we're dying out there.
Gypsy, quick! You and Manny...
Shh. He's in a trance.
Well, get him out of it!
You and your husband are up now.
Manny, we're on.
Oh? Yet again it is up to me
to rescue the performance.
Gypsy, come.
(HUMMING)
(CRASH)
(GROANS)
- The stage is the other way, dear.
- Yes, of course.
Anytime, pal! I'm gonna pick
the hairs out of your head one by one!
- Take your best shot!
- You name the place!
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah, 'cause when you get there,
- you are dead!
- Francis, let me handle this.
- That's no way to speak to a lady.
- I heard that, you twig.
Ladies and gentlemen, allow me
to present Manto the Magnificent
and his lovely assistant, Gypsy!
(GONG SOUNDING)
From the most mysterious regions
of uncharted Asia,
I give you the Chinese Cabinet
of Metamorphosis!
Rosie, whole troupe.
On stage! Finale! Now!
- Okay, I just need a little time to...
- Now!
Coming. Coming. Tuck, Roll,
let's get moving, guys. We're up next.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Don't you understand? We are up!
"Up-a."
- BOTH: Hey!
- Hey! They don't understand me.
I summon the voice of Confucius...
Get off the stage, you old hack!
I demand to know who said that!
How dare you!
(CROWD BOOING)
Ingrates!
Manny? Manny!
I only got 24 hours to live,
and I ain't gonna waste it here.
Come on.
(BUZZING)
(SHRIEKS)
I've just about had it with these losers!
Flaming death!
I hold in my hand the match,
the match that decides whether
two bugs live or die this very evening.
In a moment, I will light
this trail of matches,
leading to a sheet of flypaper
doused in lighter fluid!
Aimed directly at the flypaper
are Tuck and Roll,
the pill-bug cannonballs!
The cannon will be triggered by Dim,
trained to jump
at the sound of this bell,
set to go off in 15 seconds.
Our pill bugs' only hope of survival
is our mistress of the high wire, Rosie!
Secured to a web line of exact length,
Rosie will plummet down
to these two posts,
spinning a web of safety
in less than 15 seconds!
Not good enough, you say?
Well, what if they were all
blindfolded?
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I suggest that those of you
with weak constitutions
leave the arena,
for this act is so dangerous
that if the slightest thing
should go wrong...
- No!
- Go? Okay, through the tunnel...
GYPSY: Whoa!
(TIMER DINGS)
- Okay, that's done!
- Whoa!
- P.T.!
- Oh, no!
P.T. FLEA: Rosie!
- We need some water!
- Water, water, water, water!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
P.T. FLEA: Get me out of here!
Wow!
- It's the web. I'm sorry. It's...
- You're all fired.
- SLIM: We got the water!
- HEIMLICH: Here we come, P.T.!
(CLAPPING)
Whoo! Whoa!
Burn him again!
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
FLY: No, Harry, no!
Don't look at the light!
HARRY: I can't help it! It's so beautiful!
(SIZZLING)
(SCREAMING)
Try not to look like a country bug.
Blend. Blend in.
BUG 1: Hey, buggy!
BUG 2: What do you expect?
The guy's a tick.
(DRONING BUZZ)
Wow, the city!
(FLIK EXCLAIMING)
Making all stops to the septic tank,
including standing water,
empty bean can and dead rat.
- Watch your stingers. All aboard!
- BUG 3: Hey, watch it.
- BUG 4: Get out of the way!
- Oh, sorry.
- Watch where you're going!
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that.
Oh, sorry!
(OFF-KEY VIOLIN SAWING)
FLIK: Oh. I'm really, really sorry.
That was an... An accident.
BUG 5: Hey, tough guy!
- BUG 6: Hey, let go of me!
- I'll show you who's tough!
- And stay out!
- Tough bugs!
(SALOON PIANO PLAYING)
I knew an old lady
who swallowed a fly...
- Move it!
- Whoa.
Hey, waiter! I'm in my soup!
I've been working out. Feel my wing.
Yo! Two Black Flags over here!
- All right.
- (CHUCKLES) Hair of the dog you bit.
Hey, who ordered the poo-poo platter?
Here you go, slick. Enjoy.
Hey, I said no salt!
- BUG 7: Buzz off!
- Pardon me, sir.
I was wondering
if I could talk to you for a moment.
I represent a colony of ants,
and I'm looking for tough bugs,
you know, mean bugs,
the sort of bugs...
Fired by a flea. How humiliating!
Let's face it. We stink.
- You fired! You fired!
- You fired!
- Oh, will you shut up?
Someday I will be a beautiful butterfly,
and then everything will be better.
I can't believe
the troupe is breaking up.
We've always been together.
- Farewell, my friends.
- To the audience we'll never have.
(GASPS) Francis! Your boyfriends
from the circus are here!
(GASPS)
There she is.
- Hello there, girlie bug.
- Shoo, fly. Don't bother me.
Say, why don't you tell our pal, Thud,
- what you said to us at the circus.
- Yeah.
Something about buzzing
around a dung heap?
Excuse me. Hi.
I represent an ant colony, and we're...
Hey, bartender!
Bloody Mary, O-positive.
Sir?
♪ Ladybug, ladybug, fly away home ♪
Not so tough now, are you?
All right, clown.
Get up and fight like a girl.
- Get ready to do the Robin Hood act.
- I want to be Little John!
- What part can I play?
- I'm looking for tough warrior bugs.
Stand back, ye flies! We are
the greatest warriors in all bugdom!
- Warrior bugs!
- My sword!
Swish, swish. Clang, clang.
- Little John?
- What ho, Robin?
Justice is my sword
and truth shall be my quiver!
Wait, wait! No, no! I want to watch this!
Thrust, parry, lunge!
(GROWLING)
Me thinketh it's not working!
- HEIMLICH: Back to Sherwood Forest!
- What's going on in there?
(BUGS SCREAMING)
SLIM: (MUFFLED) Help! Help!
Get me out!
(GRUNTING)
Wow.
FLIK: You're perfect!
Oh, great ones! I have been scouting
for bugs with your exact talents!
- (GASPS) A talent scout.
- My colony's in trouble.
Grasshoppers are coming! We've been
forced to prepare all this food.
- Dinner theater!
- Food?
Please! Will you help us?
THUD: (GROWLING) Where are they?
- We'll take the job!
- Really?
Yes! You can explain the details
on the way.
Hey!
- Okay, come on, everyone. Break a leg!
- Whoa, you're vicious!
Hold on, Mr. Ant.
FLIK: Amazing!
This is too good to be true!
FLIK: So you see, it was my fault
that Hopper's coming back.
But then, Princess Atta...
Boy, is she one in a million.
She let me go out and find you.
And after seeing you
fight off those flies...
Boy, are those grasshoppers in
for a big surprise!
(LAUGHING TRIUMPHANTLY)
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(MOANS)
- Dr. Flora!
- Oh, dear. Not another one.
- This is insane.
- Insane.
There's just not enough food
left on the island!
No way we can make double quota
before Hopper comes.
Well, we have to try, Thorny.
We don't have any choice.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, look who's playing lookout again.
Little Speck!
The name is Dot.
Well, Spot, you still looking for Flik?
Forget it, Dot.
That loser's never coming back.
Flik! He did it! He did it!
What? Quit shoving!
This is it! This is Ant Island!
DOT: Flik! Over here! Flik! Flik!
- Hey!
- DOT: He did it! He did it! He did it!
- He did it!
- Cool!
At the rate these leaves are dropping,
we're gonna need a miracle.
That's right! We need a miracle!
(DRONING BUZZ)
Run for your lives!
Ta-da!
(BIRD CAWING IN DISTANCE)
(GASPS) Once again,
our reputation precedes us.
Hey, everybody! Hey! I'm back!
Hey, guys! Hey! Look. Look!
Look who's here with me!
Flik! Flik! Flik! You're back!
I knew you could do it!
- ANT 1: Flik?
- ANT 2: It's Flik!
- ANT 3: What?
- ANT 4: Yeah.
- ANT 3: No, it's not Flik.
- ANT 5: Flik?
- Flik has returned!
- He's back?
And he's accompanied
by savage insects!
What? How? He wasn't supposed
to actually find someone!
Oh, look at this. Look at this.
This is great. Look.
- Oh, my ticker!
- So, what are you supposed to be?
He's a stick, stupid.
You hit bugs with him.
- That's an oversimplification.
- That's right, kids. Like this!
No! Put me down! Oh!
Hey!
My, you just pop
right open there, don't you?
- KIDS: Ooh! Wow!
- ROSIE: Kids, he's kind of ticklish.
(DIM LAUGHING)
Let's come on out. Careful.
(RUMBLING)
(KIDS SCREAMING)
Well, my boy, you came through.
Aphie and I are very impressed.
Princess Atta! Hey!
Hey, guys, this is Princess Atta!
She's the one that sent me to find you!
- Did you see that really big bug?
- He looks absolutely ferocious!
- They're our ticket out of this mess!
- They came just in time!
So, Princess Atta, what...
What do you think?
No, no, no, wait!
This was not supposed to happen.
Mayday, mayday. We're losing the job.
We don't fight grasshoppers.
- We don't, but they will.
- Bingo!
We got to sweeten the deal.
Your Majesty, ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls of all ages,
our troupe here guarantees
a performance like no other!
Why, when your grasshopper friends
get here, we are gonna
knock them dead!
These folks are sure
hard up for entertainment.
DOT: Come on, come on. Hurry!
(PANTING)
Wow!
(PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
Honey, relax.
You should be proud of yourself.
Your instincts on that boy
were right on the money.
And to make our official welcome
complete... Mr. Soil?
- Yes, Your Highness?
- QUEEN: He's our resident thespian.
Last year he played the lead in Picnic.
The children and myself
have quickly put together
a little presentation
in honor of our guests.
Dot, Reed, Daisy, Grub?
Aren't they adorable! They're cute!
The South Tunnel Elementary
School second-grade class
would like to present you with this,
a mural we have drawn
of you bugs helping us
fight the grasshoppers away.
Oh, look at the beautiful
colors of the blood.
We drew one of you dying because our
teacher said it would be more dramatic.
(GASPS)
I tell you a tale of heroes so bold,
who vanquished
our grasshopper enemies of old.
Look, the last leaf has fallen.
GRASSHOPPERS: We are the
grasshoppers! Where's our food?
Who will come to save us poor ants?
WARRIORS: We are the warriors,
here to defend you!
I die! Die! Die!
Hail, the bugs!
Thank you, thank you! Oh, thank you!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- I say we go.
Okay, honey. You're up.
(ATTA CLEARS THROAT)
We're all very, very grateful to have...
- Here, here.
- (AMPLIFIED) The warriors...
(ANTS LAUGHING)
Thanks.
First of all, I'd like to thank the warriors
for helping us in our fight
against the grasshoppers.
Secondly, I would like to thank Flik
- for his forthright thinking...
- Thank you, Your Highness.
Sure, I'd like to take credit for all
of this, but, well, that wouldn't be right.
Because it was you, Princess Atta.
You believed in me
- and you sent me on my quest.
- SLIM: You tell that ant
- that we need to talk to him right now.
- Okay, okay. All right.
Now, I know that I've made
a lot of mistakes in the past.
- And I hope that this will make up...
- Flik!
Not right now, Rosie.
I'm making a speech.
Now, I truly believe that these bugs
are the answer to our...
No, there's no circus around here.
So I...
(GASPS)
Your Highness, the warriors have
called for a secret meeting
to plan for a circus...
Circumventing the oncoming hordes,
so they can trapeze...
Trap them with ease!
- Shouldn't I come, too?
- No!
Sorry, no, you see, it's classified
in the DMZ. Gotta go ASAP.
You know, strictly BYOB. Bye!
Sorry. Sorry I have to take
the warriors away so early,
but, you know, they have a lot to get
done, with the battle looming and all.
So, please, everyone, enjoy the party.
BYOB?
Thanks again. Bye. Bye-bye.
Okay, just... Just...
Just get in there. Go!
Go, go, go!
Circus bugs?
How can you be circus bugs?
- HEIMLICH: What?
- Hey, hey, hey.
You said nothing about killing
grasshoppers, pal. You lied to us!
Are you kidding?
Do you know what this is?
This, my friends, is false advertising.
How dare you! You, sir,
are the charlatan in this scenario,
touting your wares as a talent scout,
preying upon the hungry souls
of hapless artistes.
Good day to you, sir.
Wait! No, no! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
You can't go.
You have got to help me. Give me
some time. I'll come up with a plan.
- Just go tell them the truth!
- They can't...
They can't know the truth.
The truth, you see, is bad.
I will be branded with this mistake
for the rest of my life.
My children's children
will walk down the street,
and people will point and say, "Look.
"There goes the spawn
of Flik, the loser!"
Oh... Oh, you know, all right, fine.
Yeah, okay. Just go.
But if you could just do me a little favor
before you leave.
If you could just squish me,
that would be great, because
when they find out,
I'm as good as dead.
- ATTA: Flik!
- Huh?
ATTA: I really do think I should be
part of this meeting. Flik!
- Princess Atta! What a nice surprise.
- Just what exactly is going on?
I would like to speak
with the so-called "warriors."
You can't! They are in the middle
of a top-secret meeting right now,
and they really should not be
disturbed now. Right, guys?
(GASPS)
(STAMMERING)
Could you excuse me, please?
- Wait, wait, wait! Please, don't go!
- I'm not going anywhere.
What is going on? Flik?
Flik!
(GROANS)
I knew it!
FLIK: Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Please! Don't go!
- No! No, no, no!
- SLIM: Quick, he's losing it!
- You can't go! I'm desperate!
- Really? I couldn't tell.
Hmm.
Come on, wings.
Help!
Mother, Flik is up to something.
FLIK: No! No!
SLIM: Okay, Flik,
time to put you down now.
Get him off me. He's cutting off
the circulation to my foot.
- No, no, no, no!
- Let go!
Oh, please! Please! Don't go!
ROSIE: Put the stick down. Flik,
I mean it now.
- Drop the stick. Drop it.
- Run!
Boy, he runs fast for a little guy.
(CHIRPING)
Tweet-tweet! Tweet-tweet!
Tweet-tweet!
This way.
There they are.
- A bird!
- DOT: (SCREAMS) Flik!
- Look!
- Dot!
Flik!
(DOT SCREAMING)
- Dot!
- My baby!
FRANCIS: I gotcha! I gotcha!
I gotcha, I gotcha!
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
- QUEEN: I can't see!
- Somebody do something!
SLIM: Are they all right?
HEIMLICH: Can anyone see?
Are they alive?
- ROSIE: I can't see!
- SLIM: What is happening?
Dot?
MANNY: Good heavens,
they're in trouble!
- Francis, Francis, Francis...
- You guys, I've got an idea!
Here! I've got it!
(CHIRPING)
(ATTA GASPS)
Please, ma'am, wake up! Wake up!
- Help! Help!
- HEIMLICH: Yoo-hoo!
Mr. Early Bird! How about
a nice, tasty worm on a stick?
I'm going to snap. I'm going to snap.
Nice and juicy, succulent...
FLIK: Let's go!
- There they are!
- DOT: Flik! Help!
Okay.
- Flik!
- It's going to be okay, Dot.
(HEIMLICH EXCLAIMING)
(CHIRPING)
Bye-bye, birdie!
Help! I'm stuck! Pull me down!
The caterpillar's
using himself as live bait!
How brave!
Suck it in, man!
FRANCIS: My leg!
(GASPS) The bird! The bird!
Look out for the bird!
Flik!
- Up-a, up-a, up-a, up-a, up-a!
(SCREECHES)
(SIGHING)
(PANTING)
(FAINT APPLAUSE)
What is that?
That, my friends,
is the sound of applause!
(CHEERING)
Applause... I'm in heaven!
Our Blueberry troop salutes you bugs
for rescuing our smallest member,
Princess Dot.
And as a tribute to Miss Francis,
we've changed our bandannas!
We voted you
our honorary den mother!
(KIDS CHEERING)
What? Great.
All right, girls. Let's move
your little keisters out of here now.
The patient needs her rest, you know.
Come on.
Excuse me, Flik.
Can I talk to you just for a second?
Oh, sure.
Again, thank you all very, very much.
- HEIMLICH: Oh, stop. You're too kind.
- ALL: Thank you.
You don't think I've offended
the warriors, do you?
- You? No.
- Oh, good. Because, you see,
when you first brought them here,
I thought you'd hired
a bunch of clowns.
You did?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Don't tell them I said that.
Boy, that's all I'd need,
another royal blunder like that.
- Princess, you're doing a great job.
- Thanks. You're sweet.
You're wrong, but sweet.
- I know what everyone really thinks.
- I don't follow you.
Everyone, the whole colony. Nobody
really believes I can do this job.
(SIGHS)
It's like they're all watching me,
- just... Just...
- Waiting for you to screw up.
- Flik, I owe you an apology.
- For what?
Well, I haven't been that nice to you,
and I'm sorry.
If there's any way I can
make it up to you... Hey! I know!
How would you like to be the queen's
official aide to the warrior bugs?
- Me?
- Oh, sure.
You've got a great rapport going
with them,
especially after that rescue.
It was very brave.
- Really? No, no...
- Well, not every bug would face a bird.
- I mean, even Hopper's afraid of them.
- Yeah, well, I guess maybe I have...
- Say that again?
- I said, even Hopper's afraid of birds.
Thank you.
- Hopper's afraid of birds!
- And I don't blame him!
Oh, oh, oh, this is perfect.
We can get rid of Hopper, and no one
has to know that I messed up.
You just keep pretending
you're warriors.
Whoa, Flik, honey. We are not
about to fight grasshoppers, okay?
You'll be gone
before the grasshoppers ever arrive.
- It'll be easy. Here's what we do.
- Not another word.
I don't know what you're concocting
in that little ant brain of yours,
but we'll have no part of it.
Excuse me?
Could we get the warriors' autographs?
Autographs? Yeah!
- Oh, wow! Great!
- So you fellas catch the action today?
The bird went... and it just missed you!
Aren't you sweet?
And the way you pretended
to be stuck in that huge crack!
- That's just all part of the plan.
- Yeah, yeah.
And then you dive-bombed
into the bush!
- There you go, my boy.
- Wow! Thanks!
"Major..."
That's Major Manny, young cadet.
I outrank everyone here.
- Remember that.
- BOTH: Yes, sir!
- Dismissed!
- Wow!
When I grow up,
I'm gonna be a praying mantis!
I'm gonna be a stick bug!
Oh, they're all so cool, I can't pick!
(CHUCKLES) Delightful lads.
You were saying, Flik?
All right. We are going to build a bird,
a bird that we can operate from the
inside, which would then be hoisted...
Hoisted above the anthill
and hidden high in the tree.
Then, right when Hopper
and his gang are below,
we'll launch the bird
and scare off the grasshoppers.
Now it's going to take...
Everyone's involvement
to make this plan a reality.
I know it's not our tradition
to do things differently,
but if our ancestors
were able to build this anthill,
we can certainly rally together
to build this bird!
(CHEERING)
- Perfect!
- Okay, hit your marks!
(EXCLAIMING)
- (CHUCKLES) Hi, Flik.
- Oh?
(CHUCKLING)
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
ANT 1: Do you mind
passing the sugar crumbs?
- ANT 2: Sure.
- ANT 1: Thank you.
- I love what you did with your antenna.
- Thank you.
Oh, look. She's a natural mother.
All right, that's it!
Out! Out! Everybody out!
Now you're gonna cry, right?
You're gonna cry.
See if I care.
Go ahead and cry. Go ahead.
Please, don't cry. Please.
(ALL CRYING LOUDLY)
Ta-da!
- Yeah, Francis!
THORNY: Okay, lower, lower...
(CHUCKLING)
- You got it. And that's it!
- Whoa!
- Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up!
Rabbit through the hole, chicken in the
barn, two by two by, there's the yarn.
- Done!
- Ruben Kincaid!
- Hey!
ATTA: Good job, guys! Nice work!
Up, down. Up, down. Up, down.
Hmm.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh-uh-uh!
Read them and weep.
Huh?
(FLIK WHOOPING)
- HEIMLICH: Flik, watch out!
- Whoa!
Look! I'm a beautiful butterfly!
There you go. Good job, fellas.
Keep up the good work.
(GASPS)
Okay!
(CREAKING)
- You fired!
(ANTS CHEERING)
Yes!
(CICADAS CHIRPING)
(BAND PLAYS LA CUCARACHA)
MOLT: Look at me! I'm barefooting!
Yo, bugito, dos granitos, pronto!
You got to try this, man!
♪ La cucaracha, la cucaracha... ♪
(HUMMING)
GRASSHOPPER: We have more than enough food.
We go all the way back there
and it starts to rain,
we might as well be sucking bug spray.
Ooh! Don't even say that!
You know something?
You're making a lot of sense.
I mean, why take the risk?
- You should tell Hopper.
- Good idea.
But, you know, it's really not our place.
I mean, you're his brother.
That makes you, like...
The vice president of the gang.
Wow! It kind of does, doesn't it?
Okay, I'll tell him. Boy, I should talk
to you guys more often.
What if Hopper doesn't like it?
Then at least the genius
will get smacked, and not us.
Vice President Molt.
Yeah, that's good. Oh, that's good.
- A little lower. Lower, lower.
- Hey-a, Hop.
- Go away.
- That's fine. I won't tell you my idea.
- Good!
- Okay, okay. I'll tell you anyway.
You see, I've been thinking,
which is something that I do,
you know, being vice president and all.
This is a thought. And it was mine.
Why go back to Ant Island at all?
I mean, you don't even like grain.
- What?
- You're right.
I didn't think it was such
a good idea, myself.
Actually, it wasn't even my idea.
It was Axle and Loco's!
They talked fancy to me.
I got confused!
♪ La cucaracha ♪
(HUMMING)
Guys, order another round,
because we're staying here!
- Yeah!
What was I thinking?
Going back to Ant Island.
I mean, we just got here,
and we have more than enough food
to get us through the winter, right?
Why go back?
(SINGING FOR HE'S
A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW)
But there was that ant
that stood up to me.
- Yeah, but we can forget about him!
- Yeah, it was just one ant.
One ant!
Yeah, you're right! It's just one ant!
- Yeah, boss. They're puny!
- Hmm. Puny.
Say, let's pretend this grain
is a puny little ant.
- Did that hurt?
- (CHUCKLES) Nope.
- Well, how 'bout this one?
- Are you kidding?
Well, how 'bout this?
You let one ant stand up to us,
then they all might stand up.
Those puny little ants
outnumber us 100 to one.
And if they ever figure that out,
there goes our way of life!
It's not about food.
It's about keeping those ants in line.
That's why we're going back!
Does anybody else want to stay?
He's quite the motivational
speaker, isn't he?
Let's ride!
(DRONING BUZZ)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
- ANT/font>: To the bird!
- ALL: The bird!
(FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
ALL: (CHANTING) Hey!
Get down, roly boys!
How low can you go? Sing it now.
- ♪ How low can you go?♪
- ♪ How low can you go? ♪
Do it, princess. How low can you go?
And that's how my 12th husband died.
So now I'm a widow. I mean,
I've always been a black widow,
but now I'm a black-widow widow.
- Thorny! Any sign of those fiends?
- Let me check.
No, not yet.
But we'll be ready for them.
Blueberries, dismissed!
And quit beating the boys up.
Those little raisins do grow on you.
Hey, how you guys doing?
Some party, huh?
Is that grain dip fresh or what? Okay.
I've told everyone you'll be stationed
deep in the command bunker.
Party quiets down,
I sneak you out the back way,
and then you're out of here forever.
Dim don't want to go.
Well, if Dim stays, he's gonna
need me here. He's not fully trained.
I mean, house-trained.
(CHUCKLES)
I... I kind of promised the Blueberries
I'd teach them canasta.
It seems we've been booked
for an extended engagement.
Will you look at this colony?
Will you just look at this colony?
I don't even recognize it.
I feel 70 again!
Work that ab, baby!
And I have you bugs to thank for it.
So, thank you!
And thank you for finding them, Flik.
Me? Oh... I'll get it.
I mean, if you don't mind,
I'll just, I'll just...
It's all tangled up.
There.
I think I'll go check on the bird.
- Bird's this way.
- Yeah, the bird's that way.
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
She... What?
(GASPS)
Jiminy H. Cricket!
(BLOWING ALARM)
FLIK: They're back!
Get ready, everybody!
Get to your posts!
Battle stations, everyone.
This is not a drill!
Come on, everyone.
You know your jobs!
Let's go, go, go, go!
ANT: Look out!
Whoa, whoa, whoa there.
Steady, girls. That's it.
- It's P.T.
- P.T.?
Greetings and salutations!
Ooh-boppa-doo and how do you do?
I am the great P.T. Flea!
I'm in need of your...
Oh, let's just cut to the chase.
Look, I've been going
from anthill to anthill.
I'm looking for a bunch of
circus performers.
Have you seen them?
(GASPS)
Wait a second.
Ain't that Staff Sergeant Slim?
Nope! No, no, no. I'm sorry, no.
I've never seen
anyone like that around here.
SLIM: Be quiet!
FLIK: No one has ever seen
anyone like that around here.
So you'll probably want to get going.
I guess you've got a lot of other
anthills to check into, so bye!
Ah, guys, I've been looking all over
for you! Flaming Death is a huge hit!
- P.T.!
- P.T. FLEA: I'm serious!
Word of mouth got around.
The next day, there was a line of flies
outside the tent, went on forever!
- It must have been a foot long!
- P.T., no!
So I figured it out. You guys burn me
twice a night, I take a day off to heal.
And then we do it all over again!
We'll be the top circus act
in the business!
- You mean, you're not warriors?
- Are you kidding?
These guys are the lousiest
circus bugs you've ever seen.
And they're gonna make me rich!
You mean to tell me
that our entire defensive strategy
was concocted by clowns?
We really thought
Flik's idea was gonna work.
Oops.
Tell me this isn't true.
- No, you don't...
- This couldn't have happened
at a more inopportune time!
The last leaf is about to fall!
FEMALE ANT: We haven't collected
any food for the grasshoppers!
If Hopper finds out
what we almost did...
Hopper is not going to find out.
We're going to hide all this
and pretend it never happened.
You bugs were never here.
So I suggest you all leave.
But the bird! The bird will work.
I never thought I'd see the day
when an ant would put himself
- before the rest of his colony.
- What?
- The point is, Flik, you lied to us.
- No, no, no! I... I just...
You lied, Flik. You lied to her.
You lied to the colony! You lied to me!
And like an idiot, I believed you.
But I... I was just afraid that
if you knew I'd gotten circus bugs...
(SIGHS)
- I just wanted to make a difference.
- ATTA: I want you to leave, Flik.
And this time, don't come back.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS)
Tough crowd. Yee-haw!
Flik!
(BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE)
(DRONING BUZZ)
(PANTING)
(MURMURING)
(GRUNTING)
That's it? But there's got to be
more food on the island!
If we give up any more, we'll starve.
Hopper won't accept this!
(GASPS)
(DRONING BUZZ APPROACHING)
Mother, it's not enough.
What do we do?
I... I don't know.
(GASPS)
(SNARLING)
(ROARS)
HOPPER: You little termites!
I give you a second chance,
and this is all I get?
But, Hopper, we ran out of time!
Have you been playing all summer?
You think this is a game?
- No, no, please!
- Well, guess what?
You just lost.
(ROARS)
Not one ant sleeps
until we get every scrap of food
on this island!
Just do what he says. You don't
want to make him mad. Believe me!
No, no, no.
You're staying with me, Your Highness.
Where do you think you're going?
Get over there!
Quick! To the clubhouse.
(RUSTLING)
(GASPS)
Hurry!
Shut up a minute, will you?
I think I heard something over here.
- Have you checked over there?
- No, not yet.
Well then, get over there
and check it out!
Wait a minute.
(GASPS)
Hey, I think I found something.
(CHUCKLES)
- Cool. Hey, how do I look?
- Like an idiot.
I don't know,
maybe it'll keep me dry in the rain.
You moron, we'll be out of here
before it rains.
Didn't you hear Hopper?
After the ants pick all the food,
he's gonna squish the queen
to remind them who's boss.
Then she's dead. They cry, boo-hoo.
We go home. End of story.
Oh, cool. I love our job.
Stay here. I'm gonna get help.
(THUMPER SNARLING)
(THUMPER ROARING)
(PANTING)
Come on, wings, fly. Fly!
(SNARLS)
(DOT SCREAMS)
Yeah!
(EXCLAIMS)
P.T. FLEA: ♪ I'm gonna be rich, rich, rich
♪ I'm gonna be rich, rich, rich
♪ I'm gonna be
the richest flea in the land
♪ The streets'll be paved
with golden retrievers
♪ I'm rich, rich, rich
That's who I am ♪
Poor fellow.
Hey, maybe we can cheer him up a bit.
Don't worry, Flik.
The circus life isn't so bad.
- Yes, you can be part of our act.
- Here! Like this.
Slapstick! Get it?
I... I'm a walking stick. Oh, never mind.
- DOT: Flik!
- Dot?
Flik, wait! Wait!
Dot, you're flying!
What are you doing here?
(PANTING)
You have to go back.
Hopper moved into the anthill,
and his gang's eating everything!
- Oh, no!
- Good heavens!
And I heard a grasshopper say
that when they're finished,
Hopper's gonna squish my mom!
Oh, not the queen!
- We got to do something!
- SLIM: How?
- ROSIE: Come on, you guys, think!
- I know. The bird.
- Yes, of course.
- The bird! That's brilliant.
FLIK: The bird won't work.
What are you talking about?
It was your idea.
But you said that everything...
Forget everything I ever told you.
All right, Dot?
Let's face it. The colony is right.
I just make things worse.
That bird is a guaranteed failure.
(SIGHS)
Just like me.
You listen to me, my boy.
I've made a living out of being a failure.
And you, sir, are not a failure!
Flik, you've done so many good things.
Oh, yeah?
Okay, show me one thing
I've done right.
- Us.
- Yeah, yeah.
Dim is right, my boy.
You have rekindled
the long-dormant embers of purpose
in our lives.
And if it wasn't for you,
Francis would have never gotten
in touch with his feminine side.
Oh yeah? Well...
(CHUCKLES)
You know what?, He's right.
Lieutenant Gypsy reporting for duty.
Kid, say the word,
and we'll follow you into battle.
We believe in you, my boy.
Flik, please?
Pretend it's a seed, okay?
Thanks, Dot.
- Hey, what's with the rock?
- Must be an ant thing.
- All right, let's do it.
- That's the Flik we know and love.
- We're on!
- So, what do we do first?
♪ Bugs will pay big bucks to see
♪ A bonfire that is starring me ♪
- P.T., look. Money!
- Where? Where?
All right. Get moving! Get going.
Move your abdomens, now!
FLIK: They're rounding everyone up.
(GASPS)
Hey! Turn your butt off.
Hey, guys!
Get me out of this thing, will you?
I promise to start thinking
about paying you.
Hey! Wait, wait! Okay, I'll pay you!
I'll pay you!
FLIK: Oh, no!
They've finished collecting the food.
We've got to get the queen now.
Once she's safe,
we move on Gypsy's signal.
(RUSTLING)
(GASPS)
Someone's coming!
Hello, kids!
Ready to make
some grasshoppers cry?
It's payback time, Blueberry-style.
- Blueberries rock!
- All right!
(DRUM ROLL)
SLIM: Ladies and gentlebugs!
Larvae of all stages!
Rub your legs together
for the world's greatest bug circus!
Wait a minute!
- I think I'm going to wet myself.
- Steady.
- What's going on here?
- Well...
(CHUCKLES)
Yes.
We were invited by Princess Atta
as a surprise for your arrival.
Squish them.
(GASPS)
(SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
- Now that's funny.
- That is funny.
I guess we could use
a little entertainment.
Looks like you did
something right for once, princess.
On with the show!
♪ The circus, the circus
I love the circus ♪
...all gone! Baby wants pie!
Pie? He asked for it.
Should I give it to him?
Yeah! Give him pie! Give him pie!
- Yeah!
- Thank you, gentlemen.
Always an intellectual treat.
How many roaches does it take
to screw in a light bulb?
Can't tell. As soon as the light
goes on, they scatter!
(PANTING)
- Almost there.
- From the most mysterious regions
of uncharted Asia,
- I give you the Chinese Cabinet...
- FLIK: Come on, girls. Quick. Quick.
...of Metamorphosis!
Utilizing psychic vibrations,
- I shall select the perfect volunteer.
- Pick me!
No! Come on.
I'm asking you with my brain.
- Aha! Why, Your Majesty!
- Me?
No, no. Thumper, down. Let her go.
Maybe he'll saw her in half.
As you ascend the dung beetle
to the unknown,
put your trust in the mysteries
that are beyond
mere mortal comprehension.
This is gonna be good!
- Blueberries ready?
- ALL: Ready.
Ready!
I call upon the ancient Szechuan spirits
to inhabit the body of our volunteer!
No, no.
Just stay in there, Your Majesty.
Transformation.
Transformation!
Wow. Manny's getting good.
- (GASPS) Not now.
- If it rains,
that bird'll get ripped to shreds!
MANNY: And now, insectus
transformitus!
(ALL EXCLAIM)
Pretty!
(APPLAUSE)
Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you.
- That's the signal. That's the signal!
This is it, girls. Get ready to roll.
- It's stuck!
- That was amazing!
I have no... How did they do that?
I have no idea where she went.
- Thank you. Thank you, thank you.
- More! More!
- More! More! More!
- Wait!
- Where is she?
- Well, now... Actually...
I'm sorry.
A magician never reveals his secrets.
That's very true, Hoppy.
I mean, where would the mystery be
if we all knew how it was...
- Shutting up.
- You can do it!
- You've got to make it work!
- Hey!
I said, where is she?
Hold on!
(CAWING)
Bird! It's a bird!
Yes!
- Let's get out of here! Go!
- Go!
Don't let it get me! Don't let it get me!
Help me!
Up, down, up, down. And turn!
(SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
My eye! Help me!
Boysenberry.
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, the pain!
There goes my magic act!
- Flaming Death!
- No! P.T.!
A direct hit!
(FLAMES CRACKLING)
Flik! Flik! Help us!
(GASPS)
Dot!
Okay! Everyone out! Hurry!
Where's Dot? Has anyone seen Dot?
Whose idea was this?
Was it yours, princess?
Just get behind me, girls. It'll be okay.
FLIK: Leave her alone, Hopper.
The bird was my idea.
I'm the one you want.
(GRUNTING)
(THUDDING)
Where do you get the gall
to do this to me?
You were...
You were gonna squish the queen.
It's true.
I hate it when someone
gives away the ending.
You piece of dirt! No, I'm wrong.
You're lower than dirt. You're an ant!
Let this be a lesson to all you ants.
Ideas are very dangerous things.
You are mindless, soil-shoving losers,
put on this earth to serve us!
FLIK: (WEAKLY) You're wrong, Hopper.
Ants are not meant
to serve grasshoppers!
I've seen these ants do great things.
And year after year,
they somehow manage
to pick food for themselves and you.
So who is the weaker species?
Ants don't serve grasshoppers.
It's you who need us.
(ANTS MURMURING)
We're a lot stronger
than you say we are.
And you know it, don't you?
Well, princess!
Hopper? I hate to interrupt, but...
You ants stay back!
- Oh, this was such a bad idea!
- You see, Hopper,
nature has a certain order.
The ants pick the food,
the ants keep the food
and the grasshoppers leave!
- I'm so proud of you, Flik!
- Charge-a!
HOPPER: Where are you going?
They're just ants!
No! Bad grasshopper!
Bad grasshopper! Go home!
(YELPS)
- Yeah!
- HOPPER: Come back here,
you cowards! Don't leave!
- To the cannon!
- ALL: To the cannon!
No!
Happy landings, Hopper!
(THUNDER CLAP)
Huh?
Rain!
- Flik!
- Quick! After them!
Slim!
SLIM: Francis! Francis!
Francis, I'm stuck!
- Where are you?
- I'm over here!
- Where?
- Here!
I'm the only stick with eyeballs!
- Help! Help! Help!
- Get him!
No!
(CHUCKLING)
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
- Go that way!
- But the anthill's...
I've got an idea!
- Flik!
- Come on!
There!
Come on! We've got to hide!
No matter what happens, stay down!
Flik, no! What are you doing?
- Hopper!
- You think it's over?
No, no, no. No, I can explain.
All your little stunt did
was buy them time!
- No, please! Please, Hopper!
- I'll get more grasshoppers
and be back next season,
but you won't!
(CHIRPING)
Well, what's this?
Another one of your little bird tricks?
- Yep.
- Are there a bunch of little girls
in this one, too? Hello, girls!
No! No! No, no, no, no!
No! No!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! No, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
(CHIRPING)
(CONCH SOUNDING)
Come on, boys!
Hey, Princess Dot! Wait up!
I finally get a second to relax,
and I got to get out of my chair.
Come on! You can rub lotion
on me later, shade boy.
Yeah, hubba-hubba.
- HEIMLICH: Oh, thank you!
- MANNY: Thank you.
- You're too kind.
- The least we could do.
- All in a day's work.
- Any time.
Dim!
I'm so sorry, kids.
I wish you could come along, too.
I'm not gonna cry. I'm not gonna cry.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Hey, let's go. We got a schedule
to keep. Come on. Let's go.
- Hey!
Hey, Tiny!
Let's get this show packed up!
We got paying customers hatching!
MOLT: Yes, Mr. Flea. Yes, sir.
Of course, sir. Right away, sir.
I just wanted to thank you
for giving me a chance,
because it's an honor to work
with creative giants such as yourself.
Shutting up.
You sure you can't come
on tour with us?
Sorry. My place is here.
- Good answer.
- Oh, well. Your loss.
One minute, insects!
I want to thank all of you
for giving us back
our hope, our dignity and our lives.
And to you, Princess Atta.
You have given us so much.
Please accept this gift from us bugs
to you ants.
- For you!
- (CHUCKLES) Oh! It's a rock.
- What's with the rock?
- Must be a circus thing.
(DOT GIGGLES)
Well, Flik, you really goofed up.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, you, too.
(ALL CHEERING)
(SNIFFLES)
All right. Now it's getting mushy.
We're out of here!
- Whoa!
- ROSIE: See you next season!
- SLIM: See you, Flik!
- Bye! We miss you already!
- You fired!
(GASPS)
We forgot Heimlich!
I'm finished!
Finally, I'm a beautiful butterfly!
Mein wings! Oh, they're beautiful!
Heimlich! The wagon's taking off!
You better start flying!
But I am flying! And from way up here,
you all look like little ants!
Auf Wiedersehen!
Bye!
Present stalks!
Harvester, salute!
("THE TIME OF YOUR LIFE" BY RANDY NEWMAN PLAYING)
♪ Was a bug, little bug
♪ Hardly there
♪ How he felt, what he dreamed
♪ Who would care?
♪ Without any evidence
CHORUS: ♪ His flaws were many, ooh
- ♪ He was full of confidence
- ♪ Some people haven't any
- ♪ Didn't have much common sense
- ♪ It's highly overrated
♪ He just knew that he'd come through
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well
♪ We may only go round one time
♪ As far as I can tell
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well
♪ We may only go round this one time
- ♪ As far as I can tell
- ♪ He could be wrong about that
- ♪ It's the time of your life
- ♪ Time, life
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well ♪
- MAN 1: Speed!
- MAN 2: Marker. And action!
- Are you saying I'm stupid?
- No.
Do I look stupid to you?
(ATTA LAUGHING)
I'm sorry.
Are you saying I'm stupid?
I'm sorry. I got it. No, no, no.
Just do it again. I'm fine.
- Are you saying I'm stupid?
- (LAUGHING) Yes!
This is the 15th take.
I cannot work like this.
I will be in my trailer.
I need a break.
MAN: Marker.
Whoa, Flik, honey,
we are not about to...
(HAMMERING)α
Is someone hammering?
Can we hold the work, please?
- People!
- SLIM: Am I in this shot?
You can see me, right?
MAN: And action.
To infinity and beyond!
(LAUGHING)
I'm sorry, I couldn't resist.
Really, can you blame me?
- Okay. Okay, let's go for real now.
- MAN: Okay, cut!
Why go back to Ant Island at all?
I mean, you don't even like grain.
- What?
- You're right.
I didn't think it was such
a good idea, myself.
- Actually, it wasn't even my idea...
- MAN: Watch it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
is the camera broke?
Oh, oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Did I ruin the take?
- And thank you for finding them, Flik.
- Me?
(EXCLAIMING IN PAIN)
- Oh, no. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- This really hurts. Guys, can we cut?
So, is there a Mrs. Ant
you have to tunnel home to?
Ooh, I'm sorry! I thought he was real.
Oh, dear, put that thing in my car.
MAN: Marker.
Flik, after much deliberation... Whoa!
Ohh!
I... Oh, my eye! Oh!
No, no, seriously,
I've got berry juice in my eye!
It stings! Stop acting! I'm serious!
Oh, stop the camera!
(URINATING)
Uh-oh. Towel! I need a towel over here!
(FARTS)
MAN: Cut!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Can we cut?
(DOT SIGHS)
It's just that I don't think
I'm coming across. Hmm...
Oh, oh, I know, I know.
I could lather up a bunch of spit.
Ooh, that's good. I got it, J.L.
All right. One more for me.
- MAN 1: Speed.
- MAN 2: Marker.
- MAN 3: Action!
- Spinning a web of safety
in less than fifteen...
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well
♪ We may only go round one time
♪ As far as I can tell
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well
♪ Like us all he started small
♪ Then he grew
♪ When the time came he knew
♪ What to do
- ♪ He knew in order to succeed
- ♪ They'd have to work together
- ♪ He turned a rock into a seed
- ♪ And they were changed forever
♪ Then they had the strength
they'd need
- ♪ To get through stormy weather
- ♪ Do or die, you gotta try
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well
♪ You may only go round one time
- ♪ As far as I can tell
- ♪ He may be wrong about that
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well
♪ Isn't it a bit surprising
♪ How our fortunes ebb and flow
♪ And only to the enterprising
♪ Does the magic fortune cookie go
♪ Believe me
It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ We may only go round one time
♪ As far as I can tell
♪ It's the time of your life
♪ So live it well ♪
(CLICK)