-(ROCK CRUMBLING)
-(ROARING)
-(INDISTINCT TALKING)
-(ROARING CONTINUES)
-(GRUNTING)
-(GROANING)
Come on, you lazy Cro-Magnon!
-Ohh!
-(GROANING CONTINUES)
Hey! Back to work!
You guys had a break two days ago!
Come on, now!
(ROARING)
Come on, Sheba!
That's my big girl!
Look at those
pathetic worms
burrowing
their lives away.
Do you know why I'm up here
and they're down there, Miss Stone?
Because you lied
on your resume?
No.
Because I have vision.
And right now I have a vision
of you and me...
Dripping with coconut oil
on a beach in Rocapulco...
with Mr. Slate's fortune
to keep us company.
I'm glad we see
eye to eye.
(CHUCKLING)
And somewhere down there
is the ignorant stooge
who will make
all my schemes come true.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
(ROARS)
-(LOUD SQUAWKING)
-Yabba-dabba-doo!
Flintstones
Meet the Flintstones
They're a modern Stone Age family
(RAPID FOOTSTEPS)
From the town of Bedrock
They're a page
right out of history
Let's ride with the family
down the street
Through the courtesy
of Fred's two feet
When you're
with the Flintstones
Have a yabba-dabba doo time
A dabba-doo time
We'll have a gay old time
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
STEWARDESS: The captain has just turned on
the seat belt sign...
-(SQUAWKS)
-Signaling our descent into the Bedrock area.
On your left, you'll be able to see
the Grand Canyon in about 15,000,000 years.
(ROARING)
K-A-V-E
Radio Bedrock
ANNOUNCER: The KAVE accu-forecast
for tonight calls for light seismic activity...
and a 20 percent chance
of meteor showers.
Quick traffic update, due to lava flows,
Highway One will be closed... Forever!
K-A-V-E
Molten Oldie
(GUITAR PLAYING)
(SINGING) Sow belly, pot of beans
Tie a rope around your jeans
Tell your mom not to wait
You ain't coming home too late
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Twitch
(GUITAR CONTINUES)
There's a town I know
where the hipsters go called Bedrock
Twitch, twitch
When you get that itch
you can do the Twitch
In Bedrock
Twitch, twitch
'Cause the Twitch is fine
Have yourself a time
(SCATTING)
In Bedrock
Drum solo!
-(FRED LAUGHING)
-(GUITAR CONTINUES)
Hey! Watch it, will ya?
Finally got my hair the way I like it.
I'm so excited, Fred.
I'm gonna be a father.
It's like
a dream come true.
A son. Someone to carry on
the proud name of Rubble.
Think I'll be a good daddy, Fred?
Well, you're bound to find
something you're good at.
-Yeah, sure... Hey!
-(CHUCKLING)
(GRUNTING)
-Uncle!
-Heh, heh, heh.
You know, Fred, Betty and I
really owe it all to you.
We would've never qualified to adopt
had it not been for the money you gave us.
Remember, Barn,
that's between you and me.
I'd like to tell the world what
a great guy my best buddy is!
No, no, no!
True, it was a selfless, noble act,
if I do say so myself.
My only reward
will be your happiness.
I don't need to go
blabbin' my good deeds all around.
-You're afraid to tell Wilma, aren't you?
-(FEET SKIDDING)
Afraid? Now, let's get this straight, Rubble.
I don't need permission
from my wife to make a decision.
In my cave, I reign supreme!
Su-preme!
-I won't tell her, Fred.
-Thanks, pal.
(RAPID FOOTSTEPS)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(CHUCKLES)
(CHILDREN SINGING)
-Hiya, Timmy!
-(BOYS SHOUTING)
Here you go!
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
Hey, Charlie!
(CHUCKLING)
-Huh? (PANTING)
-Wilma!
I'm home!
-(BARKING RAPIDLY)
-(GASPS)
No, Dino! No, no!
No, Dino! Bad boy!
-(GROANING)
-(BARKING CONTINUES)
-Bad dog! (LAUGHING)
-(LICKING)
-Good doggie!
-Bad Dino breath. (GROANING)
-(BARKS)
-Fred!
Do you have to get Dino so wound up
when you come home?
It's not my fault.
Maybe he'd calm down if we had him fixed!
What? (WHINING)
(GURGLES)
(GASPS)
Here comes
the big Daddysaurus!
(BOTH SCREECHING)
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
-How was your day, dear?
-(GROANS)
I think my Brontocrane's
pregnant again.
I tell ya,
you forget to lock her up
one Saturday night...
-Comfortable, Fred?
-On my way.
All I need's a brew and a good scratch.
Which one do you want to do first?
It does my heart good
to see you relaxing
after a hard day
at the quarry.
I'm telling you, I married
the pick of the litter.
(WILMA CHUCKLES)
Fred, our garbage disposal
has been acting up a lot lately,
so I decided that it was
time to buy a new one.
But when I went to take money
out of our savings account...
-Guess what?
-New garbage disposal?
New garbage disposal?
Why throw good money down the drain?
There's nothing wrong
with this one.
-(BELCHES)
-All right, you. Say "ahh."
Uh-uh.
(SQUEALING)
Do you have any idea why there's no money
in our savings account?
-(SQUEALING CONTINUES)
-Aha!
(CLEARS THROAT)
-There's your problem right there.
-(BELCHES)
-All right, you! Spit it out!
-(BELCHES LOUDLY)
Where's the money,
Fred?
Something happened to it.
There, I said it.
We have scrimped and saved
for that money.
And every time we get ahead,
you have to go blow it on
some hare-brained scheme!
Now, see here, Wilma!
In this cave, I am the king!
-And...
-And what, Fred?
And you have every right
to know, my queen.
I gave it to Barney.
You what?
I know I should've consulted you,
but Barney Rubble's my neighbor,
my lodge brother
and my best friend since the first time
I went through the fifth grade!
Fred Flintstone!
Wilma, without that money,
they wouldn't be allowed to adopt a baby.
So go ahead, yell, scream,
let the fur fly.
Give the neighbors
something to talk about!
What you have just done
for the Rubbles...
Is the sweetest, most generous thing
I ever heard.
And I adore you for it.
Mmm.
I also bought a new bowling ball.
Wait! Come on, honey!
-Watch your step.
-Sit down.
DRIVER: All right, all together, folks.
(RAPID FOOTSTEPS)
Betty, sit down
and relax.
Oh, I can't, Wilma.
It just hit me.
From now on,
I'll be spending 24 hours a day
attending to the every need
of a helpless little boy.
(TRUMPETING)
(BOTH TRUMPETING)
(LAUGHS)
Then again, maybe it won't be
such a big adjustment after all.
(GIGGLES)
Fred!
And promise you won't say anything
like you did when you saw my sister's baby.
The kid had a tail.
Was I supposed to pretend I didn't notice?
Hello, Mommy and Daddy!
I have someone who wants to meet you!
-Aah!
-(CHITTERING)
Well, it's not exactly
what we pictured, but...
-We'll love him like he was our own.
-WOMAN: No, no, no.
This little fellow
belongs to the Hendersons.
(CHATTERING)
-So glad you'll be nursing.
-Congratulations.
Mr. and Mrs. Rubble,
this is your little boy.
-(BOTH GASPING)
-(BARNEY GIGGLES)
Barney, isn't he precious?
Precious? They'd have been better off
with the monkey.
Fred!
-Does he have a name?
-Bamm-Bamm.
-Is that short for somethin'?
-Bamm-Bamm-Bamm.
You'll have to take it slowly with this one.
He doesn't speak yet,
and he's a little skittish around humans.
But then again, I would be too
if I had been raised by wild mastodons.
-(WOMAN LAUGHING)
-BOTH: Mastodons?
Let's not nitpick.
A mammal's a mammal.
Well, sounds to me
like all he needs is a little lovin'.
Ohh.
-Come here, little guy.
-(GROWLING)
Aah! He growled.
It's cute. (GIGGLES)
It's okay, little guy.
I'm your da-da.
(SNIFFING)
-(SCREAMING)
-Bamm-Bamm!
-BETTY: Oh! Barney!
-(GROANING)
-Oh, Betty!
-BARNEY: Bamm-Bamm! No!
(GRUNTS)
-(CARS SKIDDING)
-(INDISTINCT YELLS)
Bamm-Bamm!
Bamm-Bamm, wait!
Stalactite, stalagmite
Hold your baby very tight
(BAMM-BAMM YELLING)
-(SINGER LAUGHING)
-(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GROWLS)
-Come back!
-Come here, little guy!
(YELLING)
-Bamm-Bamm! Bamm! Bamm-Bamm!
-Ohhh!
Rock with the caveman
Bamm-Bamm-Bamm-Bamm-Bamm!
Roll with the caveman
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
Shake to the caveman
Break with the caveman
Oof!
Make with the caveman
Okay, give me a C-A-V-E
BARNEY: Whoa!
M-A-N, Caveman
Whoa! (CHUCKLING)
What an arm!
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
"And Cinderocka married
the handsome prince, and...
"And they lived happily ever after."
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-(LAUGHING)
-(GROWLING)
-Yeah!
Okay, Brother Flintstone,
we need a strike to win.
-Can you do it?
-(SNICKERS)
Is the Earth flat?
-Come on, Freddie!
-Come on, hit it!
(EXHALES)
Come on, twinkle toes.
-(CROWD CHEERING)
-(LAUGHING)
Fred!
-Waka-waka-woo!
-ALL: Waka-waka-woo!
-Wooga-wooga-wee!
Piki-piki-piki!
Poki-poki-poki!
Ahhhhhhhh-oooh!
HOAGIE: Lava juice!
Hey, can I have everybody's
attention, please?
I would like to propose a toast
to not only a great bowler,
but a great human being.
-And no offense to you guys.
-(GRUNTING)
"Since I was just a lad of ten,
I've had the very bestest friend.
"He may be big,
he may be loud,
-"so you'll never lose him in a crowd.
-(CROWD MUMBLING)
"But for my friend
the special part...
"is what's behind his ribs...
His heart."
-(SNIFFLES)
-"I owe my son to him, and now...
"I stand before my peers and vow...
"I'll pay him back, someday, somehow."
(SNIFFLING CONTINUES)
-The end.
-(SNIFFLES LOUDLY)
-That was beautiful, Barn.
-I meant every word of it, Fred.
-Care to join me in a cold one?
-Love to.
(SLURPING)
(ALL HOWLING)
It doesn't get
any better than this.
(ALL HOWLING)
(BARKS)
(PANTING)
(DINO YIPPING)
Ohh!
No.
Look at him.
Drunk as a skunkosaurus.
Aaaah!
Mother, I can handle this.
What's that old fossil doing here?
Did the tar pits back up again?
Well, somebody has to be here
looking after my daughter and grandchild...
While you're out carousing
with a bunch of Neanderthals.
Oh, really?
Well, for your information,
the lodge no longer
accepts Neanderthals.
He robs your nest egg to bail out
that little troll next door
while my daughter
has to wash her clothes in the river.
-I got half a mind...
-Oh, don't flatter yourself.
That's it!
Where's my club, Wilma?
You just try it, fatso!
-If you was a man, I'd knock you...
-Enough! Mother! Fred!
You two should be
ashamed of yourselves!
I've got my hands full
just being ashamed of him.
You got your hands full
when you scratch your neck!
WILMA: Stop it!
Both of you!
Mother, Fred is a loving husband
and a good provider.
Oh, really? What has he
ever provided you besides shade?
Oh, Wilma,
you could've married
Elliot Firestone,
the man who invented
the wheel.
Instead you picked
Fred Flintstone,
the man who invented
the excuse.
Let me tell you something, Pearl.
I'm not going to be a nobody all my life.
One of these days,
I'm gonna be a somebody, a real somebody!
We'll live in luxury, and Wilma will have
everything she deserves.
When that day comes,
you'll be so busy eatin' crow
you'll be passing feathers
for a month!
Oh, you poor, poor dear.
And when I think of all the sacrifices
your father made for you.
Lambs, oxen,
your brother Jerry.
-Well...
-Oh, Wilma.
Do your mother a favor.
Just call Elliot Firestone.
Even if things
don't work out,
he can give you
a great deal on some tires.
-Yes, Mother.
-Byesie-bye.
I'll show her.
I'll show everybody.
I know you will, Fred.
-Call me fatso.
-Let's get some sleep.
-(GRUNTS)
-(GROWLS)
(Squawking)
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, what's the special?
This job sucks.
-What you got today?
-Lizard and onions. Want half?
Sure.
I hear that eatin' too much red meat
is bad for you.
What a load of bunk.
My father ate it every day of his life,
he lived to the ripe old age of 38.
May I have your attention!
I have a very important
announcement to make.
You found out why the guys in pit six
are losing their hair?
Yes!
And we are currently in the process
of refuting the results of that investigation.
But today I am here
to formally announce
the creation
of Slate and Company's
executive placement program.
-(MURMURING)
-Hold your questions, please.
That's right, this Saturday
an aptitude test will be given,
granting one of you
the opportunity
to crawl out of the primordial ooze
and be somebody.
A vice president at Slate and Company,
with an obscene salary
and a shiny nameplate.
BOTH: Ooh.
VANDERCAVE: Good luck,
and may the best biped win.
An executive?
This is my chance to be somebody.
(ECHOING) Be somebody.
PEBBLES: Whee!
-(CHUCKLING)
-(GIGGLING)
Higher, Bamm-Bamm, higher!
PEBBLES: Higher! Higher!
Whee!
-Wilma.
-Hmm?
How did you get rid of the ring
around the collar?
By washing Fred's neck.
Hmm. You know, if Fred
scores the highest on that test,
you'll be able to hire someone
to do your laundry for you.
If Fred scores the highest on that test,
I'll have to hire someone to revive me.
(GIGGLES)
Oh, it's true,
Fred's no Albert Einstone.
-But he may surprise you.
-PEBBLES: Whee!
WILMA: Well, maybe.
-He has been studying day and night.
-Whee!
I know! I've never seen him so excited
about something you couldn't spread
mayonnaise on.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
(PEBBLES GIGGLING)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Barn, I've been thinking
about this executive job.
It's not me.
Cooped up inside
some swank office all day,
kissing the big shot's feet.
Not Fred Flintstone.
Why, good afternoon,
Mr. Vandercave.
My, that's a handsome pelt
you're wearing today.
Thank you.
Your attention, please!
Please take your seats.
And welcome.
You will have one hour
to complete the exam.
Please carve all answers
with a well-sharpened No. 2 chisel.
VANDERCAVE: On behalf
of Slate and Company,
I want to wish you all
the very best of luck.
Let's begin.
Eeee!
Ohh.
Chisels down.
Please slide your answer slab
into the numbered envelope provided
and stack them neatly on my desk.
Psst! Hey, Fred!
How'd you do?
(CHUCKLING) How'd I do?
How'd I do?
(CHUCKLES)
-You want me to take that up for you?
-Yeah. Thanks, pal.
"And I stand before my peers
and vow,
"I'll pay him back, someday, somehow."
(CLEARS THROAT)
-(BELCHES)
-Ahh.
(BELCHES)
Well, Cliff,
the test results are in.
And our
unsuspecting dupe is?
Believe it or not, the one who scored
the highest was Fred Flintstone.
-That big ape?
-No, the big ape got a 65.
Flintstone? Oh, this can't be right!
He must have cheated.
He's dense, he's witless...
He's perfect.
The results of the exam
were very competitive,
and just because
an applicant was not selected...
is no indication
of lack of ability.
-I am pleased to announce...
-I know a kiss-off when I hear one. Let's go.
That the newest member
of our executive rank
is Mr. Fred Flintstone!
-ALL: Huh?
-Barney, quick. What's my name?
-Fred Flintstone!
-Don't toy with me, Barney.
You did it, Fred!
You made it!
Yabba-dabba-dabba-doo!
(CHEERING)
(FRED SNORING)
(ROOSTER CROWS)
(SNORING CONTINUES)
(GROANING)
Good morning,
Mr. Vice President.
(CHUCKLING) Good morning,
Mrs. Vice President.
(GIGGLES)
-(WHINING)
-Oh, Dino! Oh, Dino, no!
-Aaah!
-(SLURPING)
-Hey!
-Mmm!
Atta baby!
(LAUGHS)
Oh...(HUMMING)
(DINO PANTING)
Good boy, Dino.
(DINO WHINING)
(GURGLES)
Well, how do I look?
(GASPS) Daddy pretty.
WILMA: It's perfect!
Yeah. Snazzy.
What am I gonna call you now?
Boss? Chief?
No, a simple "Your Highness" will do.
-(CHUCKLES)
-No, Barn.
I'm not gonna be one of these guys that
makes it then forgets where he came from.
The first thing I'm gonna do is get everyone
in the quarry some vacation time.
And maybe a health plan
with free foot care.
I'd settle for them little packets of ketchup
for the lunch room.
-I'm only one man.
-Not from the back. (CHUCKLES)
Hey, hey.
Well, I guess this is it,
Mr. Flintstone.
Go get 'em, big guy.
-Hey, Barn.
-Yeah, Fred?
Could you spot me a couple bucks for lunch?
I'm a little short.
You're right, Fred.
Nothing's changed.
Welcome aboard,
Flintstone!
We're glad you're here.
Nice suit! (LAUGHING)
You know, Fred,
any gravel brain...
can shovel rock down in the quarry,
but up here...
-Do you know what we do up here?
-Me and the guys have always wondered.
We interface, Flintstone.
We strategize, analyze,
conceptualize, prioritize...
When do we eat?
Fred, until this moment
I wasn't sure we'd picked the right man.
Now I'm certain.
Fred Flintstone,
you've arrived.
-This is my office?
-That's right.
-This is my chair?
-Mmm-hmm.
Not to throw too much at you
on your first day,
but this big thing here is your desk.
-My desk?
-Watch out for your fingers in the drawers.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Am I interrupting?
Not at all. Fred, I'd like you to meet
your new secretary,
-Miss Sharon Stone.
-My secretary?
Personal secretary, Mr. Flintstone.
That is, of course,
if you want me.
Great.
Well, I'm sure the two of you
would like to get...
Better acquainted.
Mr. Flintstone,
I'd like you to know
that I enjoy working
long hours, late nights,
even weekends.
So feel free to use me
however you see fit.
Now, can I get you anything?
-Coffee?
-(VOICE CRACKS) Sure.
-How would you like it?
-In a cup?
Bold choice, Mr. Flintstone!
You'll go far in this company.
-(EXHALES)
-(DOOR CLOSES)
Take a memo.
Cliff, let's play golf.
We can prioritize, conceptualize
and, uh... Tenderize.
Executively yours,
Fred Fli... Ah!
Are there six or seven
"I"s in "Fli... Ah"?
-Who said that?
-It was I, your dictabird.
-Dicta-what?
-Dictabird. Read my beak.
(Squawk) "Cliff, let's play golf.
"We can prioritize, conceptualize
and, uh, tenderize."
Wow. Wow!
Mr. Flintstone, I'd like to warn you
that management positions
are fraught with peril.
Whenever you find yourself
in a befuddled state,
I urge you to avail yourself
of my experience
and sage advice.
Oh, really?
Listen, birdie, let's get the pecking order
straight here.
Hmm.
I don't need any help from you.
I'm Vice President of...
Of, uh...
Industrial procurement.
How about that?
Excuse me.
Hey, guys!
Guess what I am!
Vice President of
Industrial Procurement!
(ALL CHEERING)
Oy! Whew.
Yeah.
There. I'm all done
with the requisition forms.
What do you think?
VANDERCAVE: It's perfect.
Looks just like
the real one.
Mr. Flintstone, you are about to embezzle
a great deal of money.
Unfortunately, for you,
we get to keep it.
We can have Flintstone
sign these right away.
Not just yet.
Creatures like this Flintstone
are primitive,
prone to irrational
bouts of integrity.
We've got to make absolutely certain
he'll do whatever we say.
Fred is the greatest bowler
on Earth.
-"Fred is the greatest bowler on Earth."
-(GIGGLING)
-Now you talk, and see
how much I can remember.
(GROANS)
Workin' hard?
Okay, Fred, are you ready
for your first executive action?
Ready and willing.
Whatever you need, consider it done!
Good! I want you to fire Bernard Rubble.
Done... What?
Fire Barney? Why?
Well, for starters, he scored the lowest
on the management aptitude test.
He's an imbecile. The company can't afford
to have dead weight like him on the payroll!
But, Mr. Vandercave,
he's got a new kid, a mortgage.
I'm his best friend.
I can't.
Fred...
If you don't fire him,
I will.
And then I'll fire you.
Come on, Fred,
usually you're yakkin' my ear off,
but today you haven't said two words.
Something exciting
must have happened up there.
-You don't want to know, Barn, believe me.
-Sure I do, Fred.
You're the first one of us
to make it out of that quarry.
Look at me. (CHUCKLES)
I'll probably be working there
the rest of my life.
No, you won't, Barn.
-Take my word for it.
-(BARNEY CHUCKLES)
Come take a look... It's a dish in the shower,
you keep the soap in it.
Barney, there's something
we gotta talk about.
Yeah, yeah. Later, Fred.
ALL: Surprise!
-(ALL CHEERING)
-Way to go, Fred!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
-Wilma, you shouldn't have.
-Hmm?
I didn't. This was all Barney and Betty's idea.
Aren't we lucky to have friends
like them, Fred?
(GASPS) Ohh!
There he is!
There's my big, handsome son-in-law!
(LAUGHING)
Have you lost weight?
-Have we met?
-(LAUGHS)
Can I have everybody's
attention, please?
I've got something
I'd like to say.
-I hope it's not another poem.
-(ALL LAUGHING)
Fred... Betty, Bamm-Bamm and I
could not be happier,
-even if it was me that got that job.
-ALL: Aww!
So we got a little something
to show how proud of you we are.
-Congratulations, big guy!
-(Guests Murmuring)
Barney, I can't accept this.
-Sure, you can.
-No, I can't. Take it back.
-We can't. We had your initials branded on it.
-It's yours, Fred.
-No, it's not!
-Fred, what's wrong with you?
It's a lovely gift.
-He's thrilled to receive it. Aren't you, Fred?
-No!
-Don't you like the color?
-It's not the briefcase, it's not the color.
-I just can't take anything from you.
-But, Fred...
Take a hike, shorty.
My Freddie doesn't want
that tacky thing.
-How come, Fred?
-Because you can't afford it, Barn.
-(Chuckles)
-Ohh.
Sure I can, pal.
Not anymore.
-You're fired.
-(RECORD SCRATCHES) Fired?
-(GUESTS GASPING)
-(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Well! (CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
Let's not let a little thing like this
spoil the party!
Conga line!
-(MUSIC PLAYS)
-Conga! Conga!
(DINO BARKING IN CONGA RHYTHM)
Don't worry about me, Fred.
I've been working in that quarry
since it was eight feet deep.
Atta boy!
There could be a whole new world
opening up for me.
Maybe I'll take in that franchise show
this weekend.
That's the spirit.
There's just one thing
I gotta know.
After all these years,
how come they're canning me?
Barn,
you're
a wonderful father,
a loving husband,
a hard worker,
and one heck of a little bowler. (SNICKERS)
But, Barn, none of that counts
on an aptitude test.
You got the lowest score, pal.
The lowest score?
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Wilma, that is beautiful!
-Well, I have always wanted...
-You can't catch me!
-A Halstone original. (GIGGLES)
-Mmm.
-(Gasps) Ohh!
-Now, Wilma, don't be silly!
Your husband's a big executive.
You can afford it.
-(TRUMPETS BLOWING)
-BOTH: Charge it!
(BOTH GIGGLING)
-(GROWLING)
-Bamm-Bamm!
-Ohh! Bamm-Bamm!
-No!
-Bamm-Bamm! Bamm-Bamm!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(SHOUTING STOPS)
Gentlemen, please. I cannot endorse
this modernization...
if it means laying off
all those workers.
Some have been here
since the beginning of time.
What if I could
quadruple your income?
I'll miss them.
You were saying?
Sorry I'm late.
I had car trouble. Picked up a nail.
Thank you
for sharing that, Mr. Flagstone.
-(STUTTERS)
-SLATE: May we continue?
-(GROANING)
-VANDERCAVE: Mr. Slate. Gentlemen.
I have a vision.
While our competitors
are mired in the Stone Age,
I give you...
the future!
-Ohh.
-Slate and Company...
will revolutionize
the building industry...
by providing simple,
low-cost,
modular housing units.
Impossible, you say?
Let me demonstrate.
Through the miracle
of geothermal power,
the raw material
is elevated to the second stage,
-where our steam-powered
conveyor belt carries...
Steam?
He's a madman!
Steam-powered
conveyor belts...
carry the product
to be shaped, cleaned, inspected...
and delivered to discerning
consumers worldwide.
(BELL DINGS)
And did I mention increasing
our profit margin...
-Fourfold?
-Very impressive, Mr. Vandercave.
Very impressive. I think we should
implement this system immediately.
Yes?
Excuse me, Mr. Slate.
I know I'm the new man here,
but I don't think
you hired me to sit around and look pretty.
I hate to bust your bubble,
but if you build houses this small,
who's gonna live in 'em?
(GROANS)
(GROWLING)
-Excuse me. Mrs. Rubble?
-Yes.
There seems to be a slight problem
with your credit card.
Really?
And what would that be?
It's no damn good!
(CHILDREN YELLING)
I have never been so embarrassed
in my entire life.
-Go and play, children.
-Wilma, I promise you I'll pay you back.
-I just don't know when. (Sobbing)
-Oh, now, Betty.
-It can't be as bad as all that.
-But it is.
Barney's still out of work, we've nearly spent
all of our savings.
And, Wilma, what if the adoption agency
finds out?
I don't want to lose my baby.
I swear, Betty,
Fred and I would never let that happen.
-Oh, Wilma. (SOBBING)
-Oh, Betty.
-(LOUD ROARING)
-(GASPS)
-MAN: Pterodactyl alert!
-(PTERODACTYL ROARING)
-Mommy, help!
-(ALL SHOUTING)
(FARTING)
-Oh, yuck!
-Ew!
And in conclusion, Mr. Slate,
I feel a paid vacation for everyone
in the quarry would raise morale
and increase productivity, um, um...
A whole bunch!
Sincerely yours,
Frederick J. Flintstone.
Shall I make that "Flagstone,"
so he'll know who it's from?
My, don't we look
handsome today?
BOTH: Thank you.
Here are today's batch
of requisitions.
-All marked and ready for your signature.
-Okay.
You know, Miss Stone,
I've been signing stacks of these for weeks,
and I hate to pry, but what are they?
Oh, just tiny little forms
so that we can pay the contractors
working on the modernization.
We remodeled our kitchen
a couple of years ago,
and let me tell you,
contractors can be real pirates.
-I'm gonna read these over.
-No!
You're much too busy for that, Mr. Flintstone.
Besides,
reading is my job.
You wouldn't want to put
poor little old me
out of work, now, would you?
-No.
-(MISS STONE GIGGLING)
(BOTH GIGGLING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Your wife. Mmm-mmm. (WHISTLES)
-Your wife.
-My wife. Wilma?
-Wilma! What a surprise!
-So it would seem.
Miss Stone, I'd like you
to meet my wife Mrs. Flagstone...
and our daughter, um...
Um, um, um...
Isn't she beautiful?
My family.
-I've heard so much about you.
-Well, I wish that I could say the same.
That'll be all, Miss Stone.
I'll sign those documents
and place them on your desk.
Whatever you want.
-Your secretary is very attractive.
-Really? I hadn't noticed.
Did I mention she chisels
eighteen words a minute?
Hmm.
Hey, Wilma, did ya ever see
one of these? (CHUCKLING)
My wife is the most beautiful gal in Bedrock.
"My wife is the most
beautiful gal in Bedrock."
Nice try, Fred.
"Nice try, Fred."(GASPS)
Fred! I've come to talk
about the Rubbles' troubles.
Hasn't Barney
found a job yet?
It's gotten so bad, they've had to rent out
their house just to make ends meet.
Really. Where are they gonna live?
-(TRUMPETING)
-So glad you're over your cold. (GIGGLES)
-(ROARS)
-Thank you.
Isn't this nice, Betty?
The Flintstones and the Rubbles,
all under one roof.
Yes, but this is such an imposition.
Are you sure it's okay with Fred?
Oh, absolutely.
As a matter of fact,
he thinks it was his idea.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
-Hey, Freddie, a couple of cool ones.
-Oh, yeah.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
-(CORKS POP)
-(BOTH SPIT)
(SIGHS) How about it, Barn?
-Flintstones and Rubbles under one roof.
-But it's only temporary.
It'd better be.
-It'd better be!
-Yeah! (CHUCKLES)
Ah, Barn, I admire ya.
You've lost your job, your dignity,
but not your sense of humor.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
-Hey, cut it out, Fred!
-(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
-(DINO WHINING)
-You like your steak rare?
-Yeah.
-That one's yours.
-Hey, hey, stop!
Come here, you purple rodent!
(DINO YIPPING)
Don't forget to wash that off before you eat it!
BARNEY: Come here!
Give me that!
BARNEY: Help! Somebody!
-(BARKING)
-Oh!
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Flintstone gets the rock.
He sets his shot.
He shoots!
Oh!
Oh! Oh, boy.
Miss Stone,
what a pleasant surprise.
Oh. What happened here?
-That's what I'd like to know!
-I'll get someone to fix it.
Oh, Miss Stone?
Before you go, there's
something bothering me...
-About this new system we're putting in here.
-Oh?
Yeah. I don't pretend
to understand it all,
but wouldn't this put a lot
of my guys out of work?
How would I know?
I'm just a little ol' secretary.
(CHUCKLES) Are you kiddin' me?
You're smart!
I could tell that right off.
There's a lot more to you than you...
Er... Uh... (STAMMERS)
-You... I mean...
-Thank you.
I sure hope I didn't get you into
too much trouble with your wife the other day.
Nah. Wilma always forgives me.
She knows I love her.
-And you do, don't you?
-Are you kiddin'?
I'll never forget, the first time I met her
she was working at a restaurant.
I won this "All You Can Eat" contest
and she was the one that cleaned me off.
Every night I go home and
look at her and I think,
"What is a beautiful woman like that
doing with a big galoot like me?"
I think I know.
-Where have you been?
-With Fred.
I mean, Mr. Flintstone.
I'm worried, Cliff.
He's smarter than we thought.
He'd have to be to get himself dressed
in the morning.
He's been asking
a lot of questions.
I think we should just call the whole thing off.
No. No, I've got a better idea.
Why don't we
turn ourselves in,
then we can rot in jail
until the poles freeze over.
I was just thinking...
Stick to your strengths,
Miss Stone.
And I'll stick to mine.
Besides,
if Mr. Flintstone insists
on being so conscientious,
perhaps we can give Fred...
something to take his mind
off work, hmm?
-A bonus?
-That's right, Fred!
-You deserve it.
-For what?
Don't be modest, you go-getter, you!
And Fred, let me let you in
on a little secret.
If you really want to become a top executive
at this company,
you've got to start
living like one.
(LAUGHING)
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
FRED: Yabba-dabba-doo!
Flintstones
Meet the Flintstones
They're the modern
Stone Age family
From the town of Bedrock
They're a page
right out of history
-Good afternoon, madam.
-Full serve, please.
Let's ride
With the family
down the street
Through the courtesy
of Fred's two feet
When you're
with the Flintstones
Have a yabba-dabba-doo time
A dabba-doo time
Oh, dear!
We'll have a gay old time
(DINO BARKING)
(DINO'S FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
(SQUEALING)
(Snorting Happily)
Good boy.
Good, Wilma! Use your arms.
Perfect. That's four.
Betty! Towel.
Keep going. Go eight.
Strong, tight. Go nine.
A yabba-dabba-doo time
SINGER: The Flintstones!
(ROARS)
We'll have a gay old
Time
Oh! (Yelling)
SINGER: Yeah!
(CRASHES)
Who said money
doesn't buy happiness?
But, Fred, isn't this all
too much too fast?
Wilma, in the buffet of life
there are no second helpings.
You gotta fill up your plate,
top off your cup,
-and stuff a few rolls in your pocket.
-(GIGGLES)
-WILMA: Fred, stop!
-(FRED CHUCKLING)
Mmm. Frisky!
(GIGGLES)
(FRED MURMURING)
You know, Barney, life's funny.
One minute people
are your best friends,
the next you're fantasizing
they're being ripped apart
by a pack of rabid wolves.
-You too, huh?
-Oh, Barney, they've changed.
I hardly know them
since Fred's become such a big shot.
And it should be us squanderin' all our money
and treatin' our friends like dirt.
-What do you mean?
-Oh, nothin'.
Just sour grapes, I guess.
Oh, don't worry, Barney.
It's gonna get better.
One day we're gonna look back on all this
and we'll laugh.
Jeez, I hope so, Betty,
'cause tomorrow
they got me testin' shark repellent.
-Mmm. Oh, Barney. Ooh.
-(HISSES)
-(YAWNS)
-(CLEARS THROAT)
Leaving early?
Actually, the wife and I were going to have
dinner tonight at Cavern on the Green.
Ooh, pricey. Be sure to put that
on your expense account.
Fred, before you go... (GRUNTS)
Would you mind chipping your "X"
on a couple of these?
Yeah, sure. What are they?
Well, you sign these
and your buddies down in the quarry
get some much-needed time off.
No kiddin'! I guess Mr. Slate finally noticed
all those memos I been sendin' in.
(CHUCKLES) I hope the guys will know
who's to thank for this.
I'll make sure
you get all the credit.
(CHUCKLING)
(GRUNTS) Mr. Flintstone,
up to now our relationship
has not been based on mutuality
of admiration or respect.
Huh?
Put simply, you hate my bird guts
and I think you're dumber than mud.
-Ah. Well, good night.
-Still, I wish to pass on an old dictum...
From business school
that may be apropos here.
Only an idiot signs something
before reading it.
Excuse me. I'm the executive,
you're the office equipment.
If I want to ask
the office equipment for advice,
-I'll ask the water cooler!
-(SQUAWKS)
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
the B.C.-52's!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, hey
Twitch!
Well, I know a place
where the hipsters go
Called Bedrock
Twitch, twitch
'Cause they're itching for it
down in prehistoric
Bedrock
Twitch, twitch
It's a funky town
so I'll see you down
called Bedrock, yeah
Oh, the Stone Age crowd
is twitching proud
In Bedrock
Twitch, twitch
They do the twitch
Twitch, twitch, come on
Twitch, twitch
Do it Come on, baby
Do it, do it, do it
Do the twitch like you got an itch, itch
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Itch, itch, itch, itch
Twitch!
-Thank you, Bedrock!
-(ALL CHEERING)
Thanks, everybody.
And remember, don't drink and pedal.
Good night!
How 'bout a spin, Betty?
No, thank you, Fred.
I'll wait till Barney gets here.
He started some new job today.
I'm not sure what time he gets done.
While we're waiting, how about
another carafe of the bubbly?
Garcon! Whoops.
Don't worry, Mr. Flintstone.
I'll have that taken care of right away.
(CHUCKLES)
Table seven, sonny.
(GASPS) Barney!
Barney, nice skins!
Sit down, take a load off!
-I can't, Fred. I'm working here.
-You're a busboy?
It's honest work.
Yeah, I don't have to fight Dino for my supper.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'll get you a fresh tablecloth, sir.
Wilma, you were worried
he'd never find a job and
we'd be stuck with him forever.
(CHUCKLING) Ow!
CROWD ON TV: Flintstone! Flintstone!
We want Flintstone!
The demonstration continues
to get uglier at Slate and Company
following the unexpected layoff
of virtually the entire labor force
by V.P. Fred Flintstone.
For the Cave News Network,
this is Susan Rock.
Fred, did you hear what happened
to everyone at the quarry today?
Yup. A few hours ago,
I sent them all off on a nice, long vacation.
You mean, a permanent vacation.
He fired them!
-(GASPS)
-Fred! How could you?
-I didn't do that.
-You did too! It's all over the TV!
Fred!
Who are you going to believe,
me or some busboy?
That busboy is
your best friend!
Best friend? I lost my best friend
the day I became an executive!
He's just jealous
of my hard-earned success.
Hard-earned? Tell me something,
Mr. Vice President,
what's a graduated
inventory plan, huh?
How about supply and demand?
Hey, Fred!
What's two and two?
I didn't come here to talk business.
I'm out with my wife.
Now,
get me a clean spoon.
That does it!
The only reason you got that job
is 'cause I switched tests with you.
-Oh, Barney.
-Oh-ho-ho, that's rich!
What good would it do me to switch tests
with the guy that got the lowest score?
-Think about it, Fred.
-Oh, finally it all makes sense.
You don't believe this, do you?
Are you calling my husband a liar?
This has gone far enough.
After everything that we've done for you.
We took you into our home.
Yeah? So you could show off
every chance you got!
(GASPS)
You used to be such
nice people, but now...
You're just a couple of rich snobs!
Better than being
a couple of petty ingrates.
Come on, Barney.
We are moving out, tonight!
Hang on, Betty.
I forgot to punch out.
-(SCREAMS)
-(BIRDS TWEETING)
(GRUNTING)
-Eh, put it up top.
-(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
Betty, please.
We can work it out.
We're all civilized people here.
It's too late, Wilma.
Come on, we all said things
that we didn't mean.
Speak for yourself.
Come on, Betty.
Time to hit the road.
Fred! Aren't you even
the least bit sorry?
Sure, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I ever met the little moocher.
-(GASPS)
-(BAMM-BAMM GROWLS)
Oh, Betty.
-Good-bye, Wilma.
-Oh.
(RAPID FOOTSTEPS)
They're gone.
(SIGHS)
I cannot believe you just sat there
and let them walk out of our lives.
At least I can walk around the
house in my underwear again.
That's more important
than 20 years of friendship?
It is on a hot day.
-(SIGHS)
-They were holding us back, Wilma.
We'll make new friends.
There's 4,000 other people in this world!
-Who needs the Rubbles?
-I do.
But I'll tell you
what I don't need.
I don't need this necklace.
-You know, I don't need this lamp.
-(GLASS BREAKING)
And I don't need this television set.
Not the TV!
I don't need this.
I don't think I'll be needing
any of this bone china.
(GROWLING)
Because I don't have
any friends to invite to dinner.
I don't think I'll be using
any of these cups or saucers.
You're gonna regret this.
It's gonna take you hours
to clean up this mess.
(GLASS BREAKS)
All right, Wilma.
Enough of this charade.
Come back now,
and I'll forgive ya. (CHUCKLES)
Oh, you're bluffin',
Wilma Slaghoople.
You're not going
to your mother's.
Once around the block,
you'll realize
the folly of your ways
and you'll come crawling back.
(QUIETLY) Please.
It's finally happened,
I've become my father.
Now, Barney,
don't talk like that.
-This place is fine for now.
-Come on, Betty.
We're living downwind
from a family of wild boars.
-Face it. We've hit rock bottom.
-Hmm.
Come here, little guy.
Can you say da-da?
Say da-da.
-Bamm-Bamm!
-Oh.
It doesn't really matter where we live,
as long as we're together.
Family hug!
-(LOUD ROAR)
-(BOTH GASPING)
(ROARING CONTINUES)
-Betty?
-Hmm?
-Exactly where did you get those eggs?
-(WHINES)
Sorry.
-I think it might be twins.
-(ROARS)
(ALL YELLING)
There he is!
(YELLING CONTINUES)
You're a traitor, Flintstone!
-Listen to me. I'm your friend.
-You're no friend of ours!
You're a rotten bowler too!
Good morning, Mr. Flint...
They made a fool of me.
Look what they had to work with.
(LAUGHING)
(SQUAWKS)
Flintstone, heard you were down
in the file room.
Find anything interesting?
Yeah! I'm on to your little scam.
Billing phony companies
and keeping the money for yourself.
-I'm going to Mr. Slate.
-Good idea.
Turning yourself in
might buy you a little leniency.
-Me? This entire scheme was your idea.
-True.
But I've graciously
decided to give you all the credit,
since it's your name
on the requisitions.
I never touched
any of that money!
Hmm. Fred, please.
Remodeling your house, furs, jewelry,
a fully-equipped Le Sabertooth.
Tsk, tsk, tsk. You should
have been more discreet.
I'm innocent!
Oh, boo-hoo-hoo.
Miss Stone, call security.
Tell them we've
uncovered an embezzler.
Miss Stone, you'll back me up, won't ya?
You better run while you still have a chance.
You'll never get away with this.
I already have.
(SIGHS)
Here comes the pterodactyl.
-Mmm-mmm-mmm.
-It's no use, Mother.
She misses Fred.
-(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
-I hope it's not that pesky Avrok lady again.
(GASPS) Oh!
-Betty!
-Oh.
-Bamm-Bamm!
-WILMA: I have missed you so much.
I don't care what Barney said.
I couldn't let you go through this alone.
-Have you heard from Fred?
-No.
I spoke to a lawyer.
If he's missing seven years,
you can remarry.
Mother!
Well, wherever Fred is,
I hope he knows I still love him.
Oh.
POLICE RADIO: Calling all Bedrock units,
all Bedrock units.
Tonight, in a special edition
of Bedrock's Most Wanted,
we bring you the story
that's rocked our city,
"The Case of the Embezzling Executive."
WOMAN: Mr. Flintstone, what are you doing?
I'm an executive.
I'm embezzling.
I'm shocked!
How could you ever
marry that man?
Mother! That man is not my husband.
That's right. He plays Dr. Gravelman
on The Young And The Thumbless.
Fred might be a lot of things
but a thief is not one of them.
-Can he prove it?
-MAN ON TV: Who cares?
Yabba-dabba-dabba!
ANNOUNCER: This menace
remains at large...
We ask the public's help in apprehending...
Maybe I can.
(PIG MOANS)
A little something to take that chill off.
Take a swig of this.
Put hair on your knuckles.
(CHUCKLES)
Tell me something... You one of those guys
that was laid off at the stone quarry?
I used to work there.
A lot of guys here would like
to get their hands
on the guy who's responsible for all this.
-So they could hear his side of the story?
-What? His side of the story?
-(LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
Huh?
Flintstone!
(PIG SQUEALING)
It is! Flintstone!
(ALL YELLING)
Squealer!
Get him!
MISS STONE: Just think.
This time tomorrow,
we'll be on a pterodactyl winging our...
-Oh, Cliff.
-Hmm?
How come there's only
one ticket to Rocapulco?
For your protection, darling.
I thought I would go on a "business trip,"
while you stay here to keep up
appearances.
Then, when we're sure it's safe,
I'll send for you.
Forgive me, Cliff.
Looks like you've
thought of everything.
(SNORING)
-(SNORING CONTINUES)
-Psst. Excuse me!
-Hello.
-No, Mumsie, I don't want to go to school.
The other boys
make fun of me.
-Wake up!
-(SQUAWKS)
Oh, Mrs. Flintstone.
To what do I owe the honor of this break-in?
I need your help,
Mr. Bird.
You hear everything
that goes on in this office.
Hmm-hmm.
You are the only one who can help
clear my husband.
What a delicious irony.
Thank you for sharing it with me.
Now, let me share something with you.
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
Oh, now, Wilma, calm down.
-Maybe I can reason with him.
-Ow!
There. All set.
You know, my only regret is
I won't be around...
when that shoddy new equipment blows up
in their big, dumb faces.
Oh, well, I'll just have to console myself
with all that money.
-(WHISPERING)
-Hey, who's that?
-(WHISPERING CONTINUES)
-MISS STONE: That's Flintstone's wife.
What would she want with a stinky old dict...
Son of a brachiosaurus!
Well, Cliff. I guess you haven't thought
of everything.
Oh, this is far from over.
(CROWD YELLING)
MAN: String him up!
You can't do this.
I was framed!
-In a minute you're going to be boxed.
-(CROWD CHEERING)
-(MUSIC PLAYS)
-Anybody want a snow cone?
-Barney!
-Fred!
-What are you doing here?
-I'm getting lynched!
Oh. I got cherry, lime, rocky road.
Do you know this guy?
Know him? He used
to be my best friend.
In a way, if it wasn't for me,
this whole mess
probably wouldn't have happened.
Thanks for filling us in.
We could've made a very big mistake here.
-Hang both of 'em.
-What?
Gee, take it easy.
They make you pay for your own uniforms.
Barney, I thought
you came to save me.
Save you? I saw a crowd,
I figured I'd sell a few snow cones.
-You mean you haven't forgiven me yet?
-Nope.
And frankly, I don't think
this is going to help.
-I took a cherry.
-I can't break a 20.
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait a minute!
Look, Barn, I know you're still
a little mad at me.
But I want you to know, if I had to have
someone hanging next to me,
I'm glad it's you.
I guess switchin' them tests didn't turn out
much like I planned, huh, Fred?
Hey, got any lemon?
Check in the back.
Gee, why can't business
be this good every day?
The story of my life.
-I'm a loser.
-No, you're not.
This makes me a winner?
No, but you're the best friend
a guy ever had
and that makes you a winner
in my book, pal.
Me...
I'm just a big jerk.
Ah, everybody loves you, Fred.
Except for this lynch mob.
Ah, Barn.
Ah, Fred.
You'll have plenty of time
to bond in the afterlife.
(CROWD CHEERING)
-(GASPS) Wilma, look!
-(GASPING)
(FEET ACCELERATING)
(HORN HONKING)
-(HORN HONKING CONTINUES)
-Watch out for that tree!
-(CROWD MURMURING)
-Now wait, everybody.
Fred is innocent.
Barney, do you have to do
everything Fred does? (GIGGLES)
Everybody,
listen to him.
First things first.
I demand an apology.
-I'm sorry!
-Not you, him.
Me? Apologize to a bird?
Not Fred Flintstone! (CHUCKLING)
I had hoped we might be
colleagues but instead,
you've treated me as if I were
an ordinary piece of office furniture.
I may eat bugs, but I have feelings,
Mr. Flintstone.
(SOBBING) And you've hurt them.
CROWD: Aww.
Uh, well, look, I know I could've been
a little more sensitive.
-Especially when you were molting.
-(GASPS) Oh.
So, I'm...sorry.
I don't think they heard you in the back.
-I'm sorry.
-DICTABIRD: Pardon?
-(LOUDLY) I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
-Oh.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Now, then, gather 'round, everyone.
I'll tell you the tale
of an unsophisticated man
caught up in a treacherous web of power,
deceit and lust.
-(CROWD MURMURING)
-Ooh, yeah.
WILMA: Why is the door open?
-Betty, the door is open!
-Wilma, something's wrong!
(WHIMPERING)
-Pebbles!
-Bamm-Bamm!
(WHIMPERING CONTINUES)
What kind of madman
would do something like this?
(MUFFLED YELLING)
-(WHIMPERING)
-That's a poor poochie.
-(SCREAMING)
-That's a baby.
(WHIMPERING LOUDLY)
-Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm are gone!
-They left this.
-BARNEY: It's a note.
-If you want to see your kids again,
-bring the Dictabird to the
quarry at dawn. No police.
(GASPS)
-Mr. Flintstone.
-(DICTABIRD GASPS)
Stealing office equipment, really.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Is this the kind of example you want to set
for your daughter?
-Where are the kids?
-The bird, please.
(SQUAWKS)
-First, we want our children.
-Of course.
-(SCREAMS)
-Bamm-Bamm!
Take one more step, Mr. Rubble,
and this quarry's safety record
will be severely tarnished.
Now, give me the bird.
Go on, Fred.
Give him what he wants.
-What?
-Don't worry, I got a plan.
We're gonna get the kids back
and then we'll rescue you.
What a strategist.
I should have signed with Disney.
They never would've allowed
this sort of thing to happen. (SIGHS)
-Ahh! Thank you, gentlemen.
-Easy.
And in the words of
my beloved mother,
I'm taking the money
and moving to a warmer climate.
(CHUCKLES)
PEBBLES: Help, Daddy!
DICTABIRD: Let's discuss this, Cliff.
May I call you Cliff?
(GRUNTING) Barney, too much pressure.
(GRUNTING) One, two, three...
(YELLING)
BOTH: Nice goin'.
-Now what do we do?
-You get the kids, I'll try and stop this.
Whoa!
(CACKLING)
Cliffy, have I ever told you
you have a very distinguished chin?
Shut up!
Aah!
Whoa!
-(GROANS)
-Yo, ow, ow, ow, ow!
-(HEAVY BREATHING) Oh, dear, oh, dear.
-(GRUNTS)
Too many years behind a desk.
Mayday, mayday!
-Hi, Da-da.
-(GASPS)
You did it!
You called me da-da!
-(BOTH GASPING)
-Oh, Barney, you lunkhead!
(LOUD SQUAWKING)
What am I going to do?
I gotta think of somethin'.
(SCREAMING)
(CHUCKLING) Not now.
Wake up, Uncle Barney!
Help, help!
Save me! Save me from this mad M.B.A.!
-Don't worry. I'll take care of him.
-My hero.
Yipes.
Flintstone, kiss your bird good-bye.
Oh, mama.
(GROANS)
Will there be anything else, Mr. Flintstone?
No, Miss Stone.
Take the rest of the day off.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
Yabba-dabba-doo!
Cliff?
It's time for you and me
to interface.
-Aah!
-Stee-rike!
(SIRENS WAILING)
(SCREAMS)
And then, Cliff said,
"True. But I've graciously decided
to give you all the credit,
since it's your name on all
the requisition forms."
Mr. Flintstone,
I may not be in on Monday.
Don't worry, Miss Stone.
I'll tell 'em what you did.
-They'll let you off easy.
-I've been a very bad girl.
But you have to admit,
I was very,
very good at it.
Come on, do it for Mommy.
Who am I?
-Bamm-Bamm!
-Oh.
Thank goodness,
you're all right.
Well, I'm not going to jail,
but it won't be easy getting a new job.
What kind of reference
is Mr. Slate gonna give me
after I destroyed his quarry?
None of this was your fault.
Mr. Slate will understand.
Flintstone!
Sure, now he gets
my name right.
How did this happen?
Mr. Slate, it all started when the Rubbles here
wanted to adopt a baby.
Not that!
How did this
happen to Cliff?
FLINTSTONE: Well, you see, Mr. Slate,
the machinery went haywire
and the rocks got all crushed up
and that got mixed in with water
and that came all down the hill.
-Mr. Slate, I'm sorry!
-Sorry?
I love this stuff!
I'm gonna name it after
my daughter Concretia.
Flintstone, you're a genius!
Me? Really? Why?
Don't you see? Thanks to concrete,
man can now shape his own destiny.
-The Stone Age is over!
-Ahh.
First thing, I want you
to hire back all the men, Flintstone.
-We're going into production immediately.
-We?
That's right.
You are hereby promoted to President
of the entire concrete division.
Yabba...
That's a real nice offer, Mr. Slate,
but unfortunately,
I'm gonna have to turn you down.
Don't listen to him, Mr. Slate.
Fred, it's a great job!
This time, you deserve it.
Barney, all my life
I wanted to be a somebody.
And when I finally did,
I turned into somebody I didn't like.
Good grief, man,
have you lost your mind?
This could make you rich
beyond your wildest dreams.
I was always the richest man in the world.
-I just never knew it.
-(SIGHS)
So, if it's okay with you, Mr. Slate,
all I want is my old job back
and my old life.
Fred. (WHISPERING)
And two weeks paid vacation
for all the men in the quarry,
an annual cost of livin' increase
and those little packets
of ketchup in the lunchroom.
Done!
Thanks, boss.
See you at the company picnic.
There goes the best
executive I ever had.
-Fred, I'm so proud of you.
-And I'm proud of you, Barney.
-I'm starving!
-Me too!
What do you say we get some breakfast.
Snake and eggs for everybody.
-My treat.
-Great.
Barney...
-Yeah, Fred?
-Spot me a couple bucks? I'm a little short.
-Not this time!
-What?
-(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
-(DINOSAUR CHUCKLING)
Flintstones
Meet the Flintstones
They're a modern
Stone Age family
From the
town of Bedrock
They're a page
right out of history
Someday maybe
Fred will win the fight
Then that cat will
stay out for the night
When you're with the Flintstones
Have a yabba-dabba-doo time
A dabba-doo time
We'll have a gay old time
Wilma!
Yabba-dabba-doo!
Flintstones
Meet the Flintstones
They're the modern
Stone Age family
From the
town of Bedrock
They're a page
right out of history
Let's ride with the family down the street
Through the courtesy
of Fred's two feet
When you're with the Flintstones
Have a yabba-dabba-doo time
A dabba-doo time
We'll have a gay old time
(DINO BARKING)
MAN: The Flintstones!
Flintstones
Meet the Flintstones
They're the modern
Stone Age family
From the
town of Bedrock
They're a page
right out of history
Someday maybe
Fred will win the fight
Then that cat will
stay out for the night
When you're
with the Flintstones
Have a yabba-dabba-doo time
A dabba-doo time
We'll have a gay old time
Yeah!
Yabba-dabba-doo!
I was travelin' to Earth
and what did I spot
A little village by the water
Sign said Bedrock
I met this kid named Fred
He didn't wear no socks
He had a part-time gig
at the Gravel Pit slingin' rocks
Said he was into hip hop
Could he kick a spell I told him go for it
But at first said what you think
I said you're style is prehistoric
Sounds stuck in the Stone Age
You're still using a hammer and chisel
Carving out your lyrics
on stone pages
It's about time you heard a style from a real
before-the-wheel rapper
Set it off and he said yabba-dabba-doo
Then he got to prove
The fella's suddenly standing
In the middle of a crowd of K drummers
Sayin' tell us how you flipped
the script and ripped
I get busy one time They said yeah
yeah I'm hip, I'm hip
Didn't know the time
Didn't know about fly
So I, you know, I had to show
a Cave Man how to rock
In the Stone Age
I showed a Cave Man
how to rock
Yabba-dabba-doo!
In the Stone Age
I showed a Cave Man
how to rock
Yabba-dabba-doo!
Barney Rubble
Fred Flintstone
Hey, Freddie boy
Don't try to get too close
I don't want to catch
a man with those
We'll meet at
the Bedrock disco
Who cares that I got T. Rex
On my radio
On this prehistoric day
I feel duty-bound to say
Before I reach
my destination
On this prehistoric day
I feel duty-bound to say
I owes an explanation
Give me one good reason
Give me two good reasons
Give me three good reasons
Why's men do what they do
Yabba-dabba-doo Yabba-dabba-doo
Yabba-dabba-doo
Anarchy in Bedrock
Stop in some time
and meet Betty and Wilma
Try some Flint upside-down
Rubble bubble cake
Or just try
Fruity Pebbles
'Cause I
Wanna be
Fred Flintstone
Is this the U.S.D.A.
Is this Hollywood
Is this Bedrock
I thought it was Hollyrock
'Cause I
Wanna be
Fred Flintstone
Yabba-dabba-doo
Wilma!