Del Rio.
I've got a weird call
from a US citizen in Taiwan.
A young woman calling to tip us off
about a big drugs ring.
- I'll take it.
- I'll tape you.
Hello?
Good morning.
That's him! Pick him up.
Come with me, please.
Hello.
Sir, come with us.
Welcome to Rome.
Good morning, sir.
Please, follow me. This way.
Yeah, sure.
Del Rio.
Thanks for calling me back.
We took delivery
of your package.
Thanks very much.
I'll send you the paperwork
for the transfer.
Bye.
Okay, we got all three.
Could you bring some champagne
to the girl over there?
Yeah, I just have a nosebleed.
With a scar
on her lower abdomen?
Pretty recent,
with thread in it.
- How is she?
- Fine. She's sleeping.
With the shot I gave her,
she'll be out all day.
- She's awake!
- Are you sure?
She's sitting on the bed.
That's her.
- You didn't restrain her?
- Sure, we did!
Don't leave the car there.
Park it up.
I got you bacon...
Kill her and get the pouch.
Don't stand there, kill her!
Move!
Follow that car.
Boss, 5 men down at the hospital.
Sorry.
How many men left?
I have about 25 with me.
That damn girl,
she doesn't give in.
She's a witch.
I know that.
I'll kill her myself.
Speed it up.
Search the whole building
and find her!
Chong-Ju!
I'm here, boss.
Do something about them.
Okay, boss!
You guys, come on.
Ready?
You Okay?
Get a medic. Fast!
Where is she?
Answer me.
Answer me!