Two o'clock in Memphis WHBQ.
George TCBing
with August Super Tuesday.
The man says H and H,
hot and humid all afternoon, now 92.
The heart and soul
of rock 'n' roll going for 97.
- Ricky! Son!
- What?
Come back here.
Won't be back till late.
I want you in by dark.
I want you to watch out for your brother.
- I can watch out for myself.
- Can not.
Don't worry, Mom, I'll take care of him.
How come you always have
to watch out for me?
Because I'm older, stupid.
Mom, he's calling me stupid.
Would y'all hush up?
Don't be reading any more
of them scary comics.
- You hear me, Ricky?
- Whatever.
He can't sleep.
Shoot, I'm gonna miss my bus.
I'm gonna be late again.
I'm gonna get docked for sure.
There's some macaroni and cheese
in the cabinet, okay?
All right.
- Got your lunch?
- Thank you, baby.
Keys?
Oh, yeah.
Exact change for the bus?
Oh, shoot, baby. Thank you.
I'd forget my head
if it wasn't screwed on.
- You stay out of them woods.
- Okay, Mom.
You hear me, Mark?
Bye, baby.
- Come on, Mark, give me a cigarette.
- No way.
Mark, wait.
- Catch me and I'll give you one.
- I can't run that fast.
Catch me.
Wait up, Mark.
Better hurry or you'll
never get your smoke.
We're not supposed to go in the woods.
Go home, I'll smoke them myself.
Come get me.
- Come on.
- Wait up, Mark.
Come on, Ricky. Catch me.
Come on, give me one.
No way, pal.
I'll tell Mom.
Tattletale.
- You know the deal.
- Yeah. If I tell anyone, you'll kick my ass.
That's right. And if I catch you smoking
more than one a day...
- I know, you'll kick my ass again.
- That's right.
- How many do you smoke a day?
- Only one. I'm smart.
- Will one a day kill me?
- Nah!
Not any time soon, but more than that
and you could be in deep shit.
- How many does Mom smoke?
- Forty.
- And what about Dad?
- A hundred a day.
Oh, he's gonna die soon?
I wish. Sit there.
Don't try to swallow the smoke yet,
because I know you're not ready for that.
You'll just choke
and puke all over the place.
Suck a little and blow.
Told you not to swallow the smoke.
This is easy.
Yeah, that's why you look
like you're gonna puke.
Do not.
Where's he going?
What's he doing?
Damn, damn.
Damn.
Damn. Goddamn it.
Son of a bitch.
Jesus Christ, he's trying to kill himself.
How do you know?
I seen it on TV once.
- Why do you think he wants to kill himself?
- How am I supposed to know, stupid?
- Well, let's get the hell out of here.
- No.
You stay here. Okay?
If you move, I'll kick your ass.
What are you gonna do?
Mark.
- Come on, let's go.
- No. We gotta make sure he's okay.
- Think he's dead?
- Don't know.
Damn.
Nothing works. Nothing works.
He is crazy as hell.
Damn it. Damn.
- Let's go, please. Come on.
- No, we can't.
If he kills himself and we know anything about
it, we can be in all kinds of bullshit.
We won't tell no one.
- Just let him die.
- We're not leaving till I say we're leaving.
- Stay down, Mark.
- Stay here.
Mark.
Let him die.
You bastard.
You bastard!
Come on.
- Get in there. Get in there.
- No.
Get in there.
I said get...
Don't you touch that damn door!
Sorry, kid.
You had to be a cute ass.
Had to stick your dirty little nose
in my business, didn't you?
So I think we should die together.
Just you and me, pal. Off to la-la land.
Sweet dreams.
- You want that gun?
- No, sir.
- Why you looking at it?
- I wasn't, sir.
Don't you lie to me!
I'm crazy. If you lie to me, I'll kill you.
Please don't kill me, sir.
I got my mother and my little brother
to take care of.
I'll give you a choice.
I can blow your brains out...
and end it now...
or we could wait and let the gas do it.
You decide.
What's your name?
Mark. Mark Sway.
Jerome Clifford.
Attorney at law.
So since we're both
pretty tight right now...
you can call me Romey.
Listen. Hear that bird?
I drove all the way from New Orleans
to hear those stupid birds. Grew up here.
I played in these woods.
Now I'm gonna die here too.
Why are you doing this?
Because if I don't kill myself, he will.
- Who's he?
- The Blade.
Barry "The Blade" Muldano.
Why does this Blade guy wanna kill you?
Because I know...
I know where
the proverbial body is buried.
Whose body?
See, my client killed
Senator Boyd Boyette...
and hid the body.
So now my client, he wants to kill me.
You know where the body's buried?
The body's buried...
He hid the body...
He's still buried there,
can you believe it?
They haven't found it yet.
FBI's dug up half of New Orleans.
They haven't found it,
they're not gonna find it, no way.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, Mark, go for it.
Yeah, Mark, go ahead.
Go ahead, Mark, pull the trigger.
Yeah. Pull the trigger.
Pull the goddamn trigger! Pull it!
Pull the trigger!
Pull it!
Pretty nifty piece?
Hell, I don't even know if it works.
Let's see if it works.
It works!
- Shit.
- It works. Hey, get over here!
- Ricky.
- I told you not to go anywhere!
Ricky, damn you, come on.
Hey, Mark! Son of a bitch.
Hey!
Where are you?
Goddamn kid!
Hey!
Mark!
Come back here, kid!
If the Blade finds out what I told you,
he's gonna kill you anyway.
You hear me, kid?
Mark, where are you?
- Put my drink on my bill, babe.
- All right.
Come on, boys, dance with me.
I've been waiting a half hour.
Where the hell's Romey?
- Damn feds are on my ass.
- God, Mr. Muldano.
I don't know.
He hasn't been in here all day.
Now, Claudette, God hates a liar.
That's what my mother always said.
I'm not lying, honest to God,
I haven't seen him.
I don't know where he is.
You know, Claudette...
you're a very pretty woman.
Well, thank you, Mr. Muldano.
You wanna stay pretty, don't you?
Oh, please.
I'm just a secretary.
Listen, honest to God,
I don't know where he is.
He doesn't always tell me
where he's going...
Put your hand in there.
Put your hand in here!
I don't... I don't know. Honest to...
Put your hand in. Come on, put it in.
Please. I don't know where he is.
Come on.
Mr. Muldano.
You know, Claudette, I believe
you really didn't know where he was.
- Lift.
- Get another sample here.
Damn.
What's inside here?
- Is this something here?
- Check the hood.
Take a look at this.
- There you go.
- Watch yourself.
Bring it on through here.
What's up, kid?
What are you so scared of?
Did you have a bad dream?
You're scaring your mama.
Get your thumb out of your...
Come on, baby. Talk to your mama.
Where have you been?
What the hell is wrong with your brother?
What have you done now?
What the hell is going on?
- Boy witnessed a suicide, ma'am.
- He what?
Oh, well, me and Ricky was just
out in the woods playing...
and we seen this guy and he was dead
and he had a gun in his mouth.
Oh, my dear God.
And I ran home and called 911.
What happened to Ricky?
He just laid on the bed and started
sucking his thumb and wouldn't talk.
This is Sergeant Hardy. We need the
paramedics over here at Sway's trailer now.
This boy needs to be hospitalized.
I don't have health insurance.
That's okay,
St. Peter's will take indigent cases.
- Pack some things for the hospital tonight.
- What, like clothes? What?
You telling the truth, son?
About what you all saw.
Don't you believe me?
I didn't say I didn't believe you.
Just seems strange, that's all.
You called 911,
but you wouldn't leave your name.
Well, I was scared.
It was the first dead guy I ever saw.
Why'd you sneak back and hide
up in the woods where I found you?
I don't know.
I just wanted to see, I guess.
Did you talk to the man
before he killed himself?
No, I never talked to him.
Name "Jerome Clifford"
mean anything to you?
No.
You know, I found some
fresh cigarette butts near the body.
Same brand as your mama smokes.
Somehow I can't see you finding the body
and then deciding to have a cigarette.
Look, officer, all that happened was
we was just walking through the woods...
when we found Romey dead. That's all.
- Who's Romey?
- That's the guy's name, isn't it?
I said, Jerome Clifford.
Whoever heard of the name Romey?
I'm Dr. Greenway. Is this your son?
Yeah, he's my son.
- What's his name?
- Ricky Sway.
- How long has he been this way?
- I didn't find him, my other boy, Mark, did.
You found him, Mark? Ricky?
Is that what you called him? Ricky?
Jerome R. Clifford,
New Orleans attorney, was found dead...
in an apparent suicide
outside Memphis just hours ago.
The famed Mafia lawyer was due
to defend the alleged Mafia hit man...
Barry "The Blade" Muldano
next month...
in the increasingly notorious case
of still-missing Louisiana senator...
Boyd Boyette, now presumed dead.
It was going to be tough...
to build a case against Muldano
without a body...
but surely Clifford's death
will mean more delays.
As one informed source tells me...
the plot thickens and sickens
for U.S. Attorney Roy Foltrigg.
No body, no case, no conviction.
And that means no front-page pictures
that Attorney Foltrigg likes so much.
No CNN interviews,
no speedy ascent to Capitol Hill.
Sorry, Reverend Roy.
- I never liked that old cow.
- We're here, Roy.
He tried it first with a garden hose attached
to the tailpipe, but it didn't work.
He was probably too stoned.
He was full of downers
and about a gallon of whiskey.
Guess he figured he'd swallow a bullet
for dessert. Single gunshot to the head.
- Cheap snub-nosed .38.
- A definite suicide, Roy.
Damn him.
I called Romey two days ago, I said:
"I have enough evidence
to pierce client-attorney privilege...
and put your fat ass on the stand."
I was bullshitting him, of course.
I was trying to get him nervous,
see if he'd talk.
Didn't know he'd blow his scalp off.
He must've known where that body's at.
Oh, he's never gonna tell us now.
Without that body we got no case.
- How's the weather in Memphis?
- It's hot, Roy.
Sprite?
- What happened to your face?
- I got in a fight at school.
It's summer. There's no school.
I meant, a kid from my school.
- Who was the kid?
- Why?
Why? Because I'm a cop.
It's my job to ask questions.
Besides, I think your
story's full of holes.
I believe you were in that car
before Clifford died.
What does "indigent" mean?
Indigent?
That means "poor."
Like you and your mother
and your little brother.
So you better tell the truth...
hope it snaps him out of it.
Otherwise...
he could lie in some institution
for dirt-poor crazy people...
with padded walls and cockroaches...
and chained to some filthy bed
with snakes...
Mark...
I'm Karen. Will you come with me?
- Bye.
- We're gonna have to watch him.
- What are you gonna do?
We're just gonna watch for
now. Sometimes just a good night's sleep...
and they wake up,
they don't know what's going on.
His reflexes seem to be good.
- That's good.
- Yeah.
Mark, honey, Ricky's real sick.
- What's the matter with him?
- It's called post-traumatic stress syndrome.
Sometimes a person sees something
they just can't deal with.
I'm always telling Mark,
"No horror movies. No scary comics."
Not for Ricky.
- He's always been tender that way.
- Easy, now.
You try to protect them,
there's just so bad out there.
Why don't you get some rest
yourself? Why don't you lie down and rest?
There's nothing more you can do.
We're just gonna watch him.
You've had a rough day.
Just lie down in here. Stay with him.
Boy, that's a bad injury. What happened?
Car wreck. Got hit by an oil truck.
Nut run a stop sign.
My name's Gill Beale, I'm a lawyer.
You got a problem, I can fix it.
I specialize in car wrecks,
especially large trucks.
Let's see what you got. A broken leg,
a concussion, a couple of busted ribs...
- And a broken collarbone.
- Great.
I can get you at least 600,000.
We'll file suit tomorrow.
Did I say six? Six is just for starters.
Here, check me out.
Call up Gill Beale,
you'll see who's for real.
More lawyers around this place
than there are doctors.
Now, don't be that way. I'm gonna
outrun that little buggy of yours.
- Wait till you get a load of this guy.
- All right.
Mr. Foltrigg, Jason McThune, FBI.
Welcome to Memphis, home of the king.
City of the good abode.
What do you know, McThune?
Kid's name is Mark Sway. He told Memphis
P.D. that he and his younger brother...
just stumbled on the body in the woods,
and then ran and called the cops.
- I think he's lying.
- Why's that?
We lifted his prints off a Sprite can...
they match prints that
were all over the car, inside and out.
I think he was in that car
before Clifford shot himself.
And he was there for a while
because of the number of prints.
- Why would the kid lie?
- One, he's scared.
Two, he's a kid, they always lie.
Adults are the enemy.
And three, maybe Romey Clifford told him
something he knows he should not know.
People hate to die with secrets.
That's good work, McThune.
Thank you very much, sir.
I'm gonna keep it up, believe me.
Listen, I'm sick and tired of chasing
Elvis sightings.
I wanna get out of here.
Is there any room on your staff?
- Where you wanna go?
- Anywhere you go.
Gotta do something
about that hair first.
Yes, sir.
- Meantime, I wanna talk to that child.
- Right away, sir.
Dr. Greenway wants to see you.
How old are you?
Twenty-four. Why?
Are you married?
Sometimes.
I don't know nothing,
but he looks better to me.
I think if we get him home and get him
in his own bed, he's gonna be fine.
I don't know why you just can't...
- Mrs. Sway.
- ...give him some medicine or something.
Can't you just give him a shot
or something? I gotta go to work.
- Our trailer park takes rent by the week.
- Listen to me.
Right now, it's as if Ricky's in a dark
place and he's trying to find the way out.
Now, what's very
important... Listen to me.
What's very important
is that when he finds that way out...
the first thing he sees is your face.
Let's hope it'll only take a day or two.
There goes another job. Must be
damn near setting some kind of record.
I'll call your employer,
I'm sure he's gonna understand...
My employer runs a sweatshop, doctor.
He will not send flowers.
He will not understand.
You could take shifts.
- Perhaps the father could come in...?
- Ex-father.
And you keep him away from Ricky.
- Now hush.
- Okay, Mom, I'm sorry.
I don't know if you've seen this...
but there are policemen downstairs
and reporters.
The FBI is coming
to interview Mark at 10.
Mom, I don't wanna talk to them.
I'm gonna wind up like Ricky
if they don't stop bugging me.
- They're not gonna go away.
- I don't give a flying shit about the FBI.
- You are getting on my last nerve.
- Mrs. Sway...
Would you sit down and hush up?
I don't know what the hell to do.
- Can I see you outside?
- I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Telling me to wait for my boy to...
Some crap.
Mom?
- This boy.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I'll think of something
to get us out of this, I promise.
Hey. You and Ricky just found
that guy dead.
Right?
Come on now, there's nothing
you ain't telling me, is there?
Dr. Greenway wants to start you on Valium,
Mrs. Sway.
Those cost extra?
Yeah, don't worry about that,
just take these here.
- Both of them?
- Both of them.
You're gonna start feeling better.
- Don't go far.
- Okay, Mom.
FBI?
You know, I hear that they're sending
the Reverend Roy Foltrigg himself.
That's bad. That's...
You know that the FBI...
puts kids in jail if they break the law?
And if a kid has been involved
in a murder...
they got a special little
kid-sized electric chair.
I saw it once. It was about... so high.
Did you know that when somebody gets
electrocuted, the current is so strong...
it makes the blood in the veins boil.
God.
Fry you up just like a piece of bacon.
You're the only pig around here.
See you later, Markus.
Are you here to question Mark Sway?
I beg your pardon?
Are you here in Memphis...
to improve your own position
regarding the case, sir?
My real interest is to see justice done.
Every one of you knows that about me.
Are you ever gonna find that body?
We're gonna locate the senator's body.
You can count on that.
What do you think Mark Sway knows?
You ain't gonna run here by yourself.
- What do you want, boy?
- I need to see Mr. Beale.
- Where are your parents?
- Where are yours?
- Are you even injured?
- Do I look injured?
Well, we only do injuries.
Well, I'll just go get hit by a truck
and come back.
You all shut up too.
- Yes?
- Hell, no.
What the hell's wrong
with this damn window?
Where you going?
I'm gonna pick up something to eat
and then swing by the post office.
All right.
Hey. When's your boss coming back?
May I help you?
No, I need to see Reggie Love.
Why, may I ask?
Well, that's between me and Mr. Love.
I'm Reggie Love.
Pssh, a woman lawyer, oh, great.
I think so. Now, why is it
you think you want a lawyer?
I don't want a lawyer. I hate lawyers.
Every lawyer I ever had
just shafted me and my mom.
I said I need a lawyer.
But I don't know about no woman.
Well, this lawyer that shafted you,
what was her name?
It wasn't no her, it was a he.
Right.
Well, why is it that you think
you need a lawyer?
- Because I'm Mark Sway.
- So?
You know, the kid who found the dead guy.
I'm famous. Don't you read the paper?
You still haven't answered my question.
Because I'm supposed to talk to some
Reverend Roy guy in 10 minutes.
- Reverend Roy Foltrigg?
- Yeah, why's everybody call him that?
He loves to quote the scriptures
in court...
and knows the Bible
better than God himself.
- Does he win a lot?
- Always.
Why can't everyone just leave me alone?
Some sweaty fat guy blows his head off...
- Why did you lie to the police?
- I didn't.
Well, it says here in this paper
that you found Jerome Clifford dead.
I did.
Dead men don't sweat, now do they?
If you was my lawyer...
and I told you something,
could you ever repeat it?
No. What is it you wanna tell me?
Well, that Clifford guy came driving up
in his big black car...
and me and Ricky, we snuck up to watch,
and that Clifford guy got out...
and he put a gun in his mouth
and he blew the back of his head out.
So you did see Jerome Clifford alive?
- Yeah.
- Why'd you lie to the police?
I don't know.
I mean, I was just scared, I guess.
My little brother's in a coma
and my mom might lose her job.
The FBI's after me
but I don't know nothing.
You would lie too.
Well, you're right,
you do need a lawyer, Mark Sway.
There are a few male lawyers down the hall.
You want me to recommend one?
- How many cases have you won?
- More than I lost.
- How much do you cost?
- How much you got?
Nine thirty-two. Our boy has arrived.
Thank God your mother,
my sister, is dead, Barry.
Having a son this stupid
would have killed her for sure.
I told you not to hit Boyette, you did.
I told you not to tell Romey too much,
you did.
I hope it hurt that fat bastard.
I hope that bullet was slow.
I hope he felt the top of his head
pull right off his face.
Two kids found him, Barry,
maybe before he finished the job.
- Yeah, I know, I seen it on TV.
- There's a chance he might have talked.
Tell me Boyette's body's somewhere
the cops can't find.
The cops are not gonna find the body.
Move the body, Barry.
I will, Uncle Johnny.
Only I can't right now.
Why?
Where it's at, the body,
the cops are swarming all over the place.
Don't worry,
they're not gonna find the body.
If that kid knows anything, he's not talking,
otherwise I wouldn't be standing here.
I'm going to Memphis
and I'm gonna take care of those kids.
I'll tell you what you do.
You just sit on your dumb ass.
Gronke.
I want you in Memphis.
Come.
Oh, you must be Mark.
Hi, Mark.
Jason McThune, Memphis FBI.
This is Larry Trumann
from New Orleans FBI.
This is Thomas Fink,
assistant United States attorney...
and Mr. Foltrigg,
United States attorney.
Both from southern Louisiana.
Sit down, son.
- Come on over here, Mark. Sit down.
- There you are.
We expected your mother. Where is she?
She's upstairs with my little brother.
She can't leave in case he wakes up.
But, you know, we could hold
this off for a couple of days.
No, Mark,
let's talk a few minutes, just us.
- You nervous?
- A little.
- Do I need a lawyer?
- What for?
To protect my rights.
No, you been watching too much TV.
We just wanna ask you some questions.
You can trust us.
Lawyers just get in the way.
They object to everything.
What if I don't answer your questions?
We might have to take you downtown.
Might take your mother too.
- Will my mother get in trouble?
- Maybe.
You ever hear of obstruction of justice,
Mark? It's a federal offense.
It means if a man knows something
about a crime...
and withholds information from the FBI
or the police, well, he might be punished.
You know,
sent to jail or something like that.
So what you're trying to say is, is if I don't
answer your questions, I could go to jail?
Maybe.
Gosh, man, if y'all was in my place,
wouldn't y'all want a lawyer?
Hell no, they're a pain in the ass.
You don't need a lawyer.
Pain in the ass?
But aren't you a lawyer?
Jerome Clifford wasn't really dead
when you found him, was he?
- Yes, he was.
- We know you were in that car, Mark.
You see that?
You and Romey had a nice long chat,
didn't you?
What'd y'all talk about?
Did you talk about life? Talk about love?
Y'all talk about where bodies are buried?
I have to go to the bathroom.
Answer the question first, please, Mark.
I've gotta go bad. Please?
Well, you'd better go.
Thanks.
You don't need no stinking lawyer.
Hell no. This boy's about ready
to tell all. You know where Muldano's at?
- We're on his ass 24 hours a day.
- Better grab him so he don't skip town.
Don't mark up his face.
We can do the press conference here.
Hold on till we grab Muldano.
I wanna make sure those affidavits are set
so he can't make bail.
Did you get my makeup off the plane?
I'm gonna need Pancake number 17.
Doughnuts. Doughnuts.
Give me that telephone.
Press loves coffee and doughnuts.
See what you can do.
Where we gonna put me?
Down by the flags?
I think I look best
in front of these glass bricks...
behind a big bank of microphones.
That always looks nice, doesn't it?
- I'll call you back.
- Come in, Mark.
- Polite kid.
- Yeah, he's a good boy.
- Oh, keep your seats.
- We're in a meeting.
- I think you're in the wrong room.
- I don't think so.
My name is Reggie Love,
I'm an attorney and I represent Mark Sway.
May I see some ID, please?
When did he hire you?
I don't think that's really
any of your business, now is it?
Gonna have to forgive us, Ms. Love.
You're so pretty, how could anybody
mistake you for a lawyer?
- Please, call me Reggie...
- Reggie.
Roy.
So did you in fact...
Oh, please, sit down.
Attempt to interrogate my client
outside the presence of his mother, Jason?
No.
He tells me that you did, Lawrence.
He's confused.
We assumed his mother
was on her way down.
- Where were you during this?
- Oh, that's not really relevant.
Did you advise him
that he should talk to an attorney, Thomas?
- No... Yes.
- Did I...?
Remember, once, Larry
Mark said something, or I did, about TV...
and then Mark said that
he might need a lawyer...
and we...
I thought he was just joking.
So he never asked you guys
if he needed a lawyer?
I don't remember it that way.
Did you advise him
of his Miranda rights?
No, what for? He's not a criminal.
We just wanted to ask him a few questions.
You did attempt to interrogate him
outside the presence of his mother?
- No.
- Definitely not.
No way.
Bullshit.
Tread carefully. We know your client
lied about being in that car.
I think that's a bit of the pot
calling the kettle black.
- Do I need a lawyer?
- What for?
To protect my rights.
No, you been watching too much TV.
We just wanna ask some questions.
You can trust us.
Lawyers just get in the way.
They object to everything.
- You wired the kid.
- It's nothing personal, Lawrence.
Take your mother too.
You attempted to interrogate a child...
outside the presence of his mother
and without her consent.
He asked you if he needed a lawyer
and you said no...
stating as one of your reasons
that lawyers are a pain in the ass.
I'd like to confer with my client...
and meet with you people in my office
tomorrow around 3:00.
And if I need anything from you boys,
like the truth, well I expect to get it.
I catch you lying again...
I'm gonna use the tape.
That's blackmail, Ms. Love.
Indict me, Reverend Roy.
Still want those doughnuts?
Shut up, McThune. Goddamn.
- You want a cigarette?
- Oh, no thanks, I just quit.
There's been a mistake, ma'am.
We can't afford no lawyer.
- Don't worry about the money.
- My pig boss fired me this morning.
I mean, my baby's in a coma
and he fires me.
- Don't tell Mark.
- Just one day and he fired you? He is a pig.
Sucks.
Wasn't much of a job anyways.
Five bucks an hour at a lamp factory.
How long you been working there?
- How long you been...?
- Six months.
- Lord, I can't keep my head on straight.
- You're doing fine.
I like your ring.
They real diamonds?
Lord, no. It's semi-precious.
You got kids?
Gosh, you must have been just a baby
when you started having your babies.
I was just a dumb kid living in a dream.
All I ever wanted was a white house
with a walk-in closet.
Ain't that stupid?
No. Having a dream's never stupid.
Take it one day at a time,
that's what I say.
Come on, Ricky,
you always laugh at my air guitar.
Who's the best guitarist
in the whole world? Who?
Come on, Ricky, say it.
Yell it.
I know.
Look, Ricky, an Eskimo pissing.
Ricky, look at you.
I shouldn't have made you stay
in those woods. It's my fault.
But things are gonna be all right,
Ricky, I swear.
I've got us a lawyer...
and even though she is a woman,
she's pretty darn good.
She only costs a dollar too.
That's not it though.
I'm really sorry.
I'm gonna make it up to you.
I promise.
Hey.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Hi, Slick Moeller, Memphis Press.
I wrote the story this morning.
How's your brother?
- Get out of here! Get out!
- How's your brother?
Just a second, son,
I just wanna ask you a few questions.
- Did Clifford touch you any place?
- Get out! Just shut up!
Did he tell you why
he was committing suicide?
- Did he?
- You better get out of here.
- Did he talk to you at all?
- Get out!
I'll tell you what, I'll pay you.
Exclusive interview.
- Outside.
- Cops say you know more.
Mark, are you all right?
You understand I can't do it by day?
You Nance, private investigator?
Security specialist. Who's asking?
Name's Gronke. I need some fast work.
Who referred you?
Sulari, New Orleans.
I get $2000 cash retainer, non-refundable,
before I lift a finger.
You like kids?
First thing we'll do is...
is scheduled to be finished...
Why do you think Foltrigg was so...?
Mark, we're almost through.
Could you listen up?
Thank you.
Why do you think Foltrigg was
so convinced you were in Clifford's car?
I don't know.
If I'm gonna be your attorney,
you have to trust me.
I do trust you, Reggie.
I swear, I wasn't in that car.
You like Led Zeppelin?
Yeah. Do you like Led Zeppelin?
Oh, yeah. They were a great band.
I'll bet you never even heard
of Led Zeppelin.
You're probably one of them grown-ups
who just say they like really cool bands...
just to get close to
little punks like me.
Well, I think we've covered
just about everything.
All right,
what's your favorite Zeppelin song?
"Moby Dick," live version.
Bitching drum solo.
I'll pick you up tomorrow
about 2:30, okay?
What were the names
of their first four albums, Miss Groupie?
You tell Reverend Roy
what you told me...
and that'll probably be the last
we'll hear from him, okay?
What happens if you lie to the FBI?
It's a federal offense.
In theory, you could go to jail. Why?
You weren't smoking something besides
cigarettes in that woods, were you?
- No, ma'am.
- Is there something you're not telling me?
I'm positive
I'm not keeping something from you.
I mean, I was just curious.
Okay.
Oh, the first Led Zeppelin albums
were called I, II and III.
The fourth, which is actually untitled,
is generally referred to as IV.
See you tomorrow, groupie.
Andy, it's the space people.
They've come back, I knew they would.
Hello, out there?
Just be peaceful.
We're... We're friendly, don't be afraid.
My assistant will now approach you,
do not hurt him.
Want one?
Elvis Pezley.
Bet it's poisoned.
- She's funny, isn't she?
- Yeah.
My boy loves her.
Sorry. My boy was in a car wreck.
Drunk driver.
Don't know if he's gonna make it.
- He's only 8.
- My brother's only 8.
He's really sick.
- What's wrong with him?
- He saw something, is all.
You're not the kids
who saw that suicide guy, are you?
I seen it on TV.
Jesus. That must have been awful.
- How's your brother doing?
- He just lays there.
Man, oh, man.
What a scary thing for a kid to see.
I wasn't scared.
Jesus, he must have been out of his mind
to stick a gun in his mouth like that.
I mean, why?
Was he acting weird
or yelling crazy stuff, or...?
Maybe he said something scary
to your little brother. That could be.
Well, dude, I gotta go.
- Well, I hope your brother gets better.
- Yeah.
Karen?
- Where's Karen?
- Off duty, hon. Get you anything?
You got anything to eat around here?
- Cafeteria's open 24 hours.
- All right.
Hey, kid, can I have your autograph?
They said they were all on vacation.
Lots of attitude, you know?
But I want them on, you see.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Just fine.
Now, you listen to me, Mark Sway.
I don't know what Romey told you,
but you repeat a single word to anyone...
including your bitch lawyer,
I'll kill you.
You talk to the feds tomorrow,
And if you tell anyone about me,
I'll kill you slow.
You understand me, little big boy?
You understand?
Good. We have an understanding.
Now, I'm gonna be watching you, boy.
So everybody in New Orleans knew...
that Muldano and Boyette
were in bed together.
Boyette got himself killed.
He took money from the Mafia
to build a toxic-waste dump...
then when his constituents got pissed,
he voted against it.
- Enter Barry "The Blade."
- Right, if Foltrigg can prove it.
Why would Foltrigg risk bringing in
Muldano if he didn't have Boyette's body?
I think this guy's gonna run for office.
What are we serving?
- It's Thursday.
- Southern pecan.
- Something wrong? Your brother all right?
- I ain't talking to the FBI and that's final.
Mark, you have to talk with the FBI.
If you don't, they could subpoena you.
Foltrigg is gonna be here any minute.
I said, no. Now, you're my lawyer
and you have to do what I tell you.
Reverend Roy, I saw you on TV.
- Oh, he's so handsome.
- This place is a dump.
- Yeah, you can say that again.
- My Lord.
- Are you...?
- They are coming down the hall.
Make them go away. Please.
All right, stay here. Stay out of sight.
Something's up. I don't get it,
but I will do it. Just sit down.
Good afternoon, Ms. Love.
Is young master Sway all ready?
Roy, I'm sorry,
but the meeting's been canceled.
I beg your pardon?
Why don't you let me debrief the child
and give you a statement in writing?
- You and I know he doesn't know anything.
- We need to talk to this child, Reggie.
We have a set of confirmed fingerprints
that put him inside Jerome Clifford's car.
Now, what you and I gonna do about that?
- Well, I think that the big question is...
- Shit.
How did you match his fingerprints?
We lifted one off a soda can
at the hospital.
And did you ask either Mark Sway
or his mother before doing so?
So you invaded the privacy
of an 11-year-old child?
- We were just trying to obtain evidence.
- Evidence for what?
So his prints are inside the car.
You have absolutely no proof
that he even interacted with Clifford.
Kid has a bruise on his left cheekbone.
We found a spot of blood on
Clifford's ring, not his type.
Well, let me guess.
Mark Sway's blood type?
That's right.
And how did you obtain
Mark Sway's blood type?
From his brother's
hospital admission records.
And how did you obtain
confidential hospital records?
- Look here now...
- No, you look here.
If you get near my client again
without my permission...
I'm gonna sue you and the FBI
for civil rights violations...
file an ethics complaint with the state
bar and I'm gonna haul your ass into court.
You're playing big league hardball here.
We don't respond to threats.
Does Mark Sway's mother know
you been institutionalized...
for drug and alcohol abuse?
It was a treatment center.
You just close the door when you leave.
Reggie?
Listen, you been practicing law for 2 years,
you're not equipped to handle this case.
We know more about your client's actions
than you do. You're an amateur, Reggie.
Your client's in serious peril.
You think that over.
Open that door, let me talk to him.
You are so good.
But I'm not gonna let you use this child
to climb into the governor's chair.
You think you look good on TV?
If you or your guys attempt
to contact my client or his family again...
I'm gonna put little Mark Sway
on the news prime time.
He can tell everybody how you trampled the
constitutional rights of an 11-year-old.
And I got the tape to prove it.
We'll talk to that boy.
You miss one step, I'll eat you alive.
Jesus Christ.
I'm gonna kill that kid.
You been lying to me. You got till three
to start telling the truth. One, two...
You're the liar!
Keep the dollar, you're fired!
What are you talking...?
You come back here. Come back here.
Mark. Shit, where are my car keys?
- Where did I put my car keys?
- In your purse.
Mark.
- Mark, get in the car. Come on.
- No.
- Mark, please.
Mark. Mark.
- Mark.
- Mark, a couple quick questions.
How'd you like the story this morning?
Move on.
One question!
That kid didn't hire a
lawyer for his health.
He knows where that body is.
Even the Mob knows he knows,
that's why they flew in Gronke.
You got it, Wally?
We gotta get our hands on that child
before the Mob does.
Here. We can petition the juvenile court
alleging the boy's in need of supervision.
And protection.
Gronke's not here to visit Graceland.
We explain to the judge it's in the kid's best
interest to take him into protective custody.
To get the judge to make him talk...
- We allege the kid's breaking the law.
- He is. He's obstructing justice.
You file those petitions.
Incarcerate his young ass tonight.
Where are we? You said we was just
getting rid of the reporters.
You see any reporters around?
This is my mama's house.
- You live with your mother?
- This is Momma Love.
Hi there. You must be Mark.
Take me back to the hospital.
Listen, you and I are gonna do
some talking first.
- Talk my ass, you're fired!
- Fine.
You're the boss.
This is kidnapping or something!
Take me back right now!
I'll hitchhike if I have to!
Go ahead.
Nice meeting you, Mark.
- Who is it?
- Your mother.
Hey, Bono.
How you doing, Paulie?
Guess Johnny means business,
bringing you here.
- Where's the kid?
- With that bitch lawyer.
Got a private dick tailing him.
Any sign of the fibbies?
Yeah, a couple, watching the hospital,
same as we are.
I gave that kid a little
warning last night.
This is the directive:
We bug everything, hospital room,
lawyer's office, the works.
Find out what the kid knows.
That doesn't work, we kill them all.
How's he doing?
Oh, when he gets hungry, he'll come in.
It's a lucky thing a car
only comes by here every four hours.
That is one willful child, Regina.
Pain in the butt, if you ask me.
That's the pot calling the kettle black.
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
How you doing? You remember me?
You're the kid at the hospital, right?
Well, hop in. I'll give you a ride.
Come on now.
What are you doing out here anyway?
Come on, hop in.
Hey, you know,
my boy's getting much better.
How's your brother doing?
Come on back here.
- Elvis has left the building.
- Told you so.
- Why, hello there.
- Take me back to the hospital.
- Want some lemonade?
- I'm not taking you anywhere...
- ...until we've had a conversation.
- Or a piece of pie?
Where's a phone? I need to call a cab.
Help yourself.
It's 40 dollars from here, Momma?
Or 45? I'm not sure, something with a tip.
Look, you're fired, okay?
Can't you get that through your thick head?
Fine. Because I cannot do my job
if you keep hiding things from me.
Did it ever occur to you how it made me
feel to take on Foltrigg on your behalf...
without the facts?
I should've smelled your breath
before I hired you...
- ...then I would've known you was a drunk.
- Well, I think I'll be going.
I have been sober for 3 years.
Yeah, right. That's what all the drunks say.
How they gonna get sober and all.
They even say they love you,
but they don't.
Then they come home wasted
and beat on you and your mother so bad...
you gotta hit them in the face
with a baseball bat.
You're talking about your daddy,
aren't you?
Yeah, well I got rid of him.
When me and my mom went into court
to buy a divorce...
our lawyer sucked, as usual.
So I went up there and told the judge
myself about all the beatings...
and about how
he made us sleep in the street.
And that's when my father
became my ex-father.
And now I got you,
and you're a drunk and a bad lawyer too.
So now I'm getting rid of you.
You're fired, okay?
I can handle this myself.
Mark.
Mark, I used to think
I could handle everything by myself.
But sometimes being strong
means asking for help.
I know you've been taking
real good care of your family...
but the FBI's
not gonna leave you alone.
- You gotta let me help you.
- Let go.
- I need a cigarette.
- Smoking is terrible for you.
Hey, hey, hey.
What did Romey tell you in that car?
God, why do I always
have to answer questions?
Why don't you ever have to
answer any questions?
Okay, that's fair.
Go ahead, ask me something.
Like what?
Whatever you want. Go ahead,
there's no rules, there's no limits.
You ask me and I will answer.
And you'll tell the truth?
If it takes my skin off.
All right.
What's that thing you always wear
around your neck?
This is my mamaw's compass.
I wear it so I'll never lose my way again.
Anything else?
Yeah. These your kids?
- Yes.
- They chained down in the basement?
Close. They're with their daddy.
- There was a divorce.
- You ever see them?
- They don't really wanna see me.
- Because you was drunk and on drugs.
Because after the divorce
I drank some, yes.
I drank a lot.
Why?
You're right, there must be a cigarette
around here someplace.
I married a big Memphis doctor, worked my ass
off to put him through medical school...
and soon as he became rich and famous,
he traded me in for a younger model.
I didn't have a dollar
to put food in the fridge...
or a car to go look for a job.
But I figured I could handle it myself,
just like you.
But I was wrong.
So then you started to drink?
First, I stopped sleeping and eating.
I was scared to death. I kept staying up
every night, watching my babies...
trying to figure out
what I was gonna do.
Finally, I took some pills to sleep.
Hell, he prescribed them for me.
I was not trying to kill myself.
But that's when he pounced.
Got himself a fancy lawyer.
I didn't have anybody.
I figured after all those years
of blowing noses and wiping butts...
fixing meals and carpooling
the kids every which way...
that it'd count for something.
I was a fool.
The court declared me unfit.
Just like that, they were gone.
He took...
my little girl and my little boy.
Anyhow, that's when I started drinking.
But I got myself sober...
I stayed sober...
and I put myself through law school.
Do you miss your kids?
So much
I try not to even think about them.
He told me.
Romey told me where the body's buried.
Do you wanna tell me?
I can call the police
and put an end to this right now.
But I swore an oath
that I wouldn't tell nobody.
They're gonna get me, Reggie.
I seen it on TV.
The Mob never forgets.
Oh, my God.
They came after you, didn't they?
- Yes, ma'am.
- I gotta get security on your brother's room.
And notify the police
and get you out of here...
back to the hospital
where you'll be safe.
Reggie...
I'm scared.
What's up?
He's in there. But y'all gonna have
to deal with the two bitches.
What do you think?
I got an idea.
It's gonna take at least a week
to get that kid into protective custody.
We still gotta find a way
to make him talk.
I want that kid in court
and on the stand mañana.
- You hear what I'm telling you?
- Yes, but...
Let me have the phone.
I know how to solve this.
Don't you have something to do?
Why don't you go wake somebody up?
- Mr. Foltrigg? May I have your autograph?
- Of course you can.
Thomas, let me encourage you
to produce me some immediate results...
in the interest of your own personal
job security right, by God, now.
What's your name?
Our trailer...
They burned down our home.
We got nothing left.
Who did?
How the hell do I know?
Somebody, they saw two people,
they was leaving and...
It's all gone. All of it.
- Mom, it's my fault.
- Dianne, I'm so sorry.
Look, it's gonna be all right.
Do you know if you have insurance?
That is none of your business, really.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean anything by it.
- I was just trying to help, is all.
- What is this crap?
A few things I put together
to make you feel more comfortable...
- I don't need your charity.
- It's not charity...
And I don't need you trying
to come in here and take away my son.
- Mark's already got a mother!
- I know that. You're doing a fine job.
- I don't need your help.
- Look, I'm sorry...
Get out!
Sure.
Reggie.
- Reggie, you okay?
- I'm fine.
They got her on all kinds of medication.
She doesn't know what she's saying.
I had no call
to speak to her that way, Lord.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
Hello.
I'm Detective Ed Nassar, Memphis P.D.
- You Dianne Sway?
- Yeah.
These are from juvenile court. It's a
summons for a hearing at 10 tomorrow.
The summons requires us to take
young Mark into custody at this time.
What? You can't take my son.
- Well, we're gonna have to.
- You son of a bitch.
- Easy now.
- Over my dead body.
- It's for his own good.
- What's he done? Just tell me.
Can somebody help me?
Don't touch him.
The petition was filed
because he will not cooperate...
Son of a bitch!
- Come on. Come on.
- Help.
- Come on. Calm down. Calm down.
- Help me.
- Mark.
- Come on.
There's no reason to get excited.
We'll take good care of him.
- Give it up. Come on.
- Get off of me!
Come on, now,
you're getting yourself all riled up.
Agh!
They're taking me to jail!
I'm an 11-year-old!
- They hit my mother!
- Shut up, Markus.
Hey, you gonna read me my rights?
Hey, meathead,
you even know how to read?
- You gonna cuff me?
- This is not an arrest.
- Then what the hell is it?
- Watch your mouth, kid.
Kiss my ass, you stupid jerk.
He's all yours.
Calm down.
Empty your pockets.
Okay, now follow me.
- There you are.
- I don't look bad.
You look good.
All right.
- Hello?
- I twisted every arm, I broke every leg.
You got what you want.
The kid's in custody.
- You got your hearing tomorrow at 10a.m.
- I knew you could do it, Jason.
Well done.
- One child in jail.
- All right.
- What kind of place is this?
- Women's detention hall.
- Keep the noise down!
- Why am I being put in with the women?
Because you're a minor.
Stop treating me like a kid.
Put me where the men are.
You're safer here.
You have this whole cell to yourself.
- Is this what they mean by solitary?
- No.
You can have any bed you want.
Don't give me any trouble.
You okay, boy?
Can I call my mom?
Just to tell her where I'm at
and that I'm okay.
Please, she's probably
worried sick about me.
I suppose I could run a phone in here.
I'll make this little exception,
just this once.
Thank you, ma'am.
Brother's Pizza.
Yes, I would like to order
20 of your largest Supremes.
Okay, and where's that going, honey?
I'm ordering for Detective Nassar,
North Precinct.
Okay, and how would you like to pay
for this order?
- Well, with my credit card.
- Number, please.
The number is 4000-0306...
1954-0010.
Okay, hold on.
That'll be $248.10.
Fine. Cheaper than the last time.
- Oh, well.
- Thank you.
We'll never get him out tonight.
Foltrigg filed a custody petition.
- Roosevelt scheduled a hearing for 10.
- Ten?
There's three to seven days
after filing a petition, not hours.
That damn Foltrigg, he'll do anything.
- Got that right.
- A child behind bars for the night.
I have been through this wallet three times,
I have found everything except my Visa.
Man, these things are hot.
Hi. Did y'all order the pizzas?
My, my, my.
You didn't have to sign a custody order.
I would've brought him here.
- Good morning to you too, Reggie.
- What is going on?
According to the FBI...
a Mr. Paul Gronke and his pal, Bono,
have just arrived in our fair city.
- You ever heard of these guys?
- No.
- Your client could be in a world of danger.
- Oh, shit.
What does the child know?
- You know that's privileged.
- So he knows more than he should?
If he did know something, would you
guarantee him witness protection...
complete relocation
for his mother, his brother and him?
Well, this is not standard.
Damn it, Harry.
Why should he talk if we can't protect him?
Forgive my presumption here, Reggie,
but you do seem overly agitated.
Whatever became of that...
objectivity we used to fight about
over at Memphis State?
After all...
he is just a client, isn't he?
I'm sorry, I just didn't get much sleep.
It's just that...
he's never had a break
and he's counting on me.
Hey.
- Thanks, Doreen.
- Good luck.
- Brought your jacket.
- Thanks.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
You sure clean up good.
You too.
Why can't I just tell them
I don't know nothing, Reggie?
Because it's wrong.
Because it's against the law.
And besides, nobody's gonna believe you.
Not the Mob, not the FBI, nobody.
And besides that,
Barry Muldano's a killer.
You've got a chance to stop him
before he hurts somebody else.
Didn't you tell the truth in divorce court,
about being a good mom and all?
- Yes.
- Proof, the truth hurts.
- They took your kids away.
- All right, you're right, you're right.
But, Mark, don't you see,
if you lie, you're gonna be just like them.
If I tell the truth, he'll kill me.
All right.
Look, have you ever...?
Have you ever heard
of the witness-protection program?
Lord, yes. That's where they put you
in those funny mustaches...
and send you off to New Jersey
or someplace to live.
I saw it on TV.
But the guy in the TV movie,
the Mob found him anyways...
and they blew his legs off.
You saw that on TV?
Reggie, no matter what I do,
I could probably get killed.
- You can't let them ask me any questions.
- I'll try, Mark.
But if Foltrigg gets you on that stand...
you can't lie or
you'll be just like them.
- Okay?
- Court is in session.
Mark.
My, we certainly have drawn a crowd
this morning. Officer?
I'm Sergeant Hardy.
What are you doing in my court
wearing a firearm?
Wait...
Thank you. You may go.
And you, Mr. Moeller.
Your coverage of the case has led me
to consider having you indicted...
for reckless endangerment.
But, Your Honor...
Another word
and I will slap you with contempt.
Good day, sir.
Well now, that's better.
Shall we proceed?
Your honor, I'd like to note for the record
that the child's without custodial parent.
Request postponement
until she can appear.
I'm Thomas Fink, assistant U.S. attorney
for eastern Louisiana.
I'd like to address this issue
of the absence of the child's mother.
It's our position,
the position of the petitioners...
Your position, Mr. Fink, is in that chair.
Please sit.
And listen carefully,
I'll only say this once.
- Judge Roosevelt...
- As for you, Mr. Foltrigg...
this is not New Orleans
and I'm not one of your federal judges.
This is my private courtroom
and I make the rules.
Rule number one:
You will speak only when spoken to.
Rule number two: Do not grace His Honor
with unsolicited commentary.
Rule number three: His Honor does not like
to listen to the voice of U.S. attorneys...
who love to hear themselves speak.
Do you understand these rules, gentlemen?
Mr. Foltrigg? You want Mr. Fink
to handle the case for the prosecution?
Yes, sir. If it please the court, sir.
I'll allow it, but try and keep his butt
in that seat, please.
- Sir.
- Court will act in loco parentis.
I'll watch out for the child's interests
in this hearing, Ms. Love. Proceed.
The child moves to dismiss on grounds
the allegations are without merit.
The petition has been filed
to explore things the child might know.
- Quit calling me "the child."
- Quiet, young man.
Proceed.
Mr. Foltrigg and Mr. Fink are using
this hearing as a fishing expedition.
Their supposition that the... My client...
had any legally significant
conversation with Mr. Clifford...
is based on purely
circumstantial evidence.
The petition should be dismissed
and we should go home.
- Your Honor, if I may?
- You may.
The child is the last person
to see Jerome Clifford alive.
Now, we have established
this child willfully deceived us.
A set of fingerprints on a Cadillac
is hardly willful deceit.
We can show the child's fingerprints
on the suicide hose and on the gun itself.
We feel the child must testify for
his own good in order to exonerate himself.
Mr. Fink, are you attempting to implicate
this child in Clifford's suicide?
No, we are not. Currently, we are alleging
only obstruction of justice.
Now, involvement in a suicide
could constitute juvenile delinquency.
This child could be removed
from his mother's care.
Your Honor, there's no basis for this.
Your Honor, we are only asking that
the child testify to clear his good name.
We're not forcing the child to testify.
Not yet.
Ms. Love, will your client testify
and put an end to this foolishness?
And if we refuse?
Well, I don't like it, but I'd have to
lock him back up till we sort this out.
No.
Your Honor,
the child moves for a change of venue.
Since the alleged murder of Boyette
occurred in Louisiana...
we would like a relocation
to that locality.
As the United States attorney
for eastern Louisiana, I waive venue...
The child declines.
And release the proceedings
to your jurisdiction.
The child declines.
That's a pretty suit.
Drop dead, Roy.
All right, you two. Just settle down.
Nice try, but I think it would be
in everybody's best interests...
for Mark to take the stand.
- Your Honor...
- That's my ruling, counselor.
Mark, I want you to come up here
and take this seat right by me.
It's okay.
Put up your right hand, Mark.
You swear to tell the truth?
You have to say it.
I swear.
Okay. Mr. Fink is gonna
ask you some questions.
He'll keep them clear and simple,
understand?
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. Fink.
- May I rise?
How you doing, Mark?
Mark, were you forced into the car
with Mr. Clifford before he died?
Yes, sir.
Did you and Mr. Clifford
have a conversation?
- Yes, sir.
- Listen up.
Did Mr. Clifford mention Barry Muldano
or Senator Boyd Boyette?
You answer the question, Mark.
Is taking the Fifth Amendment lying?
No, it's not lying.
- Well, can I take the Fifth Amendment?
- No, you cannot.
Why not? It applies to kids, doesn't it?
Not in this case, Mark.
You're not implicated
in the death of Senator Boyette...
so you'll have to answer the question.
Your Honor, as Mr. Foltrigg has done
so thorough a job...
in attempting to implicate Mark,
I must, out of an abundance of caution...
advise my client to take the Fifth.
Haven't we played enough games here?
We are all searchers for the truth.
A man's been murdered and another man
lies dead by his own hand...
yet this boy remains silent.
What wanton hubris is this?
Speak, child, now.
Lying lips are an abomination to the Lord,
so sayeth the Psalm.
That's Proverbs, 12:22.
This is still a courtroom,
not a church, Mr. Foltrigg.
Please, sit down.
Did Romey Clifford tell you
where Boyd Boyette's body's at, son?
Mr. Foltrigg.
Yes, sir.
Answer the question, Mark.
I take the Fifth Amendment.
I'm sorry, but I can't answer
any of these questions...
because I'm afraid of what might happen
to me or my family.
I have no choice but to return you
to protective custody.
All right, this is over yet.
Sorry, Mark, it's for your own protection.
Why can't you get him
to answer the question?
These proceedings are closed.
- I didn't lie, Reggie.
- You did great.
What kind of a lawyer tells a child
to plead the Fifth...
send him back to jail
and hold up a federal investigation?
You trying to ruin this boy's life
or just flat-out get him killed?
You did real good, Reggie.
- We alone?
- Yeah, we're alone.
What happened?
- I was looking for a little more this time.
- What?
I asked you a question.
Kid's going back to jail.
Roosevelt just wants to keep him safe.
- What's he know?
- I'd say he knows everything.
The bastard. Harry wants him
back in court tomorrow at noon...
to see if a night in the slammer
changes his mind.
- You didn't hear this from me.
- Shut up.
Come on, man,
give me a little break here, would you?
Get out of my way.
Go powder your nose.
What is it? I'm eating here.
I just talked to Gronke in Memphis.
What can I get you?
Dos Equis.
- Where's your regular waiter?
- I don't know.
Cops got the kid.
I still can't move the stiff.
You're a dumb-ass, you know that?
We've had this conversation.
I'm sick of it. I deserve respect.
- Nice work, Ron.
- Thanks.
- Just once, Uncle Johnny...
- Picking it up just fine.
We still need to make the move.
That little bastard knows something.
Probably told his lawyer.
We're tapping the phones.
I hate goddamn lawyers.
Please, just let me hit the kid.
We got nothing to worry about
from that kid.
- Let's call the whole thing quits.
- That kid knows...
Goddamn bugs.
The city's lousy with them.
You're probably right, Uncle Johnny.
Kid knows nothing.
They're onto us.
We're out of business.
So we're just gonna put this whole thing
behind us. Is that clear?
I got it, Uncle Johnny.
- Regina, what are you doing?
- Nothing, Momma, you go back to bed.
Have you any idea what time it is?
Momma, have you seen
my notebooks from school?
In the garage, maybe.
- Garage? Oh, shit, yeah.
- Baby, you need to get some sleep.
He's your client, Regina,
he's not your child.
Damn.
Jesus.
Mark. Mark.
Telda, call the medic! Quick!
Medic on 5 now!
Goddamn, the boy's soaking wet.
- The baby's in shock, isn't he?
- Go get a towel.
Shit.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
This kid's heart is about to explode.
Get an ambulance, now.
Right. Telda, call an ambulance!
- What do we got?
- Elevated pulse and BP.
He's come down a bit since we got him.
Kid's from juvenile court.
- Is he a bleeder or anything?
- No.
He can wait five minutes.
Wheel him over there.
- Sign on the line, he's yours.
- Where are the police?
He's just a juvenile.
Goddamn it! Look at this, man.
My guitar. I just can't believe it,
man. Look at my guitar.
- Forget the guitar.
- No, honey, this is an original guitar.
- Settle down, settle down.
- Just what we need, drunk Elvis.
There's people over here who
need help. I need a new guitar.
Who's gonna pay for this? Who's paying?
- Got a light?
- Sure.
Is there coffee?
I think they got a fresh pot.
Too hot in there for you?
Mark?
Paging Mr. Sway.
Now, it's nothing personal, kid.
I don't wanna hurt you.
I just wanna talk.
Want a smoke?
Let's have a smoke together.
Mark?
Okay, you little punk, game's over.
Isn't this a nice spot to die?
Well, well, I wonder if we're gonna find
a live body in here.
Come on over here.
Boy!
Open this door, you little punk!
- McThune.
- Chief, it's Jerry.
It's about Mark Sway. He's escaped.
Pardon me?
Hi there, thought you boys
could use some coffee.
- Here you go.
- Thank you, Mrs. Love.
Oh, you're welcome.
Is this really the best time
to defrost the freezer?
Will you shut up?
- You need anything else, you just holler.
- What are you being so nice to them for?
Because they're cute.
They're just trying to be protective.
Where have you been? They are here...
because they are hoping an 11-year-old
boy comes by so they can pounce on him.
I feel like a prisoner.
Shit.
Will you just be calm?
Me? You're the one who hasn't be able
to sit still since they got here.
It isn't everyday
cops stake out your house.
All right, fine. Let's just all relax.
Can we do that?
Let's just try to sit down and relax.
I'm relaxed.
- Hello.
- Reggie, it's me.
I've busted out of jail.
You've gotta come get me.
Jeannette. It's Jeannette.
It's Jeannette.
What are you doing calling me so late?
Who's Jeannette?
I'm at St. Peter's, hiding out.
- What?
- I ran in place for an hour...
and I faked an attack
of post-traumatic stress disorder.
They rushed me right over.
It was easy as pie.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
I locked a Mafia guy in the morgue
who was trying to kill me.
- You go down the hall.
- I hear something down the hallway.
Mark, go find yourself a policeman
right now.
Found someone locked up
in a cooler.
You kidding me?
I'm not going back to jail.
Reggie, if you don't come and get me,
I'm gonna go where I'm going on my own.
- No, no, no.
- I'm serious. You've gotta come get me.
Now, you're the only friend I've got,
and you know that. Don't let me down.
Shit.
I'll meet you by the front
parking lot in a dark gray Honda.
Okay. Right in front of the cross.
The big one.
Thank you, Reggie. Thanks.
- My dark gray Honda?
- Just give me the keys.
You can't run away with an escaped
whatever the hell he is.
They'll arrest you for contributing.
You'll be disbarred. You've lost your mind.
Momma, I need you to distract the police.
I'm gonna go out the back.
Go get them a coffee or something,
and don't ask me any questions, please.
- Oh, I need some cash.
- Come on, Reg, this is my rent money.
I know, but you can live with Momma.
She likes you better than me anyway.
Well, that wouldn't be hard.
Nobody gets in.
Get in.
Stay down.
Your mama must be beside herself.
I called her from the morgue
and told her we'd fix everything.
- We?
- You're an accomplice now, aren't you?
Shit.
We're watching the mother's room
in case he tries to get to her.
We put a bug in her phone.
Anybody talk to her?
- You said you wanted to be the first.
- I do.
- You know your boy's missing.
- Missing? You mean you lost him.
Has he tried to contact you tonight?
You searched the hospital?
He knows it real well, you know.
Yes, we have searched the hospital.
Reggie Love is missing too.
Do you think Mark could be with her?
Hell, y'all are the FBI.
Since you got involved,
our trailer's been blown up...
my boy's been thrown in jail,
and now he's missing.
So let me tell you something.
Act like the FBI. You find him.
- Head towards the bridge.
- Why?
Well, I been thinking.
That witness-protection thing
sounds pretty good.
But Romey was all drunk and on pills.
What if the body ain't where he said,
would we still get protection?
We make our deal
before we tell them where the body is...
and then just keep our fingers crossed.
So first we gotta be sure
the body's even there, right?
What are you getting at?
We gotta go to New Orleans...
and try and find Boyette's body's
where Romey said it is.
You are out of your mind.
No way. Absolutely not. That's it.
Where are you going? You... Wait... Stay.
Damn it.
Get back in the car. Mark.
Where are you going? Mark.
- Someone's gonna see you.
- Let me go, I'll hitchhike if I have to.
You are crazy.
You're gonna get yourself killed.
A lot of other people could get killed
if I don't go.
- Mark.
- I'll do it on my own if I have to.
Mark, please. Please.
Remember at Momma Love's...
what you told me about,
well, asking people for help?
- Yeah.
- I guess now I'm asking you.
Please?
Hey, where are you going?
I'm gonna look for a map to New Orleans.
What do you think I'm doing?
The kid broke jail. The lawyer's missing.
Gronke spent all night in a freezer.
No one has been killed
and the body has not been moved.
Can you explain this to me,
Barry "The Blade"?
Well, the thing is, Uncle Johnny...
I hid the body under a boat
in Romey's boathouse.
You what?
I wanted Romey to remember how close he
was to being dead. It was kind of a joke.
Very funny.
After Romey died,
there were cops all over the place.
But now they're finally gone,
I can get the body.
The way this has been handled,
Barry, has been very stupid.
I will not let you take this family
down with you, do you understand?
I'm begging you, Uncle Johnny,
just let me get the body.
Help me now and I promise,
I'll never make another mistake again.
Take Gronke and Bono.
I'm giving you one chance
to clear this up.
This is my last favor, Barry.
Thank you, Uncle Johnny.
Barry.
Do you understand what I mean
when I say "my last favor"?
I understand.
Reggie Love's office.
Listen, carefully, call Dianne
Sway, tell her Mark's okay. He's with me.
Where are you?
The feds are going crazy.
A motel outside New Orleans.
I gotta go, we'll be back tomorrow.
You gotta tell me...
Clint, if anything happens,
take care of Momma Love for me, okay?
Reggie,
Reggie, don't you hang up. Reggie.
Got something.
Good. Good work.
Hot damn. We monitored a call from Clint
Von Hooser to Dianne Sway at the hospital.
Love has got the kid in New Orleans.
- We're out of here.
- Get the airplane.
- Excellent news.
- Yes, sir.
We are out of here?
We'll give you a telephone call.
Move out, Walter.
Wally.
Are we still going north?
I don't know. Check my compass.
- Take it off.
- No, I never take it off.
That's okay, we're on the right street.
1210.
Turn your lights off.
This is where the rich people live.
Holy shit, look at that one.
Don't curse.
- Shine it over there, see what that one is.
- 1212.
1213.
This must be 1214.
- There it is. Bingo.
- Bingo.
Oh, my.
Be quiet. Don't let the neighbors see you.
I see a big house,
but I don't see a boathouse.
Maybe it's further back.
Get down, you're gonna kill yourself.
We'll find another way.
We can go by the river and hide the car.
Okay.
Why don't you turn off that television?
- I'm sick of it.
- I wanted that cabinet.
Don't touch the fence.
I ain't crazy.
I don't want the shit shocked out of me.
That must be Romey's place
over there by those trees.
Yeah.
- That looks like a boathouse.
- Yeah, but how we gonna get there?
- Come on.
- No, Mark. Shoot.
That's private property.
Turn off the lights and come to bed.
What the hell do you think I'm doing?
Romey's neighbors sure are paranoid.
You would be too
with the Mafia living next door.
Don't touch it.
Damn it.
I'll look around here for another door.
There's another door but it's locked too.
Be quiet. Careful.
I'll try the window.
Know how to get to Romey's?
Yeah, everybody knows
how to get to Romey's, the smell.
Be careful.
Yeah, okay.
Can you see anything?
Yeah.
Quiet.
You'll wake up the neighbors.
- What do you see?
- It's definitely a boathouse.
Wait a minute, what are you doing?
Don't go in.
I'll climb in and unlock the door
from the inside.
Mark, you listen to me. Get down here.
Mark?
Mark? Shit.
- Are you all right?
- Gotta see if the body's here.
No, just let me in.
- It's here.
- Will you open up this door? Come on.
Mark, I'm gonna kill you
if you don't open this door.
What happened? Are you all right?
Yeah, it's just a raccoon.
Oh, good. Well, now let me in.
- Watch the water. If anyone comes...
- I know how to keep lookout.
Just take care of business.
There's somebody coming.
I think it's Barry Muldano.
- Open this door.
- It's locked.
I'm trapped.
Got a key?
- You hear something?
- No.
- Getting paranoid in your old age, Barry?
- Shut up, asshole.
Bye-bye, Rocky Raccoon.
Leave a goddamn calling card,
why don't you?
I told you I heard something, asshole.
- You buried him here?
- Yeah, under the boat.
Give me one of those picks.
Rocket scientist you are.
There are so many neighbors
around here.
- Will you shut up and start digging?
- Yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's move him out of here.
Resurrection time, you old bastard.
They found the body.
Get out of there. Come on, right now.
Let's just get out of here.
Hey!
- You okay?
- Get this thing off of me.
Run, Mark, run!
You gonna die, bitch.
Get off her. Now.
I'm serious. Let her go.
Drop the knife.
Mr. Mark Sway.
You a big man?
You a big man with a gun, Mark Sway?
You're not gonna shoot anyone.
Yes, I am.
- Mark, give me the gun. Come on.
- No.
He was gonna kill you.
He was gonna kill me, and he would've
killed my mom and my little brother.
You're just a scared little prick.
Probably piss your pants.
- Come on, big man, pull the trigger.
- No, Mark. Mark.
If I just shoot...
everything will be okay.
No, it won't you'll be just like him.
Please, come on.
Give it to me.
Mark, give it to me.
You should've let the kid shoot, bitch.
You haven't got the balls.
Really?
Jesus Christ.
You robbing son of a bitch!
- Damn!
- Who the hell are you?
No one's breaking into my place,
you son of a bitch.
Goddamn it! I'm unarmed!
Get in the house!
Call the police.
- What are you, nuts?
- We still got time.
- Oh, yeah?
- Goddamn it.
Cops gonna be here in a minute.
Get in the boat.
Damn it!
You're a genius.
You're not bad yourself. Let's see
what we got before police get here.
I wonder if he's home.
Oh, God, he's home.
What's the cloak-and-dagger all about?
You know you can trust us.
You three come here alone?
- That the truth?
- Of course it is.
Have one of them trot out to those
cars that aren't in the parking lot...
and get a pen from one of those agents
that aren't there.
- Get me something to write with.
- Hi.
You've been awful busy, Reggie.
Obstruction of justice,
tampering with federal evidence...
contributing to the delinquency
of a minor. You been real busy.
Roy, I am so flattered that you noticed.
You really see Boyd Boyette's body?
- I smelled it too.
- Where is it?
Here's a list of psychiatric hospitals
that specialize in children.
I want a bed for Ricky
in one of them by noon.
I don't believe you're in a strong
bargaining position.
You know where the body's at,
you better tell me.
I know where that body's at now...
but I don't know where
that body's gonna be in three hours.
Now, you wanna keep playing games
or you wanna make a deal?
All right.
What do you want?
- You have access to a private jet?
- I do.
Send it to Memphis.
Pick up Dianne and Ricky and their doctor.
We'll meet them at the airport.
When Mark's on board
and the plane's in the air...
I'll tell you where your body is.
How we doing so far?
- I don't hear anything I can't live with.
- Okay.
The family enters
the witness-protection program...
soon as Ricky's better,
they choose their new city.
Agreed.
Complete change of identification
and a nice little house.
White, with a walk-in closet.
Well, write it down. "Walk-in closet."
Is "walk-in" hyphenated?
She's gonna need some starting-out money
and a nice new job.
Okay, one of you guys
wanna type this up?
Soon as Dianne signs it,
we'll live happily ever after.
Give me some help, Reggie.
How far is it to that body?
Twelve little itty-bitty tiny minutes.
- Thank you, Reggie.
- You're welcome, Roy.
Yeah, they're on the move right now.
Here, give me your bag. Just get right in.
Sixteen-oh-three hours.
ETA for New Orleans, about 54 minutes.
They screwed up! You shitheads!
You never walk away! Never!
Now, settle down, Barry.
Sometimes you gotta cut your losses
to survive.
It's not too late. I can go back,
I can dig up that body myself.
Why don't you let Gronke here drive you?
And take Bono along for company.
You can all go together
for a nice long ride.
No, Uncle Johnny, please.
Let me go myself. I can handle it.
And risk getting caught? No.
No more risk, Barry. Barry "The Blade."
No more.
Not ever.
Welcome to New Orleans,
Mrs. Sway. Watch your step.
They're on the ground.
On the way to the hanger
for ground transport.
Mom.
God, I'm sorry I worried you.
- I'm glad you came.
- I'm not sure that I had that much choice.
Mom, if you don't want me to tell them
where the body is, I won't.
But they got this great hospital
in Phoenix for kids...
and once Ricky gets better,
we can move anywhere we want.
Canada, Connecticut, anywhere.
Anyplace that starts with a C anyway.
They... They told me
we'd have a real house.
And some getting-started money.
Walk-in closet.
- And later maybe a good job?
- Yeah.
Can watch my boys grow up.
Maybe even join the PTA.
Whatever.
Hell, I'm only 27 years old.
You're due for a break.
Look, about what all I said
in the hospital...
- Oh, no.
- I wanna apologize.
No need. No need.
And wherever your kids are...
they're crazy
not to want you with them.
Thank you.
You know, like you said,
one day at a time.
Phoenix.
I sure do like the sound of that.
Congratulations, Miss Sway. Jason
McThune will escort you to Phoenix...
- ...take care of matters once you arrive.
- Right this way, Miss Sway.
- All right, guys, let's go.
- Yes, sir.
- Come on.
- Let's go, boy. Come on.
Thanks, Reverend Roy.
You've been a real pain in the ass.
Thank you, son, and good luck to you.
I assure you, you have been
an even larger pain in the ass.
Give me five. All right.
You can't come with us, can you?
When you enter the witness-protection
program, you have to sever all ties.
I'll never see you again, will I?
No.
Look, you wanna...?
You wanna take care of my compass,
for me?
That way,
you'll never lose your way again.
I love you, Reggie.
I know, sweet boy, I love you too.
You better go with your mama.
Okay?
I'll call you.
The body is behind Romey Clifford's house,
in his boathouse.
1214 East Brookline.
Oh, my.
You did very well, Ms. Love.
Reggie. Thank you, Roy.
Oh, you forgot one thing.
You should have demanded immunity
for your illegal actions.
Oh, an eye for an eye.
Exodus, 21:24.
Let me tell you something, when I get to be
governor of Louisiana, do you want a job?
- I got one, thank you.
- Showtime, Roy.
Thank you, Reggie.
Thank Mark.
Hey.
Y'all come over here and gather round,
if you will, please.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- We have a...
After what I must say has been
an exhaustive investigation on our part...
we are able to make
the solemn announcement...
that we have recovered the body
of Senator Boyd Boyette.
He's quite a kid.
Don't tell him he's a kid,
he'll just get real pissed off.