Up!
Still don't wanna talk?
Very well!
You will die a brutal death.
- Keep this sucka steady, Toll!
- I'll do my best.
Here we go!!
Come on, you bastards!!
Eat shit!
- You better duck!
- Oh, shit!!
Yeah..
Turn around -
Brake!
- Watch your handling, slick!
- Shut up Gunner.
Incoming chopper!
We gotta get this thing outta here!
You got any ideas?
- That's what I'm asking you.
- Well I'm asking you!
Clear!
I got this.
Think you're tough? Did your team arrive?
Toll Road, get 'em up.
- Trench?
- Oh, this is embarrassing.
- Yeah, sure is.
- What's he doing here?
Saving this Chinese billionaire.
Oh yeah? That's funny.
So are we.
Looks like we're in a sketchy problem,
aren't we?
Cut me loose!
Frankenstein.
Don't get nuts, Gunner.
Do it..
- Where's your team?
- Waiting.
I need a weapon, something big.
Yours!
My big weapons
hangin right where it is.
Come on, Caesar, you got a back-up.
If I don't get this back,
your ass is terminated.
In your dreams.
- Trench, We've got a way out.
- Thanks, I got my own.
- Let's get you out of here, pal.
- Hey look, I hate to break up the bromance.
We're 20 seconds late.
Get money bags UP!
A 'thank you' would be nice.
- I hate owing you.
- What'll you do, big boy??
Let's go, Yang!
You in?
Of course, I'm in.
Let's go!
I'm out.
Now you put on your lucky ring?
I got the gangbang right here!
I've got your back!
Keep moving!
- Oh shit!
- Here we go!
Geronimo!!
- Why always me?
- Are you hit?
Yeah, twice..
- Better you than me.
- That's nice, nice.
You order room service?
- Not really.
- Then this could be a pissy ending.
Not loaded?
We could only hope.
Sorry sir, I had to adjust for a windshift.
No problem, hit the last position.
Moving out, over.
Let's go.. go.. go!
OK, hold on ladies. The cavalry's here.
About time you got here!
- Wake up Sam.
- On it.
Shit!
This guy's good.
- You're good.
- Appreciate it, sir.
I swear I'll pick you up, Kid.
Won't be late, sir.
Alright guys, put your toys away.
Target in sight!
- Souped up!
- Fire...!
- You missed.
- You're aiming!
Fire!
That was a statement.
Hit it!
- Dump the ski!
- Come on, we need to lose weight!
Climb, baby!
Climb!
It ain't getting UP!
Lucky ring.
- How's the oil pressure?
- Bad..
- Great! And the altimeter?
- Can you believe it? Stuck at 10,000 ft.
- Hydraulics?
- What hydraulics?
Congratulations, you flew another piece of junk.
- Hey can we talk when you're not too busy?
- Sure, anytime.
- Kid's amazing.
- Really? So am I.
You're just used up.
Get the client ready!
- What is going on?
- Looks like you're taking a shortcut home, pal.
- Parachute good?
- Parachute?
Why are you gonna parachute?
Do you believe they changed
the landing party to tomorrow?
Yeah, it's OK, I'll get
home a little earlier.
- 15 seconds.
- Opening the hatch!
Yang, get money bags home safely.
- So when are you coming back?
- Maybe soon, maybe never.
Maybe try a new life.
- Then who am I supposed to pick on?
- You will find another minority.
Yang!
Smile...
See you later, alligator.
Now that's a real Chinese takeout.
- Floor it, I'm homesick.
- You got it.
Yes!
I love this song!
Christmas, my friend..
Please tell me you ain't
going through with this.
Course I am. Look at that girl,
who wouldn't marry her.
- She cheated on you.
- It was a half-cheat.
- Which is...
- The other side of her, half-truth.
Murky. I hate to break this to you, pal.
But your girlfriend over there
has a world-class cheating gene.
I should stab you in the heart.
Too late.
Hi..
You know I used to think
you had a black heart.
Black is too colorful.
- Hey babe!
- Hey!
- Hey Barney!
- Hey Lacy.
Promise next time not to
keep my baby away so long?
Cross my heart.
If he had one.
Look who's lost in space.
Got a pen?
Hey!
You got anything that doesn't
have skulls in it?
As a matter of fact, I don't.
Einstein's theory of spatial relativity.
But we have made it better.
Believe it or not, before Gunner
became chemically unbalanced,
he went to MIT and had a Master's
degree in chemical engineering.
This idiot actually had a
brain, can you believe that?
- What happened?
- He quit to be a bouncer.
I wanted to get close to this
girl and dance at this disco.
And I can't believe she dumped you.
- Wouldn't you?
- I would, yeah.
- Can we talk outside?
- Yeah, sure, let's go!
How do I put this...
Just be straight up, honest.
I feel, uh...
I'm not sure What I feel.
This life...
it's not for you, is it?
I thought it was.
You gave me a chance to be one of you,
you got my respect forever.
And you got my respect too.
What are you gonna do?
I'd like to finish out the month.
Then I wanna go meet up my girlfriend.
Where's she from?
She's, uh, she's French. Believe it or not
I met her at Afghanistan, she was a nurse.
That comes in handy.
Yeah. You'd like her.
You know, she's the kind of person
you'd wanna do things for.
That's why I took this
job because the money's great..
Now I can afford to get
whatever that she deserves.
It's one of those things that just feels right.
I mean, you know when you could be with
someone and you don't even have to talk.
You already know what they're thinking.
You ever had that?
Sure.
I don't want you to think
that I'm deserting you.
No...
If I had to do it all over again at your age,
I'd do what you're doing.
Why don't you freshen up that beer.
Alright.
Barney Ross.
What do you want from me, Church?
Not too good on the memory
category are you, Barney?
You made a deal with me.
You gave me your word.
And you end up, blowing off half of Atlanta, punching
holes and a Bowie knife through a fellow CIA agent
even if he was a dirtbag.
But what breaks my heart,
is that you stole 5 million dollars from me.
And for all this male-patterned badness I gotta
put you in the deepest, darkest hole in Gitmo.
No sunlight.
- But I kept you out.
- Why?
Because I knew the day would come
when you were gonna pay me back.
Today is that day.
Keep talking.
Chinese plane got shot down over the
mountains near a hellhole called Gazak.
Yeah, who shot it down?
Take a guess.
Aboard that plane is a safe carrying
something you don't need to know about.
All you need to know is you can't
let it fall onto the wrong hands.
Now you're gonna get in there, you're gonna get
the contents of that safe, you're gonna bring it to me.
Should be a walk in the park for you.
And then we're even.
You get that?
The safe in that plane is very high-tech.
The access code changes every 120 seconds,
you use the wrong code, it blows.
- We need to get-
- Wait, Wait...!
We? Who's “we”? Who are you working with??
That's none of your business.
Let's just call our host The Corporation..
Alright? They're sending along a pro,
who specializes in this type of situation.
- Her name is Maggy Chan.
- A woman?
That usually goes along with the name Maggy, yeah.
- Forget it.
- She can handle herself.
But let me be clear:
If anything happens to her,
She gets hanged there, she gets hurt,
she gets roughed up, she doesn't come back in
exactly the same condition she went in,
you and your little gang of psychotic
mutts will never be seen again.
And that, I promise you.
I don't make a very good babysitter.
You sound so sure.
You're gonna make a very good babysitter.
Be there at 7.
Hey. I'm Maggy Chan.
You Barney Ross?
- Yeah.
- Mr. Church told you about me?
He said you wanna tag along.
Help, not tag along.
Nice motorcycle.
Where we're going, as you know,
we don't know what to expect.
Is it custom?
I think it's a mistake, you coming along.
Build it yourself?
Yeah, I built it myself.
Are you playing games with me, Maggy?
No.
Are you playing games with me?
Church told me what you said.
I'm combat-proficient.
I don't need a babysitter.
So, when do we leave?
0500.
Nice meeting you.
She's into me.
She hates you.
Watch this.
You know if something happens to her,
it's coming back on us.
You ever think to ask me for my opinion?
I told you 10 times before, I didn't have a
choice unless you don't mind going to jail..
- Yeah, well, Church intimidated you. Yeah.
- Really?
Is that the woman-you-can-never-
fully-trust calling again??
Yeah, I will stab you one day.
Hey, baby.
Yeah, of course I'm thinking about you.
What else is there to think about?
Hopeless.
Hey.
You're in the army, right?
I can tell.
Yes, ma'am.
3 years. Last tour was Afghanistan.
Didn't like it anymore?
It's a long story.
I would like to hear it.
Alright.
I, uh, was trained as a sniper...
and an instructor too but... I just really
wanna mix it up, you know, the action bit.
One time, we were stuck out in this hellhole valley.
About 30 Taliban opened up from these
houses in the hills above us.
They got about 8 of us pinned down bad.
So I called in for artillery support but,
“no way”, says the captain.
Didn't want to endanger the locals.
So we scattered, some crawled
through a ditch, some,
through a dry riverbed and the rest bailed, but...
We were still stuck in the killzone.
And we battled for... I don't know, 3 hours?
And finally an apache gunship chopper
showed up to provide air cover.
Scattered the hajis but..
The smoke clears and four of my squad are
dead on the ditch and two on the riverbed.
It's bad, sick...
All dead for nothing.
Do you know the most...
screwed up thing of all?
When I got back to base that night,
I found out that they had shot...
This stray dog that I adopted.
Commander's order's to get rid
of all animals on the base.
I mean, think, we had enough
damn shooting for one day, you know?
Anyway.. I, figured it was time to move on.
I heard these guys were looking
for someone and here I am.
- You got that transponder?
- Yes, apparently, 15 km northwest.
Okay.
Hello, darling..
We're a little busy...
- Right, let's move, wanna be outta here fast.
- The sooner, the better.
- Billy the Kid.
- Yeah?
Today's your lucky day, you get to take point.
My pleasure, sir.
Impressive.
Hold on.
Remember when you could do that?
No. Do you?
- I'd run away if I needed to.
- Really?
Look down.
Look down..
You see what I see'? Short legs.
A thousand bucks, you can't catch him.
Come on, Flash!
- I'm a little busy.
- Oh, yeah..
Found the wreckage, spotted a hill, sir!
Slow down, Billy.
You're making us look bad.
Say again, over?
- You heard.
- Roger that, slowing down.
We appreciate it.
- Rest of the plane's over the hill, sir.
- Good work, Billy!
Looks like somebody had a bad day.
You guys, get to the right!
Piss off, you roamers.
Alright Billy, you get a vantage point up there.
There's fur in the hands. This guy
was alive 'til the wolves got to him.
Be careful.
Is this it?
Yes, it's here.
Caesar! I need you in here!
Caesar grab a hold of this thing,
I think it's spring loaded.
Lee, hook it on.
Now on the count of three let's pull it back.
Ready?
One, two, three!
We can't hold this!
You have to.
Come on, Maggy!
Something's wrong.
- What?
- The explosive timer's triggered.
- How long?
- 54 seconds.
- If we leave now, we'll make it!
- Maggy, let it go!
No, I can do it!
- Come on, Maggy!
- Hey, What's going on?
She tripped the detonator, stay back!
I'm losing my grip.-
You just, hold it..
Got it!
Lucky I was here..
Just thinking that.
I'm sorry, it's important I get this.
You got guts, no common sense.
But guts. Come on.
It's alright, we got it, let's go.
You're strong.
Billy. Come on down, we're outta here.
What happened?
That woman is crazy, but I got a good pump.
Aren't you curious about
what's inside the case?
No, I just wanna get Church off our backs.
Billy the Kid!
Where the hell is he?
Billy!
- Drop your weapons.
- No way.
Ain't happening.
No?
Are you sure?
I'm sorry, sir, they were waiting.
- Drop the weapons now.
- Don't do it.
He's a strong soldier.
Let's see how strong he is.
Do it.
No!
Don't do nothing he says!
Don't talk.
You should not speak.
- I'm gonna kill him.
- When I fire, his head,
will be gone.
- 3 seconds.
- Don't give your weapons, you don't owe me anything!
1...
2...
Don't do this! They'll kill everyone.
He's gonna kill him.
Drop them!!
I'm impressed. Very good use of intelligence.
Everybody stay calm, we'll be done soon.
And then we will be on our way.
Bring me that knife.
What's this symbol?
I like symbol.
This is the symbol of the goat.
The pet... of Satan.
They say..
You have a case that belongs to me.
- Does it?
- Yes. Like your lives.
It's lost. He doesn't have it.
Last time, the case.
Or you will force me...
To cut..
His heart... out.
Do it, you piece of shit!
Wait!
Let me have it.
Hey!
- You talking to me?
- Pick it up.
- Hand it to me.
- Humiliate yourself.
- What was that?
- You heard..
Now pick it up..
...hand it to me nicely.
Or you will get what he got.
Do it, Lee.
You'll be alright, buddy.
Respect is everything.
Without respect, we're just people...
...common, shitty people.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's not your fault.
Now what?
We're both fighting men.
And I respect that. And fighting men, they
don't deserve to be killed like sheep.
But...
Respect, must be taught.
Lie down with your face on the ground,
until we leave.
Don't challenge me.
Get down.
Are you afraid of me?
No.
I'm not!
You should be.
- I'm dying.
- Don't talk, Billy.
Cut his hands loose.
Letter, in my pocket.
Okay kid, I got it.
I got it..
I'm so sorry..
I blame you.
What was in the case?
A computer blueprint of a mine.
A mine?
What mine?
The Russians stole nearly 5
tons of weapons grade Plutonium.
The mine was abandoned after the Cold War.
No one knows it's there.
The blueprints show where the Plutonium is stored.
We have to stop it before it gets in the wrong hands.
Guess that didn't happen, did it?
This kid died so that some
dirtbag could make bombs.
- I'm so sorry.
- Not as sorry as I am.
Let's take care of him.
“Dear Sophia.
I wish I could find something different
to do besides just missing you...
...but I can't.
The team's treating me good.
We got each other's backs..
And I want you to know
that wherever I end up,
I'll be wanting the very best for you.
And if some miracle happens and I come back again,
I hope I'm still your man. Much love, Billy”.
Why is it that one of us...
...who wants to live the most,
who deserves to live the most, dies.
And the ones that deserve to die
keep on living.
What's the message in that?
What's the plan?
Track 'em, find 'em, kill 'em.
CJ 1492 come up, requesting response immediately.
Is this Bozo?..
CJ 1492 this is a secure airwave, do you read?
What's this about?
What's taking so long, Barney Ross? This should
have been a walk in the park for you guys.
- Where's the case?
- Don't have it.
I warned you what would happen to you
mutts if you pulled this shit again.
A good man died trying to get that case.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Oh, yeah?
Yes, as a matter of fact, I am. Look, this sort of
situation comes with the territory, wouldn't you say?
And so is payback.
You know, Church, you're that kind
of guy that pulls his strings
and everyone else does your dirty work
because you've never had the
guts to do it yourself. We're done.
Sir, we got a problem.
The digging has slowed down.
Too many are dying,
and exhausted.
He's tired.
Anybody else tired?
- Get more workers.
- Already taken most of the men from the villages.
Get all the rest.
Women, children, all of them.
Show me.
Now we know where it is.
Right, right.
Ok... I know what to do.
Good, I want the Plutonium all in 3 days.
3 days?
I have people, ready to pay 4 million a kilo, now.
Three days. No more.
Understood. 483 Yes, smart, imagine
if 6 pounds of pure Plutonium
is powerful enough to change
the balance of the world.
So imagine what 5 tons would do.
It's very interesting.
- Something's happening.
- What?
The transmissions stopped.
They are underground
I'm putting it down right here.
Come on, let's hustle, hustle!
We gotta move!
Christmas! Come on, Lee.
Do you even know what the hell you're doing?
5 minutes. Don't get your knickers in a twist.
That transport truck, could be one of theirs.
Let's check this place out.
No shooting.
- Classics?
- Yeah.
I've been dying to use these.
We'll beat the truth out of them.
Maggy, tell the guys to wait in the truck.
Okay.
- They're here.
- Yeah.
You speak English?
- He's slightly gigantic.
- Shut up.
Just saying.
- He's really gigantic.
- I said that!
- Little bit of classics.
- I say we beat some info out of these guys and get moving.
- Sounds good to me.
- let's start with the midget.
Calm down, boys. I can get them to talk
with much less effort.
What are you gonna do, give them a pedicure?
That's a little sick.
Christmas, I need you to hotwire that truck
and go back to the plane and get the weapons.
- She get one of those if she sends you to do it.
- Stop complaining.
I should have bashed one of these up on your skull-
- How did it go?
- We're on, let's move!
They call themselves Sangs, they say they
control everything east of the mountains.
Robbery, kidnapping, assassinations.
Basically a cartel for hire.
- How do you know the language?
- Easy, put it together.
It's a cross between Ukraine
and Bulgarian dialect.
Impressed?
A little.
- Christmas!
- What?
Why are you yelling?
Because you gave me the shit job, that's why.
I'll shoot you in the face when I see you.
- Where are you?
- The 60-year old death-trap you call a plane.
What's taking you so long?
Because there's bridges out, signs missing, I've been
driving in these damn roads for the last 7 hours!
- You done complaining?
- Thanks for the sympathy.
This is Weird.
It's like home.
What the hell is this place?
I believe it's an old Soviet army base.
Probably used in the '80s,
The Cold War.
They most likely staged maneuvers and
practiced attacks against the US here.
Is there anything you don't know?
Great, just what I need, 50-year old pizza.
We'll bed down here for the night.
This tastes like shit. How's yours?
Can't complain about Rigatoni.
Dine ahead, fellas.
That's all I have to say. Hell,
what if you knew you were gonna die tomorrow?
What would your last meal be?
- One choice.
- One choice?
- Probably cereal for you, huh?
- Well, what the hell is wrong with cereal?
It's cliché.
You gotta be original, you know, if you
were an original, broad-thinking man,
you'd probably come up with some special cereal
like Eareal, you know, just like your ear...
Pour milk on those suckas and just lay
it in, and you don't wanna eat shit..
For the record, my hearing is 20/20.
Barney?
Donuts and most food that kills you.
- That's deep, man.
- I think so.
Maggy?
Crispy aromatic duck.
With plum sauce.
Very sexy.
But I like Italian, too.
I'm starting to think Italian’s overrated.
Hey. What about me?
My very Swedish dinner would be...
Baby seal,
and whale ass..
...In the summer.
Bu I'd really die, for some Chinese.
Then you're gonna starve to death.
Alright, sweet dreams.
Hey, Barney, I'm not done eating man.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure, go ahead.
Why are you so nervous around me?
I don't get nervous, Maggy.
What is it then?
I just like keeping a distance.
Is it because you don't
want to know any more people?
Let's just say that bad things have happened to people
I've come in close to.
Not a good way to live.
I know.
Do you think about the young man who died?
All the time.
You don't talk about him much.
No, 'cause it's how we deal with death.
Can't change what it is so we keep it light
until it's time to get dark.
And then we get pitch black.
Understand?
I understand.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Maggy-
I swear to God, if he won't
stop snoring I'm gonna shoot him.
Gunner!
You riding?
I know it's a stupid question, I don't
suppose you have any more of that coffee?
- Only makes one cup.
- Yeah, that's what I figured.
Listen up! This guy said that a congregation
of Sangs are probably in this area.
Concentrated east.
So that's where we're going.
We're out of here in 10 minutes.
Be ready, do what you got to do.
- We got to get out of here!
- Go!
Go, go, go!
Save your ammo.
Where the hell are you?
I'm almost there!
What's going on, are those shots?
Yeah!
- What's happening?
- The Sang's got us pinned down.
- Can you hold them off?
- Yeah, maybe with a tank.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
They got a tank. Come on, come on!
Let's roll, come on!
I'm out.
One left. Why not??
- Hey who did that?
- Not me, I'm out!
What just happened?
Somebody got a little carried away.
- Looks that way.
- Where're the shooters?
I don't know, but if they had
wanted us dead, we'd be dead.
Barney.
Don't freak out.
- Small world, huh, Barney?
- Booker.
- Rumor has it, you were dead.
- Yeah, I heard that too.
- So how's life treating you?
- Been better.
You did all this?
I fight solo, I thought you knew that?
Yeah, I heard but I didn't buy it.
Well now you do.
- This your team?
- Yeah..
Gunner, Toll Road,
Hale Caesar and Maggy.
Booker?
You're the one people
call the “Lone Wolf”?
I've been called that.
But I have mellowed.
Not that much.
I heard another rumor
that you were bitten by a King Cobra?
Yeah, I was. But after five
days of agonizing pain,
The cobra died.
Hey Booker, great to see you.
- So how'd you wind up in this godforsaken place?
- Yeah, we got ambushed by Sang
about a 100 km east of here,
killed one of my men,
- a young kid.
- Yeah, sorry to hear that.
Yeah..
The Sans are the lowest form of scum.
Shooting them have been a good business.
- You know who the leader is?
- Yeah a guy named Vilain.
Vilain?
Yeah, he pretty much controls
everything in this area.
You're gonna need more men if
you'd expect to get out alive.
Can you help out?
- Sorry, Barney. I work alone.
- I understand.
- Thanks for showing up.
- My pleasure.
Hey Barney, there's a village
down the road. There are good people,
and they hate the Sangs. Maybe they can help out.
- Thanks!
- Happy hunting!
What happened?
I'm still alive.
It's a matter of opinion, what did I miss?
I'll tell you all about it on the way.
Come on guys, unload these weapons.
Looks like Christmas came way late this year.
- Yeah I love you, too.
- Well, I'm happy to see you.
Finally. Somebody with class.
It's got to be the town
that Booker was talking about.
I could retire to a place like this.
Clean air, no stress, raise some kids.
You know, Maggy, I could retire
to a pace like this.
You are so full of shit.
They're missing us by a mile.
- Put down guns.
- That's not happening!
Safest place is in front of their gun.
- We will shoot you!
- No!
Wait.
These guys are here to help.
They want to help.
Even you two rejects could
get lucky around here.
- You think?
- I doubt it.
Do you mind?
- Who you are?
- We're American.
- Swedish.
- Blackford.
- Chinese.
- Retards.
Are you done?
What do you want?
We are here to take care of The Sangs.
Okay.
Come inside.
Come on.
This is who we'd think you've come for.
This is who we will die for.
First, they told us there'd be good jobs, good money.
Some went, but nobody come back.
They come for more. They say as
soon as our men go to job,
the others come home.
My husband goes. For a long time we hear nothing.
Then...
...the Sangs come and they take
all of the rest of the men.
Force them to work in the mines.
Same in the next village.
And the next, they take my sons.
Now all that is left, are the very young.
And they will be back for them, too.
I know this.
- We all know this.
- So we hide them,
- and we wait.
- Why don't you just move on?
- Leave.
- This is our home.
Our lives will be the last thing they'll take.
Tell us why you're here now.
We're tracking them.
Can't you stay?
And help? You saw the children!
Soon they'll be damned and they'll kill them all.
We have our own business with them.
Sorry..
Let's go!
I don't think they're
gonna last here much longer.
I think they know that.
So we're not gonna do anything about it?
I have an idea.
And with your ego I think
you're gonna love it.
- My ego?
- Your ego.
- What you mean my ego?
- You got a big ego.
- Check your ego out!
- Please, your ego is like the size of a dinosaur.
It's huge.
We got it.
We found the Plutonium.
Eva.. The Sangs are coming! Warn everyone!
Search all the houses!
Keep on looking!
Lari...!
Show us where the kid is, priest.
And get out of our way.
By the power vested in me..
I now pronounce you...
...man and knife.
One more!
Rest in pieces.
- Is this the last one?
- Yes.
Good.
Chambers are cleared.
Now a good sentence.
You bury them all.
I see about a dozen guards.
Light weapons, couple of badass 50 cals.
Worse, anti-tank devices.
There's no way our trucks
will get through that minefield.
Look, I know this is a stupid question, but
you got any ideas so we won't get killed'?
I got a few I'm thinking about.
- Boom time?
- Boom time!
Target in sight!
Baby wants to travel!
Fire!
- Rock and roll!
- Fire!
Bombs away!
- Tighten up.
- What's happening now?!
Chaos!
- You're not doing what I think you're doing!
- Yeah, I am!
Let's do it!
Come on, let's move!
You're gonna need a new plane.
We'll be home soon...
- We are too late!!
- What?!
The Plutonium is gone!
Come on, come on, get out of here!
- Go, go, go.
- Move it, move it!
Come on, get out of here!
We're gonna be here a while.
Doesn't seem right.
Going out this chickenshit way?
Yeah, something like that.
Hey! It ain't over
yet, kids. I got a plan.
Everybody calm down.
Phosphate rock.
- What is he doing?
- Probably making a bomb.
- You serious?
- Ask him.
- What you doing, Gunner?
- I'm making a bomb. You mind?
- A maniac with brains.
- Scary.
Phosphate rock, got a density of 1.52,
melting point 44.2 centigrade.
Guys! I want some gunpowder, fast!
Do it! The man's a chemical engineer, right?
And a full-pledged scholar.
Pour it in the pipe.
Big man might be onto something.
- You think?
- Probably not.
Need some help with that, let's go!
Here you go, blow yourself up.
Lighter.
I want that back.
Better get back! This is gonna be loud!
Get back!
Okay, alright, let's go!
Better turn around unless
you want your heads blown up.
Better cover your ears.
- All the phosphate's must've been damp.
- Yeah, right.
- Or you suck.
- there's that.
Don't cry, Gunner.
You almost had an idea.
I'm back!
How you doing, Trench?
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- We're even now, right?
- Right.
I'll be seeing you around, Trench. Thanks a lot.
Relax, it's not over yet.
- What?
- That's right.
- How you doing, pal?
- Pretty good, Church, what're you doing here?
- Heard there's a party in town.
- Yeah, but it's my party.
Has he always been this selfish?
- Always.
- Thanks.
You wanna kick Vilain's ass or not?
Don't forget the little rascal!
Move it.
Take the rest of the
nukes to the hangar, now!
And get the Plutonium on the plane.
Follow me.
We need to buy some time.
I'm out!
Go.. go! Move!
- Fun, huh?
- Yeah.
Oh, there he is!
Let's go!
- Yeah!
- Tear him apart!
I'm almost out!
I'll be back.
You've been back enough.
Yippee-ki-yay.
Who's next? Rambo?
Good bye!
Let's go.
Maggots.
Start the engine. Get this thing in
the air. I want to make some money!
Move!
Trench! Get in!
My shoe is bigger than this car.
Shoot something!
Start the helicopter.
We have a special guest coming!
Let's go!
Take care of him!
Can't beat the Classic.
- Barney!
- What are you doing here?
Now I'm going there alone, don't follow
me no matter what, you understand?
- You understand?
- Yes.
If that door opens up and
I don't come out, and he does,
you kill him.
Let's make it more dramatic!
Now that's better!
I'm out of bullets!
That's your problem.
Not really.
You wanna kill me like a man?
Or you wanna kill me...
like a sheep?
Nice knife.
So...
What is it going to be?
Man or sheep?
You wanna man up?
I'll man you up.
You must want to hurt me bad.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm gonna take your life.
Come..
Over so soon?
I want my money's worth!
- Come on, get UP!
- Coming right Up!
Tastes good?
Talking to me?
Ironic.
Here we are, you and I.
And your knife.
You're going to die.
Like him.
What was his name?
What did you call him?
What does it matter?
Come on, Vilain.
Somebody's dying.
Come on!
Come on, Vilain! Come on!
Berdiri Vilain.
Get... up!
Now turn around.
Turn around, sheep!
Now, Wham?
His name was Billy.
We oughta go to Turkey (?).
- Did you win?
- I think so.
Well, where's the proof?
Head's up.
Nice touch.
It is a nice touch.
A little extreme.
But nice.
As much as I hate to say this, Bam-Bam,
now that we got control of the Plutonium,
that makes us even.
Good.
So Maggy you'll be coming with us, then?
When you're ready.
So I just want..
You're OK, just a little immature.
I don't have to go.
If you want me to stay, I'll stay.
And I did save a babysitter's life.
That you did do.
Maybe I'm good luck for you.
But I can be bad luck for you
and I can't allow that.
If you ever want help,
call me. Or you're dead.
I'll do that.
What are you doing here?
Moving on, you killed all my business.
I thought you were the “Lone Wolf'.
Sometimes it's fun to run with the pack.
You got a point. You take care, Maggy.
Oh, I almost forgot. As a token of my
gratitude, my violent friend,
I got you, and the little rascals a ride home.
Behold!
What?
Consider it a gift.
That thing belongs in a museum.
We all do.
- Hey. Fun, right?
- Yeah. Fun.
Take care.
To Billy!