I want mead.
Give me some mead, my queen.
Thank you, my beautiful queen.
This is how it works, Aesher.
After you die, you wouldn't really be dead.
Providing you accepted Him as
the one and only god.
Back, back!
Faster, faster, faster!
I wanna a kiss. Give me a kiss.
I wanna kiss you. - Stop it!
My fays, my beautiful fays.
One year ago, I, Hrothgar your king,
swore that we would celebrate our victories
in a new hall. Mighty and beautifull.
Why not?
And in this hall we shall
divide the spoils of our conquest,
the gold and the treasure. And this shall
be a place of merriment, joy and fornication.
From now until the end of time.
I name this hall... HERAT!
Treasure,
let's hand out some treasure.
From the conquest.
Unferth. For Unferth.
For Unferth.
My wisest advisor, violator of virgins
and best and bravest of brave brawlers.
Unferth! Where the hell are you, you weasel-faced bastard?
- I'm here my king.
Let me tell you, you ungrateful lout!
Hrothgar!  Hrothgar!
Hrothgar!  Hrothgar...
He faced the demon dragon.
Where other men would freeze.
And then, my God, he took his sword.
And brought it to his knees.
Hrothgar!  Hrothgar...
The greatest of our kings!
Hrothgar!  Hrothgar!
He broke the dragon's wings.
The kingdom fell in darkness,
and shadows rule the light...
By the sign of dawn, he soldier on,
And brought us back to life.
Hrothgar!  Hrothgar...
Mead! Mead!
You're spilling. Where's my mead?
You're spilling! You're spilling!
Idiot.
How dare you waste king's mead.
He rode up like a saviour, when every hope is gone,
the beast was gone, the deed was done,
His men may live on,
Let every cup be raised...
A sword. Give me a sword!
Sword! Sword!
Fight me!
Fight me, damn you.
What was... that?
-Grendel.
Grendel, What have you done?
What have you done, Grendel?
Moth-er?
Fish, and wolf, and bear,
and sheep or two. But not men.
Men... they hurt us.
Men, Grendel.
They have slain so many of our kind.
Man hurt me, hurt me...
Was Hrothgar there?
Me hurt him not!...
Good.
Good boy. Tender.
Mother.
Men, build another pyre.
There's dry wood behind the stables.
Then burn the dead, and seal the hall.
Close the doors and the windows.
And by the king's order, there shall be
no singing or marrymaking of any kind.
This place reeks of death.
The scops are singing the shame of Herot
as far south as the middle kingdom,
And as far North as the Iceland.
I have let it be known that I will give
half the gold in my kingdom to any man
who can rid us of Grendel.
-My king, for deliverance our people
sacrifice goats and sheep to Odin and Heimdall.
With your permision
shall we also pray to the new Roman God,
Christ Jesus?
Perhaps he can lift our affliction.
No, Unferth, no. All the Gods will do nothing for us
that we will not do for ourselves.
What we need is a hero.
Hold on up!
Can you see the coast?
Can you see the Dane's guide-fire?
I see nothing but the wind and the rain.
No fire? No stars by which to navigate?
We're lost! Given to the sea!
The sea is my mother! She'll
never take me back into her murky womb!
My mother was a fishwife in Uppland.
I was rather hoping to die in battle, as a warrior should.
The men are worried.
The storm has no end, Beowulf...
It's no earthly storm!  That much is for sure.
But this demon's tempest will not hold us out.
if we really want IN!
Who wants to live!?
Then pull your oars!
Let's see you do it!
For Beowulf! For gold! For glory!
Heave! Heave!
Heave!
Beowulf!
Hold up.
No.
Who are you? From your dress, you are warriors.
Speak! Why should I not run you through right now!
We are Geats.
I am Beowulf, son of Edgethow.
We've come seeking your prince, Hrothgar,
in friendship.
They say you have a monster here.
They say your lands are cursed.
Is that what they say? -Bards sing of Hrothgar's shame
from the frozen North to the shores of Finland.
It is no shame to be accursed by demons.
- I'm Beowulf!
And I'm here to kill your monster.
I thought there are no more heroes
foolish enough to come around here
and die for our gold.
If we die, it'll be for glory,
not for gold.
My Lord!
My Lord, there are warriors outside.
Geats. But there are no beggars.
and their leader, Beowulf, is a...
-Beowulf? Edgethow's little boy?
Beowulf, where is he? Where...
Ah, there you are. Beowulf! Welcome my boy. Welcome.
How is your father?
-Dead. Died in battle with sea-raiders, two winters' back.
He was a brave man. May I ask why
you have come to us from across the sea?
I come to kill your monster,
and to taste that famous mead of yours.
There have been many brave men,
who have come to taste my lord's mead.
And many who had sworn to rid
his hall of our nightmare.
but in the morning,
there was nothing left of any of them,
but blood to be cleaned from the floor...
and the benches... and the walls.
I have drunk nothing. Yet.
But I will kill your monster.
He will kill the monster! Did you hear that?
Grendel will die!
Grendel?
-The monster is called Grendel.
Then I will kill your Grendel.
I, Beowulf, killed a tribe of giants on the Orkneys.
crushed the skulls of sea-serpents.
And this... this troll of yours will trouble you no more.
A hero! A hero!
I knew that the sea would bring us a hero!
So, will you go up to the moors,
to dark pool by the cave and kill the monster in its den?
I have fourteen brave Thanes with me.
We have been long at sea.
It is high time, mighty Hrothgar,
to break open your golden mead,
famed across the world,
and to feast in your legendary mead-hall.
The mead-hall has been sealed
by his lord's order.
Marrymaking in the hall brings
the devil, Grendel.
Well then?
- Open the mead-hall, let's drink!
We don't want any
trouble with the locals.
Hondshew. Make me feel you're
pretending to listen to me.
It's only been five days since you
waved your wife goodbye.
Five days? In the name of Odin!
No wonder my loins are burning.
Beowulf, there you are. I was thinking
about your father, great man.
He was fleeing the Wylflings.
And he'd killed one of them with his bare hands.
Heatholaf?
- That's it, yes, aye.
I paid the blood-debt for your father,
and he swore his oath to me.
So, I saved his skin,
and you are yet to save ours, eh?
All hail the great Beowulf!
Come to save our pathetic Danish skins, eh?
And we are so damn grateful, mighty Beowulf.
But, can I ask a question,
as a huge admirer of yours?
There was another Beowulf
I heard tell of,
who challenged Brecca The Mighty
to a swimming race, out on the open sea.
Was that you?
- I swam against Brecca.
Oh?
Because, I thought, it had to be
a different Beowulf.
Someone else of the same name.
Because, you see,
the Beowulf I heard of
swam against Brecca, and lost.
He risked his life, and Brecca's,
to serve his own vanity and pride.
A boastful fool.
AND HE LOST!
So,
I thought it had to be someone else...
I swam against Brecca..
- But victory was his, not yours.
A mighty warrior who cannot even
win a swimming match !
Speaking only for myself here,
Not only do I doubt that you will be able to
stand for a moment
against Grendel,
I doubt that you will even have the belly
to stay in the hall all night.
I find it difficult to argue with a drunk.
But it's true, I did not win the race...
We swam for five days, neck and neck.
I was conserving my strength,
for the final stretch... when this storm blew up,
and with it came sea monsters.
Again and again
the monsters attacked,
dark things
from the sea's depths.
I hacked and I scratched at these fowl beasts
with my sword,
spilling their guts into the sea.
Beowulf!!
Then, one of them ceased me
by its jaws,
and dragged me to the bottom...
I killed the moster with my own blade and...
I plunged it into its heart.
Yes, of course. The "sea monsters"...
And you killed, what was it... twenty?
Nine.
Last time it was three.
But... would you do me the honor
of telling me your name?
I am Unferth, son of Ecglaf.
- Unferth, son of Ecglaf?
I know who you are.
They say you killed both
of your brothers when you witness them
having knowledge of your mother.
I have another true thing to tell you,
Unferth Kin-Slayer.
If your strength and heart
was as strong and fierce as your words,
Grendel would not feel free to
murder and gorge on your people,
without fear of retaliation.
Tonight will be different!
Tonight he will find Geats waiting for him.
Not frightened sheep.
Like you.
Well done! That's the spirit, Beowulf.
That's the spirit we need.
So, you'll kill my Grendel for me,
will you?
Let's all drink, in celebration
of the kill that is to come.
"Lips ripe as the berries in June,
Red the rose, red the rose..."
"Skin pale as the light of the moon,
gently as she goes..."
"Eyes blue as the sea and the sky..." -
Beowulf, come. - "Waterfall, waterfall..."
Come with me, I want to show you something.
- "Heart, burning like a fire in the night..."
"gently as she goes..."
Come!
There. Royal dragon horn.
- It is beautiful.
Isn’t it magnificent?
She's the prize of my treasure.
I claimed her after my battle with the Farmir,
The dragon of the Northern moors.
Nearly cost me my life.
And there's a soft spot under the
throat, there. See?
You have to go in with a knife or a dagger.
That's the only way to kill a dragon.
I wonder how many men have died for love of her beauty?
Can you blame them?
If you destroy my Grendel for me,
she’ll be yours forever,
and ever, and ever...
You do me great honor.
- It is we who are honored.
Is that your demon?
- That was a wolf. You don't hear Grendel when he comes.
No, well, he'll hear me, I promise.
Come on, my mighty lust limb can transport you to paradise.
To ecstasy and back. No other man will
ever be able to satisfy you again.
- Sorry. - Oh, come on.
- I said no, and I meant no.
Why not? - Because it's late and its dark and the
monster could arive at any moment.
Well, then...
how about a quick gobble?
The hour is upon us.
This old man needs his sleep.
Where's my beautiful bed-mate?
Come, my love. - In a moment.
Come on Wealthow. Let's pound the pillows.
- Don't touch me.
That's the spirit, my girl.
- My Lord.
Perhaps her majesty could grace our ears with
one more melody before we all retire?
That's the least I can do.
Beowulf, I hope to see you in the morning,
Whole and willing.
And make sure your Thanes secure the doors.
Good night, good night...
Good night, Beowulf.
Watch out for sea-monsters.
I'm sure your imagination
must be teeming with them.
Just wait, the wide he may roam,
Always a hero comes home...
He goes where no one has gone,
But always a hero comes home...
That was... beautiful.
You need to go now, your majesty.
- Of course. Grendel.
The demon is my husband’s shame.
- It's not a shame, it's a curse.
No, shame.  My husband has no other... no sons.
And he will have no more, for all his talk.
Oy, Hondshew. How was she?
- Nah. Not my type.
I know your type.
Baa! Baa!
Lord Beowulf... What are you doing?
The creature has no sword, no armor.
And I have no weapon capable of slaying a monster.
We shall fight as equals.
And... fate shall decide.
Tight up the door chain!
Stop freaking about!
You’re mad, you know that?
- Yes.
Something affects you, my Wiglaf.
- I don't like the smell of this one, my lord.
The men are unprepared.
They're distracted.
There are too many untended women here!
Abstinent prior the battle is essential!
The warriors mind must be unblured, my lord.
- Good night, Wiglaf.
And while you're sleeping what are we meant to do?
- Sing, loudly!
Well, you heard him. He wants us to sing.
So sing. Olaf sing!
There was a dozen virgins,
Friesians, Danes and Franks!
We took 'em for some swiving,
and all we got were wanks!
OOohh, We are Beowulf's army,
We are mighty Thanes...
The fattest of the Virgins,
I knew her for a whore!
I gave her all my codpiece,
And still she wanted more!
Her sister was from Norway,
She costs me twenty groats!
She showed me there was more ways
Than one to sow my oats!
Her father was from Iceland,
And she was mighty hot!
She'll need a whole damn iceberg,
To cool her burning twa...
Grendel, he knocks.
That must be my sweet plum, Yrsa!
She's ready for me to taste her juicy fruit!
My lord.
- Patience. Patience, my love!
No, Hondshew! No!
This can't be.
It's a freaking monster.
I swear to my mother that this monster has no pintel!
No pintel!
The demon shrinks.
It shrinks.
Your blood-letting days are finished,
demon!
I am not demon!
It speaks! It speaks!
I am ripper, tearer, slasher, gouger.
I am the teeth in the darkness
the talons in the night.
Mine is strength, and lust, and power.
I am Beowulf!!
Grendel's arm! You've done it!
He's done it!
He's torn the limbs from the beast!
Beowulf has killed him! Hail Beowulf!
- Hail Beowulf! - Hail Beowulf!...
My Lord, Beowulf has killed the demon.
- Odin be praised.
Go tell the scops,
spread the word!
Yes my Lord.
Tomorrow will be a glorious day of rejoicing.
A nightmare is over.
Come to bed, my sweet.
My kingdom need a heir,
I need a son!
It's time you did your duty.
- How can I ever lay with you
knowing you laid with her?
I should never have told you.
Grendel... My son.
My poor son.
Mother.
They harmed me mother.
Sleep now, my son.
He murdered me, mother.
- Who murdered you, my son?
He ripped off my arm.
He will pay, my darling.
Who was the man?
He was so strong.
So strong.
Who was the man?
- Yes... yes.
His name was...
Beowulf.
Beowulf?
They were great warriors.
They died a fowl death.
- They were murdered by a fowl creature,
from the depths of hell.
The bards will sing of their glory forever.
Come, let's drink to their memory.
I want you to raise the first cup.
I am not in a mood for marrymaking.
I'll ride down to marine, to prepare the boat.
We still leave tomorrow, on the tide.
Do we not?
Aye.
My fays.
My friends, brothers,
This place for me has been a hall of sadness,
and for all of us it has been a place of
misery bloodshead and death.
But today, monsters reign has ended.
They said he ripped the monsters limb of
with his bare hands.
I wonder if all his strength is only in his arms,
or his legs as well...  All three of them.
After the feast tonight,
I'm sure you can find out, Gitte.
Me?
It's not me he wants, my Queen.
Wealthow, my love.
Why don't you do the honors?
For you, my lord.
Thank you, my king.
For all of you!
I wish you could've been there last night.
To see me kill the monster.
I was asleep when he arrived.
He ripped open the doors with his bare hands.
He stood twenty feet tall,
with a strength of a ten men.
I looked at him, and I said:
''I am Beowulf!''
Brave thane.
- My queen?
I love you. I want you, my king.
Only you. My hero. I love you.
I don't understand. Where is your husband?
- Dead.
Dead? This is a dream.
This is not happening, you're just a dream.
Me, darling?
A dream?
Give me a child.
Enter me and give me a son!
In the name of Odin! Is Grendel not dead?
Has he grown his arm anew?
It's not Grendel.
- Not Grendel, then who? - His mother.
It's Grendel you killed. I had hoped his
mother had left the land long, long ago.
How many monsters must I slay?
Grendel's mother, father, Grendel's uncle...
Must I hack down a whole family tree of demons?
She is the last of them. With her gone,
demon-kind will slip back into the darkness
from where it came.
Where it belongs.
And the mother's mate.
Where is Grendel's father ?
Grendel's father could do no harm to men.
Beowulf, I was wrong to doubt you before.
And I shall not again.
Yours is the blood of courage.
I beg your forgiveness.
Granted.
- Cain! Cain!
Take my sword. It belonged to my father's father.
It's called "Hrunting".
A sword is no match for demon magic.
I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
No, I'm sorry I mentioned
you murdered your brothers
They were... hasty words.
Unferth... I may not return.
Your ancestral sword might be lost with me.
As long as it is with you,
it will never be lost.
And you, mighty Wiglaf?
Are you still with me?
Till the end.
Look!
She's probably a water demon.
You don't want to meet her in her element.
I know. - You want me to go in with you?
Good. I'll be here.
I see you've brought me treasure.
- Show your self!
What are you?
Are you the one they call Beowulf?
The Be-Wolf, the Bear?
Such a strong man you are.
With a strength of a king.
The king you will one day become.
- What do you know of me, demon?
I know that underneath your glamour,
you're as much a monster as my son, Grendel.
My glamour?
One needs glamour to become a king.
A man like you, could own
the greatest tale ever sung.
Your story would live on
when everything now alive... is dust.
Beowulf, it has been a long time
since a man has come to visit me.
I need no sword to kill you.
- Of course you don't, my love.
You took a son from me.
Give me a son, brave thane.
Stay with me, love me...
Love me, and I shall weave you
riches beyond imagination.
I shall make you
the greatest king that ever lived.
As long as you hold me in your heart,
and this golden horn remains in my keeping.
You will forever be king.
Forever strong, mighty and all-powerful.
This I promise.
This I swear.
My lord.
He's dead, my lady.
When I finished-off Grendel's monstrous
mother, I severed the brute's head.
Our curse is lifted.
Our curse is lifted, Odin be praised!
Beowulf be praised!
Our curse is lifted.
Take this out of my sight. Unferth!
- Into the sea. Quickly!
I plunged "Hrunting" into Grendel's
mother chest, and when I pull
the sword free from her corpse,
the creature sprang back to life,
so I plunged the sword back
into the hag's chest.
And there it will stay.
Till Ragnarok...
And our people shall be
gratefull 'till the Ragnarok.
More mead, my lord? - Aye.
- And the drinking-horn. Do you have it?
No, I knew the greedy witch desired it,
so I threw it into the swamp.
And when she followed,
that's when I struck.
With the mighty sword Hrunting.
When she was dead
I looked for it, but it was gone. Forever.
Then find our hero another cup,
my love.
First the hero and I must talk.
Beowulf...
You brought back the head of Grendel.
But what about the head of the mother?
With her dead and cold in the bog,
is it not enough to return one monster's head?
Did you kill her?
Would you like to hear the story
of my struggle against this monstrous hag?
Huh!...
She's no hag, Beowulf.
We both know that.
But answer me,
did you kill her, huh?
Would I've been able to escape her,
had I not?
Grendel is dead. That's all that matters to me.
He can bother me no more.
The mother... The "hag",
she's not my curse,
Not anymore,
not anymore...
Listen to me, listen... to me, huh.
Because my lord Beowulf is a mighty hero,
and because he killed the demon Grendel,
and laid its mother in her grave. - To Beowulf!
and because I have no heir...
I have no sons, I declare that on my death,
all that I possess, my kingdom,
my hall of sadness and shame,
and even my lovely young queen,
my Wealthow
everything, everything,
I leave to this... Our hero.
But, my lord?
- I have spoken! I have spoken!
When I'm gone, Beowulf, son of
Edgethow, shall be king!
Beowulf?
My lord?
Everything in it's time Beowulf.
Master?!
He...
He must have fallen.
All hail king Beowulf!
- All hail king Beowulf!...
King Beowulf.
Archers. - Archers!
This is not battle, Wiglaf.
This is slaughter.
The Frisians want to make themselves
heroes, my lord.
They want the bards to sing of their deeds.
- It's going to be a short song.
How can you blame them,
your legend is known from the high seas
and the snow barriers, to the great Iceland Kingdom.
You are the moster slayer.
- We may nah the monsters now.
The time of heroes is dead, Wiglaf.
The Christ God has killed it,
leaving human kind with noting but weeping
martyrs. Fear and shame.
Show me to Beowulf!
Show me to king Beowulf!
Leave him! You think it's sport to
mock your opponent in this fashion?
Let him die quickly!
With some honor still intact!
Coward! Kill me yourself!
Balls! King must never engage in a direct battle.
Kill the invader now. Do it quickly!
Put his head on a spear.
- Stop!
My lord, the king must not engage
in a direct battle.
Let him up.
He wants your name.
He's the son of Beowulf.
You think it should end with me killed by
some Frisian raider with no name?
I'm Fin of Frisia. And my name
shall be remembered forever!
Only if you kill me!
Otherwise you're nothing.
You think you're the first who tried
to kill me? Or the hundredth, hm?
Well let me tell you something, Frisian.
The gods will not allow my death by your feeble blade.
The gods will not allow me to die by a sword,
or be taken by the sea.
The gods will not let me pass in my sleep...
ripe with age.
Plant your axe here, Fin of Frisia.
Take my life.
Someone give him a sword... or I'll... I'll...
You'll what?! Kill me?
Well, kill me! Do it! Kill me! Kill me!
You know why you can't kill me, my friend?
'Cause I died many, many years ago...
when I was young.
Give him a gold piece, and send him home.
He has a story to tell.
Your majesty? Are you hurt?
- Ah. Not a scratch.
You're so beautiful and so young.
You know Ursula, when I was young I
used to think that being a king was about battling every morning and
counting the golden loot in the afternoon.
Swiving a beautiful woman every evening...
But now... nothing is as good as it should have been.
Not even the "swiving a
beautiful woman every night" part, your majesty?
Well... Some nights for sure, some nights...
- Perhaps tonight?
No, tonight I fell my age upon me.
Tomorrow after the celebrations.
We can't forget what tomorrow is,
can we now?
Your day, when the song of Beowulf is told.
Of how you lifted the darkness from the land.
And the day after that, we celebrate the
birth of hallowed Christ.
I see you survived.
At last, my queen. The Frisian invaders
had been pushed into the sea.
You are not a widow.
Yet.
How comforting,
my husband.
Hail Beowulf!
Hail Beowulf! Hail Beowulf!...
Unferth!
You're not celebrating your king's
glory tonight?
I have something for the king.
What is it? - I said I have
something for the King.
Show it to me
- I will not!
You will show it to me first.
- Bollocks Wiglaf, I'll show it first to Beowulf.
The king needs to see it.
- The king? Needs to see what?
Lost,
and now found.
The gift fit for a king.
Do you recognize it?
Where did you find this?
- On the moors, my slave, Cain found it
on the barren hill where nothing grows.
I beat him for threading near such an unholy place.
My lord, isn't this...?
So, lord Beowulf...
it's come back to you,
after all these years.
My lord, this is the slave who found it.
- Please, please don't kill me.
Where did you found this treasure?
- I'm sorry I runned away, master. Please don't hurt me no more.
Answer your king!
- Stop!
Stop!
Where? - Up... up on the moors.
But I was going to give it back master, I swear.
Is that all? No demon,
no witch, no woman?
Look at you, you're nothing. An empty nothing.
- Come forth! Show yourself!
Even with all your riches, your kingdom,
your power, your glory, and your women...
Which one do you think I should kill first?
Your pretty little bed-warmer, or your wise queen?
What are you?
I am something you left behind.
Father!...
Another restless night?
It's all right, girl.
I'm not going to eat you.
He has bad dreams. They've become more often.
- He's a king. Kings have a lot on their conscience.
He calls your name in his sleep.
- Does he?
I belive he still holds you in his heart.
- Do you?
I often wonder... What happened?
- To us? Too many secrets...
God, help us.
What... What do you want in me?
- I have a message for my father.
Tell me, what did this?
- I saw a whole village burnt. Children screaming and dying.
I saw it, your majesty, vomiting fire and smoke.
- Damn you! What was it?
A dragon.
It's Unferth my lord. - Unferth?
- You say a dragon did this. - Stop.
You had an agreement, you would not be harmed.
But now the golden horn has return to you,
the agreement is ended.
- Who!? Who said that!?
"The sins of the fathers..." It's the last thing I heard.
The last thing before my family
was burned alive!
Sins of the fathers! Sins of the fathers!...
Sins of the fathers! Sins of the fathers!
Take up your positions along the
northern edge of a great gauge.
It's our only hope if I fail.
- My lord.
Don't go, I beg you.
- You are free. I release you.
Find a good man. Bear him children.
But bear him a son.
I don't want anyone else. I want you.
- I am not the man you think me to be.
You're a great man, and a hero.
This I know to be true.
Then you are as foolish as
the rest of them!
Very impressive, dear. But the armour
suited you better when you were younger.
I'm sure it did.
Why don't you take that poor girl,
and leave out your remaining years in peace.
Let some young hero save us.
What? And let the nightmare...
start all over again?
No. I visited this horror upon my kingdom.
I must be the one to finish her.
Her? Was she so beautiful, Beowulf?
Her beauty's so costly?
Beautiful, and full of fine promises.
I was weak. I am sorry.
So... So sorry.
I have always loved you my queen.
- And I you.
Keep a memory of me. Not as a king, or a hero.
But as a man. Fallible and flawed.
This is the place.
- Where you slained Grendel's mother.
Wiglaf, I have no sons and if this demon
kills me, I have arranged with the heralds
that you shall be king.
- Don't speak of such thing, my lord.
Great friend, there is something you should know.
- Nay! There is nothing I should know.
You are Beowulf! Beowulf the mighty, the hero!
The slayer and destroyer of demons.
Now let us kill this flying devil when he sleeps,
and go on with our bloody lives.
Do you want me to go in with you?
Good.
Beowulf,
it has been a long time.
Take your damn horn,
and leave my land in peace.
Too late, my love.
Odin's swifan balls!
It's heading for
Herot.
Hrothgar.
Damn you!
I'll have your lizard head
on a spike!
No!
My lord?!
Over here! Attend the queen!
- Attend the queen...
I told you we were too old to be heroes.
Let's get you to a healer.
- Not this time old friend.
You are Beowulf. Little thing like this
isn't gonna finish you off.
Do you hear her?
I hear nothing.
Grendel's mother, my son's mother, my... mine...
- No my lord. You killed Grendel's mother
when we were young.
They sing of it.
Too late for lies, Wiglaf.
Too late...
He was the bravest of us.
He was the prince...
of all warriors.
His name
will live forever.
His song shall be sung forever.